<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Keep Zora safe.</Source>
      <Dest>保证佐拉的安全啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Um...hello.  Thank you...for the other day.</Source>
      <Dest>呃……你好。谢谢啊……前两天的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>G-greetings.</Source>
      <Dest>你-好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you need something?</Source>
      <Dest>你要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can I help you?</Source>
      <Dest>我能为你效劳吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I...I'm sorry, I'd like some time alone.</Source>
      <Dest>对…对不起，我需要点独处的时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In a potion, tundra cotton can make fire hotter, and flesh stronger.  My sister and I, we...(sigh).  The Gods toy with us all.</Source>
      <Dest>用上这种药剂，苔原棉可以让火烧的更旺，肉体也能变得更强壮。我妹妹和我，我们……（叹息）神灵弄人啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can I truly move on, living in Riverwood?  I'm not so sure.</Source>
      <Dest>我真的能放下过去，安心在溪木镇生活吗？很难说啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I still feel like everyone is watching me.  Maybe I should change clothes.</Source>
      <Dest>我还是觉得大家都在盯着我。也许我该换身衣服。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Zora asked me about the man I traveled with.  She thought he was a lover.  He was a mercenary.</Source>
      <Dest>佐拉问那个跟我同行的男人是谁。她以为是我的情人。其实是雇佣兵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You and Zora are married...I wish you both well.</Source>
      <Dest>你和佐拉结婚了……祝你俩一切都好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This town.  It never changes...</Source>
      <Dest>这镇子。永远不会变……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This inn is nice.  Orgnar doesn't bother me. I wish the new boy would do the same.</Source>
      <Dest>这个小旅馆很不错。奥格那不会来打扰我。希望那新来的男孩也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anise said I had talent.  I never thought...I...I never meant to hurt her.  It just happened.</Source>
      <Dest>安妮斯以前说我很有天赋。没想到……我…我从没想要伤害她。可就这样发生了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The food here is better than I remember.</Source>
      <Dest>这里的食物比我记忆中的还要好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Zora and I used to wash our feet in the White River, and watch the clouds over Bleak Falls.  The view is the same as it ever was.</Source>
      <Dest>佐拉和我过去常常在白河洗洗脚，看看天上的云朵缓缓飘过寒落山峰。这道风景从未改变啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I enjoy this cabin.  It was my place away from Riverwood.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢这座小屋。我离开溪木镇后曾经住在里面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anise never told me she was a witch.  But I knew.</Source>
      <Dest>安妮斯从没跟我说过她是女巫。但我知道了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Zora says I should join the College.  I don't know...</Source>
      <Dest>佐拉说我应该进学院去。我心里没底……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you think it will snow in Riverwood this winter?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得这个冬天溪木镇会下雪吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I didn't make it across the Jerall Mountains. I...I ended up following someone back across the border, but I lost her tracks the night they came.</Source>
      <Dest>我未能穿越【杰哈尔山脉。我……不得不找个人跟着穿越边境回去，结果他们到来的那个晚上我跟丢了她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The witches believe in the old magic.  Blood is potent.  And the Gods demand sacrifice.</Source>
      <Dest>女巫们信仰古代魔法。鲜血中有强大的力量。神灵需要牺牲品。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some sisters would ask that I no longer practice witchcraft.  But Zora knows...I'm not a child.</Source>
      <Dest>一些姐妹会要我别再练习巫术。但佐拉知道……我不是个孩子了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fire burns so hot, but it feels so empty.  I...I wish I didn't need it...but living out in the wilderness, you don't have a choice.</Source>
      <Dest>火烧得这么旺，感觉上却又这么空虚。我……我希望我不需要这个……但是当在野外求生时，却别无选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Marigoth...that coven...they did horrible things.  It was a mistake to join them.</Source>
      <Dest>玛丽葛斯……那聚会……她们做了很可怕的事。加入那里完全是个错误。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sister...I...I'll see you in Riverwood.</Source>
      <Dest>妹妹……我…我们溪木镇见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Three of us?</Source>
      <Dest>我们三个？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sister, I think I'm ready to leave now.</Source>
      <Dest>妹妹，我想现在我可以离开了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Marigoth!  Zora, what's going on?</Source>
      <Dest>玛丽葛斯！佐拉，这是怎么回事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm fine sister.  Thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>我没事的妹妹。谢谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Give me a moment...I can take us home.  Our real home.</Source>
      <Dest>给我点时间……我能带大家一起回家。我们真正的家.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm so sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>太对不起了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Zora?</Source>
      <Dest>佐拉？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sure. It doesn't hurt when I'm here.</Source>
      <Dest>我确定。我留在这儿没什么不好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You stopped it!  You stopped the fire!</Source>
      <Dest>你让它停止了！你熄灭了火焰！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No!  You can't leave!  This is our place!  Our home!  I built this for you!</Source>
      <Dest>不！你不能走！这是我们的地方！我们的家！是我专门为你建造的啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you see it sister?  Do you see the snow?</Source>
      <Dest>看见了吗妹妹？你看见那雪了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No!  I'm not leaving!  You aren't leaving!  You're not my real sister!  You're someone else!</Source>
      <Dest>不！我不走！你也走不了！你不是我妹妹！你是谁扮的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you see it sister?  Do you see the snow?</Source>
      <Dest>看见了吗妹妹？你看见那雪了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come on, sister!  Let's go play!</Source>
      <Dest>来啊，妹妹！一起去玩吧！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, here we are Zora.  This is our home.  We never have to leave.  We never have to cry.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，佐拉我们到啦。这就是我们的家。我们再也不用离开，再也不必哭啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Remember that time mother said it was too warm to go sledding?</Source>
      <Dest>还记得那次妈妈说这天太热没法滑雪的事么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I cried and you cried, and then father got the idea to throw cotton all over the house instead?</Source>
      <Dest>你哭了我也哭了，结果爸爸想出个办法改用棉花铺满了整个房间？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you said we should plant cotton all over the tundra, so that we'd never have a day without snow.</Source>
      <Dest>然后你说我们要在苔原上种满棉花，这样我们每天都能在雪地里玩了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Welcome to Zora's field, sister.</Source>
      <Dest>欢迎来到佐拉的田园，妹妹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But either way, I hope it finds a use for it. And thanks again. I almost forgot what it felt like. Kindness.</Source>
      <Dest>But either way, I hope it finds a use for it. And thanks again. I almost forgot what it felt like. Kindness.</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
