<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Raven of Anvil.</Source>
      <Dest>铁砧城的乌鸦</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Those who were in attendance insist it was the saddest song ever heard by mortal ears.</Source>
      <Dest>所有在场的人们都深信那是凡人世界里能听到的最悲伤的歌曲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Raven of Anvil.</Source>
      <Dest>铁砧城的乌鸦</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They claim the sky rained for seven days and seven nights, as both the Countess and the Divines exhausted all their tears.</Source>
      <Dest>他们称在那之后就有滂沱大雨连下了七天七夜，女伯爵和圣灵们都耗尽了所有的泪水。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Raven of Anvil.</Source>
      <Dest>铁砧城的乌鸦</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That night, the entire court slept for the first time in weeks, and when they awoke, they found their cases and coffers empty of their valuables.</Source>
      <Dest>那一晚，几周都没睡好觉的整个宫廷终于安然入睡，而当他们醒来的时候，却发现金库和箱子里所有之前的东西都不翼而飞了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me how this heist happened.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我这次抢劫是如何发生的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Countess' cousin had passed away, and she was now in her twelfth day of mourning.  She refused to eat, and refused to sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>那是女伯爵的侄子刚刚去世，在她哀悼第十二天的时候。她既不吃东西，也不肯睡觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me how this heist happened.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我这次抢劫是如何发生的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Soon her court was deprived of the same, as her mood grew more and more contemptuous.  It seemed nothing would allay her grief.</Source>
      <Dest>很快她的幕僚们也被拖垮，她的心情也越来越凄凉。看来一切努力都无法抚平她的悲伤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me how this heist happened.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我这次抢劫是如何发生的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Many bards and poets came from all over Tamriel, to celebrate the life of her cousin, in hopes of appeasing the Countess.</Source>
      <Dest>泰姆瑞尔大陆上的很多歌者和诗人，都陆续前来为她的亲人歌唱，希望以此抚慰女伯爵的悲伤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me how this heist happened.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我这次抢劫是如何发生的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet it seemed that even time itself had given up all hope. Until the day a raven-haired minstrel walked into the castle and gently strummed her lute.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，似乎连时间本身都已经放弃了所有希望。直到那天一位黑发的吟游诗人走进了城堡，轻轻弹起了他的鲁特琴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your obsession tells me this woman stole something important to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你的老想告诉我这个女人偷了一些对你而言很重要的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She has indeed. She's stolen my sanity, my youth, and nearly all of my will.  </Source>
      <Dest>她确实有。她窃取了我的智慧，我的青春，和我几乎所有的热情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your obsession tells me this woman stole something important to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你的老想告诉我这个女人偷了一些对你而言很重要的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps it is because I am nearing the infirmity of old age that I long for closure.</Source>
      <Dest>或许是此身即将迈入暮年而想寻求个了结吧。【或许只是因为我想拿风烛残年为借口来做个了结吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your obsession tells me this woman stole something important to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你的老想告诉我这个女人偷了一些对你而言很重要的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Forgive me, but I no longer wish to speak of such things.  Good day.</Source>
      <Dest>对不起，我不再想谈这些了。再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to go back to my earlier questions.</Source>
      <Dest>让我们回到先前的问题上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>With every word it becomes more and more obvious that you know this thief.</Source>
      <Dest>你说的每一个字都越发地证明你认识这个贼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, my words have betrayed me more than once in this conversation.  It is not uncommon given my proximity to this case.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，我的言语这次谈话中已经出卖了自己好多次。鉴于我个人与此事的密切关联这并不奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>With every word it becomes more and more obvious that you know this thief.</Source>
      <Dest>你说的每一个字都越发地证明你认识这个贼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Few, however, are perceptive enough to find meaning in the stumble of words.   It is as you say.  I know the Raven of Anvil.</Source>
      <Dest>但是，有这本事从只言片语的疏漏中窥见真相的人，很少。确实跟你说的一样，我认识这个铁砧之鸦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>With every word it becomes more and more obvious that you know this thief.</Source>
      <Dest>你说的每一个字都越发地证明你认识这个贼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know both her and the song she played on that fateful night in Anvil. After all, I sired both of them. The Raven of Anvil is my daughter.</Source>
      <Dest>不但认识她我还熟知她在铁砧城那命运转折的夜晚演奏的曲子。实际上，【她们都是我的孩子。铁砧城之鸦是我的女儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you value trivial things you yourself will become trivial when those qualities fade.</Source>
      <Dest>如果把这些身外之物视作自己的珍宝，等到它们的光华褪去时你自己也就变得微不足道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have no regrets, and I'm strong and handsome. I bet you wish you were me.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有任何遗憾，我很坚强和英俊。我敢打赌，你肯定想变得跟我一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you value trivial things you yourself will become trivial when those qualities fade.</Source>
      <Dest>如果把这些身外之物视作自己的珍宝，等到它们的光华褪去时你自己也就变得微不足道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have no regrets, and I'm strong and handsome. I bet you wish you were me.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有任何遗憾，我很坚强和英俊。我敢打赌，你肯定想变得跟我一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I suppose even then you can cling to the lifeboat of denial.</Source>
      <Dest>我看就算到那时你也只会把矢口否认当成救命稻草抓住不放的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I suppose even then you can cling to the lifeboat of denial.</Source>
      <Dest>我看就算到那时你也只会把矢口否认当成救命稻草抓住不放的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have no regrets, and I'm strong and handsome. I bet you wish you were me.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有任何遗憾，我很坚强和英俊。我敢打赌，你肯定想变得跟我一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can do no such thing. I will not grasp for air while I lie at the bottom of this trench.</Source>
      <Dest>我可做不出这样的事。如果是躺在这样的谷底我肯定会喘不过气来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you value trivial things you yourself will become trivial when those qualities fade.   </Source>
      <Dest>如果把这些身外之物视作自己的珍宝，等到它们的光华褪去时你自己也就变得微不足道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have no regrets, and I'm strong and beautiful.  I bet you wish you were me.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有什么可遗憾的，我强大并且美貌。我打赌你希望你自己是我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you value trivial things you yourself will become trivial when those qualities fade.   </Source>
      <Dest>如果把这些身外之物视作自己的珍宝，等到它们的光华褪去时你自己也就变得微不足道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have no regrets, and I'm strong and beautiful.  I bet you wish you were me.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有什么可遗憾的，我强大并且美貌。我打赌你希望你自己是我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I suppose even then you can cling to the lifeboat of denial.  </Source>
      <Dest>我看就算到那时你也只会把矢口否认当成救命稻草抓住不放的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I suppose even then you can cling to the lifeboat of denial.  </Source>
      <Dest>我看就算到那时你也只会把矢口否认当成救命稻草抓住不放的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have no regrets, and I'm strong and beautiful.  I bet you wish you were me.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有什么可遗憾的，我强大并且美貌。我打赌你希望你自己是我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can do no such thing.  I will not gasp for air while I lie at the bottom of this trench.</Source>
      <Dest>我可做不出这样的事。如果是躺在这样的谷底我肯定会喘不过气来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Raven of Anvil. So you've given her a name.</Source>
      <Dest>铁砧城的瑞文。所以你把那个名字给她了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I thought it was best to give her a name that was more memorable, and identifiable.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，是我觉得最好给她起一个又好记又好认的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Raven of Anvil. So you've given her a name.</Source>
      <Dest>铁砧城的瑞文。所以你把那个名字给她了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Our reports are at times conflicting, but the most reliable agree on one point.  </Source>
      <Dest>我们的报告有时是会相互矛盾，但最可靠的信息都集中于一点：</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Raven of Anvil. So you've given her a name.</Source>
      <Dest>铁砧城的瑞文。所以你把那个名字给她了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The girl has hair as black as a raven, so dark that it seems to devour the light around it.</Source>
      <Dest>这女孩有着乌鸦一样的黑发，黑得仿佛吞噬了它周围的光。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Raven of Anvil. So you've given her a name.</Source>
      <Dest>铁砧城的瑞文。所以你把那个名字给她了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And like the ominous bird she is not to be trusted, and the very sight of her is a wicked portent for those who have worked hard for their wealth.</Source>
      <Dest>而她也就如那不祥之鸟一样不可信任，对于那些努力工作积累财富的人来说她的出现可不是个好兆头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Raven of Anvil. So you've given her a name.</Source>
      <Dest>铁砧城的瑞文。所以你把那个名字给她了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>None more so than the Countess of Anvil, who in her weakness opened the doors of the Great Hall to this eater of carrion.</Source>
      <Dest>没有比铁砧城的女伯爵更能证明这一点的了，她一时的软弱为这只腐食者打开了城堡的大门。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I know I regret talking to you.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道我很后悔跟你谈话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha!  Many in this outpost share your sentiments.  They find me a pitiful old dog, chasing his tail.  In many respects they are right.</Source>
      <Dest>哈！你跟这个镇上的大多数人没什么两样。他们觉得我就是只可怜的老狗，拼命追逐自己的尾巴。不过从很多角度而言他们还真说对了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I know I regret talking to you.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道我很后悔跟你谈话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For the case I slave over is a part of me, and will die with me if I cannot complete it.</Source>
      <Dest>因为我出生入死去办的案子都成了我的一部分，要是失败了也就跟我死在了一块。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My regrets haunt me every day. And I vow not to repeat them.</Source>
      <Dest>我的愧疚困扰着我的每一天。我发誓不赘述。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is the way we are meant to live. Always tumbling forward, looking back only to see how far we've come.  </Source>
      <Dest>那就正应了我们生活的本义。永远是蹒跚前行，偶尔回头只是为看自己走了多远。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My regrets haunt me every day. And I vow not to repeat them.</Source>
      <Dest>我的愧疚困扰着我的每一天。我发誓不赘述。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For some things, such a task is simple. A hastily written report. A tactless reply. A spilled drink.</Source>
      <Dest>一般而言呢，这种事小菜一碟。如同草草写就的报告，胡乱回复的信件，随手洒掉的酒水。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My regrets haunt me every day. And I vow not to repeat them.</Source>
      <Dest>我的愧疚困扰着我的每一天。我发誓不赘述。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For others, the tendrils run deeper, rooting your body in the earth.  There is no way forward.</Source>
      <Dest>也总有那么几件事，如同生根一样，始终牢牢将你的头脑占据。无处可逃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My regrets haunt me every day. And I vow not to repeat them.</Source>
      <Dest>我的愧疚困扰着我的每一天。我发誓不赘述。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not until you free yourself of the memory. Not until you make things right.</Source>
      <Dest>直到你把自己从回忆中解救出来。直到你把一切事情拨乱反正。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should've chosen a name less glorifying.  Like the Whore of Anvil.</Source>
      <Dest>你真该取个少点虚荣的名字.像是铁砧城的婊子.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She is no whore, and the Penitus Oculatus does not resort to puerile slander! Nor do we honor this thief by referring to her as a raven.</Source>
      <Dest>她不是婊子，而且锐眼鹰也不会诉诸于幼稚的诽谤！更不会把“乌鸦”这名字说成对这女贼的尊重。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should've chosen a name less glorifying.  Like the Whore of Anvil.</Source>
      <Dest>你真该取个少点虚荣的名字.像是铁砧城的婊子.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The color of the raven matches that of her hair, and the raven is a foul creature that feasts on carrion.  </Source>
      <Dest>乌鸦的颜色跟她的发色般配，而且它是种以腐肉为食的肮脏生物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should've chosen a name less glorifying.  Like the Whore of Anvil.</Source>
      <Dest>你真该取个少点虚荣的名字.像是铁砧城的婊子.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And it is through the tragedy of death that she wormed her way into the halls of Castle Anvil.</Source>
      <Dest>而她就是利用一次悲剧的丧事为通道钻进了铁砧堡的大堂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it the initiation targets are mostly criminals.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白入会任务的目标大多是罪犯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not necessarily. It is left up to the discretion of the Inspector to choose the targets.</Source>
      <Dest>并不一定。这个目标的选择是交由教官自行决定的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it the initiation targets are mostly criminals.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白入会任务的目标大多是罪犯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I tended to choose mortals who were louts, thieves, and deviants, there were other inspectors who felt that defeated the purpose.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然我倾向于选择那些废物，盗贼和变态之流，很多教官却觉得这会破坏这种考核的本意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it the initiation targets are mostly criminals.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白入会任务的目标大多是罪犯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>After all, an assassin must be able to kill those whose morality is ambiguous, or possibly even leaning toward the scales of good.</Source>
      <Dest>毕竟，做刺客的必须能够下手去杀那些善恶难辨的目标，甚至是道德上可能偏善良的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it the initiation targets are mostly criminals.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白入会任务的目标大多是罪犯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So it was our responsibility to create at the very minimum the idea that the targets were honest men. Some inspectors chose to forego the mirage.</Source>
      <Dest>因此我们的责任就是至少要为目标创造一种他是好人的印象。有些教官选择略过这层幻想。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You told that story with some emotion. How curious.</Source>
      <Dest>你在讲这个故事的时候却夹杂了些情感。真奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is a sad story.  A tale of two deaths and one birth.  </Source>
      <Dest>这是个悲伤的故事。一个包含两个死者与一个新生的童话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You told that story with some emotion. How curious.</Source>
      <Dest>你在讲这个故事的时候却夹杂了些情感。真奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The girl had the talent to give the world a gift of joy, but she chooses to lead a life that brings nothing but sorrow.</Source>
      <Dest>这个女孩有着为世界带来欢笑的天赋，可她却选择了带来悲伤的路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anvil. So the thief is from Cyrodiil.</Source>
      <Dest>铁砧城，所以这小贼是从赛瑞迪尔来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not necessarily. Anvil is merely the site of her first great heist, one done under the guise of minstrel singing dirges for the dead. </Source>
      <Dest>并不是必然的。铁砧城只是她最大一票劫案的事发地，扮成了为死者哀悼的歌者去制造的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hence the Raven of Anvil.</Source>
      <Dest>所以被成为铁砧城之鸦</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anvil. So the thief is from Cyrodiil.</Source>
      <Dest>铁砧城，所以这小贼是从赛瑞迪尔来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you're retired then you shouldn't be allowed in here.</Source>
      <Dest>要是你已经退休了就不会被允许进到这里来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A favor from the late Commander Maro. He owed me from back when he was an initiate, and I was his inspector.</Source>
      <Dest>这是后来的马洛指挥官照顾。在他还是新兵的时候欠了我一个人情，那时我是他的教官。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A favor from Commander Maro. He owed me from back in those halcyon days when he was but an initiate, and I his inspector.</Source>
      <Dest>这是马洛指挥官的特殊照顾。当年还没打仗而他还是个新兵时候欠了我个人情，那时我是他的教官。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you're retired then you shouldn't be allowed in here.</Source>
      <Dest>要是你已经退休了就不会被允许进到这里来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The age you give is awfully precise. Do you know her identity?</Source>
      <Dest>年龄你说的对极了，你知道她的身份吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I...meant it as an estimate, nothing more. Given her description she could be anywhere from 30 to 34 years of age. I choose the middle ground.</Source>
      <Dest>这……只是猜测而已，没别的意思。根据对她所做的描述记载，她的年龄大概是30岁到34岁之间，我就取了个中间数。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The age you give is awfully precise. Do you know her identity?</Source>
      <Dest>年龄你说的对极了，你知道她的身份吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I try to make my descriptions as accurate as possible, so that my words will not be distorted as they are conveyed to the next person. </Source>
      <Dest>我是要让这个描述尽可能精确，这样我说的话在被传递给下一个人的时候才不会被曲解。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The age you give is awfully precise. Do you know her identity?</Source>
      <Dest>年龄你说的对极了，你知道她的身份吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I were to say she was in her early thirties, the information will quickly degrade as it passed from mouth to ear.</Source>
      <Dest>要是我说她三十岁出头，这信息转眼就会在口耳相传之间变得含糊不清。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The age you give is awfully precise. Do you know her identity?</Source>
      <Dest>年龄你说的对极了，你知道她的身份吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For instance, someone might forget to include the word "early."  With just a simple omission she can now be as old as thirty-nine.</Source>
      <Dest>譬如说，某人传话时可能忘了强调“出头”这个词。没了这一个词把她理解成39岁也合理了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The age you give is awfully precise. Do you know her identity?</Source>
      <Dest>年龄你说的对极了，你知道她的身份吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Raven of Anvil is cunning enough on her own, it does us little good to cast more shadows where she can conceal herself.</Source>
      <Dest>铁砧之鸦本来已经够狡猾了，在她藏匿之处制造更多的阴影对我们可没什么好处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like to meet this thief. Sounds like we'd get along.</Source>
      <Dest>我想见见这个贼，听着好像我们能合得来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm not sure what I find more incredulous, that you are a thief, or that you'd advertise this fact in the office of the Penitus Oculatus.  </Source>
      <Dest>我一时听不出到底哪一个解释比较不靠谱，是说你自己是贼这件事呢，还是你到锐眼鹰的总局来表明身份的举动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like to meet this thief. Sounds like we'd get along.</Source>
      <Dest>我想见见这个贼，听着好像我们能合得来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Either way, you're not my problem any longer.  I'm retired.  It's the only way I can pursue this case without being reprimanded by my superiors.</Source>
      <Dest>不过不管怎么说，我已经管不着你了。我早退休了。只有这样我才能继续追踪这个案子而不用被上级斥责。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That story sounds apocryphal. It's more likely she seduced her.</Source>
      <Dest>那个故事听起来可疑的。不过更有可能的是她怂恿了她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is nothing but a baseless rumor, spread by those who think only of perversion! The Raven of Anvil was not raised to be a harlot.</Source>
      <Dest>那完全是毫无根据的谣言，是那些满脑子变态想法的家伙散播的。铁砧城之鸦可不是当妓女养大的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In life there are fools and those who exploit foolishness.</Source>
      <Dest>生活中总是有傻瓜和利用傻瓜牟利的人</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was not always such. When she was a small child she was so bright, and would protect those who were weak from their folly.</Source>
      <Dest>她本来不是这样的。当她小的时候是那么的乖巧，还会去主动保护那些笨笨的小伙伴们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In life there are fools and those who exploit foolishness.</Source>
      <Dest>生活中总是有傻瓜和利用傻瓜牟利的人</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, but you were referring to the Countess.  As was I.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，你说的是女伯爵啊。对的我也是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's what this is really about.  You want your daughter back.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这就是你真正想说的，你想要回你的女儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't need her back. She's her own woman now, with her own life, one that's separate from the world I would choose.</Source>
      <Dest>我没想让她回来。她翅膀长硬了，过上她自己的生活了，一种与我的意愿完全不同的生活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's what this is really about.  You want your daughter back.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这就是你真正想说的，你想要回你的女儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's not about getting justice anymore.  Perhaps it never was.  I don't need her to repent, and I don't need her to change.</Source>
      <Dest>也不再关乎什么追求正义了。也许就从来也没有过。我既不需要她悔过，也不需要她改变。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's what this is really about.  You want your daughter back.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这就是你真正想说的，你想要回你的女儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm at the age where the coffers of a few nobles won't cost me any sleep.  What I dread is the passage of time, and one final regret.</Source>
      <Dest>以我的年龄已经不会再为几个贵族的金库问题失眠。我所惧怕的是时间的流逝，以及临终前最后的遗憾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's what this is really about.  You want your daughter back.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这就是你真正想说的，你想要回你的女儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't care what it takes. Or how long I have to look.  All I want is to see her smile again.</Source>
      <Dest>现在的我愿意不惜一切。哪怕要我穷尽一生时间，跨过万水千山。只要让我能够再次一睹她的笑颜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's what this is really about.  You want your daughter back.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这就是你真正想说的，你想要回你的女儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I...I'm sorry. If you please, I need a moment to myself.  But I thank you for listening.</Source>
      <Dest>我……我很抱歉。您不介意的话，我想一个人静静。但真谢谢你听我说这么多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It wasn't enough, evidently. The Emperor's dead.</Source>
      <Dest>明显不够用嘛，皇帝还是死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes the need for vengeance is but kindle to the fire of a determined evil.  </Source>
      <Dest>有时候对于复仇的欲望不过是在为罪恶的火焰里添柴罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It wasn't enough, evidently. The Emperor's dead.</Source>
      <Dest>明显不够用嘛，皇帝还是死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I confess I don't know all the details, but I saw the anger in Commander Maro's eyes, and that alone can cause smart men to err.</Source>
      <Dest>我承认自己并不了解所有细节，但我看到了马罗将军眼中的怒火，只这一件，就足以将让一个聪明的人失去理智。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It wasn't enough, evidently. The Emperor's dead.</Source>
      <Dest>明显不够用嘛，皇帝还是死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I know the importance of family, and the kind of obsessions that can derive from losing one.</Source>
      <Dest>我也知道家人的重要，和失去家人的那种无法释怀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell me traveler, do you have any regrets?  Of course you do. We all do.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我旅行者，你有什么遗憾么？当然有吧。谁都有的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say regrets are the foundation of wisdom, for if we do not regret our mistakes, we are damned to repeat them.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说后悔是智慧的基础，因为如果我们从不因过失而回过，就得遭受重蹈覆辙的诅咒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Our successes, meanwhile, need not be remembered, for they only serve to bolster our temerity.</Source>
      <Dest>而我们的成功，也因此，不需要被铭记，因为这只会让我们骄傲自大，鲁莽行事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why a general is haunted not by his victories on the battlefield, but those that slipped from his grasp.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是为什么一名将军不会总挂念着他在战场上所取得的胜利，而是纠结于他遗憾错失的那些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for a traveler?</Source>
      <Dest>你对过路人有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say when dealing with others, you have to know when to use the carrot and when to use the stick. Yet by "when" they really mean "on whom."</Source>
      <Dest>他们说跟别人打交道的时候，你得知道什么时候该给个蜜枣，什么时候该打一巴掌。可他们说的“什么时候”指的其实是“对谁”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for a traveler?</Source>
      <Dest>你对过路人有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think the word "when" is rather appropriate.  There's more than just differences from person to person.</Source>
      <Dest>我倒觉得“什么时候”这个提法其实很贴切。比单纯区分不同的人靠谱得多。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for a traveler?</Source>
      <Dest>你对过路人有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People themselves can have different personalities depending on the time of day.</Source>
      <Dest>人的个性在每天的不同时间可是阴晴多变的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for a traveler?</Source>
      <Dest>你对过路人有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You never want to berate your spouse, for instance, first thing in the morning.  Olda seems to neglect this advice.</Source>
      <Dest>比如说吧，你永远不想跟配偶吵架，这是过日子的头等大事。那个【奥尔达】就不会听这个劝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for a traveler?</Source>
      <Dest>你对过路人有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Life is easy when your goals are small.</Source>
      <Dest>生活就会简单，只要你的目标没那么高。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for a traveler?</Source>
      <Dest>你对过路人有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When your goals are large, the problem comes not from failure, but from the inability to cope with it.  </Source>
      <Dest>当你的目标过于远大时，问题就不在于失败，而是连行动都心有余而力不足了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for a traveler?</Source>
      <Dest>你对过路人有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whether you reach for the stars or plow the earth, don't let the task consume you. (Sigh) If only I could take such sage advice.</Source>
      <Dest>无论你是要上天摘星还是下地耕种，都别让自己彻底淹没于那件事情中。（叹）要是也我接受过这么睿智的建议就好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So a blind girl with a big nose. Got it.</Source>
      <Dest>一个眼瞎的女孩，还长着个大鼻子。我明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is not what I said! I mean...I apologize.  Forgive my impertinence.  </Source>
      <Dest>我可没那么说！我的意思是……啊抱歉。原谅我的急躁吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I simply do not appreciate it when the locals fashion rumors that only seek to throw my investigation off course. </Source>
      <Dest>我只是对那些刻意制造谣言使我的调查偏离轨道的本地人没什么好感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So a blind girl with a big nose. Got it.</Source>
      <Dest>一个眼瞎的女孩，还长着个大鼻子。我明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So a blind girl with a big nose. Got it.</Source>
      <Dest>一个眼瞎的女孩，还长着个大鼻子。我明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The more unreliable the description, the less likely a witness will be able to identify the thief.</Source>
      <Dest>描述措辞越不可靠，目击者就越难以辨认出这贼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So a blind girl with a big nose. Got it.</Source>
      <Dest>一个眼瞎的女孩，还长着个大鼻子。我明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Raven of Anvil would like nothing more than for people to think she is blind, ten feet tall, and half-Spriggan.</Source>
      <Dest>别人会以为这铁砧之鸦是个瞎眼的、只有十英尺高的半树精怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What makes you think she's in Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让你觉得她会在天际省？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There have been several witness accounts made to the guard here, of a raven haired thief posing as a bard.</Source>
      <Dest>有好几个目击者向卫兵作证，是有个黑头发的盗贼扮成吟游诗人的样子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What makes you think she's in Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让你觉得她会在天际省？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you know, most Nords are light of hair and tall in stature, which already narrows down the list of possible culprits.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道的，大部分诺德人都是金发并且体型高大，这直接减少了嫌疑人的数目。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What makes you think she's in Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让你觉得她会在天际省？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And while there are bards in Skyrim from here to Riften, there is only one capable of playing that song.</Source>
      <Dest>而从这里到裂谷城，在天际所有的吟游诗人中，只有一个会演奏那首歌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What makes you think she's in Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让你觉得她会在天际省？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What makes you think she's in Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让你觉得她会在天际省？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A beautiful but solemn tune about the sunset over The Gold Coast, and the tragic death of a loved one.</Source>
      <Dest>那是一首优美而庄重的歌曲，倾诉着黄金海岸的夕阳，和心爱之人惨死的悲剧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If so, why hasn't more of an effort been made to catch her?</Source>
      <Dest>假如这样的话, 为什么不再加把劲抓住她呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unfortunately, the resources the Empire exhausted in tracking her down, forced the Elder Council to suspend all pursuit.</Source>
      <Dest>不幸的是，帝国为追踪她而调集的资源很快耗尽，迫使元老院把相关案件的处理全部停滞了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If so, why hasn't more of an effort been made to catch her?</Source>
      <Dest>假如这样的话, 为什么不再加把劲抓住她呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Given the state of the Imperial coffers, it was cheaper to let her run free and compensate the aggrieved for their losses.</Source>
      <Dest>因为从帝国财政的算盘看来，与其继续抓她话不如赔偿被抢客户的损失来的划算。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If so, why hasn't more of an effort been made to catch her?</Source>
      <Dest>假如这样的话, 为什么不再加把劲抓住她呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only I remain dedicated to the cause of justice.  And what I lack in men and resources, I make up for in will.</Source>
      <Dest>只有我仍在为正义而努力。我缺乏的人力和资源，都会用意志去弥补。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If so, why hasn't more of an effort been made to catch her?</Source>
      <Dest>假如这样的话, 为什么不再加把劲抓住她呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've chased her across Tamriel for the last 15 years, and now I believe I'm closer than ever to catching her.</Source>
      <Dest>我在整个塔姆瑞尔追寻她15年，相信现在是离她最近的一次。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly is the problem?</Source>
      <Dest>问题到底是什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A thief. The one that got away. An Imperial woman, based on the reports, and a lone operative.</Source>
      <Dest>有个贼。逃之夭夭了。报告上说，是个帝国族的女人，一贯单独行动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly is the problem?</Source>
      <Dest>问题到底是什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She's burglarized homes of a number of notable lords, thanes, and nobles.  At times she has even ransomed their children.  </Source>
      <Dest>她已经在很多家领主、男爵、贵族家入室行窃成功过。有几次甚至【】了他们的孩子</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly is the problem?</Source>
      <Dest>问题到底是什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She's outfoxed the city guards, evaded the Oculatus, and even managed to rankle prominent members of the Thieves Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>她愚弄了城市的守卫，躲过了锐眼鹰组织，甚至让盗贼工会的高手都吃苦头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It sounds like the Empire is accustomed to acts of betrayal.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来帝国像是习惯了背叛的行为.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The draw of power is a form of skooma that corrupts even the best of us. The assassin is the potion that purges it from the system.</Source>
      <Dest>权力的诱惑如同是斯库玛的一种。足以腐化我们中最强大的人。刺客则是一剂良药将他们从组织中彻底清除。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It sounds like the Empire is accustomed to acts of betrayal.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来帝国像是习惯了背叛的行为.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As such, he is often asked to target the very people he takes orders from, in order to serve the will of the only person he answers to.</Source>
      <Dest>因此，他奉命刺杀的目标经常会是自己的顶头上司，以尽忠于他唯一真正的主人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It sounds like the Empire is accustomed to acts of betrayal.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来帝国像是习惯了背叛的行为.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The life of an assassin is far from pleasant. Which is why when Maro became a father, he chose a new path. </Source>
      <Dest>刺客的生活毫无生趣。因此当马洛当了父亲之后，他踏上了一条新路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Describe the Penitus Oculatus initiation.</Source>
      <Dest>开始描述下锐眼鹰吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is as you might expect. Recruits are chosen for various positions, and given tests to determine their aptitude and readiness.</Source>
      <Dest>大概和你预期的一样。新兵都是从各种渠道精选而来，并通过考核来测定他们的资质和才能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Describe the Penitus Oculatus initiation.</Source>
      <Dest>开始描述下锐眼鹰吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ironically, before he became chief of security, Commander Maro was originally recruited as an assassin.  </Source>
      <Dest>讽刺的是，指挥官【Maro在成为首席安保之前，被招募的职位本来是刺客的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Describe the Penitus Oculatus initiation.</Source>
      <Dest>开始描述下锐眼鹰吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In the Penitus Oculatus, the assassin is merely a tool.  He is required to kill without questioning his orders.</Source>
      <Dest>在锐眼鹰组织里，刺客不过是件工具。他被要求毫无置疑地执行刺杀任务.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Describe the Penitus Oculatus initiation.</Source>
      <Dest>开始描述下锐眼鹰吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is because the most dangerous enemies typically come from within. The very advisors the Emperor trusts most are the ones likely to betray him.</Source>
      <Dest>这是因为最危险的敌人往往来自内部。皇帝身边最受信赖的言官也往往是最有可能背叛他的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have a description of the thief?</Source>
      <Dest>你能描述一下这个小偷吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do. It's been burned into the bone of my skull, from sketches and wanted posters and images from another time.</Source>
      <Dest>可以。从那些描绘和通缉令还有无数次看到的图像，那些早已深深烙印在了我的头脑里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have a description of the thief?</Source>
      <Dest>你能描述一下这个小偷吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A raven-haired woman, 32 years of age, with an aquiline nose and eyes the color of steel.</Source>
      <Dest>那是个发色乌黑的女人，今年32岁，长着鹰钩鼻和【钢铁颜色的眼睛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have a description of the thief?</Source>
      <Dest>你能描述一下这个小偷吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She is as fearsome as an Orc, but can be as cunning as a diplomat, and if need be, can charm you with the grace of a sylph.</Source>
      <Dest>她像兽人般可怕，却也会像政客一样狡猾，必要的时候，还能用仙女般的优雅令你沉醉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The executioner's axe is too good for the likes of those.</Source>
      <Dest>侩子手的斧头太适合像那些人的人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm not sure anyone would even bother. Too busy chopping the heads of elderly Talos worshippers to care about the Tamriel's most celebrated thief.</Source>
      <Dest>不知还是不是有人在乎这个。这年头都忙着去砍塔洛斯信徒的脑袋，没空去管泰姆瑞尔的江洋大盗了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The executioner's axe is too good for the likes of those.</Source>
      <Dest>侩子手的斧头太适合像那些人的人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I hadn't retired, they would still have me raid the chests of every Nord who wore a beard that resembled Tiber Septim's.</Source>
      <Dest>要是我没退休，他们也会派我天天去找那些蓄着泰伯·赛普丁一样胡子的诺德人的麻烦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No wonder they call you "specters."  You are agents of death.</Source>
      <Dest>难怪他们叫你 “妖怪”。你是死亡代理人嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True enough. There is a misconception that the Penitus Oculatus acting as a security force implies being a strictly defensive unit.</Source>
      <Dest>那倒也是。有那么一种曲解的说法认为锐眼鹰是以安保部门的名义行使国防职务的部队。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No wonder they call you "specters."  You are agents of death.</Source>
      <Dest>难怪他们叫你 “妖怪”。你是死亡代理人嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>On the contrary, the best way to stop an assassination is to root out the conspirators before their plans take form.</Source>
      <Dest>正相反，要想阻止暗杀最好的方法就是在暗杀计划成型之前铲除阴谋者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No wonder they call you "specters."  You are agents of death.</Source>
      <Dest>难怪他们叫你 “妖怪”。你是死亡代理人嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As a former assassin, Commander Maro had the advantage of knowing how the enemy operates, and that is why he was chosen as the chief security agent.</Source>
      <Dest>作为一名前刺客，马洛指挥官非常善于判断敌人动向，这也是为什么他被选为首席安全顾问的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You've lost your head, soldier. I think you're in love this woman.</Source>
      <Dest>你已经犯晕乎了，士兵。我想你恐怕爱上这个女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that what you think?  I am not some young buck, maddened by lust.  </Source>
      <Dest>这就是你的结论？我又不是某些年轻人，被形形色色的欲望冲昏了头脑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You've lost your head, soldier. I think you're in love this woman.</Source>
      <Dest>你已经犯晕乎了，士兵。我想你恐怕爱上这个女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It matters not whether the Raven of Anvil is a woman or a wraith.</Source>
      <Dest>不管瑞文是人还是鬼。我都是为锐眼鹰效力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You've lost your head, soldier. I think you're in love this woman.</Source>
      <Dest>你已经犯晕乎了，士兵。我想你恐怕爱上这个女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My loyalty to the Empire is greater than some lover's passing fancy.</Source>
      <Dest>我对帝国的忠诚远远大于某些情侣的三分钟热度。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see, this could tarnish your reputation.  You want to cover up your shame.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了，这可能会损害你的声誉。你想掩饰你的耻辱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you reach my age, you care naught for such things.  Yes, there may have been a time when I wanted justice for her crimes.</Source>
      <Dest>等你到了我的年纪，这类事情你就不怎么关心了。是啊，或许有那么一段时间我真是要审判她的罪行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see, this could tarnish your reputation.  You want to cover up your shame.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了，这可能会损害你的声誉。你想掩饰你的耻辱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For years I struggled to reconcile my love for her and my loyalty to the Empire.</Source>
      <Dest>多年来，我一直努力平衡自己对她的爱和对帝国的忠诚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see, this could tarnish your reputation.  You want to cover up your shame.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了，这可能会损害你的声誉。你想掩饰你的耻辱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But as I approach the twilight of my life, none of that matters.  All I want is to see her once more.</Source>
      <Dest>但随着我的生命走向迟暮，才发现那些根本都不重要。我想要的仅仅是想再见她一面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see, this could tarnish your reputation.  You want to cover up your shame.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了，这可能会损害你的声誉。你想掩饰你的耻辱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To stroke her hair, to look into her eyes, and know that she's happy.  Only then can I find peace.</Source>
      <Dest>能抚摸着她的秀发，注视着她的眼眸，知道她活得快乐。我才能死而无憾哪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see, this could tarnish your reputation.  You want to cover up your shame.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了，这可能会损害你的声誉。你想掩饰你的耻辱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I...I'm sorry. If you please, I need a moment to myself.  </Source>
      <Dest>我……我很抱歉。你不介意的话，我想一个人静静。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem almost fond of her.</Source>
      <Dest>你对她喜欢的不得了啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What are you implying? One cannot evade the Penitus Oculatus and not earn a measure of respect. And one cannot defy them without earning their wrath.</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么？能从锐眼鹰手中逃脱的高手当然会令人佩服。而藐视他们的人也必然吃不了兜着走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem almost fond of her.</Source>
      <Dest>你对她喜欢的不得了啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am soldier sworn in the service of the Penitus Oculatus.  Sworn to uphold the law.</Source>
      <Dest>我是宣誓效忠锐眼鹰的士兵。宣誓要维护法律的尊严。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem almost fond of her.</Source>
      <Dest>你对她喜欢的不得了啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If someone breaks the law, it matters not whether they are The Raven of Anvil or the Emperor's own kin.  They are all criminal scum.</Source>
      <Dest>只要有人违犯法律，不管他是铁砧城之鸦还是皇帝的亲戚。都是可耻的罪犯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It may surprise you to find that in this regard, the initiation for both the Dark Brotherhood and the Oculatus are one in the same.</Source>
      <Dest>这事儿说出来你可能会吓到，锐眼鹰的入会仪式跟黑暗兄弟会是一个套路的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Both ask their initiates to shed the blood of a stranger as proof of their fealty, their mettle, and willingness to do the hard thing.  </Source>
      <Dest>都是叫学徒去杀一个陌生人来证明他们的忠心，大胆、和有难同当的意志。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When first presented with this task, Commander Maro faltered, as do all men of conscience. It was then that I broke the rules.</Source>
      <Dest>当第一次看到这个任务时，指挥官马洛动摇了，如同每个有良心的人一样。然后就由我打破了规则。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I told him who the target was. Or more precisely, what he was.</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉了他那个目标是谁。或者更准确的说，他是什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did something happen during his initiation?</Source>
      <Dest>在他受刺激的时候有什么事情发生了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>More like what didn't happen. Commanders like Maro may seem like hard, unyielding men, and there is certainly that side to them.</Source>
      <Dest>想起来更像是没有发生过。马洛那样的指挥官是看起来像个硬汉，而且本来也应该有那样的一面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did something happen during his initiation?</Source>
      <Dest>在他受刺激的时候有什么事情发生了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is also the side that is the caring father, the loving husband, and the humble servant of the Empire.</Source>
      <Dest>而另一面的他则是个体贴的父亲、一个深情的丈夫，还有帝国的忠实仆从。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The side of kindness is something that is almost innate.  Even as children we know the value of friendship, empathy, and love.</Source>
      <Dest>人类那仁慈的一面几乎是与生俱来的。即使是孩提时代我们也懂得友谊，同情和爱的价值。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did something happen during his initiation?</Source>
      <Dest>在他受刺激的时候有什么事情发生了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did something happen during his initiation?</Source>
      <Dest>在他受刺激的时候有什么事情发生了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The other side, the one that makes you a man, that must be forged through a crucible of blood, sacrifice, and at times, even apathy.</Source>
      <Dest>另一面，要把你铸成一个男人的一面，必须用上鲜血、献祭，有时，甚至是冷酷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's clear you and this Raven are working together.</Source>
      <Dest>很显然你和这次的掠夺是一伙的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Retired or not, my allegiance lies with the Empire, and I will not tolerate such groundless assaults on my character!</Source>
      <Dest>不管我是不是退休，都绝对忠于帝国，也决不能容忍如此毫无底线的人身攻击！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's clear you and this Raven are working together.</Source>
      <Dest>很显然你和这次的掠夺是一伙的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suggest you turn around and leave from whence you came.  Good day!</Source>
      <Dest>我建议你从哪儿来就滚回哪儿去。不谢！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Safe travels.</Source>
      <Dest>旅途安全。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until next time.</Source>
      <Dest>下回见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Citizen.</Source>
      <Dest>公民。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can I help you?</Source>
      <Dest>我能为你效劳吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you need?</Source>
      <Dest>你想要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But either way, I hope it finds a use for it. And thanks again. I almost forgot what it felt like. Kindness.</Source>
      <Dest>But either way, I hope it finds a use for it. And thanks again. I almost forgot what it felt like. Kindness.</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
