<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She...what? But you don't even know her! The two of you rarely even speak!</Source>
      <Dest>She...what? But you don't even know her! The two of you rarely even speak!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Peragorn, can I ask you a question? In your time here at the Bunkhouse, has Haelga ever made any...romantic advances?</Source>
      <Dest>Peragorn, can I ask you a question? In your time here at the Bunkhouse, has Haelga ever made any...romantic advances?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I see.  So, just the bottom half then?</Source>
      <Dest>明白了。也就是说只有下半部分？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is it true that the Elves in Valenwood enjoy being...one with nature?  I wonder if I'll even need clothes.</Source>
      <Dest>威木省的精灵还真的喜欢……天人合一？我都不知道要不要穿衣服了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've retrieved the Statue of Dibella.</Source>
      <Dest>我拿回了那尊迪贝拉雕像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Congratulations. It seems you have succeeded in performing this mundane and extremely tedious task.</Source>
      <Dest>恭喜恭喜。看这情况，你似乎已经完成了这件枯燥乏味的工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've retrieved the Statue of Dibella.</Source>
      <Dest>我拿回了那尊迪贝拉雕像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've retrieved the two Statues of Dibella.</Source>
      <Dest>我拿回了那两尊迪贝拉雕像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your persistence is remarkable. Not only have you successfully retrieved two statues of Dibella, but you have done so while maintaining your sanity. </Source>
      <Dest>你的持久性令人惊讶，不仅仅是因为你取出了两个迪贝拉的雕像，还因为你仍然如此清醒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've retrieved the Statue of Dibella.</Source>
      <Dest>我拿回了那尊迪贝拉雕像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've retrieved three Statues of Dibella.</Source>
      <Dest>我取回了三个迪贝拉雕像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You've done it! Glorious! Now surely Haelga will allow me to consummate this marriage. </Source>
      <Dest>你做到了！太帅了！现在哈尔嘉肯定会准许我让这场婚礼完美起来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Whatever.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，爱咋地咋地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't be flippant, or I will have Haelga suffocate you with her bosom. Now go. Failure is not an option.</Source>
      <Dest>别如此轻薄，不然让你死于哈尔嘉的胸器之下。现在该干什么干什么去。失败可是不被允许的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It cannot be done.</Source>
      <Dest>这个没办法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do not take such a negative attitude. Even the journey to High Hrothgar begins with a simple step. Now go. Achieve the unthinkable.</Source>
      <Dest>不要这么悲观嘛，不积跬步，无以至千里。现在好了，去找寻奇迹吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I can, my Jarl.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以，我的男爵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Excellent. Go forth, gather the statues, and bathe yourself in glory!</Source>
      <Dest>好极了。继续前进，收集雕像，接受荣耀的洗礼！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can you do it?</Source>
      <Dest>你能做到吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not in the least. If Haelga's bosom is the last thing I ever see, then I consider myself a lucky Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>完全不是。石榴裙下死做鬼也风流。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the Divines, Amicus, do I have to do everything for you? You're worse than Peragorn. Here.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵在上，艾美斯，你非得什么事儿都让我替你做吗？在这点上你可比不上佩勒根。给。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, no. You've proven more than adequate at that. No, to escape this place, you will have to overcome one of two challenges.</Source>
      <Dest>不，不。你已经证明了自己的能力绰绰有余。不过，要离开这个地方，你还要赢得这两项挑战的其中一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Behind the door on the right, you will find a twenty skeever-sized Centurions.  Behind the door on the left, one Centurion-sized skeever. </Source>
      <Dest>穿过右边的门，你会遇到二十个雪鼠体积的矮人百夫长。穿过左边的门，则有一头矮人百夫长大小的雪鼠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Make your choice, and you'll find your exit.</Source>
      <Dest>做出选择，你就能离开这里了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can leave whenever you wish. The sooner the better. I get performance anxiety when I know people are listening.</Source>
      <Dest>你想什么时候走都行。但是越快越好。有观众的时候我总会怯场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can take the door on the left, or the door on the right. Both present their own unique challenges.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以开左边的门，也可以开右边的门。两边都有他们特有的挑战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh right. But where am I going to find a trout at this hour?</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。不过在这个时间我该去哪儿找一条鳟鱼？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well. What I ask is a feat never attempted in the history of mortals. I ask you to fetch not one, not two, but three statues of Dibella!</Source>
      <Dest>很好。我的要求是一个人类史上前所未有的成就。我要你取的不是一个两个，而是整整三个迪贝拉的雕像！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bravo. But what I ask next, may wilt even the hardiest of minds.</Source>
      <Dest>很棒。但我接下来的要求，会让最坚强人畏缩不前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not all of you will survive this task, but those that will, shall carve their name into the sky for all eternity.</Source>
      <Dest>并不是你们中的每一个人都能活下来，但是那些回来的人将会流芳百世。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Actually Amicus, since I'm the Jarl, technically nothing I say can ever be ridiculed. Otherwise people lose their toes and other body parts.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上艾美斯，由于我是领主，原则上我不能乱说话。否则的话，人民就会被斩断脚趾乃至身上的其他部位。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Besides, I'm only playing the role you gave me. After all...</Source>
      <Dest>此外，我正在扮演你给我的角色。毕竟……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But now I will ask you to do something far more harrowing. Before, you may recall that I asked you to fetch one statue of Dibella.</Source>
      <Dest>但现在我将让你做一些更苦恼的事情。你可能还记得，之前我有要你去取一尊迪贝拉的雕像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Somehow, you managed to survive. But now, I ask you to be twice the hero you were before. For I need two statues of Dibella, and I need them now.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说，你活着回来了。不过现在，我要让你有更高的声望。我需要两个迪贝拉雕像，现在就要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes. In fact, precisely the one over there.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。准确的来说，那边那个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm glad you asked. I need you to fetch an item of great importance.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴你过问。我需要你去取一个很重要的物品。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One that could very well save the entire kingdom, but more importantly, my marriage. Haelga is a very needy woman.</Source>
      <Dest>一个能够守护整个王国的人，但是更重要的是我的婚姻。哈尔嘉是一个很穷的女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I need you to retrieve for me, one statue of Dibella.</Source>
      <Dest>我要你帮我找个东西，一个迪贝拉的塑像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What, did you think you could just clap your hands and wake up? Not in my domain.</Source>
      <Dest>什么你以为你可以简单的合上双手然后醒过来？在我的领域里，不可能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Especially given my entire existence is dependent on you staying asleep.</Source>
      <Dest>尤其在我完全依赖于你的沉睡才能存在的情况下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do. But getting out won't be easy.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，想出去可没那么容易。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not just any face, Amicus. The face of your Jarl. Nice hat, by the way.</Source>
      <Dest>不是什么面子的问题，这关系到作为贵族的你的威信。顺便提一下，帽子不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How should I know, Amicus, it's your dream.</Source>
      <Dest>我为什么应该知道，阿米卡，那是你的梦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was wondering if you knew the creator of this sculpture of Mara, and whether there was a...mortal inspiration for its contour.</Source>
      <Dest>我想知道你是否了解谁才是这座玛拉雕像的制作者，以及在制作它的轮廓时是否有一些……参考凡人外貌的成分在里面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Jade, I was wondering if you could perhaps answer a question for me. A purely intellectual one of course.</Source>
      <Dest>Jade, I was wondering if you could perhaps answer a question for me. A purely intellectual one of course.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Forget her. There aren't enough potions in Nirn to cure the diseases you'd get.</Source>
      <Dest>忘了她吧。这里有足够的奈恩药水来治疗你的伤痛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I suppose you're right. It's just from a purely intellectual standpoint, there aren't too many places to learn Dibellan arts.</Source>
      <Dest>Yes, I suppose you're right. It's just from a purely intellectual standpoint, there aren't too many places to learn Dibellan arts.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Forget her. There aren't enough potions in Nirn to cure the diseases you'd get.</Source>
      <Dest>忘了她吧。这里有足够的奈恩药水来治疗你的伤痛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, I don't even have to bed her. I'm fairly observant. The least she could do is let me watch.</Source>
      <Dest>I mean, I don't even have to bed her. I'm fairly observant. The least she could do is let me watch.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I enjoy the classics.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢经典的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You and me both. Too many people see books as practical tools to boost their acumen, but pass over the wealth of wisdom held within each story.</Source>
      <Dest>You and me both. Too many people see books as practical tools to boost their acumen, but pass over the wealth of wisdom held within each story.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I enjoy the classics.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢经典的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Others will read a story but miss the point entirely.</Source>
      <Dest>其余的人读了故事，但却完全没抓到重点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I enjoy the classics.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢经典的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stories about Daedra, for instance, are not about Daedra.  They are meant to show us the grotesqueness of man.</Source>
      <Dest>就拿魔族的故事来说好了。它们的目的不是在说魔族怎样，而是告诉我们人有多荒诞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I tend to skip through books, to be honest.</Source>
      <Dest>我实话，我比较倾向于略览书籍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I get it. You seek the knowledge, but not the wisdom. You boost your skills while failing to develop your character.</Source>
      <Dest>I get it. You seek the knowledge, but not the wisdom. You boost your skills while failing to develop your character.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Haelga is built like most Nord women. It's not a bosom, it's a chest plate.</Source>
      <Dest>Haelga is built like most Nord women. It's not a bosom, it's a chest plate.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you've seen it? Or touched it? Why has everyone in this town done so but me?</Source>
      <Dest>So you've seen it? Or touched it? Why has everyone in this town done so but me?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Haelga is rather beautiful. I can see why men chase her.</Source>
      <Dest>Haelga is rather beautiful. I can see why men chase her.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But that's the problem. I didn't envision there would be any chasing at all. Not with her reputation, anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>But that's the problem. I didn't envision there would be any chasing at all. Not with her reputation, anyway.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Her bosom is ample, but she also has a chin that's squarer than a table.</Source>
      <Dest>Her bosom is ample, but she also has a chin that's squarer than a table.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, but I won't be groping her chin. I'm more interested in the parts that are common to all women.</Source>
      <Dest>Yes, but I won't be groping her chin. I'm more interested in the parts that are common to all women.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you a friend of Haelga's?</Source>
      <Dest>你是哈尔嘉的朋友？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm not a friend, I'm a suitor. If only I could convince her to see me as such.</Source>
      <Dest>I'm not a friend, I'm a suitor. If only I could convince her to see me as such.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No, you're quite right. Her bosom is very ample.</Source>
      <Dest>No, you're quite right. Her bosom is very ample.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although granted, it's not all about her bosom, although that does weigh heavily into my decision to pursue her.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然我承认，这不都是因为她的巨乳。虽然那确实是最重要的决定因素让我去追求她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>None taken.</Source>
      <Dest>一个都没说对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, it's not like I don't have friends that are Argonian. Real ones. Not the imaginary kind people make up to hide their prejudice.</Source>
      <Dest>Yes, it's not like I don't have friends that are Argonian. Real ones. Not the imaginary kind people make up to hide their prejudice.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>None taken.</Source>
      <Dest>一个都没说对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can even tell you their names!  Wujeeta's a kind soul and a good fisherman, at least when she isn't offering favors for skooma.  </Source>
      <Dest>我甚至可以告诉你他们的名字！巫杰塔是一个善良的渔夫，至少在她吸食斯库玛之前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>None taken.</Source>
      <Dest>一个都没说对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Keerava and Talen-Jei are the personification of true love. Something we all aspire to achieve.</Source>
      <Dest>基拉瓦和塔伦杰就像是真爱的化身，我们所有都渴望得到这些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You'll have to get in line. I think it ends somewhere in Black Marsh.</Source>
      <Dest>You'll have to get in line. I think it ends somewhere in Black Marsh.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And follow a bunch of Argonians? Talk about your sloppy seconds. No offense.</Source>
      <Dest>And follow a bunch of Argonians? Talk about your sloppy seconds. No offense.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fear not. I have no desire to kill you. I might lop off a hand though.</Source>
      <Dest>Fear not. I have no desire to kill you. I might lop off a hand though.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hope not! I've grown quite attached to it. We're practically inseparable.</Source>
      <Dest>I hope not! I've grown quite attached to it. We're practically inseparable.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That shouldn't be too difficult, if you don't mind sharing.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你不介意分享的话，这事就不会太困难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh I don't mind. I'm not in it for the long haul. All I want is to bed a woman with as little effort as possible.</Source>
      <Dest>Oh I don't mind. I'm not in it for the long haul. All I want is to bed a woman with as little effort as possible.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That shouldn't be too difficult, if you don't mind sharing.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你不介意分享的话，这事就不会太困难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Especially one with such an ample bosom. I think that's the right word. Ample.</Source>
      <Dest>Especially one with such an ample bosom. I think that's the right word. Ample.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you ultimately want with Haelga? Romance? Marriage?</Source>
      <Dest>What do you ultimately want with Haelga? Romance? Marriage?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Marry Haelga? Now there's a frightening thought. Oh no, I assure you, my intentions are entirely puerile. I want to bed her.</Source>
      <Dest>Marry Haelga? Now there's a frightening thought. Oh no, I assure you, my intentions are entirely puerile. I want to bed her.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you ultimately want with Haelga? Romance? Marriage?</Source>
      <Dest>What do you ultimately want with Haelga? Romance? Marriage?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I want to dip my face in her ample, ample bosom and make crude animal noises.</Source>
      <Dest>I want to dip my face in her ample, ample bosom and make crude animal noises.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you ultimately want with Haelga? Romance? Marriage?</Source>
      <Dest>What do you ultimately want with Haelga? Romance? Marriage?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I want to taste her apple pie, eat her sweet roll, and...now I'm hungry.</Source>
      <Dest>我想尝她的苹果派，吃她的甜甜圈，然后…然后我饿了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Leave her be. A thoughtful guy like you deserves better.</Source>
      <Dest>离开她吧。想你这样的人应该值得更好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And what if "better" deserves more than what I am?  No, if I cannot woo a debauched woman like Haelga, I might as well marry a Draugr.</Source>
      <Dest>要是那个“更好的”值得比我更好的人呢？不，如果我无法对哈尔嘉这种荡妇求爱，我干脆娶尸鬼为妻算了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know what I'm doing wrong. Why won't Haelga acknowledge me?</Source>
      <Dest>I don't know what I'm doing wrong. Why won't Haelga acknowledge me?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Really? I just lost my appetite.</Source>
      <Dest>Really? I just lost my appetite.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did I mention her bosom was ample? It seemed like an important detail.  </Source>
      <Dest>Did I mention her bosom was ample? It seemed like an important detail.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's that working out for you?</Source>
      <Dest>你做得如何啦？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not well. No matter how ferociously I chase Haelga, she treats me as if I just contracted Swamp Fever.</Source>
      <Dest>Not well. No matter how ferociously I chase Haelga, she treats me as if I just contracted Swamp Fever.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's that working out for you?</Source>
      <Dest>你做得如何啦？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Does she think I'm an Argonian! I've never even seen a swamp! Um, no offense.</Source>
      <Dest>Does she think I'm an Argonian! I've never even seen a swamp! Um, no offense.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And here I thought your motives were noble. You're just another deviant.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你的动机是高尚的。你只是离经叛道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not entirely. There are two heads at play here. One sees this as training. No different than becoming a bard or mastering the sword.</Source>
      <Dest>Not entirely. There are two heads at play here. One sees this as training. No different than becoming a bard or mastering the sword.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And here I thought your motives were noble. You're just another deviant.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你的动机是高尚的。你只是离经叛道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The other's goal is fairly self-explanatory. But if you like I can explain it for you, with pictures and shadow puppets.</Source>
      <Dest>The other's goal is fairly self-explanatory. But if you like I can explain it for you, with pictures and shadow puppets.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's not funny.</Source>
      <Dest>这可不好笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, rats. You're gonna beat me up now, aren't you. Well, I'll have you know I am well trained in the art of curling up in a ball and weeping softly.</Source>
      <Dest>Oh, rats. You're gonna beat me up now, aren't you. Well, I'll have you know I am well trained in the art of curling up in a ball and weeping softly.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is that why this place smells so bad?</Source>
      <Dest>Is that why this place smells so bad?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say that the best way to answer life's biggest questions is to look inward. This is no different.</Source>
      <Dest>They say that the best way to answer life's biggest questions is to look inward. This is no different.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ever consider that your habits are why Haelga deflects your advances?</Source>
      <Dest>你就没有想过其实正是你的习惯才使得哈尔嘉不愿意接受你的好意？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that was sarcasm. Trust me, my skin may be colored like a mudcrab, but I've taken care not to smell like one.  </Source>
      <Dest>这个嘛……挺讽刺的。相信我，也许我的肤色很像泥沼蟹，但我已经努力让它别闻起来也像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I apologize for my rudeness. I was simply curious.</Source>
      <Dest>I apologize for my rudeness. I was simply curious.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I understand. Curiosity is the driving force in many of our lives, and the failure to sate it can lead to many a frustration.</Source>
      <Dest>Yes, I understand. Curiosity is the driving force in many of our lives, and the failure to sate it can lead to many a frustration.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I apologize for my rudeness. I was simply curious.</Source>
      <Dest>I apologize for my rudeness. I was simply curious.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes I think it's best to just sit down and read about other people's adventures instead.</Source>
      <Dest>Sometimes I think it's best to just sit down and read about other people's adventures instead.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I apologize for my rudeness. I was simply curious.</Source>
      <Dest>I apologize for my rudeness. I was simply curious.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What about you? Do you enjoy the art of reading?</Source>
      <Dest>What about you? Do you enjoy the art of reading?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are you? What is it you do here?</Source>
      <Dest>Who are you? What is it you do here?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now that's an odd and brusque way to address a stranger now, isn't it?</Source>
      <Dest>这样的方式跟陌生人说话很奇怪也很冒失，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I like to read the fear in a man's eyes as I bludgeon him.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢在棒击别人时品味他眼中的恐惧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, then we have much in common. Me being the person who is usually bludgeoned.  Not much else though.</Source>
      <Dest>Ah, then we have much in common. Me being the person who is usually bludgeoned.  Not much else though.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you tried other women? What of the Temple of Dibella?</Source>
      <Dest>Have you tried other women? What of the Temple of Dibella?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know. I saved up all my gold, traveled to the opposite end of Skyrim and what did they tell me?</Source>
      <Dest>I know. I saved up all my gold, traveled to the opposite end of Skyrim and what did they tell me?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you tried other women? What of the Temple of Dibella?</Source>
      <Dest>Have you tried other women? What of the Temple of Dibella?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you tried other women? What of the Temple of Dibella?</Source>
      <Dest>Have you tried other women? What of the Temple of Dibella?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh no, I'm not going through that again. Haelga is right here, and by all accounts not a picky woman.</Source>
      <Dest>Oh no, I'm not going through that again. Haelga is right here, and by all accounts not a picky woman.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Source>
      <Dest>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What makes you think bedding Haelga will be that easy?</Source>
      <Dest>What makes you think bedding Haelga will be that easy?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's well known that Haelga is what ruffians call a very "loose" woman.</Source>
      <Dest>It's well known that Haelga is what ruffians call a very "loose" woman.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Source>
      <Dest>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What makes you think bedding Haelga will be that easy?</Source>
      <Dest>What makes you think bedding Haelga will be that easy?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Man, Mer, Dwarven Centurion, they say she takes all who are willing.</Source>
      <Dest>人类、精灵、矮人百夫长，据说不管谁想要她都愿意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Source>
      <Dest>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What makes you think bedding Haelga will be that easy?</Source>
      <Dest>What makes you think bedding Haelga will be that easy?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Somehow I manage to be excluded from this special fraternity.</Source>
      <Dest>不知何故，我被这个特殊的组织拒于门外。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Source>
      <Dest>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah yes, you speak of the difference between perception and reality.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你提到了理想与现实的差距。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Source>
      <Dest>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've read enough phony bard tales to know how stories like to wash heroes clean while the villains are run through the mud.</Source>
      <Dest>读过这么多唬烂人的吟游诗人故事，足以让我明白故事如何漂白英雄，而恶棍沾了满身烂泥。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Source>
      <Dest>Is it possible Haelga isn't as promiscuous as you think?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So maybe you're right. But blaming others for your failings seems rather daft.</Source>
      <Dest>So maybe you're right. But blaming others for your failings seems rather daft.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then what's stopping you? Go for it.</Source>
      <Dest>Then what's stopping you? Go for it.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh you jest, but bedding a woman is not so simple as you make it sound. I should know, I'm terrible at it.</Source>
      <Dest>Oh you jest, but bedding a woman is not so simple as you make it sound. I should know, I'm terrible at it.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My favorite books are about Argonian maids and their varying degrees of lust.</Source>
      <Dest>我最喜欢的书事关于蜥蜴人女佣的情欲故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you've come to the right place!</Source>
      <Dest>那你真是来对地方了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My favorite books are about Argonian maids and their varying degrees of lust.</Source>
      <Dest>我最喜欢的书事关于蜥蜴人女佣的情欲故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wujeeta will knead your loaf for a drop of skooma, and you could probably slip a maid outfit on From-Deepest-Fathoms without her ever noticing.</Source>
      <Dest>巫杰塔会为了一滴斯库玛搓爆你的脑袋，而你则可以把她的女仆装塞进她的乳沟还不会被她发现。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My favorite books are about Argonian maids and their varying degrees of lust.</Source>
      <Dest>我最喜欢的书事关于蜥蜴人女佣的情欲故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In Riften, everyone's spear gets polished!  Please don't tell Keerava I said that.</Source>
      <Dest>在裂谷城，每个人的矛都被磨得发亮！请别告诉基拉瓦这是我说的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Some people write about confronting the Wolf Queen. I live it.</Source>
      <Dest>Some people write about confronting the Wolf Queen. I live it.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In that case, I envy you. A book's greatest strength and weakness is its ability to distort reality. I'm curious as to how big the effect is.</Source>
      <Dest>In that case, I envy you. A book's greatest strength and weakness is its ability to distort reality. I'm curious as to how big the effect is.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Relax. I don't want to soil my fists pummeling such a filthy worm.</Source>
      <Dest>Relax. I don't want to soil my fists pummeling such a filthy worm.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then thank the Divines I neglected to bathe.  </Source>
      <Dest>Then thank the Divines I neglected to bathe.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Works on everyone else.</Source>
      <Dest>为其他人工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That I believe. I will never understand the etiquette here. Everything is about saving time and how short life is.</Source>
      <Dest>That I believe. I will never understand the etiquette here. Everything is about saving time and how short life is.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Works on everyone else.</Source>
      <Dest>为其他人工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No one ever stops to sit down and read a good book. Or a bad book, for that matter. The Divines know there are plenty of those.</Source>
      <Dest>No one ever stops to sit down and read a good book. Or a bad book, for that matter. The Divines know there are plenty of those.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Works on everyone else.</Source>
      <Dest>为其他人工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What about you? Do you enjoy the art of reading?</Source>
      <Dest>What about you? Do you enjoy the art of reading?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you have any tips on how to woo Haelga, let me know.</Source>
      <Dest>If you have any tips on how to woo Haelga, let me know.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Safe travels.</Source>
      <Dest>旅途安全。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right then.</Source>
      <Dest>那好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What can I do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么可以效劳的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you want my opinion on Black-Briar Mead, I have nothing bad to say. I'd rather not go to bed missing a toe.</Source>
      <Dest>If you want my opinion on Black-Briar Mead, I have nothing bad to say. I'd rather not go to bed missing a toe.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You should try the fish here. Nothing like a good book and good mead to warm the heart.</Source>
      <Dest>You should try the fish here. Nothing like a good book and good mead to warm the heart.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I asked Haelga's niece for a refill, but I think she forgot. Tythis was harassing her again last night. Poor thing.</Source>
      <Dest>I asked Haelga's niece for a refill, but I think she forgot. Tythis was harassing her again last night. Poor thing.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the way, I was wondering if you caught a glimpse of that statue of Dibella. Notice its shape. You don't think...No, it couldn't possibly fit.</Source>
      <Dest>By the way, I was wondering if you caught a glimpse of that statue of Dibella. Notice its shape. You don't think...No, it couldn't possibly fit.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The mead here is cold and dry. Just like Haelga.</Source>
      <Dest>The mead here is cold and dry. Just like Haelga.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How much do you want for them?</Source>
      <Dest>How much do you want for them?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nothing. They didn't cost me anything to read them, so why should it cost you. Hopefully they'll help you fill some of those empty hours.</Source>
      <Dest>Nothing. They didn't cost me anything to read them, so why should it cost you. Hopefully they'll help you fill some of those empty hours.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you mind if I take a look at them?</Source>
      <Dest>Do you mind if I take a look at them?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can have them, actually. Hopefully they'll help you fill some of those empty hours.</Source>
      <Dest>You can have them, actually. Hopefully they'll help you fill some of those empty hours.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No, I don't know. What else could you possibly be talking about?</Source>
      <Dest>No, I don't know. What else could you possibly be talking about?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I'm actually talking about two things, and they're both attached to Haelga's chest. Which would make my love of books a distant third.</Source>
      <Dest>Well, I'm actually talking about two things, and they're both attached to Haelga's chest. Which would make my love of books a distant third.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, we all know about your infatuation with the bunkhouse woman.</Source>
      <Dest>Yes, we all know about your infatuation with the bunkhouse woman.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She has a name you know. Although I suppose that's not really important to either of us.</Source>
      <Dest>She has a name you know. Although I suppose that's not really important to either of us.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not interested in discussing your other hobbies, sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>I'm not interested in discussing your other hobbies, sorry.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Understood. We'll keep this conversation completely focused on bosoms, I mean, books, no, sorry, what I'm trying to say is...breasts.</Source>
      <Dest>Understood. We'll keep this conversation completely focused on bosoms, I mean, books, no, sorry, what I'm trying to say is...breasts.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not interested in discussing your other hobbies, sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>I'm not interested in discussing your other hobbies, sorry.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At least if we're talking about the erotic brand of literature.</Source>
      <Dest>At least if we're talking about the erotic brand of literature.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Stalking, from what I understand.</Source>
      <Dest>Stalking, from what I understand.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that what I'm doing? Well, it does sound rather malevolent when you put it that way.</Source>
      <Dest>Is that what I'm doing? Well, it does sound rather malevolent when you put it that way.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to ask you about some books.</Source>
      <Dest>I want to ask you about some books.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh? Books are my favorite subject. Well, other than, you know...</Source>
      <Dest>Oh? Books are my favorite subject. Well, other than, you know...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to ask you about some books.</Source>
      <Dest>I want to ask you about some books.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What can you tell me about the person who sent you these books?</Source>
      <Dest>What can you tell me about the person who sent you these books?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not much. I received them from a courier not too long ago, with specific instructions to hold on to said books until the owner retrieved them.</Source>
      <Dest>Not much. I received them from a courier not too long ago, with specific instructions to hold on to said books until the owner retrieved them.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to ask you about some books.</Source>
      <Dest>I want to ask you about some books.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What can you tell me about the person who sent you these books?</Source>
      <Dest>What can you tell me about the person who sent you these books?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But he said if he didn't show up within a week, I was free to do with them as I pleased. </Source>
      <Dest>But he said if he didn't show up within a week, I was free to do with them as I pleased. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to ask you about some books.</Source>
      <Dest>I want to ask you about some books.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What can you tell me about the person who sent you these books?</Source>
      <Dest>What can you tell me about the person who sent you these books?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The whole thing was rather bizarre, but these days what isn't.</Source>
      <Dest>The whole thing was rather bizarre, but these days what isn't.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to ask you about some books.</Source>
      <Dest>I want to ask you about some books.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you receive a gift of books from a friend recently?</Source>
      <Dest>Did you receive a gift of books from a friend recently?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why yes. Three of them in fact. I'm not entirely sure from why, or even who sent them. </Source>
      <Dest>Why yes. Three of them in fact. I'm not entirely sure from why, or even who sent them. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to ask you about some books.</Source>
      <Dest>I want to ask you about some books.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you receive a gift of books from a friend recently?</Source>
      <Dest>Did you receive a gift of books from a friend recently?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But perhaps it was someone who knew of my fondness for literature.</Source>
      <Dest>But perhaps it was someone who knew of my fondness for literature.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, we all know Niluva's addicted to skooma. What if you were to place a bottle in your trousers and...</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，我们都知道尼路佤磕斯库玛上瘾了。如果你把一瓶斯库玛搁进裤子里，然后...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What? Don't look at me like that, I'm being serious.</Source>
      <Dest>啊？别用那种眼神看我，我是认真的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Will you shut up and just hear me out for a second?</Source>
      <Dest>你就不能闭上嘴听我说两句吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Listen to me Peragorn, you'll never get Niluva's attention the way you're going about it.</Source>
      <Dest>听着佩勒根，用这种方法的话，你永远也得不到尼路佤的关注。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmm...maybe you're right. I'll take fifty.</Source>
      <Dest>Hmm...maybe you're right. I'll take fifty.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh no Yushari, I'm not falling for that again. I've been giving Haelga mountain flowers every day and every day I find them in the waste bucket.</Source>
      <Dest>Oh no Yushari, I'm not falling for that again. I've been giving Haelga mountain flowers every day and every day I find them in the waste bucket.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha! What do you know about clothes?</Source>
      <Dest>Ha! What do you know about clothes?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that's disappointing. Now where am I going to go to get new clothes? </Source>
      <Dest>Well, that's disappointing. Now where am I going to go to get new clothes? </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No! Really?</Source>
      <Dest>No! Really?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yushari, why is the tailor not around? </Source>
      <Dest>Yushari, why is the tailor not around? </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But either way, I hope it finds a use for it. And thanks again. I almost forgot what it felt like. Kindness.</Source>
      <Dest>But either way, I hope it finds a use for it. And thanks again. I almost forgot what it felt like. Kindness.</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
