<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Huh, just like that.  My own shadow, gone.  Never asked for this.  Don't need it.  I sneak the old fashioned way.</Source>
      <Dest>哈，就像那样，我的阴影斗篷不见了。我从未索取过斗篷，也从来不需要。我只遵循古老的传统去偷盗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A Dwarven city. Big deal.</Source>
      <Dest>一座矮人城市，呵呵，真了不起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh. I don't like being this high up. My fingers get numb and my head gets dizzy.</Source>
      <Dest>呃。我不想把它弄得更高了。我的手指已经麻木而我的头也在发晕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Another ruin. Gold, traps, and bones.</Source>
      <Dest>另一个遗迹。黄金丶陷阱及骸骨等着我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This cave is cold and sticky. That means frostbite spiders. And a lot of them.</Source>
      <Dest>这个洞穴又冷又黏。这代表着寒霜蜘蛛，很多的寒霜蜘蛛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bloody nirnroots, something big's coming out of the water.  Don't look at me, you probably stepped on something.</Source>
      <Dest>血红的耐恩根，好大的一棵从水里冒出来。别看着我，瞧你踩到了什么东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The shadows here...something big and cavernous is up ahead.</Source>
      <Dest>这里有片投影……前面有块巨大而多孔的东西存在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh.  I know pressure plates are my thing, but I think I broke my brain trying to solve the first puzzle.  Excuse me if I sit this one out.</Source>
      <Dest>呃。我知道压力板是我的事儿，但我在想破脑袋的试着解决第一个难题。如果我袖手旁观的话就抱歉啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm ready. I feel like I can take on an army of shadows.</Source>
      <Dest>我准备好了。我感觉自己可以在阴影中与一支军队较量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Plenty of danger, but fight or flee, we can use their own shadows to our advantage.</Source>
      <Dest>有很多危险，但无论或战或逃，我们都能用他们自己的阴影变成我们的优势。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey. There's some weird shadows up ahead.  Like a section of wall where it just breaks off. A hundred septims says it's a passageway.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿。前面有些奇怪的影子。像一段被打破了的墙。我赌一百金币，这铁定是个通道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Looks like there's bandits up and down this passageway. Although some of them are hanging from the ceiling.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来这个走廊一定来过土匪，尽他们有的是被悬挂在天花板上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bone chimes. Almost too easy to sidle past them. Of course, if you're a bad sneak, you can always dive into the water.</Source>
      <Dest>骨制编钟。从它们中间溜过去易如反掌。当然，如果你对自己的潜行术没自信，倒是可以一直猫在水底下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dwarven ruins.  I wish they'd do like their owners and just go away.</Source>
      <Dest>矮人遗迹。我希望他们像他们的主人一样赶快人间蒸发。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now that's what I call a behemoth.  That treasure's shadow is bigger than I am.  Oh, and the talking wall behind it is impressive too.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我所说的比蒙巨兽.。它裤子的阴影都比我大。对了，还有它后面会说话的墙也让我印象深刻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Trapping starlight?  Of all the useless things to build.  Tell me when the Dwarves invent a gold tree.  Then I'll be impressed.</Source>
      <Dest>收集星光？竟然会用这种无用的东西来创建吗。什么时候矮人造了一棵黄金之树就告诉我吧，我一定会印象深刻的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This place smells like bandits, dirt, and...cats. And not the kind that land on their feet.</Source>
      <Dest>这地方闻起来有股强盗味儿，土腥味儿，还有……猫骚味儿。没有一种方法能从那气味中幸免于难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is the part where we walk down the hall, slit some throats, and say good morning to the corpse at the end.  Right before we say good night.</Source>
      <Dest>我们就这样走下大厅，撕开一些人的喉咙，最后对着那些尸体说早安。就在我们说晚安之前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Draugr ahead.  We should draw them toward us somehow, and let them run through this gauntlet first. Maybe their bones will get the blades stuck.</Source>
      <Dest>前面有尸鬼。我们应该想辙把他们引过来，让他们先通过这波猛烈攻击。也许他们的骨头会被刀片卡住。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bright lights and tons of noise. Those Falmer think they can hide in the shadows. But not from me.</Source>
      <Dest>明亮的光线和很多的噪声。那些雪精灵以为他们能隐藏在阴影中。但却瞒不过我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A single guard, and by the looks of it, an idiot.   Still, might be hard to get behind the blood-drinker with that fire lengthening our shadows.</Source>
      <Dest>只有一个守卫，而且从面相上来看就是个白痴。然而，火光这么亮，要偷偷接近饮血者的身后也许还是有难度的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>More vampires ahead. They probably already know we're here, what with the smell of wet dog everywhere.</Source>
      <Dest>前面有更多的吸血鬼。他们可能已经知道我们在这里，多亏了落水狗的臭味那么浓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some kind of ruin. How long do you think they've stood here? Twenty years? Thirty?</Source>
      <Dest>一些古遗迹，你认为它们在这默默矗立了多久？二十年，还是三十年？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm getting bad vibes from this place. It ain't natural for a forest like this to be so far north.</Source>
      <Dest>从这里我有种不详的预感，这么靠北的地方有一片森林很不正常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's too many waterfalls in here. I can't even hear myself think. Not that I was thinking about anything, but still.</Source>
      <Dest>这儿瀑布真太多了。我都没法集中精力思考了。倒也不是我真在想啥子东西，但反正就是特闹腾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know what you did, but I might just punch you in the face for it.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道你做过什么，但是我就是想揍你那张脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This cavern is so huge they had to build stairs so the stupid thralls can get around. Lords don't have that problem. Must be nice to turn into a bat.</Source>
      <Dest>这个洞穴大到他们不得不制作台阶好让那些愚蠢的奴隶能过来。大君就没有这个问题了。变成蝙蝠一定很爽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By Nocturnal, another Dwarven city. I can already taste the metal.</Source>
      <Dest>我的诺克图娜尔啊，又一座矮人遗迹。我已经尝到金属的味道了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This fight is stupid.</Source>
      <Dest>真是打得毫无意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Spiders. We can try and use the grass for cover, but heck, so can they.</Source>
      <Dest>有蜘蛛。我们可以试着用草丛隐蔽自己。但真见鬼啊，它们也可以这么干。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These bandits may be good at slaying mammoths, but that might work in our favor. They won't see us coming.</Source>
      <Dest>这些强盗可能很擅长猎杀猛犸象，但这或许对我们有利。他们注意不到我们来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look. One of them old Nord castles or something, I don't know.</Source>
      <Dest>看啊。这是古诺德城堡还是别的什么来着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Get your weapon out. Whatever's behind this door, it's poison.</Source>
      <Dest>拔出武器准备好。这扇门后必定是有毒之物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you can heal people.  Whatever.  I don't need your pity.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说你会治疗。随便吧。我不需要你的怜悯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Watch your step. I'm sure the view's nice for you, but all I sense is a short ledge and a long way down.</Source>
      <Dest>注意脚下。我敢肯定这视角对你来说相当不错，但我的感觉是就一截短短的山脊和很长的下坡路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The ground is marked with a stag's head. That means hagravens. Get ready for a fight.</Source>
      <Dest>地面绘有雄鹿的头像. 这是乌鸦鬼婆的地盘. 准备战斗.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is a cozy little hideout.  Although if I were a Nightingale I think I would prefer sleeping in the Flagon. That river is noisy.</Source>
      <Dest>真是一个舒服的小窝。尽管如果我是夜莺的话，我会更倾向于在大酒壶里休息。只是那条河有些吵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Shadows.  The trees have one too many shadows.  Something's wrong about that light too.  It's downright perverse.  Keep your guard.</Source>
      <Dest>影子，那些树的影子也太浓了。光源好像也有问题。这显然不正常。保持警惕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This pass is cold, and I don't mean the temperature.  I guess that's why they call it Brittleshin.   Your knees freeze off.</Source>
      <Dest>这条路太冷了。要我说，不是天气的原因。布莱特辛应该就是这样，能把人的膝盖都冻掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Looks like a surprise party in there, and all of Golldir's ancestors showed up. Get ready for a brawl.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来这儿正在举行一个令人称奇的聚会呢，好像高迪尔那十八辈子祖宗都从地里冒出来了一样。准备好大吵一架吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Archer up top. Looks like three more bandits to the right. Might be hard to stealth them. More lights than usual. It's almost like a tavern.</Source>
      <Dest>上面有弓箭手，看起来右边有至少三个强盗。看来要偷偷做掉他们非常困难。（这儿）比平时更亮，感觉像是一个酒馆似的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There are more guards in this museum than they have watching the front gate.  All for this junk.  Damn machine scraps are too heavy to steal.</Source>
      <Dest>这里有比博物馆前门更多的守卫.都为了这破烂.垃圾机器残骸重的难偷得走.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fresh kill. Looks like someone's already raided this cave.  Someone strong.</Source>
      <Dest>尸体还很新鲜。看来已经有什么人搜查过这个洞穴里。某个强大的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Old ruins. Who knows what kind.</Source>
      <Dest>古老的遗迹。谁知道里面什么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hold up. Bandit camp, straight ahead. Place like this must be hard to see at night, but that's what I'm here for.</Source>
      <Dest>一直往前就是强盗营地了。那地方在晚上很难被发现，但这就是我在这儿的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is the leader's keep. Might want to go in quiet. I doubt that fool's wife is still alive, but you never know. She sees us, she might scream.</Source>
      <Dest>这是领导者的塔楼，迈特想悄悄溜进去。我怀疑那个蠢货的老婆还活着，但是你是不会知道的。她看到我们的话，没准会叫出来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Three sentries. That's it? Give us a real challenge.</Source>
      <Dest>三个哨兵。就这么简单？给我们点真正的挑战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't have to lie. Skyrim is a better place without Krog</Source>
      <Dest>没有必要撒谎. 没有Krog天际省会是个更好地方</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't have to lie. Skyrim is a better place without Krog</Source>
      <Dest>没有必要撒谎. 没有Krog天际省会是个更好地方</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gambling is a sin and you should remove yourself from this den of iniquity.</Source>
      <Dest>赌博是罪恶，你应该把自己从这个罪孽泥潭中解救出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was self-defense. Besides, the guards don't care about some nameless Orc.</Source>
      <Dest>这是自卫。此外,保安不关心一些无名的兽人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is the kin you speak of?</Source>
      <Dest>你提到的那个亲戚是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is the kin you speak of?</Source>
      <Dest>你提到的那个亲戚是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is the kin you speak of?</Source>
      <Dest>你提到的那个亲戚是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's not like you to let a bite from a crazy Orc stop you from stealing.</Source>
      <Dest>被一个发疯的兽人咬了一口就不再偷窃了？这不像你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's not like you to let a bite from a crazy Orc stop you from stealing.</Source>
      <Dest>被一个发疯的兽人咬了一口就不再偷窃了？这不像你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's not like you to let a bite from a crazy Orc stop you from stealing.</Source>
      <Dest>被一个发疯的兽人咬了一口就不再偷窃了？这不像你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't I just give you all my money and save us the hassle.</Source>
      <Dest>要不我把我的钱都给你，咱就不用争吵了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure, if you want all your winnings to end up with me.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，如果你想让你全部的胜利在我这里得到终结。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We need to come up with a better story than that.</Source>
      <Dest>我们需要拿出一个比这更好的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We need to come up with a better story than that.</Source>
      <Dest>我们需要拿出一个比这更好的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It looks like you're doing quite well on your own.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来你自己干的非常好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If he ever tried to hurt you, I'd rip out his tonsils.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他曾试图伤害你，我会扯断他的嗓子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If he ever tried to hurt you, I'd rip out his tonsils.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他曾试图伤害你，我会扯断他的嗓子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If he ever tried to hurt you, I'd rip out his tonsils.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他曾试图伤害你，我会扯断他的嗓子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you care? It's just one less oaf in the world.</Source>
      <Dest>你在乎吗？只是一个无关紧要的糊涂虫而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should have just beat him unconscious and walked away.</Source>
      <Dest>你就应该把他一下打晕转身就走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should have just beat him unconscious and walked away.</Source>
      <Dest>你就应该把他一下打晕转身就走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean? You don't exactly have green skin.</Source>
      <Dest>你说啥？你的皮肤又不是全都是绿的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean? You don't exactly have green skin.</Source>
      <Dest>你说啥？你的皮肤又不是全都是绿的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean? You don't exactly have green skin.</Source>
      <Dest>你说啥？你的皮肤又不是全都是绿的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>哈啰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright. Let's go meet this Orc.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，咱们去会会这个兽人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright. Let's go meet this Orc.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，咱们去会会这个兽人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is what happens when you ignore the Gods to hang out with worthless thugs.</Source>
      <Dest>這就是當你常與惡棍為伍而忽略了神後會發生的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is what happens when you ignore the Gods to hang out with worthless thugs.</Source>
      <Dest>這就是當你常與惡棍為伍而忽略了神後會發生的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maybe some other time.</Source>
      <Dest>也许改天吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why would the guard listen to a crazy person?</Source>
      <Dest>守卫为什么会听信一个疯子的话呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why would the guard listen to a crazy person?</Source>
      <Dest>守卫为什么会听信一个疯子的话呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why would the guard listen to a crazy person?</Source>
      <Dest>守卫为什么会听信一个疯子的话呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This Orc literally bit your hand?</Source>
      <Dest>这个兽人真的咬你的手了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This Orc literally bit your hand?</Source>
      <Dest>这个兽人真的咬你的手了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This Orc literally bit your hand?</Source>
      <Dest>这个兽人真的咬你的手了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Cave up ahead. Keep your steps light.</Source>
      <Dest>山洞就在前面，注意你的脚步声。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which is good, because this is a family squabble, and we ought to keep it in house.</Source>
      <Dest>这样就很好，因为是家丑就不要外扬了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stick and move!  Stick and move!</Source>
      <Dest>坚持住，动起来！坚持住，动起来！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You mean Krog? I couldn't care less about him. But his brother and I got history. He's the one who's kin.</Source>
      <Dest>你是说克罗格？鬼才关心他呢。但是他的兄弟和我颇有渊源。他只是一个亲戚而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fight!  Fight!</Source>
      <Dest>上啊！上啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey, there's my favorite accomplice! Want to join us? We're almost finished with this round.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，那是我最牛的同伙！想加入吗？我们这一轮就快搞定啦！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They said I stole some noble's amulet. It's because I was working the street for the past week, doing the whole blind beggar bit.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说我偷了个大人物的项链。因为上周我在街上干活，就是那种装瞎子要饭的生意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, and nearly broke every bone in my hand. But if you ask him, I had it coming.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，我手掌上几乎每一根骨头都碎了。但如果你问他的话，这都是我自找的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Except he has a name, and it's Krog, brother of Lurgok. And Lurgok, believe it or not, is kin.</Source>
      <Dest>要不是他也姓克罗格，我还真看不出他和路卡是兄弟呢。和路卡！不管你信不信，他们是亲兄弟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I guess I still haven't brought you over to the dark side. Eh, but you'll come around. I'm a persistent girl.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我还没有把你带入黑暗的一面。嗯,但是你迟早会来到我的身边的。我是一个执着的女孩儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Confident, huh. Fair warning, I'm not going to go easy on you, even if you're family.</Source>
      <Dest>你很自信嘛，呵呵。给你个小警告，我不会轻易放过你，还有你的家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Kick that stupid snowberry!</Source>
      <Dest>踢掉这愚蠢的雪莓！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, he did me a favor, and I owe him. Not that he knows it. We're all just meat to him.</Source>
      <Dest>不过,他帮了我一个忙,我欠他的。他自己也知道。We're all just meat to him.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lurgok's no priest, but he's not dangerous either, at least if you keep your distance. Of course, step in his space, and you're meat.</Source>
      <Dest>路卡可不是素食者，如果你和他保持点距离他并不危险。当然，如果你离他太近，他会把你当成一块肉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Except I quit that play the day before. You know why? Because Lurgok bit my hand when I reached for his purse.</Source>
      <Dest>除了我一天前不干了。你知道为什么吗？因为路卡在我拿他钱包的时候咬了我的手！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it's not Krog I'm concerned about. It's his brother. After all, he's kin.</Source>
      <Dest>可我关心的不是克罗格 。是他兄弟。反正，是他的亲戚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These Dwarven cities are filled with treasure.  Makes me wish I was a brute, so I could actually carry some of it out.</Source>
      <Dest>这些矮人城市充满了宝藏。我多希望自己是一个残忍的家伙啊，这样就可以把一些宝藏带出来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know this Orc, you see. He's my kin by choice, but Krog is his brother by blood.</Source>
      <Dest> 我知道这个兽人，你瞧。他是我拜把子的兄弟，而克罗格则是他血缘上的兄弟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lurgok's a tribal sort, and likes to stay at the Strongholds.  Krog said he stopped over at Largashbur in the mountains to the west. Let's go there.</Source>
      <Dest>路卡是个喜欢守着要塞的部落。克罗格说他在西边山脉的拉加施布尔等着呢。咱们往那儿走吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look. A cave. Plenty of gold inside. At least, there better be.</Source>
      <Dest>看，一个洞穴。里面都是金子。至少比这里好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stay low! Dodge and stick! Keep those hands up!</Source>
      <Dest>低下身子！躲开然后给他一拳！把你拳头举起来啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He's family the way you're family. Lurgok vouched for me one time, when the guard captain over in Falkreath tried to pin a theft on me.</Source>
      <Dest>他和你们一样，都是一家人。之前佛克瑞斯的守卫长想诬陷我偷东西，是勒高克把我保下来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Watch their feet, not their eyes!</Source>
      <Dest>看他们的脚！别看眼睛！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha, good one. I'm a worthless thug, and you still hang out with me. But with relatives, some you choose and some you don't.</Source>
      <Dest>哈，真好笑。我是个一无是处的恶棍，而你却还跟我呆在一起。但说到你的亲戚，你选择和他们中的一些在一起，却不跟另一些为伍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I love it when you talk crazy. But you'd like him. He's just as nuts.</Source>
      <Dest>你不羁的语气让我着迷，但是你会对他感兴趣的。他就像坚果一样硬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Me being family isn't going to make it any easier.</Source>
      <Dest>我的家人要做到它并不容易。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey.   I stole this for you.  So you don't owe me anything.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿。我偷这个是给你的。所以不要认为你欠我什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, the air smells fresher already. Well, at least until his corpse rots.</Source>
      <Dest>行吧，空气都清新不少了。当然喽，至少在他的尸体腐烂之前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I didn't take her amulet. Never had a chance. You know why? Because Lurgok bit my hand when I reached for his purse.</Source>
      <Dest>但我没有偷她的护符。压根儿没有机会。知道为什么吗？因为当我伸手去偷他钱包时路卡打了我的手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A cave.  Dimly lit and full of treasure, I hope.</Source>
      <Dest>一个洞穴。昏暗而充满宝藏，但愿如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A cave. What will we find, trouble or treasure?  Better be more of the second thing.</Source>
      <Dest>一个山洞。我们能找到什么，麻烦还是宝藏？希望后者能多些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I haven't, even though I've been trying to let you win the small pots. That's just how bad you are.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑)不，我没有做过，虽然我想方设法让你赢得这些小盆子。你太♂坏了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An oath-relative, same as you. Saved my skin when some fat sload of a guard captain was too lazy to do his job.</Source>
      <Dest>一个oath-relative，就跟你一样。当某个肥胖的蛞蝓人守卫队长懒得干自己该干的活儿的时候，他救了我一命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh skeevers, he's not getting up, is he. Maybe we can make it look like an accident, like he tripped and fell on my knife.</Source>
      <Dest>哦skeevers，他死翘翘了，对吧。也许我们能伪造个意外现场，比如他脚滑摔在了我的匕首上啥的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's not that I was scared, it's that he broke every bone in my hand. Couldn't hold a spoon, let alone pick a pocket.</Source>
      <Dest>不是我害怕，是他打折了我手上的每一根骨头，勺子都握不住，更别说偷窃了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean sure, he keeps to himself. But you step one foot inside his space, and he's cooking your toes for supper.</Source>
      <Dest>我的意思是，的确他很沉默寡言。但你若胆敢踏入他的空间一步，他就会用你的脚趾头做顿晚餐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Twelve septims on my partner!</Source>
      <Dest>12个金币押我的搭档胜！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Then it wouldn't be stealing. It'd be charity. Just saying that word makes my tooth ache.</Source>
      <Dest>（大笑）那就不是偷窃而是做在慈善了——单提到这词我都牙疼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Get behind that fool! That always works!</Source>
      <Dest>绕到那个蠢货的后面去！那招很有效的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes! I knew I could count on you! You're the Dragonborn, so you got authority and muscle.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊！我就知道我可以依靠你！你是龙裔，所以你有权力和力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say Dwarven ruins are haunted. At least that would make them interesting.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说矮人废墟闹鬼。至少这会让它们变得有趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh come on, get up you stupid ogre! Don't tell me you died that easy!</Source>
      <Dest>噢，得了，快爬起来吧你个愚蠢的怪物！别告诉我你这么容易就挂了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know, do we? Guards around here got there hands full, and they'd be more than happy not to make this a murder case.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道，对吧？这些守卫已经有够忙的了，少犯一起血案的话他们肯定会更开心的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, just dumb luck. This is my first time playing Iron Hearts, believe it or not. Krog over here is the real expert.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，只不过是运气好. 这是我第一次玩Iron Hearts, 信不信由你. 那边克罗格才是专家.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But sure, Lurgok's insane. But he keeps to himself. Of course, you get in his space, and you're just another kind of meat.</Source>
      <Dest>但是是的，鲁卡疯了，但是他不和人来往。当然，你要是进了他的地盘，你就不过另一块肉而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can't say I agree, seeing as Krog was about to kill us. Can't say I disagree either, seeing as his brother is going to kill me when he finds out.</Source>
      <Dest>我说不上同意，看上去克罗格要干掉我们一样。我也说不上不同意，看上去他兄弟找到我们之后就会宰了我一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some noble had her amulet picked off her neck, and of course it had to be the blind beggar girl.</Source>
      <Dest>有的贵族从她脖子上抢来的这条项链，理所当然的，她成了一个瞎乞丐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I like how you can see the Giants' camp from here. I bet these bandits peppered them arrows every night. At least I would.</Source>
      <Dest>我的法子跟你发现巨人营地的办法一样。那些强盗们每天晚上都要派人巡逻吧，要是我的话就会这么做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Damn you. That's asking too much. This place is light on purses and heavy on smell.</Source>
      <Dest>该死，真是太过分了。这个地方的臭味儿可比钱包的分量重多了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's a long jump. My advice? Don't.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一次长跳。我的建议？不要这么做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So instead of locking the treasure chest like a normal person, they've got this locked door, which probably has a lever behind it.</Source>
      <Dest>他們選擇把門鎖上並且放下門桿，而不是像平常人那樣把珍貴的寶箱鎖上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's magic for you. And for some reason, it's stealing that's against the law.</Source>
      <Dest>这是给你的魔法。因为某些原因 ，偷窃是违法的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that and I don't want your men standing behind me looking at my cards.</Source>
      <Dest>唔，我可不想让你的人站在我身后偷看我的底牌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Swirling shadows, Draugr...looks like some kind of freak show up ahead.</Source>
      <Dest>正在旋转的阴影，尸鬼……看起来就像在前面突然出现了什么极为怪异的东西一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey, this corpse has skulls on his belt. I wonder what he did to piss his friends off. Although I can't say I blame them. He just looks annoying.</Source>
      <Dest>&gt;嘿，这具尸体的脑瓜系在他的皮带上。我不知道他做了什么让他的朋友生气了。虽然我不能责怪他的朋友。毕竟他看上去太惹人厌了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, the Jarl of Riften should really put up a gate here. Block off all the cold coming in from the west.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道吗， 裂谷城的领主真的应该在这儿设个门，用以抵挡所有来自西方的寒气。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, I shadowed them for a while, even tried chatting up this stuttering brute, but there was nothing but leather in those purses.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，我跟踪了他们一段时间，甚至试着跟那个结结巴巴的畜生搭讪。但那钱包里除了皮革什么都没有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't see, idiot. But I'm not blind. When you move, your shadow moves. I can tell by the way it's angled that you're up against the wall.</Source>
      <Dest>我看不见，白痴。但我不是瞎子。当你人动的时候，你的影子也跟着动了。顺便一提，影子的角度使我知道了你正靠在墙上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, I didn't spring you just to let you run around eating people.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样，我没有为了让你出去到处吃人而【spring】你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But you keep your arms crossed to make your boss think otherwise. Which is even dumber, seeing as having you rested is good for the both of you. </Source>
      <Dest>但你就那么交叉着手臂让你的老板想歪了。再加上你休息的话对你俩都有好处……这件事看起来就更蠢了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We need to find you a home, somewhere you can only eat people we don't like.</Source>
      <Dest>我们得给你找一个家，一个你可以只去吃我们不喜欢的人的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, but don't say I didn't give you a chance to win your money back.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，但是不要说我没有给你把你的钱赢回来的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If someone came charging in, Krog would be dead before you managed to get your fingers out of your armpits.</Source>
      <Dest>如果有人冲进来， 克罗格来不及手抽出胳肢窝就死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I go, "Which coin purse?"</Source>
      <Dest>然后我说，“哪个钱袋？”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Normally I'd be ecstatic about a chest that big, but it's probably just filled with more spiders.</Source>
      <Dest>正常情况下我看到这么大的箱子一定会狂喜不已，不过这次可能是因为这箱子里塞着的更多是蜘蛛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why does that not surprise me.</Source>
      <Dest>为什么我一点儿都不奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I got a bad feeling something lives down here. Something dangerous. Maybe in the water, as if those candles are a distraction. Don't trust your eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>我感觉有什么东西住在这下面。某种危险的东西。也许是在水里,那些蜡烛看上去好像是用来迷惑你的。不要相信你的眼睛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>[Picks lock]</Source>
      <Dest>[撬锁]</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, well, I can't be blamed for that. Although your lover might find a way.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我不应该责备这个。尽管你的另一半可能找到另一个方法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then he looks at me all angry and says "I only have one! And you stole it!"</Source>
      <Dest>然后他看着我愤愤的说:“我只有一个!而你偷了它!”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is the part where I steal the pickaxe from your sack. Because I'll die of old age by the time you finish mining this place.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我要从你口袋里把镐偷出来的原因。因为当你在这地方挖掘完成的时候，我差不多就要老死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hold up. There's three levers in this room, and only one is lit up brighter than King Olaf. What did I tell you? The eyes tell lies.</Source>
      <Dest>且慢。这间房里有3个控制杆，而只有一个被照得比独眼奥拉夫国王还要亮。我跟你说过，眼见并不为实。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He was about your height, but he had short strides and a bad knee, maybe from fighting, but probably from age.</Source>
      <Dest>他跟你差不多高，但是步幅小一点，而且膝盖不太好，有可能是战斗导致的，也有可能是年纪大了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So the shopkeeper grabs me by the wrist and screams "You were the one in the market! The blind girl who stole my coin purse!"</Source>
      <Dest>所以那个店主抓住我的手腕尖叫：“当时在市场的就是你！你这个偷了我钱包的瞎丫头！”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Pulling the lever opens a gate in a separate room that guards a chest. But there's still only one lock! By Nocturnal, I think my head just exploded.</Source>
      <Dest>在一个有宝藏的密室里，拉下杠杆之后打开了一扇门。但是还有一把锁！诺克图娜尔在上，我头都炸了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're going to execute me!  I'm innocent!  You have to help me!</Source>
      <Dest>他们要处死我！我是无辜的！救救我！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) You and your best friend Malacath. Well too bad, your family comes first. </Source>
      <Dest>（叹气）你和你最好的朋友Malacath。太糟糕了，你的家庭是最重要的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I did notice the leader never put down his axe, even when he went to sleep. </Source>
      <Dest>但是我也注意到了那个首领永远不曾放下他的斧头，甚至在他睡觉的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I gave his hands something else to hold, and took home my fee in the morning.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我把别的东西塞到他手里，然后清晨带着“出场费”回家了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By Nocturnal, we just got in here, and I already smell corpse. (Snickers) Worst adventurer ever.</Source>
      <Dest>我的亲诺克图纳尔啊，我们才刚进来，就问得到尸体的气味了。（窃笑）史上最烂的冒险者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Archers! Might want to do our best to stay close to the wall before it starts raining arrows.</Source>
      <Dest>弓箭手！我们是想着尽可能地靠近那堵墙呢，但箭如雨下，我们根本靠近不了啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So when do you think this wizard brings out the silver bowls? For the living guests, or the famous dead ones?</Source>
      <Dest>那你觉得这个法师是在什么时候把那只银碗拿出来的呢？是准备招待活生生的客人呢，还是准备招待那些死去的名人呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't have to apologize to me. Cook me for dinner, and most of what you'll be eating is the stuff in your coin purse.</Source>
      <Dest>你不用向我道歉。把我做成晚餐，然后你and most of what you'll be eating is the stuff in your coin purse.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The thief wants to know what in Oblivion this is all about. The job was taken care of weeks ago.</Source>
      <Dest>那个窃贼想知道这他妈到底怎么回事。工作早在数周之前就已被料理。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What if we took you to Ivarstead? High Hrothgar is probably the most sacred rock of them all.</Source>
      <Dest>要是我们把你带去伊瓦斯泰德呢？霍斯加高峰可能是天下所有岩石中最令人肃然起敬的一块了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whatever. I'm only responsible for two things. Stealing your item, and making sure your man pays me. All the other stuff is your job.</Source>
      <Dest>随便你。我只对两件事负责，一是偷到你要的东西，二是确保你的人会付我钱。剩下的事那可就都是你的工作了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Help me!  Please!  I've done nothing wrong!  You can't do this!</Source>
      <Dest>帮帮我！求你了！我没做错什么！你不能这样做！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He kept his coin purse on his right hip. By the way it sagged it probably was about a week away from splitting.</Source>
      <Dest>他把钱包放在自己的右臀上。顺便一提，大概是一周不花钱所以钱包沉甸甸的……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But yeah, I haven't the slightest clue what he looks like.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，是啊，我一点也不知道他长什么样儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It always seems like there's no way to go but straight. That's why adventurers are stupid. They forget you can still go back.</Source>
      <Dest>除了前面的路以外好像无路可走。这就是为什么说冒险者都很蠢。他们忘了他们可以回头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, fine, you stubborn Orc.  Stay here. But don't say I didn't give you a chance to win your life back.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。好极了。你个顽固的兽人。你就呆在这儿吧。但别说我没给过你保住小命的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can go back to polishing your Lord Malacath's spear when we're safe at the tavern.</Source>
      <Dest>等我们安全到达旅馆的时候，你可以回去摩亮你家玛拉凯斯大人的长矛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But that's the easy stuff. I can tell by the way your back is bent that you're as worn out as Krog's shoes. </Source>
      <Dest>这很简单。我可以顺便告诉你，你只要把背弯下来，就会和克罗格的鞋一样累。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I say, "Is that what you tell your wife?"</Source>
      <Dest>所以我才说，“这就是你告诉你老婆的？”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is the back road everyone talks about. You use it to slip into Solitude, or if need be, slip out.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是大家说的小路了。你用这条路溜进独孤城，或者说如果需要的话用它溜出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nope. It turns out they just threatened people to get what they wanted. </Source>
      <Dest>不。原来他们只是威胁人们来得到他们想要的东西。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here for a moment.</Source>
      <Dest>在这儿等一下.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's nothing. Never mind.</Source>
      <Dest>没什么事，不用担心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need you to do something for me.</Source>
      <Dest>我需要你为我做件事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes. Let me show you.</Source>
      <Dest>不错，你看看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here.</Source>
      <Dest>在这里等着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Go ahead.</Source>
      <Dest>Go ahead.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This looks like some kind of arena. I like the way these bandits do things. Got an argument? Settle it in the pit.</Source>
      <Dest>这看起来像某种竞技场。我喜欢这些强盗的做事方法。有矛盾？在角斗场解决。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  Let's keep to the shadows.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。让我们继续隐于阴影之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This place is a death trap. How much do you think Danica will give us for that knife? Anything short of a 1000, I'll have to make up the difference.</Source>
      <Dest>這地方是個死亡陷阱。你認為Danica會為了那把小刀給我們多少？除了那1000金幣，我還必須自己補上不足的部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How the heck did this noisy old farmer sneak past those bandits? There's just no way.</Source>
      <Dest>真他妈见鬼，怎么才能让这个吵闹的老农民从那群强盗旁边溜过去？我可没辙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, let's trade.</Source>
      <Dest>那好，我们交换点东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You gotta to watch yourself in these Forsworn camps. A witch might come out of nowhere and put a hex on you. Really, it happened to a friend of mine.</Source>
      <Dest>你在弃誓者营地里可千万小心。说不定哪里就会冒出个鬼婆给你下咒。真的，我有个朋友就遇见了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, I got an idea. What if we agree to help both Saadia and the Alik'r? Then we rob them both of the reward money.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道，我有个计画。不如他们俩我们都帮，然后我们把他们的奖励通通洗劫而尽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Huzzah, the tree's back. And now it's so skinny we can't even use it for firewood. Nope, wasn't a waste of time at all, saving that tree.</Source>
      <Dest>万岁，这棵树又活过来了。现在它是那么的瘦弱，甚至不能用来当木材。但没关系，救这棵树，这不是浪费时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, so you're not mad?</Source>
      <Dest>等等，这么说你没生气【没疯】？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is this hag going to stop wheezing, or am I going to have to make her stop?</Source>
      <Dest>那老东西能别喘来喘去的么，或者我去帮她停下来？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure, best we keep it light.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，我们最好让它亮着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think these bandits were targeting the mill. I'm not even going to pretend to know why.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这些强盗对那个磨坊有所企图。但实际上我不清楚其中的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think these bandits were targeting the mill. I'm not even going to pretend to know why.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这些强盗对那个磨坊有所企图。但实际上我不清楚其中的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's a shame.  But you'll be back.  If not for me, for the profit.</Source>
      <Dest>这是个耻辱。但你会回来的。如果不是为了我的话，就是为了利润。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So this bandit chief was stashing some of the loot away for himself, huh. Stealing from family's about as low as it gets.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这个强盗头子给自己藏起了些战利品。哼，就像从家里偷东西那么低级。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Departs}</Source>
      <Dest>{离开 }</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Smoke some incense and talk to a Daedric Prince, huh. Sure, I'm game.  Strange place for a party though.</Source>
      <Dest>把香点上，再和魔神说话，嗯。当然，我可不怕什么，尽管在这聚会有点奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can't do it, sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>不行，抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Planting stuff just seems so backwards. We should just steal everything and punish them that way.</Source>
      <Dest>种植原材料看起来如此的落后，我们应该透光所有的东西然后用这种方式惩罚他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No point holding on to a bad marriage. Fjola reminds me of myself, except for that clunky steel armor.</Source>
      <Dest>没有理由挽留失败的婚姻。菲欧拉让我想起了自己，除了他那身笨重的盔甲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thought you'd never ask.</Source>
      <Dest>我还以为你不会开口了呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Zzzzz...</Source>
      <Dest>Zzzzz……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh, that hay pile is covered in feathers. It's like a bed full of skin flakes.</Source>
      <Dest>呸，那个干草堆上都是羽毛。它看起来像一张洒满皮屑的的床。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ogre's blood, Lurgok, did you really leave your leftovers all over their sacred rocks?</Source>
      <Dest>巨魔之血， 路卡，你真的把你那剩菜剩饭全倒在他们那些神圣的石头上了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These mercs aren't really loyal to the Silver-Bloods. Pay them off and they'll leave. It's not like we can't just steal it back.</Source>
      <Dest>这些雇佣兵并不会真正效命于银血家族。付点钱就能把他们打发走。不像我们，不能直接偷回来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you need to take?</Source>
      <Dest>你需要多长时间?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know how they say teach a man to fish? Somebody should have taught this kid to pick a lock. Would've saved us all a lot of trouble.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道为嘛他们老说要授人以渔吗？应该有人教教这孩子开锁。这样就能给我们大家省去很多麻烦了。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Everything in the cave is running downstream. These bandits could hear us, smell us, you name it. That is, if they were actually paying attention.</Source>
      <Dest>这山洞中的一切都会顺流而下。这些强盗可以听到我们的声音，闻到我们的气味儿，不管是什么都能传达到。如果他们真的留心的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Weird. There's Falmer arrows on the ground, but they usually take hostages. No stolen goods, just an old fashioned butchering. I don't get it.</Source>
      <Dest>离奇的是。这里有些雪精灵之箭落在地上。不过雪精灵它们通常都是搞绑架的。也没有啥货物被偷，只有一场血腥的杀戮，我有些难以明了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come on, let's go talk to the chief. They said it was blood or gold, so it might as well be the one you can steal.</Source>
      <Dest>来吧，咱们去跟首领谈谈。他们说要么是鲜血要么是金子，所以是金子的话说不定你能偷得着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You got orders?</Source>
      <Dest>你接到活了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These fingers are your fingers.</Source>
      <Dest>这些手指就是你的手指。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So they call this place Widow's Watch, huh. I was almost a widow, but I couldn't live with the title. It just makes you sound old.</Source>
      <Dest>所以他们把这地儿叫做寡妇望。嗯，我差不多是个寡妇了，但我不能顶着这大名过日子，这听起来显得太老了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, then prepare to get angry. Because like it or not, I'm springing you out of this dung hole.</Source>
      <Dest>好了，那么留着你的脾气。因为不管你喜不喜欢，我要把你弹出这个粪坑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This Redguard is an idiot. The person who gets to the treasure first has nothing to do with who comes out with it. Let's let them take the lead.</Source>
      <Dest>那个红卫人是个蠢货。谁先摸到财宝跟谁能带走财宝是两回事。让他走前面吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These hives got bugs, beasts, and bodies, but not a lot of boon. But hey, maybe we'll get lucky and find a rich alchemist to buy all these eggs.</Source>
      <Dest>这些巢穴里有虫子，野兽，死尸，就是没什么油水。不过嘛，也许运气好的话我们能找到有钱的炼金师愿意买这些蛋呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah...about that. You might be seeing him sooner than you think.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊......关于这一点。你可能会很快看到他，比你想象中快得多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I would if I could, but I can't.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我可以的话，我会的；但真的是心有余而力不足。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By Nocturnal, we just got in here, and I already smell corpse. (Snickers) Worst adventurer ever.</Source>
      <Dest>我的亲诺克图纳尔啊，我们才刚进来，就问得到尸体的气味了。（窃笑）史上最烂的冒险者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm glad the bandit tried to rob us. It saved us some awkwardness. Because there's no way I was sharing any loot with him.</Source>
      <Dest>这些强盗能打劫我们真是太好了。这省掉了我们不少尴尬。我可不想和让他们来和我们分赃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Go ahead.</Source>
      <Dest>继续。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I say we hawk this beacon for everything it's worth. It's not like this Meridia can do anything about it, or else she wouldn't ask us to fetch it.</Source>
      <Dest>我得说我们寻得这个灯塔的一切都是值得的。似乎美瑞蒂亚对此无能为力，否则她不会要我们帮忙取回它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, is this some kind of arena? I like the way these bandits do things. Got an argument? Settle it in the pit, and let the rest of us gamble on it.</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，这是某种竞技场吗？我喜欢这些强盗的行事方法。想吵一架吗？那就在竞技场里解决，让剩下的人能借此赌上一把。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, what's the map say? "Golden Rock?" Well, where's the gold? All these shadows belong to Giants. And cheese.</Source>
      <Dest>等等，地图上怎么说的？“金石？”我说，金子在哪里？所有这些东西都是巨人的。哦，还有奶酪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It doesn't matter if you can see the trap. You're still blind to the answer. Notice that pull chain above the helmet? That's what opens the gate.</Source>
      <Dest>你看不看得到陷阱都没关系。你对回答依旧熟视无睹。看到头盔上的拉链了吗？打开口子的是它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great. Give it to me.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了。把它给我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, so now it's okay to break into Mercer's house.  Unbelievable.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，现在可以闯进墨瑟家里了。不可思议。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whoever bought Goldenglow had it in for both Maven and the Guild.  Which means all of Skyrim is a suspect.  Hell, I'm a suspect.</Source>
      <Dest>不知道是谁帮玛雯和公会控制了Goldenglow。这说明天际省人人都有嫌疑。妈的，我也有嫌疑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Damn.  He's opening it.  I would've killed for a chance to pick that lock.</Source>
      <Dest>该死！让他抢先了。我早就想开那个锁想疯了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So that's the Nightingale Armor, huh.  A lot of things come to mind when I look at you three.  But "stealth" isn't one of them.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来那就是夜莺套装嗯？一看见你们仨我的脑子里就冒出好多事。不过“潜行”不是其中之一。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not all of these pressure plates are rigged.  You just got to figure out the pattern.</Source>
      <Dest>不是所有紧身甲都是这样装配的。你要弄清楚结构。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You alright?  Sounds like Mercer put the knife in you.  Too bad.  He was just my type, and now we're going to have to cut his balls off.</Source>
      <Dest>你还好吗？听起来像是墨瑟捅了你一刀。真糟糕。虽然他以前是我的菜，但现在我们得去把他的balls切掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These priestesses have it right.  I need another marriage like I need a kick in the teeth.</Source>
      <Dest>那些女祭司拥有了它，对吧。我真需要一段新的婚姻，就好像我需要一记当头棒喝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I still can't get over the fact that she just gave you the horn.  What's her play?</Source>
      <Dest>我还是想不通，她仅仅是把角给你了？她可真够逗的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd trust Gulum-Ei about as far as I can throw him.  For all we know Karliah is his mother.  Of course, that wouldn't keep him from selling her out.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以相信Gulum-Ei那么一点点。虽然大家知道Karliah是他妈妈，他毫无疑问是不介意坑妈的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's faint, but I smell skooma on that cat. Not that you needed me to tell you.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然很微弱，但我还是在那只猫身上闻到了斯库玛的味道。并不是说你需要我来告诉你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is this, some sort of ancient fungus museum? I'm not impressed.</Source>
      <Dest>这是啥，大约可以说是远古真菌博物馆？我看没什么了不起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow. So, that was Potema. She's famous right? I mean, I know who she is. I just want to make sure you do.</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，那就是Potema.。她很出名是吧？我是说，我知道她是谁，只是确认一下你也知道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let me get this straight.  The skeleton key Mercer stole can open any door?  Hmph.  What's the fun in that?</Source>
      <Dest>让我把事情搞清楚。墨瑟偷的这把骷髅钥匙可以打开任何一扇门？哼，这有什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There you are.  You alright?  Brynjolf here didn't slow you down too much, did he?  I'm kidding Brynjolf, lighten up you big oaf.</Source>
      <Dest>你在这儿啊。你还好吗？布林乔夫没耽误你太多时间对吧？【我作弄了一下布林乔夫，好让你这个呆子开心一点】。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Jarl doesn't give a rat's ass about what's happening in Wolfskull. That's why we shouldn't feel bad for rich people. They deserve what they get.</Source>
      <Dest>那些贵族才不会关心狼头骨洞穴那里发生了什么。这就是为什么我对那些富人产生不了丁点儿的好感。他们那是自作自受。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Spectres.  This place makes my skin crawl.</Source>
      <Dest>有幽灵啊。这地方让我直起鸡皮疙瘩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whoever stole that horn wants to meet you?  That means they've already fenced it.  Otherwise we'd just take it back.  </Source>
      <Dest>那个偷了号角的人想要见你？那说明他们已经把号角给出手了吧，否则我们能借此机会把它拿回来。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Keep that thing tucked away, will you? It messes with everything. I think I have another headache.</Source>
      <Dest>把那东西藏起来成吗？它把一切都弄乱了。我又有个头痛的事儿了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is this like the vampire way of marking their territory? Because I smell blood everywhere. On the walls, on the floor...hot, sweet, and sticky.</Source>
      <Dest>这就像是吸血鬼标记领地的方式吗？因为到处都是血腥味儿。墙上，地上……热，甜，黏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could've told you this place was a waste of time. That is, if my tongue wasn't frozen solid.</Source>
      <Dest>我铁定得告诉你在这里就是浪费时间。铁定的，如果我的舌头没被冻成冰块儿的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whatever Mercer's up to, it's bigger than any heist we've pulled up to this point. And our cut is that much more if we don't tell Brynjolf.</Source>
      <Dest>无论墨瑟暗中做了什么，这都比我们迄今为止经历的任何一次抢劫要严重得多。 如果我们再不告诉布林乔夫，我们的损失就要更多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know much about art, but I know what I like.  And I like this wall.</Source>
      <Dest>我不太懂艺术，但我知道我喜欢什么，我喜欢这个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't understand why we can't just break into the Thalmor Embassy.  I mean, all this bootlicking and playing dress up...it's just wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>我不明白为什么我们不直接硬闯梭莫大使馆。我是说，所有这些拍他们马屁，盛装打扮的行为……它们全都是错的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't even want to reach into some of these pockets. These slaves probably keep all sorts of weird mementos.</Source>
      <Dest>我甚至不想掏其中一些人的口袋。这些奴隶可能还留着各种各样稀奇古怪的纪念品呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Paarthu-what?  You mean to tell me there's an even grayer beard, who lives up on an even higher mountain? This is just insane.</Source>
      <Dest>帕图——啥？你是想告诉我还有个更灰的胡子在一座更高的山上过活？这简直是疯了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So they've got you running collection?  What, did Dirge break a nail?</Source>
      <Dest>所以他们让你管理那些收藏品？等等，难道挽歌受伤了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So this mystery backer was trying to split up the guild and Maven Black-Briar?  We ought to be giving him a medal.</Source>
      <Dest>那么这个神秘的支持者是想要离间工会和黑荆棘玛雯？我们该给他发个奖章。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Greybeards put an awful lot of faith in Klimmek. What if he decides he's sick of climbing? I'm sick of it already, and we haven't even started.</Source>
      <Dest>灰胡子对科林麦抱有的希望太高了不是吗？要是他厌倦爬山了怎么办？你瞧瞧我，我还没开爬呢就已经烦透了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is a cold place to live. If I were these bandits, I wouldn't chop firewood. I'd set flame to that entire ship. But only after looting it.</Source>
      <Dest>这地方可真冷。如果我是那些强盗的话，我才不会去砍柴禾，我会把整艘船都烧了！当然是在洗劫完那艘船之后。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What a stupid place to hide your treasure. I feel dumber having just been in this cave.</Source>
      <Dest>你是有多傻才会把财宝藏在这个地方。一进这个洞我都不知道要说什么了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I smell grapes.  And ugh...how old is that cheese?</Source>
      <Dest>我都闻到一股酸葡萄味儿了……呃，那块儿奶酪你搁了多久了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hate men like Savos, sitting around reading books all day.  Someone should tell Arch-Mage Mirabelle that he's sleeping in her bed.</Source>
      <Dest>我真是烦死萨沃斯那样的人了，整天窝在椅子里啃书本.真该有个人去和米拉贝勒大师说这货正躺在她的床上.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bandit blood.  Always a little weirdness in the smell, on account of all the crap they're putting in their mouths.</Source>
      <Dest>强盗的血。里面总有股怪味儿，好像闻得出他们整天吃的都是些什么垃圾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You should take Vex's advice.  Breaking and entering is sort of her thing.  That and being a bitch.  Both good reasons to do as she says.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该听取Vex的意见。破门而入是她做的出来的事。不管是这一点还是考虑到她是个婊子。这两个都是照她说的做的好理由。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That was by far the weirdest bar fight I've ever been a part of. But not the bloodiest.</Source>
      <Dest>这是迄今为止我参与过的最奇怪的酒吧打架。但不是最血腥的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know what you're thinking, but you can't replace me with some magic key.  And you're going to have to return it anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你是在想什么，但是你不能用我去换那所谓的魔法匙。还有，很快你便不得不把它还回去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For a second I thought the shadows on the floor moved. This whole place is shaky, and seeing bones everywhere doesn't help.</Source>
      <Dest>有那么一瞬间我以为地板上的影子在动，整个空间都在摇晃，【就算看见四处散落的骨头也没用。】</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, what'd you find in that Embassy?  And I'm not talking about information.  </Source>
      <Dest>那么，你去那大使馆要找的是什么？我说的可不是指情报。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if there's gems and things in the wall.  Like Alduin's eye is some priceless ruby.  Damn, now I'm actually excited to touch it.</Source>
      <Dest>我想知道这墙上挂的东西是不是宝石之类的东西。比如说不定奥杜因的眼睛就是某种无价的红宝石做的。该死，我现在都忍不住想去摸摸它了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is a good place to hide.  Lots of deep shadows.  Still, it's a stupid place to live. Are we saving this old fool from the Thalmor, or himself?</Source>
      <Dest>这是个躲藏的好地方。很多深重的阴影。可是这也不是个生活的好地方。你是要从梭默手中救出那个老傻瓜呢？还是任他自生自灭呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, who let the crazy person out of his cage?</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，是谁把那疯子从笼子里放出来的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh. The air around here is disgusting. It's like mushrooms trying to bed each other. I'll just be back here sneezing.</Source>
      <Dest>呃啊，这里的空气令人作呕。闻起来就像叠的密密麻麻的蘑菇。我待会一定会打喷嚏的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I'm glad that's over with.  Being around old people makes me want to slit my wrists.</Source>
      <Dest>呼，终于结束了。身边被一群老大爷围着搞得我都想割腕自杀了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know what you did in that Twilight whats-it-called, but everything's different.  Like the shadows are darker, and I can see more clearly.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道你在黄昏什么什么的地方干了啥，但一切都不同了。就算阴影愈发晦暗，我也能看清一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh!  The vault smells like the inside of Delvin's boot.  No wonder nobody ever went inside.</Source>
      <Dest>呸，难怪没人进来，这地下室闻起来就像是戴文鞋子里的味道</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I like how it took you seconds to master what these old milkbeards have been studying their whole lives.  What a bunch of losers.</Source>
      <Dest>我就喜欢看你用几秒钟就学会那群老奶油胡子学了一辈子的东西。一群废物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So is this High Hrothgar?  Doesn't look like a monastery to me, and I haven't seen one person with a beard.  Shouldn't they be waiting for us?</Source>
      <Dest>这就是高吼峰?  在我看来不像是个修道院, 我也没有看到有人留胡子.  他们不是应该在等我们吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No wonder me and the Thieves Guild never saw eye to blind.  You mess with Nocturnal, I slit your throat.</Source>
      <Dest>难怪我和盗贼工会互翻白眼。你敢惹诺克图娜尔，我便割开你的喉咙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Rats...bugs...seriously, who wants to drink Honningbrew after smelling this armpit of a meadery?</Source>
      <Dest>扯淡……太疯狂了……老实说，谁会愿意在闻完的酒庄里的那些肮脏的角落之后再喝蜜酒？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's a lot of weirdos living in the Ratway.  A lot of rats too, but that goes about saying.</Source>
      <Dest>鼠道里住着很多奇怪的人。也有很多老鼠，不过那完全不是一码事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stupid old man.  Even I can see all of this is trash.</Source>
      <Dest>老蠢猪。我甚至能看见所有的这些垃圾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just solve the damn puzzle Esbern.  Save the speech.</Source>
      <Dest>解决那个烦人的伊斯本。挽救这次演讲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So let me get this straight.  We get to keep everything...and she gets a piece of paper?  Deal's a deal, you stupid wench.</Source>
      <Dest>让我捋一捋这件事。我们没什么损失……而她只得到了一片纸？生意而已，你个蠢女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something smells rotten in this inn.  Although it's not like there's anywhere else to live.  The buildings have more holes than a sailor's smile.</Source>
      <Dest>这旅馆里有股什么东西腐烂的味道。虽然并不像是有人住的样子。这屋子上的破洞比水手笑脸上的坑还要多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fetch this, deliver that.  Companion work sounds a lot like courier work to me.</Source>
      <Dest>拿着这个，传递那个。团队合作对于我来说更像是快递工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can't pick a pocket?  Smash a skull.  I mean, you do realize everyone here is someone who couldn't cut it as a thief?  Now you're one of them.</Source>
      <Dest>钱包都摸不到？动动脑子吧。我的意思是，你发现在座的都是笨手笨脚的蠢贼了么？现在你也成他们的一员了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hate Draugr.  All dried and shriveled up.  Things without blood are just unnatural.</Source>
      <Dest>我讨厌尸鬼。它们全都萎缩而干枯。无血的东西是违背自然的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This level reeks of blood.  Smells like some trolls were having themselves a festival.  No way a skeleton leaves that kind of mess.</Source>
      <Dest>这一层的空气全是血腥味。闻着好像有多少巨魔在这里开宴会一样。这样的事恐怕连骨头都很难剩下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All those Companions and they couldn't save the old man?  This family only cares about themselves.</Source>
      <Dest>整个战友团那么多人居然保不住那位老人的命？这个团队都是些自私的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, its like they built the floor out of pressure plates.  Now this is more like it!</Source>
      <Dest>哇，那就像建造空中阁楼。现在更像了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dream eaters?  This Mara priest is crazy. We should keep him around for comic relief.</Source>
      <Dest>食梦者？这个玛拉牧师可真疯了。我们应该让他留在这里当做有趣的调剂品。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not bad for an amateur. You've caught Brynjolf's eye. Good. With my hair cut short and Nocturnal's luck, he'll keep it fixed on you, and not me.</Source>
      <Dest>对于外行来说你做的不错。Brynjolf已经开始关注你了。很好。我头发剪短了，还有Nocturna的运气在你这边他会继续关注你的，而不是我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait a minute.  There's four levers but only three symbols.  Agh, these puzzles make my head hurt.</Source>
      <Dest>等一下先。这儿有四个控制杆可是只有3个标记。嗄，这些迷题真让我头疼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lessons are boring.  Magic is boring.  Not enough blood.</Source>
      <Dest>【课程挺无聊的。魔法也挺无聊的，它们都没有足够的流血事件。】</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow.  Look at all those coffins, jammed in there sideways. Kind of crowded though.  Our cemetery's going to be just us family.</Source>
      <Dest>喔。看看那些棺材，挤挤攘攘地放在一边。看起来真拥挤。我们的墓地只会安葬家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All this trouble for a bunch of books no one understands.  I don't get mages.  Even their thieves are sniveling cowards.</Source>
      <Dest>没人能理解这些书所带来的所有问题。我不清楚法师们怎么想。但就连他们的贼都会鄙视懦夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't look at me for help, oath-sister.  You don't keep me around for my mind.  No one's that stupid.</Source>
      <Dest>别找我帮忙，誓约姐妹。我可不会留在你身边。没人会做那种蠢事的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, this guy we're helping...Stalleo?  Now that has to be a made-up name.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我们所帮助的那个人叫...斯塔莱奥吗？现在看来这是个假名字啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look at this crazy skull collection.  I love it.  I mean, why not?  Mounting bear heads is just as weird. That chest's rigged, by the way.</Source>
      <Dest>看看这个疯狂的头骨收藏吧！我爱它。我是说，为什么不爱呢？那个熊头装饰有够奇怪的吧。顺便一提，它就是那箱子开启的机关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The townsfolk here actually think you stopped their nightmares.  People are idiots.</Source>
      <Dest>这里的居民竟然以为是你停止了他们的噩梦。这帮人都是白痴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I bet you forty septims this talking light ball changed his name after the fact.  There's no way anyone takes him seriously if his name's Sven.</Source>
      <Dest>我跟你赌40个金币，这个说话的光球事后改了他的名字。如果他的名字是胡德，就没人会把他当回事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>See, this is what I'm talking about.  This guy is the leader, the richest one here.  And what do I find in his pockets?  An apple.  A sodding apple.</Source>
      <Dest>看，这就是我想说的。这家伙是个领导者，这旮沓地儿最富的那个人。而我在他口袋里翻到了什么？一个苹果。他妈的就一个苹果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, so we helped the old man.  Big deal.  I want some boon.  Let's raid Ysgramor coffin before the Aela the Spear-Chin complains.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，那我们就帮这个老人的忙吧。这很重要。我想做些好事。那咱就在枪锋艾拉开始抱怨之前赶紧撬开伊斯格拉谟的棺材吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't look at me for help, oath-brother.  You don't keep me around for my mind.  No one's that stupid.</Source>
      <Dest>别看着我帮忙，誓言兄弟。别让我迷糊了。没人那么傻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Move aside, I think I've got this figured out. Just match the pictures right?  Wait, something's different about these. Agh...forget I said anything.</Source>
      <Dest>闪边去，我想我已经明白怎么回事了。只要和图案相符就行了对吧？等等，有什么地方不对劲…啊，当我没说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I smell blood. Everywhere. And it's mixed with saliva.</Source>
      <Dest>我闻到血腥味了。这味道无处不在。而且还混合着唾液的味道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This place smells strange.  Like burnt ash and old rust.  And is that a pickaxe?  Mages are so weird.</Source>
      <Dest>这地方闻起来很奇怪，就像烧焦的灰尘和古老的金属锈迹一样。那是鹤嘴锄吗？法师真是怪异啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So this Orthorn stole some books to ditch the guild for some weirdos. Sounds like a loser. What? Don't look at me like that. I'm nothing like him.</Source>
      <Dest>那这个奥松恩有怪癖，偷一些书丢在公会里。听起来就像那些人生不得意的人一样。干嘛？别这样看着我。我跟他不一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This place smells like blood, steam, and oil.  Just like every Dwarven ruin.  Except there's a faint smell of ash too.</Source>
      <Dest>这地方充斥着鲜血，蒸汽，汽油混合在一起的味道。就跟所有锻模遗迹一样。不过闻起来也稍微有些灰尘味儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Figures Tolfdir was a corpse lover.  Why else would he want to be alone with all those bodies?  The old man's a freak.</Source>
      <Dest>鉴于托夫迪尔是个恋尸癖，为什么在有了那些尸体之后他还会想和别人在一起？这老头就是个变态。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who do you think this was, lying in the sun all day.  Some Nord chief or something?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为这位成天躺着晒日光浴的人是谁。一位诺德酋长还是别的谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh, I think that thing slimed me.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，我觉得有什么东西黏在了身上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whoa, did that just happen?  I got chills from that fight.  It was better than any man I've ever had.</Source>
      <Dest>嚯啊，刚刚发生一切都是真的吗？我【这场仗】打得都发抖了。这是我【遇见过】最厉害的一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know what Orthorn, your Arch-Mage doesn't even know you exist.  That's how insignificant you are.  Face it, you're a test subject. Kill yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>你听说了吗 Orthorn，你们首席大法师根本不知道有你这么个人。你就是这么的【被无视】。接受现实吧，你是一个实验品。自己了断吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The shadows here are off.  There's some kind of smoke too, but I can't smell it.  In fact, all I smell is fur.</Source>
      <Dest>这里的暗影已经消退。还有些烟雾，不过我闻不到了。其实，我能闻到的只有毛皮的味道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey Anska, why don't you grab that soul gem over there.  Grab it before it hits you with a spell.  Then maybe stand by those coffins.  Idiot.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，安斯卡，你干嘛不把那只灵魂石给抓住呢，至少在它用魔法击中你之前抓住它们嘛，不然你就得跟这堆棺材一样直挺挺地竖在这儿一辈子了哟。蠢货。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why can't these alchemists stay alive for once?  It's no fun pilfering from a corpse.</Source>
      <Dest>为什么那些炼金术士们就不能活上一次呢？从死人身上偷东西一点都不好玩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Looks like this is one lock I can't pick.  Alright, you take down the wall.  There's an ugly hunk of Elven treasure inside with both our names on it.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来这个锁我撬不开。好吧，你还是把墙给拆了吧。里面那个丑陋大个头精灵的财宝已经是我们的囊中之物啦！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It doesn't look like they left any hostages.  Didn't leave any wine either, judging by those empty racks.  Wonder which one Stalleo will miss more.</Source>
      <Dest>看来他们没留下人质。从那狼藉的架子来看，也没有下一滴酒。猜猜看斯塔莱奥会更想念他们中的哪个呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look at these bloodsuckers, thirsty for revenge.  I say we open these cages and give it to them.</Source>
      <Dest>看看这些吸血鬼，饥渴于复仇。我说，把笼子打开让他们上吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know about all this stuff about witches, werewolves and curses, but if you've got bad blood, it's always best to spill it.</Source>
      <Dest>关于女巫、狼人、诅咒那些杂七杂八我不是很懂。但是如果你心怀怨恨，发泄出来总归是比较好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Looks like I was wrong about Orthorn.  He had a use after all.</Source>
      <Dest>看来我错看奥松恩了。不管怎么说他还算有点用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright Orthorn, I'm officially stumped.  How is it you're still alive?  Because you're completely useless.  This Caller must be your sister.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧奥松恩，我真的没辙了。你怎么还活着？你已经完全没用了。Caller肯定是你的姐姐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Smell that?  I love it when the bandits do all the cooking for us.  Not much of a menu though.  I hope you like salmon steak.</Source>
      <Dest>闻到没？虽然没什么好菜，但是强盗替我们做饭真是太让我开心了。希望你爱吃鲑鱼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Forget the old man and his older friend.  We need to loot everything we can before that cat does.  He's fast, but we're faster.  Well, I am anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>忘了那个老人和他更老的朋友吧。我们需要在那只猫之前夺走一切我们能带走的东西。他很快，但我们更快。好吧，至少我更快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I like you Enthir.  Didn't think I'd find someone like you hanging out with these bookworms.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢你Enthir。没想到我会找个像你这样的书呆子与我相伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are those things in the display case worth anything?  They're shiny like gems, but I can't tell the difference when it comes to mage stuff.</Source>
      <Dest>那些摆在陈列柜里展示的东西有啥值钱的吗？他们都跟宝石似的闪闪发光，但我不看不出它们跟法师的东西有啥不同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I'm sure Grosta will be comforted by the fact that her worthless husband died a gruesome death.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，我敢肯定格罗斯塔会因她那无能的丈夫的惨死而感到宽慰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This room smells like the College, but different.  Can't really explain it, but it's giving me a headache all the same.</Source>
      <Dest>这个房间闻起来跟学院一个味儿，但又有所不同。真是只可意会不可言传，总之它们都让我头疼的厉害。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I was a girl, I thought temples like these were a great place to pick pockets.  Turns out half the people in here are beggars.</Source>
      <Dest>我还是个小女孩的时候，我曾想过像这样的寺庙是一个偷东西的绝佳地方。结果在这里一般的人都是乞丐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My head hurts just looking at all these books.  I wish I could go back in time and kill whoever invented them.</Source>
      <Dest>我看到这些书就头疼.  真想回到过去把写这些书的人全杀掉.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Kolskeggr Mine's just about the only one around Markarth that isn't owned by the Silver-Bloods.  Of course it has problem with the Forsworn.</Source>
      <Dest>科斯凯格矿场差不多是马卡斯城周围唯一不属于银血家族的矿场了。当然，弃誓者们也经常找它的麻烦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh good, an angry mob.  I've always wanted to participate in one of these.  Usually I'm the one they're chasing.</Source>
      <Dest>哦好啊，一个愤怒的暴民。我其实一直想参与其中的，虽然一般来讲我会是那个被他们追的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I love the small hours.  People were meant to stay up all night, and sleep until noon.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢后半夜的时间。人们晚上就应该都通宵，然后都睡到中午起床。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You made it out of Cidhna Mine.  Just so you know, I would've been willing to kill another husband to help you escape.</Source>
      <Dest>你想把它带出希讷矿坑。如你所知，我一直愿意杀了另一个丈夫来帮助你逃跑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So a miner attacks a woman, and the guards waste no time killing him.  Why not put him to work in Cidhna Mine?  Was he overqualified?</Source>
      <Dest>这么说是个矿工去袭击一个女人，而守卫二话没说就把他杀了 。为什么不把他扔进希讷矿坑干活去？是他资质过高了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Blood on the floor, statues with holes in them.  There's no way this trap can be that obvious.</Source>
      <Dest>染满鲜血的阶梯，布满小孔的雕像。这陷阱也不至于如此显眼吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Snicker) Look at this fool, trying to play blacksmith.  I've met skeevers who had more skill with a hammer.</Source>
      <Dest>（窃笑）看看这白痴，还想玩铁匠的活儿。我见过的雪鼠都比他更会用锤子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dwarves are tricky little bastards. Weight based traps. Better to leave something in each chest, so they think it's full. And no, scraps don't work.</Source>
      <Dest>矮人都是狡猾的小混蛋。专注陷阱若干年。他们爱在每个箱子里都藏点儿东西，以为这就齐活了。嘿，报废了的东西可不会工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bugs, toads, mushrooms.  Is any of the stuff in this grove worth anything?  Alchemists.  Forest beggars is what they are.</Source>
      <Dest>臭虫，蟾蜍，蘑菇。难道这片树林的任何材料都有价值吗？炼金术士，还是叫他们森林乞丐好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look at this town.  Like the back end of a mammoth.  I don't even know what a Sybil is, but it can't be any worse than this place.</Source>
      <Dest>看看这个小镇，就像猛犸的屁股，我都不知道【Sybil】是什么，但肯定再没有地方比这儿更糟了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thane of Hjaalmarch.  That's like being crowned King of the Horkers.  Nothing worth celebrating.</Source>
      <Dest>希雅陲的领主。这就好比是三牙海象的加冕之王。没什么值得庆祝的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I heard about this dungeon.  Soldiers would throw prisoners down a pit.  If you survived, you were free.  The joke was, no one ever could.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说过这个地牢。狱卒们会把囚犯丢到一个深井里。如果还活着，你就自由了。可问题是，没人能活下来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Movarth dead, city saved.  That should be worth a home, a sack of gold, and a housecarl for the each of us.  At least.</Source>
      <Dest>莫瓦斯死了，城市也保住了。这应该值得给我们每人一套房子，一袋黄金和一个侍卫了。至少的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Meeko, is it?  Is that a boy's name or a girl's?  We should bring it along either way.  Might prove handy in battle, or in our stomachs.</Source>
      <Dest>米科，是吗？是男孩名还是女孩名？不管怎样我们都应该带它走。也许打仗时会有点用，或者在你肚子里有点用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dwarves sure know how to waste a lot of space.  Look at the size of this cavern, and there's nothing inside it save Falmer.</Source>
      <Dest>矮人肯定知道如何浪费很大的空间。看看这洞的大小吧，结果这里也没能住进几个雪精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This vampire had a boot for every day of the month.  Might want to check the insides, maybe he stashed something.  Just pray it's not sticky.</Source>
      <Dest>这个吸血鬼一个月每天有只不同的鞋子。应该再到里面看看，说不定他还藏着什么，不过千万别是黏糊糊的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By Zenithar, look at that vault.  And it's guarded by what, the help?  This is the kind of house that makes me moist.</Source>
      <Dest>泽尼萨尔在上，看那个金库。它被什么守卫着，【帮助】着呢？这种房子真是让我热泪盈眶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Roggi Knot-Beard?  That's obviously a made up name.</Source>
      <Dest>罗吉·结须 ?这显然是个随口胡诌的名字嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This Dunmer ranger hardly makes any shadow at all.  Or rather, her body is the shadow.  Not bad.</Source>
      <Dest>这个黑暗精灵游侠几乎没有尝试融入任何的阴影之中。或者说，她的身体就是阴影。真不赖。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Crazy witch.  Didn't even try and buy you off first.  First thing I would've done.</Source>
      <Dest>疯狂的巫师。想都没想就先买下了你。我应该第一个这么做的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Blood everywhere, and another dead researcher.  No wonder Calcelmo stays outside.  It must pain him to be so far from his precious Dwarves.</Source>
      <Dest>满地都是血，还有另外两个死去的研究者。怪不得卡赛默会呆在外面。如此远离他心爱的矮人们一定伤透了他的心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We'll take that claw off your hands, thank you very much.</Source>
      <Dest>我们都忍不住想跟你握一下爪了，真是太感谢你了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mages, bards, and now us.  This is officially now the weirdest tavern in Skyrim.  Heh, that's a good thing.  Sometimes, weird is a good thing.</Source>
      <Dest>法师们，吟遊诗人们，现在再加上我们。现在这可是公认的天际省最怪异的酒馆儿了。嘿，这可是件好事儿。有时候，怪异是件好事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Silver-Bloods are right about one thing.  You don't secure a prison with locks.  You do it with gold.</Source>
      <Dest>银血算是做对了一件事。你真不用为了安全考虑就去给一个牢笼加锁。你这么做还得花钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did you remember to loot Eltrys' body?  We ought to hit his house next.  Where did he live, anyway?  The Warrens?  Damn.  Never mind.</Source>
      <Dest>你还记得要去抢艾崔斯的尸体吗？我们接下来应该去他家碰碰运气。但是，他住哪儿啊？贫民窟吗？该死的。别放在心上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With Kodlak dead, the Companions will need a new Harbinger.  How convenient for you.</Source>
      <Dest>克拉科去了，于是战友团需要一名新的预言者。 (窃笑)对你而言倒是省事儿了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That weapon lacks finesse.  You seem like the type who uses a battleaxe to cut butter.  You know, the type who overcompensates.</Source>
      <Dest>那柄武器耍起来不需要什么技巧。你看着像那种砍个什么东西都要提把战斧只求痛快的人。那种极度自慢的人，你懂的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh.  I hate watching you sneak.  You have to crouch more, like your bootlaces are tied to your earlobes.  Stay low.  Think low.</Source>
      <Dest>哼。你这也叫潜行吗。你得蹲的再低点，就像你的鞋带能绑上你的耳朵那么低。保持低姿态。时刻想着放低姿态。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Her shadow was faint, but there was a shadow.  I knew she wasn't a ghost.  Didn't fool me for a second.</Source>
      <Dest>她的影子很模糊，但并没有消失。于是我明白了她并不是一个幽灵，她骗不过我的眼睛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeesh.  You've got guts to walk around with that mace strapped to your belt.  Fashion sense?  Gods no.  But guts?  Yeah.</Source>
      <Dest>是~~啊。你够胆儿就把狼牙棒挂在腰带上出去溜溜。时尚感？呵呵。但勇气？是啊，你很勇敢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Man, everywhere we go we end up killing half a dozen people.  You're a damn spider, and the flies can't help but aim for your web.</Source>
      <Dest>哥们儿，不论走到哪儿我们都不免会干掉半小打人。你就他丫就是只蜘蛛，那些苍蝇从来都只会往你的网上撞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, I get you want to help the Dibellan harlots find their god baby, but we're still coming back for the statue, right?</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我明白你想帮迪贝拉的妓女们找到他们的圣婴，但我们还是得为那雕像回来，对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't need to tell you who Hroggar reminds me of.  (Scoffs) Men.  They all need their eyes plucked out.  Only way to keep them from wandering.</Source>
      <Dest>我不需要告诉你是赫鲁加提醒的我。(嘲讽) 傻逼。他们的眼睛都需要挖出来。这是唯一让他们保持傻逼的办法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>From what I gather, nobody sleeps here, but the owner leaves her supplies overnight.  Upstairs door will make for an ideal exit too.</Source>
      <Dest>就我所知，没人睡在这儿，但物主把她的补给品放在这儿过夜。楼上的门也很方便逃跑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This house has some good loot, but we'd better fence it before it starts flying around again.</Source>
      <Dest>这个房子有些不错的战利品,但我们最好在它再次飞起来前插死他.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Winking Skeever.  I could use a good skeever steak right about now.  What?  Meat's meat.</Source>
      <Dest>眨眼雪鼠。看来我可以吃到上好的雪鼠排了。啥？肉就是肉啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So is this the house that burned down?  Because it should've been.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是那座被烧毁的房子吧？因为看来它是被烧过的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't like the way that bard is looking at me.  I might just pluck out his eyes if he keeps staring.</Source>
      <Dest>那个 吟遊诗人 看着别扭。要是他再盯着我们就把他眼珠子挖出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look at all this junk.  Just out in the open, waiting to be stolen, and nothing worth getting into a crouch over.</Source>
      <Dest>看看这些垃圾吧。到处散落着，根本便不值得弯腰，何况是特意去偷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, are you like some kind of archer or something?  Don't like to get messy, huh.  But daggers are cleaner, if you have the skill to use it.</Source>
      <Dest>那么说来，你是弓箭手还是别的什么?  不喜欢麻烦，呃…但是如果你有本事去用的话，即便匕首也可算得上割草利器。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why does the big ugly shadow get to boss around the other ones?  He's just as dirty and poor as they are.</Source>
      <Dest>为什么反倒是那个又丑又肥的影子能从这些人里脱颖而出当上老大的？他跟他们一样脏也一样穷啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Advances in Lockpicking. I had that book read to me once. It's firewood. Everyone knows gold picks are softer than copper, and better for bent locks.</Source>
      <Dest>开锁进阶。那本书我读过一次了。是柴火。大家都知道金质开锁器要比铜质开锁器质地要软，也更容易把锁给扭开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What a worthless lock.  Which means it's a worthless treasure.  Damn Nords are just toying with us now, building this mausoleum around nothing.</Source>
      <Dest>这锁一钱不值。换句话说，里头的宝物也一文不名。该死的诺德人空造一座壮丽的古坟，就只是为了耍我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh, that spider spit on me.  This is going to take weeks to get rid of the stink.</Source>
      <Dest>唔，蜘蛛朝我吐毒液了。要消掉这股味道可要几周呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's a general goods store around here, Bits and Pieces I think.  Sell the robes and take the coin.  Faster that way.</Source>
      <Dest>这附近有个杂货铺，我记得是叫“零零碎碎”。去把长袍卖掉好了，这样快一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So this Laelette, she gets bitten by Alva, then she's told to kill this kid but ends up trying to adopt her?  This just gets weirder and weirder.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这个拉莱特，她被阿尔瓦咬了，还被告知要杀掉这孩子，但最终却想收养她吗？真是越来越奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is that awful noise?  It sounds like a horker giving birth to a Sload.  Is that...is that an Orc bard?</Source>
      <Dest>这可怕的声音到底是什么？听起来就像一只三牙海象正在分娩出一只蛤蟆人。难道说……这是那个兽人吟遊诗人?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let's go pick some pockets, Thane of the Reach.  If a guard makes a fuss, you just remind him who really feeds his family.</Source>
      <Dest>让我们去掏些人的口袋吧，瑞驰的男爵大人。如果守卫们大惊小怪的，你只要提点他到底是谁真正养活着他的一家子就行啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't like playing the informant, but I do like stealing.  This is so confusing.</Source>
      <Dest>你不喜欢告密，但我却爱偷听，真是纠结。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These Nord forts always have a rear entrance.  Although this one's built on the edge of a mountain, so who knows.</Source>
      <Dest>这些诺德人的要塞通常都有一个后部入口。经管这个要塞建在了山崖边上，但是谁知道呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's blood on the ground here, and it smells sweet. Someone left a skull, a book, a staff, and...an arrow?  What's the arrow for?  I don't get it.</Source>
      <Dest>这地上有血迹, 闻上去还新鲜. 这留下一个骷髅, 一本书, 一根棍子,和...一支箭?  箭干嘛用?  我搞不懂.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Damn you!</Source>
      <Dest>混蛋！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know these shadows, and I know that smell.  Sleeping tree sap.  We could make a small fortune bottling and selling it to the cat caravans.</Source>
      <Dest>我认识这些阴影，也知道那种气味。沉睡之树的汁液。 我们把它用瓶子装起来卖给虎人商队能赚一笔大钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not all blind people can see.  Some of them are too busy trying to open their eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>不是所有的盲人都有视觉，他们中的一些人总是太过于忙碌以至于忘了去试着睁开眼睛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stupid bandits.  Whoever they were waiting for either escaped with the treasure or died chasing it.</Source>
      <Dest>那帮白痴强盗。他们等的那些人要不就已经在寻找财宝的过程中死了，要不就已经带着财宝远走高飞了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This Severio guy went from a Legion warrior to a cabbage farmer.  If I ever lose the taste for adventure, just slit my throat.</Source>
      <Dest>这位Severio从帝国军战士变成了圆白菜农夫。要是我有一天没兴趣冒险，就自己抹脖子算了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that a piece of dirty cheese?  People have the strangest bedtime habits.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一块肮脏的奶酪吗？人类有着最奇怪的睡觉习惯.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bards are nice, but stupid. A lot of them work for free.</Source>
      <Dest>吟遊诗人都是好人，也都够蠢的。他们有很多都是免费服务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An inn.  Great, I could use a good nap.</Source>
      <Dest>一家旅店。太好了。我可以睡个踏实的午觉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This must be where the bandits stockpile their goods.  That chest is as big as the Katariah.  My mouth's watering just looking at it.</Source>
      <Dest>這裡一定就是強盜們藏戰利品的地方。這箱子大的跟卡塔瑞亞號一樣。光是看著這些，我嘴裡的口水就流個不停。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Candles, set up in circles like some kind of ritual.   Whatever's at the end of this cave won't be pretty.</Source>
      <Dest>把蜡烛放在圈子里就像某种仪式。但不管怎样，这个洞穴最终都不会变漂亮点儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hunters are the worst.  You dip your hands in their pockets and it's either soggy meat or a bear trap.</Source>
      <Dest>猎人是最糟糕的目标，你就算把手伸进了他们的口袋，能掏出来的也只有湿哒哒的肉或者熊皮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do your worst!</Source>
      <Dest>你还是做好最坏的打算吧！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The food here smells foul.  But then it isn't really food, is it?</Source>
      <Dest>这食物闻起来臭死了。但它不是我们真正的食物，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh look, the Orcs turned this keep into a Stronghold.  And here I thought these forts couldn't get any more droll.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，看呐，兽人们把这些存进了要塞。这些要塞让我觉得再滑稽不过了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't say this often, but we should kill him.  Trust this greedy Elf and I'll slit both your throats on principle.</Source>
      <Dest>我一般不这样说，但我们必须得杀了他。（如果继续）相信这个贪婪的精灵那我就按照规定把你们俩的喉咙都给撕了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Agh! Enough! This ends now!</Source>
      <Dest>嘿！够了！已经结束了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello secret passageway!  And look at all those traps!  One trap means good treasure.  Three or four?  Looks like meat on the table tonight.</Source>
      <Dest>你好啊，密道！看看这些陷阱！一个陷阱意味着珍贵的宝藏。如果有三个或是更多？看起来就像是今晚摆在餐桌上的肉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Damn, smells good in here.  One thing about pyromancers...they can roast a piece of meat. </Source>
      <Dest>该死的，那儿闻起来真香。看来那里有烈焰术士……他们可以烤肉的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So as Thane, you get a "House Carl?"  Well, I hope this Carl knows how to cook.  Where's he hiding, anyway?  You around here, Carl?</Source>
      <Dest>身为贵族，你却请了个“侍卫”的？呃，我希望这个粗人会做饭。总之，他藏哪儿啦？你在这儿吗？ Carl?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These Orcs didn't trust each other one bit.  Everyone has their own little corner, and their own personal treasure chest.</Source>
      <Dest>这些兽人一点儿也不信任彼此。每个人都打着自己的小九九儿，也藏着他们自己的小金库。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You need to do better than that!</Source>
      <Dest>你需要做得更好！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Agh!  Bastard!</Source>
      <Dest>啊！混蛋！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You pray at a Shrine like this, you're basically inviting the Thalmor into your pants.  These people should've known better.</Source>
      <Dest>你在这样的神社祈祷，基本上等同于邀请梭默随便强X你。这些人应该知道得更清楚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Two men are fighting over her?  I suppose she's pretty, but so is a portrait.  They both wear a lot of paint.</Source>
      <Dest>两个男人为她而争斗? 我想她很漂亮，可惜这只不过是一幅虚幻的画像。他们两个都为此增添了不少的浓墨重彩呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, with the old man dead, the others are distracted.  Now's the time to hit Jorrvaskr.  Your shield-family never liked you anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>所以，随着这个老家伙的死去，其他的人都心烦意乱。现在是个攻打月瓦斯卡的好时机。反正你的盾牌家人从来也没喜欢过你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By Nocturnal, this Ghunzul must've been pretty brave, if he spent every night in the shadow of that bear.</Source>
      <Dest>诺克图娜尔在上，如果他每晚都在那只熊的阴影下过夜，这个叫Ghunzul的人一定非常勇敢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dragonborn?  Those Nords made it sound like you're some sort of god.   I don't think we'll have a problem getting them look the other way.</Source>
      <Dest>龙裔? 那些诺德人这样一说，搞得你听起来好像神仙一样。（窃笑）我想我们可以毫不费力地把他们装扮得谁都认不出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lucky hit!</Source>
      <Dest>会心一击！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come on, is that all you've got?</Source>
      <Dest>过来这里，这是你做到的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dragon Bridge.  Ever get a taste of that Dragon Breath Mead?  Sounds disgusting.</Source>
      <Dest>龙桥。你有尝过龙息酒的滋味儿吗？听起来挺恶心的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Jarl of Whiterun's pretty pathetic, if he can't even hold Fort Greymoor.  I can spit on Dragonsreach from here.</Source>
      <Dest>白漫城领主真可悲,如果他不曾掌管灰色荒原堡垒。我就能向龙临堡吐口水。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This cave is too clean. Let's make it dirty.</Source>
      <Dest>这个洞穴太干净了，让我们给它添点儿血。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>See, this mammoth had it right.  When I die, don't bury me, turn me into a battering ram.  Also, coin purse up high, and one around the corner.</Source>
      <Dest>瞧，这只 长毛象 【说得对】。我死之后，不要埋，把我做成【攻城锤】。还有，【高高挂着的钱包，角落里还有一只。】</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The planks in this cave look creaky, but the sound of the waterfalls should mask our steps.</Source>
      <Dest>这个洞穴里的木板看起来摇摇欲坠，但瀑布的声音应该可以掩盖我们的脚步声。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What a waste of a perfectly good pit wolf.  You can't train something like that.  You just have to let it kill.</Source>
      <Dest>多完美的一只狼崽子，真是可惜了。你不应该训练它去做那样的事情。你应该让它去杀戮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not only did that idiot Silus pay us already, he left his entire museum unattended.  You thinking what I'm thinking?</Source>
      <Dest>那个笨蛋Silus不仅已经付清了我们的钱，而且整个博物馆都无人看守。你觉得我是在想着什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We aren't actually paying for things, are we?</Source>
      <Dest>我们又不是真的付钱买东西，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is really happening, isn't it?  A sodding dragon.  Wow.  You want my advice?  We stay here and take advantage of the mayhem.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这是真的，不是吗？一条该死的龙。哇哦。想要我的建议吗？我们待在这里，把这封闭的环境作为战略优势。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That the best you can do?</Source>
      <Dest>这就是你的极限了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I like small towns.  Some thieves only steal from city nobles.  I don't play favorites.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢小镇。有的小偷只从成立的贵族那里偷东西，而我可没有什么最爱名单。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like the pinch of a mudcrab!</Source>
      <Dest>就像一只跳蚤咬的!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In the land of the poor and hungry, the cabbages are diamonds.</Source>
      <Dest>在这贫瘠的土地，卷心菜如同钻石一样珍贵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who puts their bed by a window?  You're just asking to have your throat slit.</Source>
      <Dest>谁把床放在窗边的。 等着被割喉么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know if this qualifies as stealing.  Seems everything in this marriage belongs to that woman.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道这是不是一种偷窃。看上去这场婚姻的一切都属于那个女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Coin purse, on the support beam over the bridge.  Wonder how that got there.  Wonder how you're going to get it.</Source>
      <Dest>那个装满钱的钱包在桥的承重柱上。我很奇怪它怎么跑到那去的。我也很奇怪你是怎么弄到他的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll cut right through your scales, monster!</Source>
      <Dest>我会连你的鳞片一刀切的，怪物！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're nothing!</Source>
      <Dest>你这无名小卒！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Time to pluck that fur, werewolf!</Source>
      <Dest>狼人，到了该拔毛的时间囉！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You won't get away!</Source>
      <Dest>你跑不了！ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't stand a chance!</Source>
      <Dest>你一点机会也没有！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eyraargh!</Source>
      <Dest>伊呀阿阿！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Shadows swallow you whole!</Source>
      <Dest>阴影吞没了你！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Filthy Forsworn!</Source>
      <Dest>肮脏的弃誓者！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This isn't over.</Source>
      <Dest>这事儿没完。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not quite good enough!</Source>
      <Dest>还不够好！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Give up while you still can!</Source>
      <Dest>趁你还有反悔的机会，投降吧！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hyargh!</Source>
      <Dest>嘿呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Think you can take me, Orc?</Source>
      <Dest>你还觉得你能搞定我么， 兽人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take that, you fiend!</Source>
      <Dest>接招吧，你个魔鬼！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come on, is that it?</Source>
      <Dest>加油，就这样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Die, damn you!</Source>
      <Dest>去死吧，混蛋！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You'll need to do better than that!</Source>
      <Dest>不给力啊！！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Go back to where you came from, dragon!</Source>
      <Dest>巨龙，滚回你来的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Say hello to Ysmir for me, Nord!</Source>
      <Dest>帮我向伊斯米尔问个好，诺德佬！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Say hello to Ysmir for me, Nord!</Source>
      <Dest>帮我向伊斯米尔问个好，诺德佬！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is this what you want?</Source>
      <Dest>这就是你想要的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eyaargh!</Source>
      <Dest>哎呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yield or die!</Source>
      <Dest>屈服或死！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've had enough of you!</Source>
      <Dest>我受够你了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Too slow!</Source>
      <Dest>太慢了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take that!</Source>
      <Dest>接招！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why won't you die already?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么还不去死？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will cut off your tail, cat!</Source>
      <Dest>我会把你的尾巴给砍下来的，你这只死猫！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some legend you are!</Source>
      <Dest>【你只不过是个传说】！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Will you just stand still!</Source>
      <Dest>站住别动！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're outmatched!</Source>
      <Dest>你输了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is too easy!</Source>
      <Dest>这根本没挑战性!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You thirsty, bloodsucker?!  Well you aren't drinking me!</Source>
      <Dest>你饥渴了，吸血鬼？！但你也不能喝我的血！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Victory is yours!</Source>
      <Dest>胜利是属于你的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Die witch!</Source>
      <Dest>死巫婆！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can take you!</Source>
      <Dest>你完了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll have your head!</Source>
      <Dest>我要剁你的脑袋！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You picked the wrong dinner, animal!</Source>
      <Dest>你选错晚餐了，畜生！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me. I need your help.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着我。我需要你的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What went wrong with your marriage?</Source>
      <Dest>你的婚姻发生了什么不幸？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the reason they put you in prison? What did they charge you with?</Source>
      <Dest>他们把你关进牢里的理由是什么？他们拿什么控告你？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the reason they put you in prison? What did they charge you with?</Source>
      <Dest>他们把你关进牢里的理由是什么？他们拿什么控告你？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't worry, if anybody tries to squeal to the guard,  I got some fresh dagger loaf waiting for them.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心, 如果有人向守卫哭闹,  我有些刀削面包留给他们.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I get that he's a necromancer, but what do you mean you never saw eye to eye?</Source>
      <Dest>我知道他是个亡灵法师啊，不过你说你们的观点从来没有一样过是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is it, oath-brother?</Source>
      <Dest>那是什么，誓言兄弟？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I stole something for you the other day. Something called a console. Seemed worthless though, so I scrapped it.</Source>
      <Dest>前两天我从你这儿偷了点东西。一个叫什么控制器的。可是看起来没用，所以我就扔了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All these Companions and they couldn't save the old man?  This family only cares about themselves.</Source>
      <Dest>战友团里就没有一个人能救这个老人吗？那帮家伙也只关心他们自己罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah?</Source>
      <Dest>啊?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Make sure you order a round for everyone.  Then I'll ask if anyone can teach me Iron Hearts.  You know, to help a poor little girl pass the time.</Source>
      <Dest>我请大家喝一杯。然后谁能教教我铁心【Iron  Hearts】怎么玩，我得陪那个可怜的小女孩玩这游戏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The shinier something is, the more I want it.</Source>
      <Dest>越是亮晶晶的东西，我越喜欢得不得了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, let's keep to the shadows.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，让我们继续潜行于阴影之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Guts trump wit every time.</Source>
      <Dest>无论何时，勇气都胜过智慧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some of the sheets in this inn have some strange shadows, and even weirder smells.  This town got a stable?  Might be safer to sleep there.</Source>
      <Dest>这家酒馆儿的被单上有些奇怪的污迹，甚至有些更为古怪的气味儿。这小镇有畜舍吗？也许在那里睡更安全些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now we're talking.  This is a dagger.  Sharp, balanced, and it sucks up the light.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我们聊聊吧。这是把匕首，锋利，协调，同时吸收了光芒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We've stopped.  You're not going to ask a blind woman for directions, are you?</Source>
      <Dest>我们停下了。你不会去跟个失明的女人问路，对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Care for a game of iron hearts?  I figure your coin purse could lose some weight.</Source>
      <Dest>介意稍后来一把铁心iron hearts的游戏么？我觉得你的钱包该减减肥了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is it, oath-sister?</Source>
      <Dest>那是什么，义姐?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Heh, turns out the romance part faded months ago.  The only reason he stuck around was so I could protect him from Maven's thugs.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，结果浪漫的部分几个月前就褪色了。只因为他被困住后我就能从玛雯的恶棍手里保护他了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Shadow hide you, shadow guide you.</Source>
      <Dest>阴影庇护你，阴影指引你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You got a lock, I'll pick it. You got a joke? I'm laughing. There ain't a face butcher in Tamriel that can wipe off this smile.</Source>
      <Dest>你遇到锁，我来解决。你讲了笑话？我来捧场。找遍泰姆瑞尔都不会有人能把这笑容从我脸上除掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who knows. I mean, I never leave a trace when I steal. But there was that one time something was stolen from me.</Source>
      <Dest>谁知道呢。我是说，我在偷东西的时候从不会留下把柄。但有一次我竟然被人摸了腰包了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You've stolen from the Black-Briars more than once?</Source>
      <Dest>你已经不止一次去Black-Briars偷过东西了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It seems Larsdon and Falatild have been playing me for a fool.</Source>
      <Dest>看来Larsdon和Falatild是在捉弄我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It seems Larsdon and Falatild have been playing me for a fool.</Source>
      <Dest>看来Larsdon和Falatild是在捉弄我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It seems Larsdon and Falatild have been playing me for a fool.</Source>
      <Dest>看来Larsdon和Falatild是在捉弄我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not interested in introductions, girl. Who did you sell the journal to?</Source>
      <Dest>姑娘，我对介绍什么的不感兴趣，我感兴趣的是你把日志卖给了谁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My name's &lt;Alias=Player&gt;. And I need some answers.</Source>
      <Dest>我是 &lt;Alias=Player&gt;。 我需要一些解释。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You lying little thief. I know you sold it to someone else for more coin.</Source>
      <Dest>说谎你这小贼！我知道你是高价卖给别人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You lying little thief. I know you sold it to someone else for more coin.</Source>
      <Dest>说谎你这小贼！我知道你是高价卖给别人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You lying little thief. I know you sold it to someone else for more coin.</Source>
      <Dest>说谎你这小贼！我知道你是高价卖给别人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You lying little thief. I know you sold it to someone else for more coin.</Source>
      <Dest>说谎你这小贼！我知道你是高价卖给别人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Winterhold is a good place to lay low.</Source>
      <Dest>冬堡是个隐居的好地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you follow me, there will be people who need to die.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你跟着我，就会有人需要死去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Careful.  It's a slippery slope to vampirism.</Source>
      <Dest>小心。这是成为吸血鬼的捷径。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Careful.  It's a slippery slope to vampirism.</Source>
      <Dest>小心。这是成为吸血鬼的捷径。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Careful.  It's a slippery slope to vampirism.</Source>
      <Dest>小心。这是成为吸血鬼的捷径。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Careful.  It's a slippery slope to vampirism.</Source>
      <Dest>小心。这是成为吸血鬼的捷径。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your fishing technique.</Source>
      <Dest>给我说说你的钓鱼技巧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your fishing technique.</Source>
      <Dest>给我说说你的钓鱼技巧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your fishing technique.</Source>
      <Dest>给我说说你的钓鱼技巧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your fishing technique.</Source>
      <Dest>给我说说你的钓鱼技巧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What went wrong with your marriage?</Source>
      <Dest>你的婚姻发生了什么不幸？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What went wrong with your marriage?</Source>
      <Dest>你的婚姻发生了什么不幸？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What went wrong with your marriage?</Source>
      <Dest>你的婚姻发生了什么不幸？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good. I try to avoid death whenever possible.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。我总是尽可能地避免杀人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good. I try to avoid death whenever possible.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。我总是尽可能地避免杀人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the reason they put you in prison? What did they charge you with?</Source>
      <Dest>他们把你关进牢里的理由是什么？他们拿什么控告你？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the reason they put you in prison? What did they charge you with?</Source>
      <Dest>他们把你关进牢里的理由是什么？他们拿什么控告你？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the reason they put you in prison? What did they charge you with?</Source>
      <Dest>他们把你关进牢里的理由是什么？他们拿什么控告你？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't wear sleeves.</Source>
      <Dest>你不要穿袖子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't wear sleeves.</Source>
      <Dest>你不要穿袖子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't wear sleeves.</Source>
      <Dest>你不要穿袖子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't wear sleeves.</Source>
      <Dest>你不要穿袖子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Windhelm should have plenty of opportunities for an enterprising thief.</Source>
      <Dest>对专业盗贼来讲风舵城肯定有很多发财的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Windhelm should have plenty of opportunities for an enterprising thief.</Source>
      <Dest>对专业盗贼来讲风舵城肯定有很多发财的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Strange. I was told you double-crossed your contract.</Source>
      <Dest>陌生人，我听说你出卖了你的合同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Strange. I was told you double-crossed your contract.</Source>
      <Dest>陌生人，我听说你出卖了你的合同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Strange. I was told you double-crossed your contract.</Source>
      <Dest>陌生人，我听说你出卖了你的合同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Strange. I was told you double-crossed your contract.</Source>
      <Dest>陌生人，我听说你出卖了你的合同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, that isn't creepy or anything.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，那不是什么可怕的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, that isn't creepy or anything.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，那不是什么可怕的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, that isn't creepy or anything.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，那不是什么可怕的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We don't know if they're connected, if at all.  This is a fact finding mission.</Source>
      <Dest>我们不知道他们之间是不是有关联，或者根本是一伙。这是一个挖掘真相的任务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We don't know if they're connected, if at all.  This is a fact finding mission.</Source>
      <Dest>我们不知道他们之间是不是有关联，或者根本是一伙。这是一个挖掘真相的任务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Perhaps Riften was both the obvious choice and the best one.</Source>
      <Dest>也许裂谷城既是权宜之策也是最佳选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Perhaps Riften was both the obvious choice and the best one.</Source>
      <Dest>也许裂谷城既是权宜之策也是最佳选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Perhaps Riften was both the obvious choice and the best one.</Source>
      <Dest>也许裂谷城既是权宜之策也是最佳选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's enough about the Black-Briar thefts.</Source>
      <Dest>黑荆棘所做的勾当已经够多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure. That wasn't my intent. I had nothing against the woman personally, at least, back then. Her properties just cast the longest shadows.</Source>
      <Dest>真的. 那是我的主意. 我对那女人没有私人恩怨,至少以前沒有。 不過就在剛才我改觀了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I'll kill them.  Bandits, Thalmor, guards, whatever.  I'll spill the blood of anyone who asks for it, but not a soul who doesn't.</Source>
      <Dest>不管是强盗、梭默还是守卫，无论杀谁，赴汤蹈火，唯命是从。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Needless to say, he won't be seeing anyone ever again.</Source>
      <Dest>不用说,他不会再见到任何人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Slice the neck or the gut, basically.  This looks like a "neck" town.  Solitude, you go for the gut.</Source>
      <Dest>抓住咽喉，掏出脏腑，这是最基本的。这看起来像是咽喉之所在。独孤城，你去找那个”脏腑“。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Funny, now that makes me want to go somewhere else.  But first instinct is best instinct, and yours is as good as any.</Source>
      <Dest>有意思，我现在都快熬不住想去别处了。不过第一选择往往是最好的选择，而你的选择也是这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No way. That's bad for business, and a good way to get yourself killed. It's hard enough escaping the guard.</Source>
      <Dest>没用的，这对交易无益，让你自己死亡是一个好办法。想要逃离守卫实在太难了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But relax.  I don't like the taste of blood.  I like the smell.  You wouldn't eat a rose, would you?</Source>
      <Dest>但放松点，我可不喜欢血尝起来的味道。我只喜欢用闻的，就像你不会真的去吃玫瑰花，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, I know it wasn't me who screwed up. Their guy is supposed to wait at the docks, with 3 stones in a satchel and my gold in a purse.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我都知道搞砸的人不是我。他们的人应该在码头等着，带着装有3块儿石头的背包，还有装着我金币的钱包儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You want a vampire, go open a coffin.  But if you're smart, you'll keep me around to pick his pocket.</Source>
      <Dest>你要找吸血鬼，去找个棺材打开看看。不过要是聪明的话，你就放我去扒他的口袋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, I've seen some people carry knives no longer than a thumb.  The one I carry is a little longer than that.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，我还见过带着比拇指还短的小刀的人。我带着的那把比拇指稍微长一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You want a killer, go find a Dark Brotherhood assassin.  But if you're smart, you'll keep me around to pick his pocket.</Source>
      <Dest>你想要一个杀手？去找一名黑暗兄弟会的刺客。但如果你够聪明，你会让我去掏他的口袋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had a feeling you and me would get along great.  But don't worry, I'm not afraid to kill. </Source>
      <Dest>我有种感觉，我们会相处的很好的。也别担心，我不害怕杀戮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Damn. Didn't know this place had a magical barrier around the college.  That place looks like it's teeming with loot.</Source>
      <Dest>妈的。没想到这学院周围有魔法屏障。这地方看起来可抢的东西可真多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, is everything really that complicated or is Delphine just stupid?  Ah, you do want you want.  Just give me a shadow to stand in.</Source>
      <Dest>我是说，到底是一切真的那么复杂，还是戴尔菲娜就那么蠢？噢，做你想做的吧。只有给我留个阴影能猫着就成。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He tells me he wants to see other people.  Two of them, in fact.  Only cost him half our remaining coin to bed them both at the same time.</Source>
      <Dest>他告诉我他想见见其他人。而且是两个。他们只花费了剩余一半的金币就和二人同床共枕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nothing but empty pockets there.  I think I saw some Dark Elf eat a bucket of snow for dinner.</Source>
      <Dest>那儿除了些空口袋啥都没有。我想我看见了一些黑暗精灵吃一桶雪当做晚餐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sibbi was always a cute one.  His face would look great on a fence post.  I'm kidding, of course, I don't kill.</Source>
      <Dest>西比真的很可爱。如果把他那张小脸贴在篱笆上的话那就更可爱了。哦好吧我只是在开玩笑，我才不杀生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I lift the purse and put the journal in the satchel. So unless there was some other guy carrying around a bunch of rocks, I did my job.</Source>
      <Dest>然后我拿走钱袋，把笔记放进包里。除非还有人会带着一堆石头乱逛，我就算完工了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Pickpocketing is all about misdirection.  Brush someone's shoulder.  Stumble into them.  Tap them on the back and ask for directions.</Source>
      <Dest>偷东西的诀窍就在于误导。抚一下别人的肩膀啦。假装倒向别人啦。拍他们的背问个路啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>About the journal? Yeah, I stole it. So what? Someone pays me to steal something, I steal it for them.</Source>
      <Dest>我的确偷了那本日记。。那又怎样?我只不过是干这拿钱消灾的生意罢了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This city is too guarded.  Eyes everywhere, not enough shadows.  No one trusts outsiders.  Although at least its better than the Cornerclub.</Source>
      <Dest>这座城市戒备太森严了。到处都有人盯着你，让你无处藏身。没有人相信外地人。不过这里还是比街角吧要好一点儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I jest.  I'm not a killer.  I'm a thief.  Anyone can steal from a dead man.  Being a cutpurse takes skill, and guile.</Source>
      <Dest>开个玩笑。我不是一个杀手。我是一个贼。任何人都可以偷死人。作为一个扒手需要技巧和一点诡计。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I did my job.  But I'll tell you what. Why don't you take me to your boss? We'll sort this out, one way or the other.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我做了我该做的。我会告诉你具体内容的。为什么不带我去见见你们老大呢？我们要把这事儿搞清楚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I did my job.  But I'll tell you what. Why don't you take me to your boss? We'll sort this out, one way or the other.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我做了我该做的。我会告诉你具体内容的。为什么不带我去见见你们老大呢？我们要把这事儿搞清楚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So that night, I crept into the brothel house, and I took all four of them.  The two girls' purses...and my husband's two eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>所以那个夜里我就爬进了妓院，把四样东西都带走了。那两个姑娘的手提包......还有我丈夫的两只眼睛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why pickpockets usually wear long, loose sleeves.  Normal daggers are no good.  You want one without a hilt.</Source>
      <Dest>那就是为什么小偷通常穿着又长又松的袖子。普通的匕首一点好处都没有，你会喜欢无柄的匕首的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I sold it for a higher price, I'd admit it. Heck, I'd probably brag about it, depending on how much.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我把它卖了个高价钱的话，我就会承认了。真见鬼，根据具体卖了多少钱我说不定还能吹个牛什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He'd have a satchel with 3 stones inside, and a coin purse with my payment. Then I lift the purse and put the journal in the satchel.</Source>
      <Dest>他会背着一个装着三个石头的挎包，和一个装满我的报酬的钱袋，然后我会拿出钱袋，让他背着他的挎包继续他的旅程。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He'd have a satchel with 3 stones inside, and a coin purse with my payment. Then I lift the purse and put the journal in the satchel.</Source>
      <Dest>他会背着一个装着三个石头的挎包，和一个装满我的报酬的钱袋，然后我会拿出钱袋，让他背着他的挎包继续他的旅程。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So...you might find nothing?  What good does that do?  Why don't we just do like you did at Kynesgrove?  Find the dragon, kill the dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>那么。。。。你也许什么都没找到？这样做有什么好处？为什么我们不照上次凯娜之林那样做？找到那条龙，杀掉那条龙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look, I'm pretty awful with voices, for a blind girl anyway, so I have a system. I told them to have a man waiting for me at the docks.</Source>
      <Dest>要知道，我的嗓音很差，【就算是盲人也一样】，所以我想了个办法，让他们找个男人到码头等我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look, I'm pretty awful with voices, for a blind girl anyway, so I have a system. I told them to have a man waiting for me at the docks.</Source>
      <Dest>要知道，我的嗓音很差，【就算是盲人也一样】，所以我想了个办法，让他们找个男人到码头等我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's not as sharp as most knives, but it works for purse strings.  Problem is, some of the more quality pouches are made from coarser rope.</Source>
      <Dest>它并不像大多数刀具那样锋利，但它擅长于切开制作钱袋的绳子。问题是，一些较优质的袋子是用更粗的绳子制成的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bandits, Thalmor, guards, whatever.  I'll spill the blood of anyone who asks for it, but not a soul who doesn't.</Source>
      <Dest>不管是强盗、梭默还是守卫，无论杀谁，赴汤蹈火，唯命是从。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not yours, though. You've proven more than resourceful, and if we work together, you might prove invaluable as well.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然不是你的。你已经证明了你非常的足智多谋，如果我们一起努力的话，你也许也能证明自己的宝贵价值。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then the only way to make things right is to dip in their pockets. It's not even stealing. It's like...justice or something.</Source>
      <Dest>那么将一切扳回正轨的唯一方法就是去刨他们的口袋。这可不能说是劫财，这更像是...以正义或者别的什么的名义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you say that, it makes me want to try it out.  And why not?  Vampires are as strong as an ox and live forever.</Source>
      <Dest>你这么一说，我反倒想试试看了。话说回来有什么理由不去试试呢？吸血鬼们都比公牛还强壮而且还都长生不老。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, I'm not a killer of any kind. I'm a thief. Anyone can steal from a dead man.  Being a cutpurse takes skill, and guile.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我什么杀手都不是。我是个贼。不论是谁都能从尸体身上偷走东西。作为一名小偷需要技巧，和狡诈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, you don't need sleeves when the knife fits in your hand like a middle finger.  When it's time to cut the strings, I just close the fleshy ones.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，如果小刀能像你的中指一样灵活的话你就没有必要有什么袖子了。当需要切线的时候，我只需要把原来长着的中指缩回去。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although...I could chop her up first.   Maybe make a nice little tableau out of her family.</Source>
      <Dest>不过……我能先把她砍咯。也许能用她的家人搞出一个美丽的小场面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Except Maven Black-Briar won't let me set foot in that town unless it came in a sack.  </Source>
      <Dest>除非把我装在麻袋里，否则黑荆棘玛雯不会让我进城的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You won't be saying that when I line your pockets with valuables.  Can't make a horse haunch without slaying the one you rode in on.</Source>
      <Dest>在我往你包里放些值钱的东西之后你就不会这么说了。不把自己骑的马杀掉就拿不到马腿肉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The idea is to make some sort of contact as your free hand slices their purse strings.</Source>
      <Dest>基本思想是在你与他交流的同时用你闲着的那只手把他们钱包的束带割掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who else? The person who contracted me to steal it.</Source>
      <Dest>还能有谁？那个跟我定下契约要我偷这东西的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stupid nobles though, they'll have quality strings but use a velvet pouch instead of leather.  So you cut the purse instead.</Source>
      <Dest>贵族都是蠢蛋，他们用高质量的绳子系着钱袋，但却用绒布代替皮革制作钱袋，所以你可以直接割破它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm the Guildmaster now.  If you want in, just say the word.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在是公会首领。如果你想加入，说句话就行了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm the Guildmaster now.  If you want in, just say the word.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在是公会首领。如果你想加入，说句话就行了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm the Guildmaster now.  If you want in, just say the word.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在是公会首领。如果你想加入，说句话就行了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm the Guildmaster now.  If you want in, just say the word.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在是公会首领。如果你想加入，说句话就行了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You make being blind sound like a completely different experience.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来你盲当作一种完全不同的体验。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You make being blind sound like a completely different experience.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来你盲当作一种完全不同的体验。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your eyes...How do you maneuver around if you can't see?</Source>
      <Dest>你的眼睛...如果你看不见的话你要怎么机动呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your eyes...How do you maneuver around if you can't see?</Source>
      <Dest>你的眼睛...如果你看不见的话你要怎么机动呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your eyes...How do you maneuver around if you can't see?</Source>
      <Dest>你的眼睛...如果你看不见的话你要怎么机动呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your eyes...How do you maneuver around if you can't see?</Source>
      <Dest>你的眼睛...如果你看不见的话你要怎么机动呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your eyes...How do you maneuver around if you can't see?</Source>
      <Dest>你的眼睛...如果你看不见的话你要怎么机动呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's a dragon rookery.  A place where dragons are bred and raised to fight.</Source>
      <Dest>这里是龙的栖息地，负责繁殖和培养他们战斗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You look like you've got something to say.</Source>
      <Dest>你看起来有话要说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You look like you've got something to say.</Source>
      <Dest>你看起来有话要说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You look like you've got something to say.</Source>
      <Dest>你看起来有话要说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You look like you've got something to say.</Source>
      <Dest>你看起来有话要说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ancano is no more, and the College is saved.</Source>
      <Dest>Ancano 成为过去了，学院保住了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ancano is no more, and the College is saved.</Source>
      <Dest>Ancano 成为过去了，学院保住了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How come you never joined the Guild? Maven isn't the only mark around.</Source>
      <Dest>怎么你没加入公会？ Maven可不是周围唯一的污点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, that makes perfect sense. Wait, no it doesn't.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，这很有道理。等等，它不对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, that makes perfect sense. Wait, no it doesn't.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，这很有道理。等等，它不对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's not about living together, it's about living apart from the world.</Source>
      <Dest>重點不是在一起生活，而是分開在世界的兩地生活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's not about living together, it's about living apart from the world.</Source>
      <Dest>重點不是在一起生活，而是分開在世界的兩地生活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's not about living together, it's about living apart from the world.</Source>
      <Dest>重點不是在一起生活，而是分開在世界的兩地生活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Companions Quest) The Companions have accepted me into their family.</Source>
      <Dest>（Companions 任务）Companions 接纳了我并邀请我加入他们的大家庭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Companions Quest) The Companions have accepted me into their family.</Source>
      <Dest>（Companions 任务）Companions 接纳了我并邀请我加入他们的大家庭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That sounds like a terrible substitute for eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来是个糟糕的眼球代用品。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That sounds like a terrible substitute for eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来是个糟糕的眼球代用品。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That sounds like a terrible substitute for eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来是个糟糕的眼球代用品。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) Looks like I have to challenge Alduin alone.</Source>
      <Dest>(Dragonsreach) 看来我得独自迎接Alduin的挑战了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) Looks like I have to challenge Alduin alone.</Source>
      <Dest>(Dragonsreach) 看来我得独自迎接Alduin的挑战了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) Looks like I have to challenge Alduin alone.</Source>
      <Dest>(Dragonsreach) 看来我得独自迎接Alduin的挑战了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Whiterun) Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>(白漫城)你有什么心事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your lack of scruples disturbs me. I bet you would steal from your own mother.</Source>
      <Dest>我讨厌你的无良。我打赌你连你亲妈的东西都会偷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Never mind.</Source>
      <Dest>不用介意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You know, there are people who want you dead. I could be here to kill you.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道的，有很多人想要你死，我很有可能是来这里杀你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You know, there are people who want you dead. I could be here to kill you.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道的，有很多人想要你死，我很有可能是来这里杀你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want your thoughts on Anum-La.</Source>
      <Dest>我想知道你对安努姆菈的想法</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright, you fooled me. Now stay in your cage and serve out your sentence.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，你耍我。那就在你的笼子里呆到刑满释放吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>By the Divines you're stupid.  I've met mudcrabs with more plausible theories.</Source>
      <Dest>我的天呐你能有多笨！我见过的泥螃蟹都比你有脑子！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>By the Divines you're stupid.  I've met mudcrabs with more plausible theories.</Source>
      <Dest>我的天呐你能有多笨！我见过的泥螃蟹都比你有脑子！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was an impressive display of acting.  You got me.</Source>
      <Dest>真是个令人印象深刻的表演啊。你懂的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was an impressive display of acting.  You got me.</Source>
      <Dest>真是个令人印象深刻的表演啊。你懂的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Riften) This is a homecoming for you, isn't it?</Source>
      <Dest>(裂谷城)这对你而言是一个家，对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Riften) This is a homecoming for you, isn't it?</Source>
      <Dest>(裂谷城)这对你而言是一个家，对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Riften) This is a homecoming for you, isn't it?</Source>
      <Dest>(裂谷城)这对你而言是一个家，对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Riften) This is a homecoming for you, isn't it?</Source>
      <Dest>(裂谷城)这对你而言是一个家，对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Riften) This is a homecoming for you, isn't it?</Source>
      <Dest>(裂谷城)这对你而言是一个家，对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what?  The world's saved.  What more could you ask for?</Source>
      <Dest>还有什么想法？全世界都拯救了，你还要我怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what?  The world's saved.  What more could you ask for?</Source>
      <Dest>还有什么想法？全世界都拯救了，你还要我怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what?  The world's saved.  What more could you ask for?</Source>
      <Dest>还有什么想法？全世界都拯救了，你还要我怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what?  The world's saved.  What more could you ask for?</Source>
      <Dest>还有什么想法？全世界都拯救了，你还要我怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what?  The world's saved.  What more could you ask for?</Source>
      <Dest>还有什么想法？全世界都拯救了，你还要我怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought you were a jester, as laughable as that performance was.</Source>
      <Dest>我一直把你当小丑看，就像你的表演一样滑稽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But the Forsworn lost their home, and I know how that is.  I know it ain't easy.</Source>
      <Dest>但弃世者失去了他们的家园, 我也知道是怎么回事. 我知道那不简单.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't need magic. When she took my eyes, Nocturnal blessed me with a keen sense for the dark. And everything in the world casts a shadow.</Source>
      <Dest>我不需要魔法. 她夺取我眼睛的时候, 夜母赋予我黑暗中敏锐的触觉. 世间外物都产生阴影.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You think that was something?  If you waited a minute, I would've literally cried.  Goes pretty well with the eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>你不把那当一回事？如果你再等等，我几乎就真的哭出来了，我的眼睛都泛着泪花了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Guess it does sound pretty bizarre without the rest of the whole story.  My gold was stolen, but it wasn't a crime.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜这些听起来挺诡异的吧——如果没有结局的话。偷了我的钱，却不违法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But no, even if you had that kind of clout, you wouldn't be doing me a favor.  </Source>
      <Dest>但是不是这样的。即使你有那种影响力，也没什么用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So draw your weapon or shut up.  I'm getting out of here.  If you aren't gonna help, then stay and keep Bjartur company.</Source>
      <Dest>要么拿起武器，要么闭嘴。我要走了。如果你不帮忙的话，就留下来继续经营布贾特公司吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It has things to steal and fences to move them.  Which is why we should sell the horn.</Source>
      <Dest>那里有的是宝物和需要移除的栅栏，这就是为什么我们要卖掉这些喇叭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It must be the ugliest substance in the world, the way people scream at the sight of it. But it smells absolutely perfect.</Source>
      <Dest>这恐怕是世界上最难看的食材了，谁见到它第一眼都会惊叫出来。不过它的香味闻起来真是完美啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Either way, you ain't leaving without me.  I'll lick a harpy's backside before I let you go off alone.</Source>
      <Dest>反正你不能丢下我。否则的话我绝对会在你离开之前，去舔鹰身女妖的屁股。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But you raise a good point.  You don't keep me around for my brain.  Maybe it's best I don't think at all.</Source>
      <Dest>可是你提了个好主意。我这脑筋跟不上你的节奏，所以我还是省省吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can step on us, poison us, and throw us in the oven and we'll still be in your pantry come morning.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以践踏我们，毒害我们，把我们扔进火炉里。而到了第二天早上，我们仍会出现在你的厨房里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why not? If she had the coin, it would have been the easiest pocket I ever fished.  But why aim low, when Black-Briar Manor casts such a long shadow.</Source>
      <Dest>为什么不呢？如果她有硬币，这会是我最轻松的一次扒窃了，但为什么目标定得这么低，当黑荆棘别墅投下那长长的阴影。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then we're both fools.   But I'd rather not be a dead one.  So I'm getting out of here. If you aren't gonna help, then stay and keep Bjartur company.</Source>
      <Dest>那我们都是傻瓜 。但我可不想死。所以我将会离开这里。如果你不打算帮忙，那就呆在那里继续跟Bjartur做伴吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But this isn't the time to talk.  I'm getting out of here. If you aren't gonna help, then stay and keep Bjartur company.</Source>
      <Dest>但这不是聊天的时候。我得离开这里。如果你不打算帮忙 ，那就呆在这儿和Bjartur做伴儿吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You did what you had to.  Doesn't mean I have to like it.  Yeah, I don't care much for politics, or who owns what.  Neither do my fingers.</Source>
      <Dest>你做了你必须做的事情，并不意味着我也要去喜欢它。是，我不怎么关心政治，也不关心谁拥有着什么。 【这些我都不会去做的。】</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sorry, but I've been cooped up in here long enough. This little bird is about to take flight.  If you're going to make to trouble, then make it.  </Source>
      <Dest>对不起，但我已经被困在这里足够久的了。而你这只小鸟想要飞走。如果你正准备闹些事儿的话，就去干吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if it makes you feel better, I agree with your choice.  The Forsworn lost their home, and I know how that is.  I know it ain't easy.</Source>
      <Dest>但如果这能让你感觉好些，我同意你的选择。这些弃誓者失去了家园，我知道这是怎么回事儿，我也知道这并不容易。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe the darkness blends into a single color, and I don't see the value of one shadow over another.  The eyes tell lies.</Source>
      <Dest>有可能黑暗已经融合为一种单一的色彩，我无法发现重阴叠影的价值。有时候眼见并不为实。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>See, while you were gone, I learned all about these snowbacks that live in Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>瞧，你离开的这些天，我了解了这些生活在松加德的北方佬的一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, kind of. Things change when your eyes aren't in the way. Take blood, for instance.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，诸如此类。当眼睛不再碍事的时候事情会改变许多。就拿血来说吧，举个例子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's because you're like me.  We're both a couple of cockroaches. </Source>
      <Dest>(偷笑)因为你跟我一个样。我俩就是一对儿蟑螂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well that's stupid.  You mean to tell me that dragon isn't big enough for the both of us?</Source>
      <Dest>真蠢，你难道想告诉我对我们两个人来说龙还不够大么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What, you want a prize?  Go ask a Jarl.  I don't care much for politics, or who owns what.  Neither do my fingers.</Source>
      <Dest>什么？你想要赏钱？找领主要去。我根本不关心政治，也不关心谁的得失。我偷东西时也不管这么多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Even in the dimmest, darkest caves, there's shadows made by torchlight, and every shade has its own shape, color, and coolness.</Source>
      <Dest>即使在最为昏暗幽黑的洞穴中，都有火炬映出的影子在闪动，而每一个影子都有它自己的形状、颜色、与温度。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You run that by Maven? Seems to me she's the one running things.  Still.</Source>
      <Dest>你跟玛雯这么说了？在我看来她仍是那个管事儿的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not when I was married to the thief.</Source>
      <Dest>不是我嫁给小偷的那时候.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What we do is beyond that. I don't even feel like a thief. I feel like an adventurer.</Source>
      <Dest>我们要做的比那更甚。我甚至不觉得像个盗贼。更像是个冒险家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's what happens when I'm not around to keep you honest.  In fact, if I were you, I would never leave me again.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我不在你身边督促你保持诚实时会发生的事。事实上，如果我是你，我永远都不会再离开我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I talked to a fence I know, and he says there's even crazy people who give up their fortunes to collect stuff like that.</Source>
      <Dest>我有跟一个认识的销赃犯聊起过，他说，真的会有疯子愿意倾家荡产来收集那种东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, really?  Why doesn't the Empire have one of those?  Probably why they lost the war.  Idiots.</Source>
      <Dest>哇噢，真的？为什么帝国没有弄到一个这玩意？活该他们被打败。笨蛋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah. Just figured I should come clean about something I said before.  It wasn't exactly a lie, but it wasn't the whole truth.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊。不过我觉得我得先对以前叙述的那个故事做一个澄清。我那时说的并不全是谎言，但也并不全是真的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just a bunch of shield-strangers is more like it.   What do you even know about them?  Do you even know the ugly one's favorite color?  Mine's black.</Source>
      <Dest>而他们呢，要说是一帮【盾牌陌生人】反倒更适合一些。对于他们你又知道些什么呢？难道说你还说得上来最丑的那个最喜欢的颜色？我最喜欢的颜色是黑色。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like I told you the day we met.  We're family.  And if this dragon is too lazy to carry the both of us, then find another one and I'll ride that.</Source>
      <Dest>正如我们见面时，我告诉你的一样。我们是加入。如果这头龙懒得驮我们两个人，那我再去找一头坐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh?  Works for me, sunshine.  Got a better chance going through you than Ahtar's axe.</Source>
      <Dest>哦？我没问题，sunshine。比起阿塔的斧头，你会得到一个更好的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But she's the biggest, fattest, and ugliest one.  What, you're going to tell me size isn't everything?</Source>
      <Dest>但她是最大，最胖，最丑的人。什么，你要告诉我的尺寸并不是一切？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But they're not really family, are they?  They're not like you and me.  A shield-sister isn't like an oath-sister.</Source>
      <Dest>但他们不是真正的家人，不是吗？他们不像你与我。盾牌姐妹可不像誓约姐妹那样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I could see, maybe the treasure at the end of the hall is too tempting to walk a crooked line.  So I walk straight into a trap.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我看得见,或许因为那些宝藏太吸引人使我沿直线走了过去.所以我就踩中陷阱里去了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who?</Source>
      <Dest>谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look at Vex and Tonilia, spending all day in that old sewer. I don't want to end up like them.</Source>
      <Dest>看看威克斯和托尼利亚，整天待在那老旧的下水沟里。我不想变成她们那样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But you've let me be your shadow since day one.  You let me walk with eyes open.  And well, I'm just trying to say...thanks for that. </Source>
      <Dest>但自从第一天起，你就让我如影随同跟着你。你让我走路的时候睁大眼睛。所以，我只是想说……谢谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe for some.  But I'm not the kind of artist who paints.  For me, the eyes see too much.  </Source>
      <Dest>也许对某些人是的。但我可不是那种画画的艺术家。对我来说，眼睛就已经看到的够多了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, well have you met a mudcrab that can pick a lock with a rusty nail using nothing but her teeth?  </Source>
      <Dest>河蟹，锈色的钳子，天赋异禀光用牙就能开锁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But you didn't get anything did you?  I can tell by that stupid question of yours.</Source>
      <Dest>但你一无所获是吧？我可以回应你那愚蠢的问题.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It won't do us any good to let it stew in that 7000 step throat hole.</Source>
      <Dest>把它闷到7000 step throat hole对我们没有任何好处的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Truth is, that was the last I ever saw of him.  He disowned me.  My own father.  Ever since then it's been hard to trust anyone.  </Source>
      <Dest>实际上，那便是我见他的最后一眼，我的父亲，他断绝了我们的父子关系。自那以后，我便再难相信任何人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought you said you like fast men. Did you see Wulfgar's Whirlwind Sprint?</Source>
      <Dest>我想你说过你喜欢速度快的男人，你有没有见过Wulfgar的旋风冲刺？（阳痿早泄？）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought you said you like fast men. Did you see Wulfgar's Whirlwind Sprint?</Source>
      <Dest>我想你说过你喜欢速度快的男人，你有没有见过Wulfgar的旋风冲刺？（阳痿早泄？）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vex and Tonilia get out at night.  We just don't notice.  They're thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>Vex 和 Tonilia 趁黑出动。我们只是没注意。他们是贼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vex and Tonilia get out at night.  We just don't notice.  They're thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>Vex 和 Tonilia 趁黑出动。我们只是没注意。他们是贼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vex and Tonilia get out at night.  We just don't notice.  They're thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>Vex 和 Tonilia 趁黑出动。我们只是没注意。他们是贼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's important to have a place to come back to.  Mine's a tavern.</Source>
      <Dest>关键得有个落脚的地方。我选择旅馆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's important to have a place to come back to.  Mine's a tavern.</Source>
      <Dest>关键得有个落脚的地方。我选择旅馆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's important to have a place to come back to.  Mine's a tavern.</Source>
      <Dest>关键得有个落脚的地方。我选择旅馆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's important to have a place to come back to.  Mine's a tavern.</Source>
      <Dest>关键得有个落脚的地方。我选择旅馆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just be sure I get my cut.</Source>
      <Dest>我得确定我拿得到我的那一份。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just be sure I get my cut.</Source>
      <Dest>我得确定我拿得到我的那一份。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Blood has a smell that's undetectable at best.</Source>
      <Dest>闻起来没有血腥味最好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Blood has a smell that's undetectable at best.</Source>
      <Dest>闻起来没有血腥味最好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Blood has a smell that's undetectable at best.</Source>
      <Dest>闻起来没有血腥味最好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's your plan?  You're just going to keep following me?</Source>
      <Dest>所以那就是你的计画？就只是继续跟着我？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's your plan?  You're just going to keep following me?</Source>
      <Dest>所以那就是你的计画？就只是继续跟着我？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's your plan?  You're just going to keep following me?</Source>
      <Dest>所以那就是你的计画？就只是继续跟着我？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's your plan?  You're just going to keep following me?</Source>
      <Dest>所以那就是你的计画？就只是继续跟着我？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's your plan?  You're just going to keep following me?</Source>
      <Dest>所以那就是你的计画？就只是继续跟着我？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sundas is a better name. The afternoon sun is better than any morning.</Source>
      <Dest>桑达斯是个好名字。午后的太阳比早上的要好得多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wish you would stay out of my "pantry."  You eat all my food.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望你能离我的“储藏室”远一点，你都快把我的食物吃光了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wish you would stay out of my "pantry."  You eat all my food.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望你能离我的“储藏室”远一点，你都快把我的食物吃光了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where will you go?</Source>
      <Dest>你要去哪儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where will you go?</Source>
      <Dest>你要去哪儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Clairvoyance is an imprecise skill.</Source>
      <Dest>洞察术并不是一个很精准的技能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Clairvoyance is an imprecise skill.</Source>
      <Dest>洞察术并不是一个很精准的技能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Clairvoyance is an imprecise skill.</Source>
      <Dest>洞察术并不是一个很精准的技能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that you're free, do you have a place to stay?</Source>
      <Dest>既然已经自由了，你有地方可去吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that you're free, do you have a place to stay?</Source>
      <Dest>既然已经自由了，你有地方可去吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that you're free, do you have a place to stay?</Source>
      <Dest>既然已经自由了，你有地方可去吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that you're free, do you have a place to stay?</Source>
      <Dest>既然已经自由了，你有地方可去吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that you're free, do you have a place to stay?</Source>
      <Dest>既然已经自由了，你有地方可去吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that you're free, do you have a place to stay?</Source>
      <Dest>既然已经自由了，你有地方可去吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's simple arithmetic. A lifetime of jobs is worth more than Maven's fortune.</Source>
      <Dest>这是个简单的算术。一辈子的工作可比玛雯的财富更值钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's simple arithmetic. A lifetime of jobs is worth more than Maven's fortune.</Source>
      <Dest>这是个简单的算术。一辈子的工作可比玛雯的财富更值钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright, you fooled me. Now stay in your cage and serve out your sentence.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，你耍我。那就在你的笼子里呆到刑满释放吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You got what you deserved, criminal.</Source>
      <Dest>你罪有应得，罪犯！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You got what you deserved, criminal.</Source>
      <Dest>你罪有应得，罪犯！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You got what you deserved, criminal.</Source>
      <Dest>你罪有应得，罪犯！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You move well. I hardly noticed a difference.</Source>
      <Dest>表演的不错啊，完全看不出区别嘛！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You move well. I hardly noticed a difference.</Source>
      <Dest>表演的不错啊，完全看不出区别嘛！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You move well. I hardly noticed a difference.</Source>
      <Dest>表演的不错啊，完全看不出区别嘛！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You move well. I hardly noticed a difference.</Source>
      <Dest>表演的不错啊，完全看不出区别嘛！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No, because I'm not a no good dirty thief.</Source>
      <Dest>不，因为我作为一个卑鄙的小偷还不够称职。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't you stay here and plan our next heist.</Source>
      <Dest>要不要留下来就下次抢劫行动商量个计划。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't you stay here and plan our next heist.</Source>
      <Dest>要不要留下来就下次抢劫行动商量个计划。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't you stay here and plan our next heist.</Source>
      <Dest>要不要留下来就下次抢劫行动商量个计划。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bonds are forged in battle, not through conversation.</Source>
      <Dest>感情是在战斗中建立的，不是在聊天里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bonds are forged in battle, not through conversation.</Source>
      <Dest>感情是在战斗中建立的，不是在聊天里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bonds are forged in battle, not through conversation.</Source>
      <Dest>感情是在战斗中建立的，不是在聊天里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly did you steal from Maven?</Source>
      <Dest>你到底从Maven那里偷了 什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hope this story ends with someone getting murdered.  I like murder.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望这个故事以某人被杀结尾，我就喜欢杀人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hope this story ends with someone getting murdered.  I like murder.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望这个故事以某人被杀结尾，我就喜欢杀人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about now? Would you categorize yourself as stubborn?</Source>
      <Dest>现在呢？你可以把自己归入二货那一类了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about now? Would you categorize yourself as stubborn?</Source>
      <Dest>现在呢？你可以把自己归入二货那一类了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about now? Would you categorize yourself as stubborn?</Source>
      <Dest>现在呢？你可以把自己归入二货那一类了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whatever, I didn't want to be part of their stupid guild anyway.  Not when it answers to some old hag instead of a real thief.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何, 我都不会加入他们那蠢工会.  尤其是当下他们用一些老妖婆顶替真正盗贼的时候.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't have much going on.  You're the most exciting thing around here.  Not to mention you're family.</Source>
      <Dest>没有什么事能引起我的兴趣. 这里只有你最能激动人心.  更何况我们是一家人.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We used to move from farm to farm, begging for work, praying to Zenithar we'd have enough for a roof over our heads.</Source>
      <Dest>我们曾今从一个搬到另一个农场, 找着活儿，向泽尼萨尔祷告我们能有一个栖息之处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I'll go unnoticed whenever I stalk our enemies.  They won't know it isn't their own shadow until my blade sends their souls to the void.</Source>
      <Dest>我隐蔽而诡秘的潜近我们的敌人。直到我的利刃将他们的灵魂送入虚无，他们才意识到那不是自己的影子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My bones are your blood, and your blood is my bones.</Source>
      <Dest>吾骨为汝血，汝血为吾骨.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My bones are your blood, and your blood is my bones.</Source>
      <Dest>吾骨为汝血，汝血为吾骨.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?  Does it have your name on it?  Besides, I thought we were sharing.  We're blood siblings by oath.  My blood's your blood, and so is my spit.</Source>
      <Dest>什么！？上面有你的名字？另外，我还以为我们在分享。我们是拜了把子的兄弟。我的血就是你的血，我的口水也一样！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe it's just you who can't smell it.  I think there's a potion for that.  Next time we're in an alchemist shop, I'll steal it for you.</Source>
      <Dest>恐怕不光是你闻不见它。我想应该有种药治这个的。下次我们去炼金药店，我帮你搞点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But you're going to have a hard time convincing anyone you had nothing to do with this.  Either way, I'm leaving.</Source>
      <Dest>不过到时候你又很难向每个人解释你真的对此无能为力。不管怎么样，我得走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But the eyes tell lies, my friend, the eyes tell lies.</Source>
      <Dest>但这眼睛在说谎，我的朋友，这眼睛在说谎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't be stupid, you know that's not what I meant.  We do more than just steal.</Source>
      <Dest>别犯傻,你知道那不是我的意思。我们能做的不仅仅是偷窃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That second is the difference between being fast and acting rushed.  The eyes tempt you into moving too quickly.</Source>
      <Dest>其次是速度变得更快和冒进的区别。  注意力集中会让你变得更快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I figure some crowded city like Windhelm would be a nice place to start.  Always wanted to clean out the Palace of the Kings.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得一些像风盔城那样拥挤的城市是个开始的好地方。我一直想清理众王之殿来着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We get drunk, we kill some people, maybe do a good deed, and then get drunk some more.</Source>
      <Dest>我们喝多了，我们杀了几个人，也许干了点儿好事，然后又多喝了不少。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you don't need me right now, then I guess I'll have to keep the riches to myself.  And it's a great day for a heist.</Source>
      <Dest>可你现在要是不需要我，那宝物我就只好独吞啦。今天是个打劫的好日子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you don't need me right now, then I guess I'll have to keep the riches to myself.  And it's a great day for a heist.</Source>
      <Dest>可你现在要是不需要我，那宝物我就只好独吞啦。今天是个打劫的好日子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Actually, they had planned on naming me after the priestess.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，他们本打算指定我继承祭司的位子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Besides, I said the vows at the Temple of Mara, and I promised Jade I'd do my best not to piss on them.  Just breaking them was a good compromise.</Source>
      <Dest>另外，我在玛拉神殿发下了誓，对洁承诺，会尽自己最大努力的不去冲他们撒尿。光是打残他们就够了。做出这个妥协的我是多么善良啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's not real family.  That's just a bunch of people wearing the same clothes.  So don't forget who's really got your back.</Source>
      <Dest>那不是真正的家庭。只是一群人穿着同样的衣服罢了。所以不要忘了是谁真正把你带回来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh...I like fast men.  Not old, wrinkly grandpas who move around by screaming.</Source>
      <Dest>啊……我喜欢动作麻利的人，而不是那些边走边尖叫的脆弱老头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whatever.</Source>
      <Dest>无所谓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You practically had to yank the purse from their belt for them to notice.</Source>
      <Dest>为了让他们注意，你可能不得不突然从他们的皮带上扯下钱包。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm cautious. Not because I want to be, but because I've got no choice.  It takes me a second to read the shadows around me.</Source>
      <Dest>谨慎并非我所愿，而是因为我无路可退。谨慎让我在极短的时间内察觉到了四周潜伏的阴影。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A girl can get used to that kind of stuff.  So I rather stick with you and do it some more.</Source>
      <Dest>一个女孩可以习惯这种事。所以我当然缠上你了，再多干几次吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, I know people say that stuff all the time, but I mean it.  Your blood is my blood.</Source>
      <Dest>是，我知道人们都在说那事。但我是认真的，我们亲密无间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There isn't a lot of things in this world I take seriously, but blood is one of them.</Source>
      <Dest>这世上我认真对待的东西不多，”血与火“算一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, except these jesters took you in after you ran a couple errands.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，除非这些小丑们在你跑完一些差事后拉你入伙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So if you find a half-eaten piece of bread roll in your sack, that's because I'm leaving you the rest.  No need to thank me, we're family.</Source>
      <Dest>所以如果你在口袋里发现一个吃了一半儿的面包片，那是我吃剩下留给你的。别客气，我们是一家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You sure about that?  I was starting to like you, and now you have to go and ruin it by talking.</Source>
      <Dest>你确定是那样？我过去开始喜欢你，而现在你却说必须要去毁了它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Funny you bring up taverns, because that's where I'd ply my trade.  Drunks made for good practice. </Source>
      <Dest>说起酒馆那可是很有趣的，因为那里是我一直干活的地方。醉鬼们可是很好的连手对象。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course.  We're accomplices, right?  No, more than that.  Like I said, bones and blood.  You and me, we're family.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。我们是帮凶，对不对？不，不止这些。就像我说的，骨子里和血液中。你和我，我们是一家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stubborn yes, patient, no.  Being born was the first and last time I was ever late for anything.</Source>
      <Dest>坚决地肯定，忍让地…否定。打出生以来，第一次也是最后一次为某件事迟到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>First time you smell it, you'll know what I'm talking about.  Don't drink it though.  Tastes like a rusty dagger.</Source>
      <Dest>你第一次闻到的时候，你就会知道我在说什么。但是别去喝，那玩意尝起来就像生锈的匕首。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can't blame the priestess.  Two out of three isn't bad.  Two blind eyes, one wrong date.</Source>
      <Dest>不能怪女祭司，至少三分之二还不坏。两个是盲人，还有一个则是记错了日期。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That depends. Which time?</Source>
      <Dest>那要看，什么时候？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, you're not getting rid of me that easily. I owe you my life. That makes us family. Oath sisters.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，休想轻易地摆脱我。我还欠你一条命呢。我们是家人不是吗。我们是誓约姐妹啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's right.  If you say the word, I'll be your shadow.  Might just follow you anyway, even if you don't say it.</Source>
      <Dest>是的。只要你说一句话，我就会是你的影子。即使你什么也不说，我也会坚定的追随你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That was the last time I was late for anything.  Now I'm just making up for lost time.</Source>
      <Dest>这是最后一次我为什么事情迟到了。现在我只会弥补失去的时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So if you need a little advice on how to best relieve these townsfolk of their burdens, just ask.</Source>
      <Dest>所以，如果你需要一个关于如何减轻这些居民负担的小小忠告，那就请问吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Seems to me you can just polish a few swords and pretty soon everyone's ready to call you kin.</Source>
      <Dest>在我看来，你只需要把你的剑磨得铮亮，那马上就会一大堆人等着来跟你称兄道弟了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that your way of trying to get rid of me? (Laughs) That's pretty good.  Looks like you're learning.</Source>
      <Dest>那就是你用来摆脱我的办法么？(笑声) 棒极了。看来你还是有长进的啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or maybe now I'm making up for lost time.  But I don't like waiting.  I like fast jobs, fast hands and fast men.  </Source>
      <Dest>或者我现在可以化妆来节省时间.  但是我不喜欢等待.  我喜欢干脆的工作, 熟练的家伙和做事利落的人.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know that!  I just...I just couldn't help myself.  It's not my fault the stupid bitch has to flaunt her wealth in front of me.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道！我只是……我只是情不自禁。是那个愚蠢的婊子自己在我面前显摆她的财富的，这不是我的错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll bring you to my side eventually.  You'll see the truth in the darkness.  But rest assured, I was the victim here.</Source>
      <Dest>我最终会把你带回我身边的。你会看到黑暗中的真实。但请放心，我是这里的受害者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although that might be the first place they look.  Maybe it's best I go to the last.  Winterhold.  Soul gems are as valuable as any diamond.</Source>
      <Dest>估计这里是他们第一个要查看的地方。但愿也是最后一个地方吧。冬堡，在这里，灵魂宝石的价值和任何珠宝别无二致。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, you're not getting rid of me that easily.  I owe you my life.  That makes us family.  Oath brother and sister.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，你没那么容易摆脱我。我欠你一条命。我们是一家人。我们是誓言兄弟姐妹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But look at you now.  You've got guile, and you've got cunning.  And you've got your oath-sister to thank.</Source>
      <Dest>但看看现在的你吧。你变得狡诈了，变得圆滑了，而这一切你都得感谢你的誓言姐妹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I remember the day I tricked you into rescuing me.  I had you fingered as some naive little milk-drinker.</Source>
      <Dest>我记得曾欺骗过你去救我。我因那如同未戒奶小baby般的幼稚而受到你的谴责。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anyone tries to break that up, and their blood gets spilled.  So, what do you say?  We heading out?</Source>
      <Dest>任何试图拆散我们的人都会血溅当场。所以，你想说什么呢？我们该出发了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, are we sure those shouts are coming out of their mouths?  Seems to me the other end makes more sense.</Source>
      <Dest>我的意思是，你确定那些吼声是从他们嘴里发出的么。感觉像是从另一面出来的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ever try stealing the clothes off a man's back?</Source>
      <Dest>尝试过从后面偷一个人的衣服吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Horn of Jurgen Windcaller) You look like you're up to something.</Source>
      <Dest>（Jurgen Windcaller的号角）看来你已做好准备了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Horn of Jurgen Windcaller) You look like you're up to something.</Source>
      <Dest>（Jurgen Windcaller的号角）看来你已做好准备了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Horn of Jurgen Windcaller) You look like you're up to something.</Source>
      <Dest>（Jurgen Windcaller的号角）看来你已做好准备了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Horn of Jurgen Windcaller) You look like you're up to something.</Source>
      <Dest>（Jurgen Windcaller的号角）看来你已做好准备了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Horn of Jurgen Windcaller) You look like you're up to something.</Source>
      <Dest>（Jurgen Windcaller的号角）看来你已做好准备了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A sword is much harder to lift than a purse. How did you manage to take it?</Source>
      <Dest>一把剑可比钱包沉多了，你当初怎么带着它的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A sword is much harder to lift than a purse. How did you manage to take it?</Source>
      <Dest>一把剑可比钱包沉多了，你当初怎么带着它的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A sword is much harder to lift than a purse. How did you manage to take it?</Source>
      <Dest>一把剑可比钱包沉多了，你当初怎么带着它的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A sword is much harder to lift than a purse. How did you manage to take it?</Source>
      <Dest>一把剑可比钱包沉多了，你当初怎么带着它的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll get the door open and lead you out.</Source>
      <Dest>我将会把门弄开然后领你出去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll get the door open and lead you out.</Source>
      <Dest>我将会把门弄开然后领你出去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll get the door open and lead you out.</Source>
      <Dest>我将会把门弄开然后领你出去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Whatever, I don't listen to what you babble on about anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样，我不想听你的胡言乱语了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lover's quarrel? How ridiculously petty.</Source>
      <Dest>情侣吵架？多么荒唐而微不足道的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lover's quarrel? How ridiculously petty.</Source>
      <Dest>情侣吵架？多么荒唐而微不足道的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lover's quarrel? How ridiculously petty.</Source>
      <Dest>情侣吵架？多么荒唐而微不足道的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't come to help you escape. I just want to ask you some questions.</Source>
      <Dest>我并不是来帮你逃跑的。我只是想问你一些问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't come to help you escape. I just want to ask you some questions.</Source>
      <Dest>我并不是来帮你逃跑的。我只是想问你一些问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't come to help you escape. I just want to ask you some questions.</Source>
      <Dest>我并不是来帮你逃跑的。我只是想问你一些问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't come to help you escape. I just want to ask you some questions.</Source>
      <Dest>我并不是来帮你逃跑的。我只是想问你一些问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I love blood myself.  It's my favorite thing about murder.</Source>
      <Dest>我很喜欢鲜血，那是关于谋杀我最喜欢的部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I love blood myself.  It's my favorite thing about murder.</Source>
      <Dest>我很喜欢鲜血，那是关于谋杀我最喜欢的部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I love blood myself.  It's my favorite thing about murder.</Source>
      <Dest>我很喜欢鲜血，那是关于谋杀我最喜欢的部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sundas is a better name. The afternoon sun is better than any morning.</Source>
      <Dest>桑达斯是个好名字。午后的太阳比早上的要好得多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you steal from Black-Briar Manor?</Source>
      <Dest>你从黑荆棘酒庄偷了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, as long as you learned your lesson.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，但是記住你學到的教訓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, as long as you learned your lesson.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，但是記住你學到的教訓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any time, oath-sister.</Source>
      <Dest>随时都行，我的宣誓姐妹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They'll put you in jail for anything these days.</Source>
      <Dest>他们会为这几天的事情而把你扔进监狱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They'll put you in jail for anything these days.</Source>
      <Dest>他们会为这几天的事情而把你扔进监狱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. I'll go interrupt the guard like you asked.</Source>
      <Dest>好。我会像你请求的那样打断守卫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. I'll go interrupt the guard like you asked.</Source>
      <Dest>好。我会像你请求的那样打断守卫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alduin is dead.  The world is safe.  The next one will have to wait.</Source>
      <Dest>Alduin死了。天下和平，下一个人必将继续等待。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How about I give you a lockpick.</Source>
      <Dest>我给你一个开锁器怎么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How about I give you a lockpick.</Source>
      <Dest>我给你一个开锁器怎么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How about I give you a lockpick.</Source>
      <Dest>我给你一个开锁器怎么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And yet the real monster survived.  And no one was the wiser.</Source>
      <Dest>结果是那个真正得怪物还存活着，所有人都犯了蠢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And yet the real monster survived.  And no one was the wiser.</Source>
      <Dest>结果是那个真正得怪物还存活着，所有人都犯了蠢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And yet the real monster survived.  And no one was the wiser.</Source>
      <Dest>结果是那个真正得怪物还存活着，所有人都犯了蠢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And yet the real monster survived.  And no one was the wiser.</Source>
      <Dest>结果是那个真正得怪物还存活着，所有人都犯了蠢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think they bathe together.  They probably shout the dirt off each other.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认为他们会一起洗澡。他们可能会直接吼掉对方的污垢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not my fault.  I told you to go to Riften.  You never listen to anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>这事不怪我。我告訴你要去裂谷城。是你谁的话也听不进。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not my fault.  I told you to go to Riften.  You never listen to anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>这事不怪我。我告訴你要去裂谷城。是你谁的话也听不进。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not my fault.  I told you to go to Riften.  You never listen to anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>这事不怪我。我告訴你要去裂谷城。是你谁的话也听不进。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would Winterhold have been the better choice?</Source>
      <Dest>那么冬堡不是更好的选择吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would Winterhold have been the better choice?</Source>
      <Dest>那么冬堡不是更好的选择吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait. I need to ask you about a journal you stole.</Source>
      <Dest>等一下！我要问问关于你偷的一本日记的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait. I need to ask you about a journal you stole.</Source>
      <Dest>等一下！我要问问关于你偷的一本日记的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait. I need to ask you about a journal you stole.</Source>
      <Dest>等一下！我要问问关于你偷的一本日记的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait. I need to ask you about a journal you stole.</Source>
      <Dest>等一下！我要问问关于你偷的一本日记的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, we think the Thalmor are dragons in mortal form.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，我觉得那些梭默其实是龙化作人形的样子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, we think the Thalmor are dragons in mortal form.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，我觉得那些梭默其实是龙化作人形的样子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's a passageway two cells down. I can tell by the way the air comes through the wall. Probably got a Shadowmark on it too.</Source>
      <Dest>再走过两个房间就能看见通道了。我闻着空气的味道就能分辨出来。说不定上面还有个暗影标记呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You really are crazy.  Like voices in your head crazy.  Like talking to chickens crazy.  (Snickers) Well, that's fine with me.</Source>
      <Dest>你真的疯了。比如听到有声音脑中疯狂叫嚣，再比如着迷的和鸡说话。（嗤嗤的笑）很好，正合我意。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, I could've been out of here days ago, but I figured I'd wait for some hero to help me distract the guards. That's where you come in.</Source>
      <Dest>我要是能走，当然几天前就走了，可我发现必须要有个牛人帮我引开那些守卫。现在就看你啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Naturally.  Last I heard it wasn't infested with spiders like the Rift, or angry folks like Windhelm.  Just mages. </Source>
      <Dest>自然的，最后我听说没有像裂谷城一样上面爬满蜘蛛,，或者像风盔城那些愤怒的民众，仅仅只是法师。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In this case though, the thief stole from me and himself.  And spending your wife's coin is apparently not a crime.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然在这种情况下，贼把我和他的都偷了一遍，但花你老婆的钱显然不是犯罪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, the whole thing's kind of weird.  A bunch of old men living together, bathing together...On second thought, it's not weird, it's gross.</Source>
      <Dest>我是说，整个事情感觉都有些古怪。一群老男人一起住，一起洗澡……再一想，那不是古怪，是讨厌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great.  Now that that's settled, let's do a little fishing, shall we?</Source>
      <Dest>太好了。现在问题都解决了，让我们做一个小渔港，好吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, and?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，然后呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's right.  In Solitude, it doesn't take any missing gold for you to be accused of being a thief.</Source>
      <Dest>就是那样，在独孤城，你可不能拿走任何丢失的金币，否则会被指控是小偷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The robes, the shouting, the monastery...it's all part of the plan.</Source>
      <Dest>长袍，吼声，僧侣……都是计划的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's pretty smart.  They get these "pilgrims" to come up here, then they tell them to go get their hands on something valuable.</Source>
      <Dest>真聪明。他们忽悠这些“朝圣者”来这儿，然后告诉他们要用自己的双手得到一些有价值的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sibbi was always a cute one.  His face would look great on a fence post. I'm kidding, of course.</Source>
      <Dest>Sibbi一直是个可爱的家伙。他的脸紧贴着篱笆的时候很好看。当然，我在开玩笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something about married people can't steal from each other.  If what he did isn't theft, then I'm a priest.</Source>
      <Dest>就是些关于结婚的双方不能从对方那里偷东西的事儿。如果他没偷东西，那我就是个牧师了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's because I still need my gear. There's a passageway two cells down, which probably has a Shadowmark. We need to break into that one.</Source>
      <Dest>这是因为我还想要回我的装备呢。两个牢房下面有一个通道，边上可能会有个暗影标记。我们需要进到那个通道里去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At some point though, the guild turned their eyes elsewhere. Things settled down, and for a moment I thought of doing the same.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然某些时候，公会把他们的目光放向了别处，但当事情安顿下来，我一时间也想做同样的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mages are like bandits.  Always good to have a couple around to blame things on, in case a job gets bloody.</Source>
      <Dest>法师跟强盗一个样。【两个人双双抱怨周围的东西总归是好的，至少这些事代替了血腥的工作。】</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One night we went to the temple, woke Jade up, and asked her to marry us.  Had to be her, being a fellow cutpurse. Then we ran.  And kept running.</Source>
      <Dest>那个晚上我们去了神殿，把洁叫醒，让她嫁给我们。作为小偷的同伙，她不得不同意。然后我们就跑了，不停地跑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I just had to act drunk and fall in his arms.  Wasn't even theft, as far as I'm considered.  I'd say he still owes me a septim or too.</Source>
      <Dest>然后我醉醺醺的倒在他怀里了。就我来说，这不算是偷窃。但我得说他还欠我一两个金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You want a killer, go find a Dark Brotherhood assassin.  But if you're smart, you'll keep me around to pick his pocket.</Source>
      <Dest>你想要一个杀手？去找一名黑暗兄弟会的刺客。但如果你够聪明，你会让我去掏他的口袋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I told you Maven Black-Briar won't let me set foot in that town unless it came in a sack.</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉你，黑荆棘玛雯是不会让我进这个镇的，除非把我装进麻袋里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What lesson?  He stole from me, and I paid him back in kind.  Only problem was his theft wasn't technically stealing.</Source>
      <Dest>什么教训？他偷了我东西，我让他偿还，唯一的问题在于他的行为不是严格意义上的偷窃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But don't think you didn't blow an opportunity back there.  Not every day you can come back from Sovngarde alive.</Source>
      <Dest>但别以为你没能把握住一个回到那里的机会。不是每一天你都能从松加德活着回来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm going to fetch my gear. There's a passageway two cells down. Might be noisy getting inside, so make sure to stamp your feet or something.</Source>
      <Dest>我要去取我的装备。下去两个牢房有个通道。也去进去后会很吵，所以确保跺跺你的脚或者做些其他什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, they wouldn't need a plan if they just came down from the mountain every now and then.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，如果他们不时地从山上下来的话就不需要计划了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hemming's the type to carry his weapons to bed with him, so I figured the best way to lift the sword was to have him invite me to bed.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道的，而且赫明是那种睡觉都带着武器的类型，所以我估摸着拿到那把剑的最好办法是让他邀我上床。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You sure? A lockpick was all I really needed. Well, if you're going to open it yourself, get the key off of one of the guards.</Source>
      <Dest>你确定？我倒是只要一个开锁器就能搞定了。好吧，如果你想自己开的话，去守卫身上把钥匙弄过来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right.  You know you heard every word.  But yeah, I get it.  Save the pillow talk and get back to doing what you do best.  Well, I plan on it.</Source>
      <Dest>得，看来你都听见了。 不过，嗯哼，我懂的。 回去该干嘛干嘛去，别想吹枕边风。。。嗯，就这么定了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're crazy.  I like crazy.  I like you. But you're making a mistake if you think I'm some cold-blooded assassin.</Source>
      <Dest>你很疯狂，而我喜欢疯狂。所以我挺喜欢你。但如果你认为我是个冷血的刺客那你就错了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well in that case, maybe I ought to sit my rear end back in this cage. You aren't with the Brotherhood, are you? I suppose they don't ask questions.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，如果是那样的话，或许我应该坐回牢房里去。你不是兄弟会的人对吧？我猜他们是不会问问题的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that was easy.  Cry for help and the white knights come running to the rescue.</Source>
      <Dest>哎，很简单嘛。大声哭喊着救命然后就有白衣骑士冲过来救啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No offense to Argonian names, but Swamp-Breath-Wusha puts the wrong kind of fear in your enemies.</Source>
      <Dest>全然不是想要嘲笑亚龙人的名字，不过“有着沼泽之息的乌沙”这个名字，会让你的敌人们对你产生一种异样的恐惧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Want my help? It's gonna cost you. Don't want my help? It's gonna cost you more.</Source>
      <Dest>想要我帮忙吗？那你可得大出血了。不要我帮忙？你会为此付出更多的代价。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Want my help? It's gonna cost you. Don't want my help? It's gonna cost you more.</Source>
      <Dest>想要我帮忙吗？那你可得大出血了。不要我帮忙？你会为此付出更多的代价。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No. Wait, have you?</Source>
      <Dest>不，等一下，你呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The least you could've done is stolen something.  It was crazy not to.</Source>
      <Dest>你能做的事情唯有去偷些什么东西，如果不那么做的话你会疯的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's as good as giving me the key. But I can't just walk out of here dressed like this. We have to get my stuff too.</Source>
      <Dest>就像给了我钥匙一样好。可我不能穿成这样就走出去。我们还得去拿我的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's what happens when I'm not around to keep you honest.  In fact, if I were you, I would never leave me again.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我不在你身边督促你保持诚实时会发生的事。事实上，如果我是你，我永远都不会再离开我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you're sneaking into their nest basically to find proof.   Sounds like a plan.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你是打算潜行到他们的居所去搜集情报。听起来倒是一个不错的计划。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You go head off the guard and just keep flapping your gums. Then follow me down the passageway.</Source>
      <Dest>你直接朝着卫兵的方向走就好，要一直拍着头套的粘合处。然后跟着我走通道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This time I was after a sword, one of Hemming's.</Source>
      <Dest>这次我是在找一把剑，是属于 Hemming 的剑之一。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Because I'm getting out of here one way or the other, and I suggest you make it easier on the both of us.</Source>
      <Dest>反正我总会找到条路从这儿出去的，所以我希望你能选个对你我都好的选项。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Because I'm getting out of here one way or the other, and I suggest you make it easier on the both of us.</Source>
      <Dest>反正我总会找到条路从这儿出去的，所以我希望你能选个对你我都好的选项。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who's asking? Seems to me the only thing I know will get you killed for saying it.</Source>
      <Dest>谁在说话？我只知道你肯定会杀掉说话的那玩意儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm not a killer.  I'm a thief.  Anyone can steal from a dead man.  Being a cutpurse takes skill, and guile.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是一个杀手。我是一个小偷。谁都能从死人那儿偷东西。但要做一个贼不仅需要足够的技巧，还需要足够的狡猾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, okay.  That makes sense.  I think.  That's how they've been hiding all this time.  Changing their shadows.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，好吧。我想那气消了。这就是他们总能够隐藏自己的原因。（通过）变换他们的影子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh!  That's even worse!  Next time you get a visual like that, do me a favor and keep it to yourself.  Some of us prefer being blind.</Source>
      <Dest>啊!  没比这更糟的!  下次你搞的那么难看,就留着你自己用吧.  我们宁愿眼睛都瞎了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I guess what it comes down to is this. You need me, and I sort of need you, but not really.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我猜事情会变成这样。你会需要我，而我可能也会需要你，但并不会很需要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I guess what it comes down to is this. You need me, and I sort of need you, but not really.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我猜事情会变成这样。你会需要我，而我可能也会需要你，但并不会很需要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The problem was he and Maven were like a child and a fresh thumb.  They call people milk-drinkers in Skyrim, but Hemming is the real deal.</Source>
      <Dest>问题是，他和Maven就像一个孩子和一个新手。在天际他们被称为乳臭未干，但 Hemming是实打实的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not me, but I think those gray-bearded mouth breathers are.  I mean, you do realize what they asked you to do, right?</Source>
      <Dest>我可不是，我只把灰胡子的话当耳边风。我是说，你知道他们要你去干嘛的，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I'm gonna need a lockpick too. These things don't open themselves. But yeah, anything to slow down the guard will help.</Source>
      <Dest>那好，我还缺一个开锁器，那些东西可不会自个儿打开，顺便，你要是能拖住守卫那也是妥妥的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I see what you're saying...You think I should chop her up first?  Maybe make a nice little family portrait?</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我明白了……你的意思是说先把她剁了？也许做个漂亮的小半身像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Didn't seem so at the time.  He was a fisherman.  Not fishing pockets, but actual fish. Left it all behind when I stuck my hand in Maven's honey jar.</Source>
      <Dest>那时候还不怎么样。他那时候是个渔民。不是掏人腰包，而是真真正正的打渔。当我的手卡在玛雯的蜂蜜罐里之后就什么都顾不得了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The truth is I joined them to destroy them.  You're going to help me.</Source>
      <Dest>其实我加入他们是为了消灭他们，你要帮助我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>At least you aren't in prison. Windhelm is less kind to thieves than Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>至少你不在牢里。对贼来说风盔可比独孤城差远了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>At least you aren't in prison. Windhelm is less kind to thieves than Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>至少你不在牢里。对贼来说风盔可比独孤城差远了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Goldenglow Estate job.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲金芒庄园任务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Goldenglow Estate job.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲金芒庄园任务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Goldenglow Estate job.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲金芒庄园任务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Goldenglow Estate job.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲金芒庄园任务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Goldenglow Estate job.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲金芒庄园任务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was it?</Source>
      <Dest>那是啥?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was it?</Source>
      <Dest>那是啥?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was it?</Source>
      <Dest>那是啥?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I do, but it's not something I can just explain.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道，但是我不知道如何去解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then there wasn't anything particularly valuable inside.</Source>
      <Dest>那里面没有任何有价值的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then there wasn't anything particularly valuable inside.</Source>
      <Dest>那里面没有任何有价值的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then there wasn't anything particularly valuable inside.</Source>
      <Dest>那里面没有任何有价值的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Passion stokes fires of all kinds, some more dangerous than others.</Source>
      <Dest>冲动是魔鬼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Passion stokes fires of all kinds, some more dangerous than others.</Source>
      <Dest>冲动是魔鬼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Passion stokes fires of all kinds, some more dangerous than others.</Source>
      <Dest>冲动是魔鬼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And it's good to see you?  I really don't know what you're fishing for here.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴见到你  我真不知道你在这钓什么。（这句待议）.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And it's good to see you?  I really don't know what you're fishing for here.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴见到你  我真不知道你在这钓什么。（这句待议）.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And it's good to see you?  I really don't know what you're fishing for here.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴见到你  我真不知道你在这钓什么。（这句待议）.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you steal from Black-Briar Manor?</Source>
      <Dest>你从黑荆棘酒庄偷了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you steal from Black-Briar Manor?</Source>
      <Dest>你从黑荆棘酒庄偷了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're my oath-sister, and my friend.  That's why I want you to stay.</Source>
      <Dest>你是我宣誓的姐妹，也是我的朋友，這就是為什麼我希望你可以留下來。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're my oath-sister, and my friend.  That's why I want you to stay.</Source>
      <Dest>你是我宣誓的姐妹，也是我的朋友，這就是為什麼我希望你可以留下來。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're my oath-sister, and my friend.  That's why I want you to stay.</Source>
      <Dest>你是我宣誓的姐妹，也是我的朋友，這就是為什麼我希望你可以留下來。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Let's just move on.</Source>
      <Dest>算了，我们走吧。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what happened exactly?</Source>
      <Dest>到底发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what happened exactly?</Source>
      <Dest>到底发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what happened exactly?</Source>
      <Dest>到底发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How dare you suggest we rob honest, hard-working townsfolk!</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么敢建议我们去抢劫诚实、勤奋的市民！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How dare you suggest we rob honest, hard-working townsfolk!</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么敢建议我们去抢劫诚实、勤奋的市民！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Mourning the dead, perhaps.  Dragons have been spotted in the area.</Source>
      <Dest>或许是对死者表示哀悼。龙已经侵入这个地区了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Mourning the dead, perhaps.  Dragons have been spotted in the area.</Source>
      <Dest>或许是对死者表示哀悼。龙已经侵入这个地区了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Diplomatic Immunity) You look a bit confused about this next mission.</Source>
      <Dest>（外交豁免） 对接下来的任务你似乎有些迷惑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Diplomatic Immunity) You look a bit confused about this next mission.</Source>
      <Dest>（外交豁免） 对接下来的任务你似乎有些迷惑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you break in?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么闯进来的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you break in?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么闯进来的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you break in?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么闯进来的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the actual fishing part?</Source>
      <Dest>关于捕鱼的那部分是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the actual fishing part?</Source>
      <Dest>关于捕鱼的那部分是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the actual fishing part?</Source>
      <Dest>关于捕鱼的那部分是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you choose your victims?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么选择牺牲品的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you choose your victims?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么选择牺牲品的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you choose your victims?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么选择牺牲品的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Riften is always a home for thieves. The guild will provide you safe haven.</Source>
      <Dest>裂谷城一直是盗贼的老家，有公会可以给你提供安全庇护。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Riften is always a home for thieves. The guild will provide you safe haven.</Source>
      <Dest>裂谷城一直是盗贼的老家，有公会可以给你提供安全庇护。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Guild didn't warn you there would be consequences?</Source>
      <Dest>公会没有告知你会有后果？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Guild didn't warn you there would be consequences?</Source>
      <Dest>公会没有告知你会有后果？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Guild didn't warn you there would be consequences?</Source>
      <Dest>公会没有告知你会有后果？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wish I could, but I don't know how.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望自己有办法，可是没有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did your father do?</Source>
      <Dest>你父亲做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did your father do?</Source>
      <Dest>你父亲做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did your father do?</Source>
      <Dest>你父亲做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Seems like a perfectly healthy lifestyle to me.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来简直是极品健康生活方式啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Seems like a perfectly healthy lifestyle to me.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来简直是极品健康生活方式啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did your parents ever find out you were a thief?</Source>
      <Dest>你家人知道你在做贼了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did your parents ever find out you were a thief?</Source>
      <Dest>你家人知道你在做贼了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did your parents ever find out you were a thief?</Source>
      <Dest>你家人知道你在做贼了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It gets worse. That place was guarded better than a princess' maidenhead.</Source>
      <Dest>这更糟。要突破这地方可比破了公主的处还要难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No one can resist the sound of coin.  No sweeter music in all of Tamriel.</Source>
      <Dest>没人能抗拒硬币的叮当声，这是泰姆瑞尔大陆最美妙的音乐了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dad knew them his cabbage picking days were over. And I knew, that if I wanted to survive, I had to become a better thief.</Source>
      <Dest>爸爸知道他摘卷心菜的日子到头了。而我明白,如果我想活下去,就不得不成为一个更好的小偷。
</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The mead's probably sour too, and I bet everyone stinks of the dead.  In fact, the whole place sounds miserable.</Source>
      <Dest>蜜酒大概也酸了。我打赌每具尸体都烂的发臭了。事实上，所有地方都听上去很凄惨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know what it was or where it came from, but it fetched a good price.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道它是什么玩意儿或者它是从哪儿来的,但它应该能卖出个好价钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I snuck in from the docks, and used the long moonlight shadows to my advantage.  Better when there's some light to distract the eye.</Source>
      <Dest>我从港口哪里潜入，用月光下的长影有效隐蔽。要是附近有醒目的光源就更好</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ivarstead.  Lots of gullible pilgrims, but poor ones.  Shor's Stone, on the other hand, sits on the road to Riften.  </Source>
      <Dest>紫杉镇。这儿有很多轻信的朝圣者，但他们大都很穷。舒尔之石，在另一边，座落在通往裂谷城的道路上。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I became the best. Nothing more important than family.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我是最好的。没有东西比家庭更重要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only there was nothing.  I almost woke Aringoth up to demand where he kept his valuables.  Then I noticed a shadow by the door.</Source>
      <Dest>只是这里什么都没有。我几乎就要把Aringoth叫醒，询问他把他的财宝藏在哪儿了。然后我注意到了门旁的一个影子。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wasn't just that.  Even the Black-Briar's have those bookcases with griffins on top.  Aringoth's were understated.  It didn't bode well.</Source>
      <Dest>不只是这样。即使黑色荆棘有那些顶端刻有狮鹫的书架，阿林格斯也太低调了。这可不是个好兆头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Way to get my hopes up.  But I doubt there's anything you know that I wouldn't.</Source>
      <Dest>这是重新燃起我的希望的方法。但我恐怕你知道我什么都不行</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I can tell by that stupid question of yours that you didn't manage to get anything.  Worse yet, you didn't even try.</Source>
      <Dest>但是我能区分你的问题和那个愚蠢的问题，因为你的什么都没办成【上下文？】。更糟的是，你连试都不试。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He called the guard.  Punishment for a thief was to lose your thumbs, and they would've taken both of them, if dad hadn't shown up.</Source>
      <Dest>他喊来了守卫。他们对偷窃的惩罚是剁掉你的拇指，【如果老爹没有出现的话，就两个都要剁掉。】</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well...I got that Delphine wants to kill dragons, but now we're messing with Thalmor?  Because they what...raised them?</Source>
      <Dest>好吧……我明戴尔菲娜想去屠龙，但为什么我们现在又要给梭默捣乱呢？因为梭莫……什么……召唤了龙？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Little mining village. Plenty of shadows from the mountain.  Perfect.</Source>
      <Dest>一座矿业小村。山脉投下了大片的阴影。真完美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stole from that bitch Maven Black-Briar.  And why not?  What kind of skeever's excuse for a thief doesn't steal from the fattest pockets in the city?</Source>
      <Dest>从那个叫黑荆棘玛雯的婊子手里偷东西如何。为什么不呢？难道skeever能给出什么不让小偷们从城市里最富得流油的口袋里偷东西的理由吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh, now I'm making myself sick.  But really, old people just should die.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，我现在就是在自寻烦恼。但说真的，老家伙们就该去死嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmph, now I want to go there even less.  But I like you, and the Rift is a good location...although I'm not on the best terms with the Thieves Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>恩，我现在不怎么想去那里，但是我喜欢你，而且裂痕领是个挺好的地方的……虽然我感觉那里还不是安放盗贼工会的最好条件。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still haven't won you over, huh?  I told you, I'm a stubborn one, and I'll bring you over to my side in due time.</Source>
      <Dest>谁都还没争取到你，是吧？告诉你，我是个固执的家伙。在适当的时候我一定会让你改变立场站到我这边的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At some point though, the guild turned their eyes elsewhere. Things settled down, and for a moment I thought of doing the same.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然某些时候，公会把他们的目光放向了别处，但当事情安顿下来，我一时间也想做同样的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Same rules apply.  If the widows and orphans here are too busy scouring the sky for flying lizards, then their eyes won't track my hands.</Source>
      <Dest>这规则同样适用。如果这里的寡妇和孤儿忙着给那些会飞的大蜥蜴擦洗天空，那他们就不会紧盯着我的手了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I want you to tell me you saved the world to steal it.  That you didn't come back from the Mead Hall of Nord heroes empty handed.</Source>
      <Dest>我想要你告诉我你去拯救世界，是为了偷窃，我想你一定没有从蜜酒大厅的诺德英雄那里空手而归。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He begged the guard to take his thumbs instead of mine. Guard was willing, so long as somebody took the blame</Source>
      <Dest>他恳求守卫，想代替我去坐牢。守卫同意了，只要有人承担责任其他的都无所谓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One night we went to the temple, woke Jade up, and asked her to marry us.  Had to be her, being a fellow cutpurse. Then we ran.  And kept running.</Source>
      <Dest>那个晚上我们去了神殿，把洁叫醒，让她嫁给我们。作为小偷的同伙，她不得不同意。然后我们就跑了，不停地跑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One night we went to the temple, woke Jade up, and asked her to marry us.  Had to be her, being a fellow cutpurse. Then we ran.  And kept running.</Source>
      <Dest>那个晚上我们去了神殿，把洁叫醒，让她嫁给我们。作为小偷的同伙，她不得不同意。然后我们就跑了，不停地跑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We were both fishermen.  I fished pockets, he fished fish.  Stood by me when I stuck my hand in the Black-Briar honey jar.</Source>
      <Dest>我们都是捞东西的。他捞河里的鱼，我捞别人兜里的财物。直到我在黑荆棘的地盘里失了手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All the usual telltale signs.  Nobles stand out like a vampire's smile, with their clothes and jeweled pendants.</Source>
      <Dest>就是那些贵族们最为常见的标志，他们那服装以及佩戴的珠宝让他们如微笑着的吸血鬼一样显眼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah. Got too sloppy. I tried to lift a pendant off this old noble, lying still on a bench.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，我太草率了。我看那老贵族还躺在长凳上，就试着想把他脖子上的挂坠顺走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>His eyes didn't reflect any light.  So I thought he was sleeping.  Turns out he was blind.</Source>
      <Dest>他的眼中不见反光。所以我以为他在睡觉。结果发现他是个盲人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You go and save the world.  I'll just stay here and help the Jarl clean up.  I hear he's got a safe that's particularly filthy.</Source>
      <Dest>去吧，去拯救这个世界。而我会呆在这儿帮领主扫除的。我听说他有个安全之所特别的脏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Healthy?  Have you seen what they eat?  Dried fish and salted meat.  And I'm not talking about the food.</Source>
      <Dest>健康？你到底有没有看到他们吃什么？鱼干和盐腌的肉。还有，我不是在说食物.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Heavily guarded too, and easy to get lost.  They say the first floor was built like a maze.</Source>
      <Dest>这里戒备森严，而且容易迷路。他们说这里简直就像一个迷宫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, fine.  Maybe you'll try to show me later then, and I'll find out what a big liar you are.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，好极了。也许你一会儿会想要我看看，然后我就会指出你是个多大的骗子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The weightier a purse, the more misdirection you'll need.  Sometimes, if their pendants are bright enough, the purse is the misdirection.</Source>
      <Dest>钱包越重, 你就需要更多的误导.  有时当坠饰足够明亮, 钱包本身就是误导物.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't even know what that means.  If you're saying it's my fault, all I know is it was his idea to come with me after I fished old Maven's pockets.</Source>
      <Dest>我甚至都不知道那是什么意思。如果你的意思是错误在我的话，那么我要说，我扒了玛雯口袋以后是他自己要跟我来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You mean you want to kill them?  Eliminate the fabled Companions?  You crazy son of a razorfish.  I'm in.  Just give the word.</Source>
      <Dest>你是说你想杀了他们？把传说中的战友团给端平了？尼玛真是脑子进水了吧。行，算我一个。就等你一句话了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some purses sag from the weight of their coin, others are tight but bulge.</Source>
      <Dest>一些钱包里一个子儿都没，但其他的又紧又鼓.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's what happens when I'm not around to keep you honest.  In fact, if I were you, I would never leave me again.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我不在你身边督促你保持诚实时会发生的事。事实上，如果我是你，我永远都不会再离开我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not likely.  I'd probably have stolen Brunwulf's crown by now.  Do Jarl's wear crowns?  Well, they won't when I'm through stealing them.</Source>
      <Dest>不可能。目前为止，我可能会去偷乌佛瑞克的王冠。你说领主佩戴的王冠？呃，就算我把它们都偷了，领主们也不会发现。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At some point though, the guild turned their eyes elsewhere. Things settled down, and for a moment I thought we'd do the same.</Source>
      <Dest>然而不知何时，公会把目光移向了别处。事情开始安定下来，而一瞬间我以为我们也能获得安宁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not likely.  I'd probably have stolen Ulfric's crown by now.  Do Jarl's wear crowns?  Well, they won't when I'm through stealing them.</Source>
      <Dest>不可能。目前为止，我可能会去偷乌佛瑞克的王冠。你说领主佩戴的王冠？呃，就算我把它们都偷了，领主们也不会发现。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You want to what, protect me or something?  That's...unexpected.  Well fine!  It's not like there's any good loot in Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>你想要什么，保护我还是其他什么？这还真是……出乎意料。那好吧！似乎在松加德也没啥好的战利品了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure, they told me "Hands off." But when someone tells me not to do something, it just makes it all the more tempting.</Source>
      <Dest>恩哼，他们告诉我“放手”。但当某人告诉我不要做某事的时候，只回使这一切更诱人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some wealthy merchants try to wear the farmer's costume, but you know them by the size of their gut.</Source>
      <Dest>一些富商试图穿上农民的衣着，但你知道他们肚子的大小的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was shape unlike anything I had ever seen.  A bizarre fish of some kind, stuffed and mounted.</Source>
      <Dest>这种我前所未见过的模型。某种奇怪的鱼，被制成了标本。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, but if you want to hear the basics, I'm willing to share what I know.</Source>
      <Dest>没问题，但你若想听一下基本要素，我会很乐意把我所知的告诉你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So what's that mean...the Thalmor have a dragon nest? But where did they get the eggs?  I don't get it.  My head hurts.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，这是什么意思……梭默控制着一个龙的巢穴？但是他们是从哪儿得到龙蛋的？我不明白，头开始痛了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It hangs from their waist like a pair of balls, and if you nudge them, they'll reach for them out of instinct.  </Source>
      <Dest>它就像球一样挂在他们的腰间，如果你轻轻的推他们的话，出于本能，他们会伸手去拿它的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Funny, my favorite color is white.  It's no wonder we don't get along.</Source>
      <Dest>真可笑，我最喜欢白色。难怪我们合不来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Funny, my favorite color is white.  It's no wonder we don't get along.</Source>
      <Dest>真可笑，我最喜欢白色。难怪我们合不来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Funny, my favorite color is white.  It's no wonder we don't get along.</Source>
      <Dest>真可笑，我最喜欢白色。难怪我们合不来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The female Argonian knight over there.  The one you've been traveling with.</Source>
      <Dest>那边的那个Argonian女骑士。你曾一起旅行过的那位。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The female Argonian knight over there.  The one you've been traveling with.</Source>
      <Dest>那边的那个Argonian女骑士。你曾一起旅行过的那位。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was it?</Source>
      <Dest>那是啥?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was it?</Source>
      <Dest>那是啥?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Capturing this dragon was hard enough.  We don't have time to lure another.</Source>
      <Dest>捕获这条龙已经够难了，我们没时间去再引一条来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Capturing this dragon was hard enough.  We don't have time to lure another.</Source>
      <Dest>捕获这条龙已经够难了，我们没时间去再引一条来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry.  I don't care for any of these people. We're in it for the boon.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，这些人我谁都不在乎，我们是来领福利的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry.  I don't care for any of these people. We're in it for the boon.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，这些人我谁都不在乎，我们是来领福利的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry.  I don't care for any of these people. We're in it for the boon.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，这些人我谁都不在乎，我们是来领福利的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry.  I don't care for any of these people. We're in it for the boon.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，这些人我谁都不在乎，我们是来领福利的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So if a bandit's approaching and his shadow is behind him, then what?</Source>
      <Dest>所以，若一個強盜正在接近並且身影就在他的背後，那接著是？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So if a bandit's approaching and his shadow is behind him, then what?</Source>
      <Dest>所以，若一個強盜正在接近並且身影就在他的背後，那接著是？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So if a bandit's approaching and his shadow is behind him, then what?</Source>
      <Dest>所以，若一個強盜正在接近並且身影就在他的背後，那接著是？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maven's not fat or ugly.  She's beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>Maven不胖也不丑，她很漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maven's not fat or ugly.  She's beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>Maven不胖也不丑，她很漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's why I can't seem to get rid of you.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我为什么一直无法摆脱你的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's why I can't seem to get rid of you.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我为什么一直无法摆脱你的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So that's why I can't seem to get rid of you.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我为什么一直无法摆脱你的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you slipped past him?</Source>
      <Dest>错过他之后又发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you slipped past him?</Source>
      <Dest>错过他之后又发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you slipped past him?</Source>
      <Dest>错过他之后又发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, yes, you never had a home and your parents never loved you. Now let's go.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，是的，你从来没有过一个温馨的家和一对爱你的父母。现在我们走吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, yes, you never had a home and your parents never loved you. Now let's go.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，是的，你从来没有过一个温馨的家和一对爱你的父母。现在我们走吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, yes, you never had a home and your parents never loved you. Now let's go.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，是的，你从来没有过一个温馨的家和一对爱你的父母。现在我们走吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm glad to see you care.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴看到你的关心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm glad to see you care.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴看到你的关心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm glad to see you care.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴看到你的关心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm glad to see you care.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴看到你的关心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm glad to see you care.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴看到你的关心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened at Black-Briar Lodge?</Source>
      <Dest>在黑荆棘酒坊发生什么事了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maven does whatever I want her too, or she will die.</Source>
      <Dest>玛雯必须要按照我的意愿做事，否则她就会死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maven does whatever I want her too, or she will die.</Source>
      <Dest>玛雯必须要按照我的意愿做事，否则她就会死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maven does whatever I want her too, or she will die.</Source>
      <Dest>玛雯必须要按照我的意愿做事，否则她就会死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maven does whatever I want her too, or she will die.</Source>
      <Dest>玛雯必须要按照我的意愿做事，否则她就会死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bravo. Your tenacity is something we all aspire to have.</Source>
      <Dest>棒极了，我们都向往拥有你这样的毅力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bravo. Your tenacity is something we all aspire to have.</Source>
      <Dest>棒极了，我们都向往拥有你这样的毅力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Big deal.  Go cry to someone who cares.</Source>
      <Dest>重要的人。去别处找在乎你的人哭去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Big deal.  Go cry to someone who cares.</Source>
      <Dest>重要的人。去别处找在乎你的人哭去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Big deal.  Go cry to someone who cares.</Source>
      <Dest>重要的人。去别处找在乎你的人哭去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think it works like that.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认为它是那样起作用的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think it works like that.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认为它是那样起作用的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think it works like that.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认为它是那样起作用的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Windhelm is a fine choice. Give my best to the Jarl when you get there.</Source>
      <Dest>风舵城是个理想选择。到了那儿替我向领主带个好儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The world could end, and cockroaches like us will survive until the next one.</Source>
      <Dest>这个世界也许会结束。而像我们这样的蟑螂们会幸存到下一个世界的到来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The world could end, and cockroaches like us will survive until the next one.</Source>
      <Dest>这个世界也许会结束。而像我们这样的蟑螂们会幸存到下一个世界的到来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you mad?  Do you see a lake anywhere near this forest?</Source>
      <Dest>你疯了吧？这森林附近哪来的湖？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you mad?  Do you see a lake anywhere near this forest?</Source>
      <Dest>你疯了吧？这森林附近哪来的湖？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really are rather dense, aren't you?</Source>
      <Dest>你们真是相当的合群，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really are rather dense, aren't you?</Source>
      <Dest>你们真是相当的合群，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really are rather dense, aren't you?</Source>
      <Dest>你们真是相当的合群，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Perfect Touch) Yes, it's like slipping their clothes into their shadow.</Source>
      <Dest>(完美之触)没错，就像把他们的衣服放到他们的影子里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Perfect Touch) Yes, it's like slipping their clothes into their shadow.</Source>
      <Dest>(完美之触)没错，就像把他们的衣服放到他们的影子里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, it's just like cutting purses. Neck or gut.</Source>
      <Dest>是的。这就像割开钱袋、脖子或者内脏一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My parents used to work the farms.  Thought an honest living would give us a roof over our head.  It didn't.  But a dishonest living did.</Source>
      <Dest>我父母在农场工作.  以为淳朴的生活至少能让我们有瓦遮头.  但不是这样，坑蒙拐骗才能做到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If the shadow's in front, I'd be tempted to fish his pockets.  The hardest thing to do is wait.  If I had eyes, I wouldn't be able to.</Source>
      <Dest>如果阴影就在面前，我会立刻摸进他的口袋。等待是个最艰难的事情。如果我能被看见，就不可以那样做了。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, we wait until they're sleeping, and then we hit 'em hard and we hit 'em fast.  Just the way I like it.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说，我们一直等到他们睡着，然后狠狠地打了他们就跑。我就喜欢玩这个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We wait until they're sleeping, and then we hit 'em hard and we hit 'em fast.  Just the way I like it.</Source>
      <Dest>等他们睡着，然后来个又快又狠的突袭。就像我一直喜欢的那样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was wandering about the forest for some fresh air when I noticed a cabin perched on a hill.</Source>
      <Dest>当我漫步于森林，呼吸着新鲜的空气时，我注意到一个小屋座落在山冈上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And while there were plenty of thieves who can't read, only I had the gall to cross Maven.</Source>
      <Dest>考虑到有那么多小偷连大字都不识一个，也只有我才有与玛雯对着干的胆量了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, I get it.  I think.  It's not about stealth so much as speed.  Shadows are like that.  They come and go in an instant.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我想我明白了。连速度方面都不像是在潜行。就像影子一样，来去于须臾之间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could do about 30 sets a minute, no health potion.  Cleaned out so many pockets they were paying me in fish.</Source>
      <Dest>我一分钟可以做大约三十套，不用血瓶。把这些都搞定以后他们会赏我条鱼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Found a stash of gold and a piece of paper.  Don't know what was on it, so I left it on a table.</Source>
      <Dest>找到一个金库和一张纸条。不知道上面写的啥，所以我把它留在桌子上了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever seen me play five finger fillet? Me and some of the other thieves used to play by the docks.  Sometimes even the fishmongers would join in.</Source>
      <Dest>曾经看到我这五个指尖的艺术吗?我和别的盗贼曾在码头如此表演。有时候鱼贩也会与我们为伍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure, I'll blow him a kiss as I walk out of the palace with his favorite axe.  He'll never feel it though.  Just like he'll never see me.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。当我走出宫殿，我会给他那把最爱的斧头一个吻。尽管他永远不会察觉。就像他的眼中从来没有我一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're a funny one.  You know damn well what I mean.  We've got five hooks per hand, and an entire ocean of fish.</Source>
      <Dest>《你真有趣。你懂我的意思。我们每人手上都有五个钩子，还有整个海洋的鱼。》</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't have to be careful, you just have to slide it off quick before they know what hits them.  Fast and hard.  I like it.</Source>
      <Dest>你不需要小心,你只需要在他们弄清是什么打了他们之前快点儿溜走就行了。又快又猛，我喜欢这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I knew you were a damn white knight the day you saved me.  I also know you can't have shadows without light.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你救我那天你他妈的是我的救星。但我也知道你不会无缘无故救我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, you go on ahead.  It's not like this cage has room for another dragon anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>好啊，你先走吧。这笼子看来也没地方装另一条龙啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whatever.  I wasn't crying.  Just telling you how it is.  Not everyone had everything handed to them like you.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么样，我没有哭。告诉你是怎么回事吧。不是所有人都能像你那样把所有东西都交给他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right now, that means telling you what you don't want to hear.  If you want to stay Guildmaster, don't mess with Maven.</Source>
      <Dest>不过现在，得告诉你一些你所不愿听到的事情。如果你还想接着当会长，那就别跟玛雯凑一块。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, right.  Talk about cutting off your prick to spite your balls.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，对啦。就说切掉你那根刺儿气死你的蛋吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're going to have your hands full, and I don't mean dealing with Alduin.</Source>
      <Dest>估计你得忙的不可开交。我说的可不是收拾奥杜因那档子事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait...you mean killing them, and then taking their clothes?  Pfff, I thought you meant something else.</Source>
      <Dest>等等...你的意思是杀死他们，然后取他们的衣服？噗，我还以为你在打别的主意呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't have to be an oracle to see this relationship is going to grow more and more profitable.</Source>
      <Dest>你没必要像个圣人一样去看待，这种关系将会变得越来越有利可图。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The scaleback?  I can't be expected to remember all your friends' names.  It'd be easier if you listed the stuff in her pockets.  That I'd know.</Source>
      <Dest>那个亚龙人？我不可能记住你所有朋友的名字。如果你列举她口袋里的物件儿，让我回想起来还能更容易些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look down, and I'm crouching by your feet with a knife in my teeth.  I'm waking you up in the mornings, I'm watching you in your sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>向下看，我就叼着匕首潜伏在你旁边。早上我会叫你，你睡觉时我会看着你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So where should we start?  You can try dipping in pockets but you might hook an onion.  My fingers will be on the belts, trawling for heavy purses.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我们从哪里开始？你可以试试伸进口袋，但也许你只能掏出个葱头。而我会对皮带下手，偷摸儿顺走沉甸甸的钱包。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We don't have to like the same things.  In fact, that's pretty much what being a family is.  We stick together regardless.</Source>
      <Dest>我们不必喜欢同样的东西。事实上，这正是家人的意味。无论如何，我们都团结在一起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe its best I let a Dragonborn handle dragon business.  But I'm counting on you to at least steal something on my behalf.</Source>
      <Dest>也许最好让龙裔干跟龙有关的事，但我还指望着你至少能以我的名义偷点儿什么呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If his feet are quiet, then he passes before I know it, and only then do I blend into his shadow.  The more dangerous situation is the reverse.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他的脚步静默无声，那么他会在我发现前通过，只有那时我才能混入他的影子之中。反过来就更加危险了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or mess with her, I don't care.  We don't need those thieves anyway.  It'll be just you and me from here on out.</Source>
      <Dest>要不你就去惹她，我是无所谓。我们并不需要那些小偷。就咱们俩安全就行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I guess that only works on the sensitive ones, or else you couldn't whisper "Alduin" without him showing up in your bedroom.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜那只对敏感的家伙有效，否则你悄悄说“奥杜因”它就出现在你房子里了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The eyes tempt you with their shine.  But the eyes tell lies, my friend, the eyes tell lies.</Source>
      <Dest>眼睛用光芒诱惑你。可眼睛是会说谎的我的朋友，眼睛会说谎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the Divines you're an ass.  No, I never had a home.  My parents were farm hands.  They went wherever there was work.  And yeah, they loved me.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵在上，你是个混蛋。不，我从没有过家。我父母都在农场做活。他们走到哪儿都有工作。是啊，他们是爱我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's what I'm talking about, oath-sister.  Here I was thinking you switched your stones for snowberries.  Well, if you were a man.</Source>
      <Dest>（窃笑）这就是我要说的话，我的誓约姐妹。 我在想，你怎么就怂了。好吧，假如你是个爷们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thought I'd find a city full of brothers and sisters. A family of orphans. What I found is a bunch of milk-drinkers sucking on Maven's teats.</Source>
      <Dest>我以为我会找到一个城市，那里的人都亲如手足。就像是个孤儿们的大家庭。但我真正找到的却是一群吸吮着Maven奶嘴的吃奶小儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's right.  We'll just be out there floating in the void, saying stuff like, "Is that all you got?"</Source>
      <Dest>对。我们将会漂浮在那虚空中，说着些什么，就像“这就是你的全部了？”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I suppose saving the world is important too.  And there's plenty of coin purses down here that aren't guarded by some legendary killer.</Source>
      <Dest>不过，我想拯救世界也很重要。并且这儿有大量的零钱包并没有被一些传说中的杀手守卫的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I looked for the low shadows with sharp corners, but the one that drew my attention was a helmet-shaped one sitting on a crate.  A strongbox.</Source>
      <Dest>我在找带尖锐拐角的低阴影，但吸引我注意的是一个坐在箱子上的头盔状的。一个保险柜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now who's blind. But whatever, her looks aren't the point. All I'm saying is, she isn't really a thief, and those guild idiots look up to her.</Source>
      <Dest>现在看看谁是盲目的。但无论如何，她的​​长相不是问题的关键。所有我要说的是，她不是一个真正的小偷，而且那些公会的白痴们敬仰她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Probably was a bad move.  Must've been valuable, because the next day everyone knew.  Turns out the paper was worth more than the gold.</Source>
      <Dest>这可能是一个糟糕的举动。一定是很有价值的，因为第二天每个人都知道。结果是纸的价值要超过黄金。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know as family, you'll do anything for me, and I'll do anything for you.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道作为亲人，你会为我做任何事，我也愿为你付出一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I knew there was something I liked about you from the moment I tricked you into opening that cage.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道，自从我骗你打开笼子的那一刻开始，我就不知怎的爱上你了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh, this is so confusing.  I liked it better when they were extinct.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，那可就难办啦。如果它们毁灭的话我会更开心的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What's that supposed to mean?  You calling me stupid?  Well, as long as you aren't calling me slow.</Source>
      <Dest>这是什么意思？你说我是个傻瓜？好吧，只要你不说我反射弧长就行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While mom and dad picked cabbages, I picked pockets.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父母在地里采卷心菜，而我在别人包里采钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While mom and dad picked cabbages, I picked pockets.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父母在地里采卷心菜，而我在别人包里采钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's what I'm talking about, oath-brother.  For a second there I thought someone had switched your stones with snowberries.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑) 这就是我想说的，盾牌兄弟。我想一会儿就会有人拿雪浆果换你的石头了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Was the deed to some horse. They said any thief who left it had to be stupid or blind.</Source>
      <Dest>契约转让给了一匹马，他们说，任何无视那匹马的窃贼不是傻子就是瞎子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm having issues springing you on my own.</Source>
      <Dest>【我在躲开你的时候出了点儿差错。】</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You never told me about your childhood.  You lost your home?</Source>
      <Dest>你从来没有跟我提过你的童年。你失去了家园吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You never told me about your childhood.  You lost your home?</Source>
      <Dest>你从来没有跟我提过你的童年。你失去了家园吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You never told me about your childhood.  You lost your home?</Source>
      <Dest>你从来没有跟我提过你的童年。你失去了家园吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You never told me about your childhood.  You lost your home?</Source>
      <Dest>你从来没有跟我提过你的童年。你失去了家园吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Morndas is an unusual name.</Source>
      <Dest>摩恩达丝是个罕见的名字.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Morndas is an unusual name.</Source>
      <Dest>摩恩达丝是个罕见的名字.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Morndas is an unusual name.</Source>
      <Dest>摩恩达丝是个罕见的名字.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Morndas is an unusual name.</Source>
      <Dest>摩恩达丝是个罕见的名字.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You wouldn't want to come. There isn't any treasure in Sovngarde. Just ghosts.</Source>
      <Dest>你不会想要过来的。Sovngarde这里没有财宝，只有鬼魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You wouldn't want to come. There isn't any treasure in Sovngarde. Just ghosts.</Source>
      <Dest>你不会想要过来的。Sovngarde这里没有财宝，只有鬼魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You wouldn't want to come. There isn't any treasure in Sovngarde. Just ghosts.</Source>
      <Dest>你不会想要过来的。Sovngarde这里没有财宝，只有鬼魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You wouldn't want to come. There isn't any treasure in Sovngarde. Just ghosts.</Source>
      <Dest>你不会想要过来的。Sovngarde这里没有财宝，只有鬼魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You wouldn't want to come. There isn't any treasure in Sovngarde. Just ghosts.</Source>
      <Dest>你不会想要过来的。Sovngarde这里没有财宝，只有鬼魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think you wanted to be part of the Guild. I think you feel betrayed by them.</Source>
      <Dest>我看你是想加入盗贼工会。我想你觉得自己被背叛了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think you wanted to be part of the Guild. I think you feel betrayed by them.</Source>
      <Dest>我看你是想加入盗贼工会。我想你觉得自己被背叛了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened at Black-Briar Lodge?</Source>
      <Dest>在黑荆棘酒坊发生什么事了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened at Black-Briar Lodge?</Source>
      <Dest>在黑荆棘酒坊发生什么事了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened at Black-Briar Lodge?</Source>
      <Dest>在黑荆棘酒坊发生什么事了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not sure if that's an insult or a compliment.  So, thank you?</Source>
      <Dest>我听不出你是损我还是夸我。所以，谢谢吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not sure if that's an insult or a compliment.  So, thank you?</Source>
      <Dest>我听不出你是损我还是夸我。所以，谢谢吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That depends.  Which one is the ugly one?</Source>
      <Dest>那取决于，哪一个比较丑？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That depends.  Which one is the ugly one?</Source>
      <Dest>那取决于，哪一个比较丑？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That depends.  Which one is the ugly one?</Source>
      <Dest>那取决于，哪一个比较丑？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An adventurer?  So are you going to trade your dagger for an axe?</Source>
      <Dest>冒险者吗？要不要拿你的小刀换一把斧头用？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An adventurer?  So are you going to trade your dagger for an axe?</Source>
      <Dest>冒险者吗？要不要拿你的小刀换一把斧头用？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Real family doesn't hire the Dark Brotherhood to knife you in your sleep.  So no, I don't want anything to do with the Guild.  End of story.</Source>
      <Dest>真正的家族才不会雇佣黑暗兄弟会在你熟睡的时候捅你一刀。所以说，我并不想让公会出什么事，到此为止吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're all ugly!  Can't you see that?  You're the one with eyes.  If I were you, I wouldn't admit I was related to any of them.</Source>
      <Dest>他们全是丑八怪！你看不见吗？你是有眼无珠啊。如果我是你的话，绝不会承认我跟他们中的任何人有任何关系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Me and you though, we're practically twins.  I bet it's like looking in a mirror.  </Source>
      <Dest>我和你简直是一对儿双胞胎。我敢打赌我们看着彼此的时候就像是看着镜子中的自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I have you to thank. But let's not get all mushy, okay?</Source>
      <Dest>我得感谢你。别让我们那么感伤，好吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I bet Ancano thought he was one too, that's why he let you step on him.  Now all his guts are all over the floor.  Just like they should be.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢打赌安卡诺觉得他也算一个，所以才会让你踩着他。现在他的肠子流了一地。本来就应该这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not exactly.  Didn't have a home to lose.  My parents were farmers without a farm.  We moved from the Rift to the Reach, begging for work.</Source>
      <Dest>也不准确。没有什么家可失去的。我父母也是没有农场的农民。我们从裂谷城搬到边塞领。到处找事做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We'd travel from place to place, praying to Zenithar we'd have enough to sleep at the inn that night.</Source>
      <Dest>我们会到处旅行，向泽尼萨尔祈祷我们能够在小旅馆里过夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Think of all the loot we can take off these Nord heroes.  I'm not just talking swords and armor either.</Source>
      <Dest>想想我们能从这些诺德英雄这儿弄到的宝贝吧。我可不光是指武器盔甲什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, but you got bigger things on your mind.  You go on ahead and kill that World Eater.  This place should keep me busy until you get back.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，但是在你心里有更重要的事要去做。你得继续前进，然后杀掉世界吞噬者。在你回来之前，我会一直替你照看这个位子的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?  Of course it's a compliment.  Who wouldn't want to be a cockroach?  Those things are like six-legged diamonds.</Source>
      <Dest>什么？当然，这是恭维。谁不想做一只蟑螂？这些东西可是有是六条金刚钻似的腿呢。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Scoffs) That's a surprise. Are you sure you don't want to let me handle it?</Source>
      <Dest>（嘲笑）真是个惊喜。你确定不想让我来处理吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You sure about that? I seem to recall killing a few wayward spirits that dropped more than their share of coin.</Source>
      <Dest>你确定吗？我觉得杀掉那些刚愎自用的灵魂可不仅仅为了他们身上的那几文钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know how Nords always talk about Ysmir's beard?  What if we actually plucked that thing off his face?  Like a bushel of gold.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道诺德人有多喜欢说伊斯谟的胡子吗？要是我们真的把胡子从他脸上拔下来会怎么样？就像是一蒲式耳的黄金吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's not like he'd miss it either, seeing as he could just grow it back.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来他也不会不会少什么，鉴于他可以再长出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, his face was stuck but that body yawned.  Damn shoulders almost touched his toes.  It would've taken an ogre to wake him.  I'm not one.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，他的脸被卡住了，但他的尸体却分家了。他的肩膀几乎能碰到他的脚趾头。叫醒他的一定是个食人族。我可不是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Skyrim's so cold, you get to know the seasons by the crop and the farm.  Gourds from Merryfair in the fall.  Berries from Hollyfrost in the spring.</Source>
      <Dest>天际省太冷了，你需要考虑好季节对作物以及农场的影响。秋天收获Merryfair的葫芦，春天收获寒霜农场的浆果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What are you, blind?</Source>
      <Dest>你瞎眼了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure enough, the following Sundas, my mother went into labor.  But I didn't come out right away.</Source>
      <Dest>果然，接下来的Sundas，我老母去了研究室。但是我没立马出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I always made sure we did.  Dad scolded me once.  Told me begging wasn't honest work.  He had no idea.</Source>
      <Dest>But I always made sure we did.  我爸有一次骂了我。说讨饭不是真正的工作。他懂什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's enough!</Source>
      <Dest>够了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not likely. Especially after you put Nocturnal in a good mood again. The extra shadows are going to help. Big time.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑）我看不会。尤其是你们帮诺克图纳尔重整旗鼓之后。额外的阴影之力会帮上大忙。不得了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One section was darker than the rest.  A guard standing by the door.  His shadow had high cheek bones.  A mercenary's grin.</Source>
      <Dest>有一段比其他地方更加黑暗的路。一个守卫靠着门懒懒的站着。从影子来看，他的颧骨很高。一个雇佣兵露齿而笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These idiots aren't even people.  Just a bunch of shield-horkers.  So don't forget who really has your back.</Source>
      <Dest>这些蠢都不配叫做人。顶多算群是扛着盾的三牙海象。所以别忘记事实上是谁在保卫你的身后。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You idiot!</Source>
      <Dest>你个白痴！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's ridiculous.  What, you think they were family?  Family doesn't abandon you when you do something wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>这太荒谬了。什么，你以为他们是家人？家人是永远不会背弃你的，无论你做错了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was a stubborn baby.  Wouldn't leave the womb.  Always clung to the darkness, even then.</Source>
      <Dest>我是一个顽固的孩子，总是舍不得离开子宫，总是向往着黑暗。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
