<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting news, rumors...thoughts?</Source>
      <Dest>对时下的消息、传闻……你怎么看？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting news, rumors...thoughts?</Source>
      <Dest>对时下的消息、传闻……你怎么看？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting news, rumors...thoughts?</Source>
      <Dest>对时下的消息、传闻……你怎么看？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That sounds like a horrible deal.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来是笔糟透了的交易。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A true knight does not require coin to do what is right.</Source>
      <Dest>一个真正的骑士是因自己的信念而行动的，而不是为钱而行动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's more to life than gold.</Source>
      <Dest>生活中有比金钱更重要的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An excellent trade good sir, where should I deposit the gold?</Source>
      <Dest>真是一次棒极了的交易，好心的先生，那么我该把这些金币放在哪里呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An excellent trade good sir, where should I deposit the gold?</Source>
      <Dest>真是一次棒极了的交易，好心的先生，那么我该把这些金币放在哪里呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Killing dragons can be quite profitable.</Source>
      <Dest>屠龙肯定能大赚一笔的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why should I choose you over Belrand?</Source>
      <Dest>给个让我选你而不是Belrand的理由？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why should I choose you over Belrand?</Source>
      <Dest>给个让我选你而不是Belrand的理由？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why should I choose you over Belrand?</Source>
      <Dest>给个让我选你而不是Belrand的理由？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why should I choose you over Belrand?</Source>
      <Dest>给个让我选你而不是Belrand的理由？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why should I choose you over Belrand?</Source>
      <Dest>给个让我选你而不是Belrand的理由？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why should I choose you over Belrand?</Source>
      <Dest>给个让我选你而不是Belrand的理由？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why should I choose you over Belrand?</Source>
      <Dest>给个让我选你而不是Belrand的理由？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why should I choose you over Belrand?</Source>
      <Dest>给个让我选你而不是Belrand的理由？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a little too rich for my blood.</Source>
      <Dest>那有点太贵了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a little too rich for my blood.</Source>
      <Dest>那有点太贵了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I will pay thrice your fee, if you prove your loyalty by slicing off a finger.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你能切下一根手指来证明你的忠诚，我会付给你三倍报酬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I will pay thrice your fee, if you prove your loyalty by slicing off a finger.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你能切下一根手指来证明你的忠诚，我会付给你三倍报酬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you're saying he does neither well.</Source>
      <Dest>你的意思是说他什么都做不好？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you're saying he does neither well.</Source>
      <Dest>你的意思是说他什么都做不好？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>说说你的事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're just a tool I need to help me complete a pilgrimage.</Source>
      <Dest>你只能算是我的朝圣之旅上一块垫脚石。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're badly misreading the mercenary market.</Source>
      <Dest>你严重地错估了市场上的买卖双方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Consider yourself hired. (1000 Gold)</Source>
      <Dest>你被雇佣了。(1000金币)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Consider yourself hired. (1000 Gold)</Source>
      <Dest>你被雇佣了。(1000金币)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Exactly.  Specialization is key.  The question is, what's yours.</Source>
      <Dest>很对。特长是关键。但问题是你的特别之处在哪里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Exactly.  Specialization is key.  The question is, what's yours.</Source>
      <Dest>很对。特长是关键。但问题是你的特别之处在哪里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Exactly.  Specialization is key.  The question is, what's yours.</Source>
      <Dest>很对。特长是关键。但问题是你的特别之处在哪里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should care. The world could very well end tomorrow.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该小心，明天很可能就是世界末日。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll give you 1200. I think that's more than fair.</Source>
      <Dest>我会给你1200。我觉得这可不少。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I should hire the idiot who does nothing well instead?</Source>
      <Dest>那么我应该雇佣一个什么都干不好的傻瓜？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I should hire the idiot who does nothing well instead?</Source>
      <Dest>那么我应该雇佣一个什么都干不好的傻瓜？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I actually need to hire you for a specific job.</Source>
      <Dest>我还真需要雇你做一个特殊的任务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All I need is your blessing, not your blade.</Source>
      <Dest>我需要的只是你的祝福，而不是武力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You will be the champion of Zenithar and carry the banner of the Divines.</Source>
      <Dest>你将会成为泽尼萨尔的勇士，以圣灵的名义行事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I noticed you charge twice as much as any other mercenary.</Source>
      <Dest>你比一般的雇佣兵要价高一倍呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My thoughts exactly.</Source>
      <Dest>我就是这么想的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A fish pie sounds incredibly delicious.  I'll go hire Belrand then.</Source>
      <Dest>一个鱼饼，听起来是挺美味的哈。我会去雇博兰德然后让他给我做这个的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A fish pie sounds incredibly delicious.  I'll go hire Belrand then.</Source>
      <Dest>一个鱼饼，听起来是挺美味的哈。我会去雇博兰德然后让他给我做这个的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Keep the drink, and I'll keep my money.</Source>
      <Dest>你留着你的酒，我省下我的钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have no idea what you just said, but it sounds expensive.  1200 gold ought to do it.</Source>
      <Dest>我搞不懂你刚都说了什么，但觉得很厉害的样子。1200 金币该给的值。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're a little short on coin.  Best go gather up some more.</Source>
      <Dest>你给的钱有点儿少，最好再去凑一些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just the basics.  Sword and shield.  No fancy knight training.  What I know, they don't teach you in any tourney.</Source>
      <Dest>随便耍两招而已。挥挥剑举举盾什么的，不是潇洒的骑士训练。我猜骑士训练的时候练不了什么有用的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's pretty simple.  In this world, you got people who want other people dead.  They pay me to kill them.</Source>
      <Dest>相当简单。世界上有人希望别人去死，就花钱雇我弄死他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't think you understand how this works.  You pay me gold to slice off someone else's finger.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你还不了解这事儿是怎么办的。你付钱给我帮你剁掉某人的手指头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now that's what I'm talking about.  Let's go.</Source>
      <Dest>那才是我要说的重点。我们走吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Well, had I known you had the coin, I would've said 10,000 gold pieces.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑）我要是知道你那么有钱，我就管你要一万块啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The choice is as clear as the reasons, brother.</Source>
      <Dest>兄弟，这还需要理由么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In that case, you might be alright with Belrand.  It's not like he's some decrepit old sellsword with a brain the size of my balls.  Oh wait.</Source>
      <Dest>在那种情况下，你是能与博兰德友好相处的。哪怕那老佣兵的脑子还没我的蛋蛋大。哦等等。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Belrand likes to say you can go for a swordsman or spellcaster, but not why not have both?</Source>
      <Dest>Belrand总喜欢说：你可以去当个剑客或施法者，但为什么不能两者兼得呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Belrand likes to say you can go for a swordsman or spellcaster, but not why not have both?</Source>
      <Dest>Belrand总喜欢说：你可以去当个剑客或施法者，但为什么不能两者兼得呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then that person pays me more gold to slice off yours.  Everybody wins.</Source>
      <Dest>然后那个家伙会付我更多的钱来干掉你，共赢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't say I didn't warn you.  Actually, you probably won't be saying much of anything with that old man at your back.</Source>
      <Dest>别说我没提醒过你。事实上，你可能不会和躲在你身后的老人多说些什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, if one day the bandits all trade in their blades for jousting spears, then by all means, find yourself a knight.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，如果哪天强盗都愿意跟你点到为止的话，那你差不多可以去做个骑士了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I'd almost do it for free, except I don't know what that word means. If I had to take a guess, it means 1200 septims.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，我其实挺想免费的，只是我不明白那个词的意思。要是非让我猜，大概是表示1200金币吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why, you looking to hire yourself? (Laughs)  Because you can't be talking about me.</Source>
      <Dest>为什么，你想雇你自己么？(笑声)因为你无法评价我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that's because you didn't let me finish.  You get more than a drink.  You get a tough son of a bitch like me by your side.  </Source>
      <Dest>没错，那是因为你没有让我说完。你得到的可比一杯酒多多啦。你都说服一个像我这样的混账呆在你身边了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My only opinion on the dragons is that I don't care.</Source>
      <Dest>我对龙的唯一看法是，我不在乎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's not like all those skulls scattered around Skyrim bashed themselves in!</Source>
      <Dest>你以为天际的那些王八蛋们都是怎么死的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Probably.  So's killing men. I'll stick to what I know.</Source>
      <Dest>或许吧，其实杀人也挺容易来钱的。我只会这个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Otherwise, you're better off paying me.</Source>
      <Dest>另外，你最好一次性付清钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The choice is as clear as the reasons, sister.</Source>
      <Dest>妹子，这还需要理由么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>More to life than gold, huh.  Say...that's pretty deep.  I'll remember to carve it on your tombstone.</Source>
      <Dest>金币诚可贵，生命价更高，嗯...这很深奥。我会记得把它刻在我的墓碑上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right in my pockets is a good place to start.  Then maybe my coin purse, and my sack too.  Or just dump it on the table, I'm not all that picky.</Source>
      <Dest>我的右边衣兜儿是个好地方。还有我的钱包，我的口袋。或者干脆把它放在桌子上好了，我没那么多事儿的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've been called worse.  In fact, "tool" pretty much sums up what I do.  And this tool costs about 1500 gold to use.</Source>
      <Dest>要我说，还不如垫脚石呢。事实上，“垫脚石”大概概括了我能干什么。并且垫脚石的使用费大概是1500个金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that right? Didn't really think about it.  Just tried to put a number on what you're getting.</Source>
      <Dest>是吗？真的没有想过。还只是信口开河。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey brother, you look thirsty.  Tell you what, you give me 1000 gold pieces, and I'll buy you a drink.</Source>
      <Dest>嗨伙计，你看上去渴了，告诉你吧，如果你给我1000个金币，我就给你买点喝的来！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You got yourself a deal. And don't worry, you're getting the better end of it.</Source>
      <Dest>你给自己找了点麻烦。不过别担心，结果肯定会更好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I ain't one to brag, but I still think you'd be getting a discount.</Source>
      <Dest>不是我吹牛，我真觉得你应该得到【折扣】的啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, but a thousand gold covers regular mercenary work. For this kind of special request, I'll need about 200 more.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，不过一千金币只是常规价。要接你这种特殊的活儿，我得多要200块。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey, I'm just a dumb old merc, don't know nothing about anything.  But I'll lower my prices when people stop paying them.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，我只是个粗俗的老佣兵，对所有事情都一无所知。但我知道在没人愿意花钱雇我的时候应该把价钱压低。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You keep the clink flowing, and I'll be more than happy to buy you more drinks.  Might even offer you my blade, if you're in need of it.</Source>
      <Dest>只要我能一直听见金币的响声，然后我说不定一时开心就多请你几杯酒了。甚至如果你需要的话，我甚至可以为你效劳。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey sister, you look thirsty.  Tell you what, you give me 1000 gold pieces, and I'll buy you a drink.</Source>
      <Dest>嗨姐姐，你看起来很渴啊。告诉你吧，给我1000金币，我就给你买喝的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So we're in complete agreement.  Knights are dumb.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我们完全同意。骑士们都是哑巴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He likes to say that a lot, "Why not have both?"  I'll tell you why.</Source>
      <Dest>他总是这样说，“为什么不呢？”我会告诉你为什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He likes to say that a lot, "Why not have both?"  I'll tell you why.</Source>
      <Dest>他总是这样说，“为什么不呢？”我会告诉你为什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My next opinion of the war will be my first.</Source>
      <Dest>我对战争的观点跟上一个一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You got that right.  They pay us to kill, not to care.</Source>
      <Dest>你说对了。他们付钱，我们杀人，别往心里去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I tend to have only happy thoughts.  Mostly because I only think about one thing.  It's round, gold, and buys me mead.  </Source>
      <Dest>我很乐观。很大程度是因为我只考虑一个东西。它是圆的，金光闪闪的，还能换取蜂蜜酒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But sure, keep your gold, spill your blood.  It's not like it's less painful inside your body or anything.</Source>
      <Dest>但是确实，卖命拿钱。想不出血就过上好日子是不可能的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's just the way it is.  Maybe if you're some kind of genius you could pull it off. Or maybe if you're young and fast enough, it won't matter.</Source>
      <Dest>本来就是。如果你天赋异禀的话就可以横扫全天际了。或者说你身强体壮，动作敏捷，也能混得下去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's like you're out for a meal, and you got a choice of pie, or fish.  Belrand is like a pie made out of fish.  Why not have both?  That's why.</Source>
      <Dest>就像你出去吃饭，然后你得选你是吃鱼还是吃馅饼。博兰德就像是一个鱼肉馅饼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's like you're out for a meal, and you got a choice of pie, or fish.  Belrand is like a pie made out of fish.  Why not have both?  That's why.</Source>
      <Dest>就像你出去吃饭，然后你得选你是吃鱼还是吃馅饼。博兰德就像是一个鱼肉馅饼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah?  It might cost you extra, depending on how dangerous it is.  Hell, make it dangerous enough, and it might cost you less.  But it'll still cost.</Source>
      <Dest>啥？也许会额外花费你很多东西，当然这和他到底有多危险有关。见鬼，越是危险花的就越少。但是花肯定是要花。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>要不是我父亲那晚上被困在独孤城了，卫兵们才抓不到他呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was just about suggest that myself.  You need me again, you come by the Skeever.  And bring money.</Source>
      <Dest>我几乎就让我那么干了。你又一次需要我了，你抓到了雪鼠，还带来了钱。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
