<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then what good are you.</Source>
      <Dest>然后你有什么好处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then what good are you.</Source>
      <Dest>然后你有什么好处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>At least we'll have plenty of time to say goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>至少我们有充裕的时间说再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>At least we'll have plenty of time to say goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>至少我们有充裕的时间说再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She's fine. The occasional step on the pressure plate notwithstanding.</Source>
      <Dest>她挺好的，虽然偶尔会踩上压板。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what are you now? An assassin? A friend?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在的身分究竟是什么？刺客还是朋友？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what are you now? An assassin? A friend?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在的身分究竟是什么？刺客还是朋友？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So why do you consider him an enemy?</Source>
      <Dest>那为什么你将他视为敌人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ivarstead? Alchemist's Shack. You can't possibly be referring to Godrod.</Source>
      <Dest>紫杉镇？炼金术士的小屋。 你指的不可能是葛卓吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ivarstead? Alchemist's Shack. You can't possibly be referring to Godrod.</Source>
      <Dest>紫杉镇？炼金术士的小屋。 你指的不可能是葛卓吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My companions do not have to be heroic. Only obedient.</Source>
      <Dest>我的同伴不需要当一名英雄，只要能懂得服从命令就好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My companions do not have to be heroic. Only obedient.</Source>
      <Dest>我的同伴不需要当一名英雄，只要能懂得服从命令就好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's never too late.</Source>
      <Dest>不嫌晚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's never too late.</Source>
      <Dest>不嫌晚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's never too late.</Source>
      <Dest>不嫌晚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you killed your captors?</Source>
      <Dest>在你杀了你的俘虏后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you killed your captors?</Source>
      <Dest>在你杀了你的俘虏后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you killed your captors?</Source>
      <Dest>在你杀了你的俘虏后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should have spoken to her. At that time, you were still a victim.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该跟她说一下的，那时候你还是个受害者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should have spoken to her. At that time, you were still a victim.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该跟她说一下的，那时候你还是个受害者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should have spoken to her. At that time, you were still a victim.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该跟她说一下的，那时候你还是个受害者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That must've been strange.</Source>
      <Dest>那一定很奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That must've been strange.</Source>
      <Dest>那一定很奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is all your fault, you know.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道这都是拜你所赐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is all your fault, you know.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道这都是拜你所赐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is all your fault, you know.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道这都是拜你所赐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You sound like her mother. She's a grown woman.</Source>
      <Dest>你听起来像她母亲，那个成熟的女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then we better find someone fast.</Source>
      <Dest>然后我们最好去找個飞毛腿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then we better find someone fast.</Source>
      <Dest>然后我们最好去找個飞毛腿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why give me the sword?</Source>
      <Dest>为何给我这把剑?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why give me the sword?</Source>
      <Dest>为何给我这把剑?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Things never work out quite the way we want them to.</Source>
      <Dest>事情总是无法完全如我们所愿地那样发展。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Things never work out quite the way we want them to.</Source>
      <Dest>事情总是无法完全如我们所愿地那样发展。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think Tikrid has an exceptional laugh.</Source>
      <Dest>我想剃克瑞德的笑不寻常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think Tikrid has an exceptional laugh.</Source>
      <Dest>我想剃克瑞德的笑不寻常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think Tikrid has an exceptional laugh.</Source>
      <Dest>我想剃克瑞德的笑不寻常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You have committed crimes against the innocent. I'm sorry, but you must die.</Source>
      <Dest>你对无辜者犯下重罪。很遗憾，你必须死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Weren't you handling contracts from Deneris to kill the Darksteel?</Source>
      <Dest>不是你接手丹尼勒斯的契约去杀黑铁的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I may know a few alchemists who can help.</Source>
      <Dest>我认识的几个炼金师可能帮得上忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I may know a few alchemists who can help.</Source>
      <Dest>我认识的几个炼金师可能帮得上忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She wanted to become a housecarl, but the Jarl already has one.</Source>
      <Dest>她想做一个侍卫，可领主已经有侍卫了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So part of you did want to go back to the way things were.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你还是有一些想回到过去的日子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So part of you did want to go back to the way things were.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你还是有一些想回到过去的日子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So part of you did want to go back to the way things were.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你还是有一些想回到过去的日子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's the alchemist's fault. He must have screwed up the potion.</Source>
      <Dest>这是那个炼金师的错。他肯定把药水搞错了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's the alchemist's fault. He must have screwed up the potion.</Source>
      <Dest>这是那个炼金师的错。他肯定把药水搞错了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's the alchemist's fault. He must have screwed up the potion.</Source>
      <Dest>这是那个炼金师的错。他肯定把药水搞错了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I might've given the alchemist the wrong ingredients.</Source>
      <Dest>我好像给那个炼金师送错了材料。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I might've given the alchemist the wrong ingredients.</Source>
      <Dest>我好像给那个炼金师送错了材料。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I might've given the alchemist the wrong ingredients.</Source>
      <Dest>我好像给那个炼金师送错了材料。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Jarl has enough guardsman. More of them should become adventurers.</Source>
      <Dest>领主的守卫已经够多了。他们中间很多人都应该去当冒险者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Jarl has enough guardsman. More of them should become adventurers.</Source>
      <Dest>领主的守卫已经够多了。他们中间很多人都应该去当冒险者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Deneris is the only one to blame for Tikrid's death.</Source>
      <Dest>丹尼勒斯是唯一要对剃克瑞德之死负责的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Deneris is the only one to blame for Tikrid's death.</Source>
      <Dest>丹尼勒斯是唯一要对剃克瑞德之死负责的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to talk about you and Tikrid.</Source>
      <Dest>我想谈谈你和剃克瑞德之间的事。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to talk about you and Tikrid.</Source>
      <Dest>我想谈谈你和剃克瑞德之间的事。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not with this. It's a special poison I had brewed up. Acts slow, but always kills. </Source>
      <Dest>别用这个. 这是我做的一种特效毒药. 起效慢, 但致命. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But right now, if you don't mind, I'd appreciate it if you gave me a second to say goodbye to an old friend.</Source>
      <Dest>但是现在, 如果你不介意的话, 我会对你给几秒钟让我向一位老朋友说再见表示感激的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell me about it. I was training to become a housecarl of all things. That girl seems so far away now.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我细节. 我被训练成一个守卫了. 这妞现在看上去差远了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She's a good kid. Had a lot of talent, even if it didn't look that way. I'm not surprised she's as strong as she is.</Source>
      <Dest>她是个好孩子. 尽管看不出来，但她有一定天赋. 我不会为她像她一样强而感到惊讶.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then what good are you.</Source>
      <Dest>那你还顶个屁用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then what good are you.</Source>
      <Dest>那你还顶个屁用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why we're going to kill him, and kill him slow. It won't be pretty, and it won't be clean.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是为什么我们要杀了他，而且还得慢慢儿的杀了他。这会让他死的很难看，而且不容易被清理干净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why we're going to kill him, and kill him slow. It won't be pretty, and it won't be clean.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是为什么我们要杀了他，而且还得慢慢儿的杀了他。这会让他死的很难看，而且不容易被清理干净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why we're going to kill him, and kill him slow. It won't be pretty, and it won't be clean.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是为什么我们要杀了他，而且还得慢慢儿的杀了他。这会让他死的很难看，而且不容易被清理干净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I was kid, sure, that's what I wanted to be. But it's too late for that now.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，在我还是个孩子的时候，这就是我想要的。但现在太晚了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was my poison, but it wasn't my fault. Deneris. It's nobody's fault but his.</Source>
      <Dest>是我下的毒，但不是我的错。丹尼勒斯。是他的错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No need to give up just yet. I don't know if there's an antidote, but the guy who made the poison, I'm willing to bet he does.</Source>
      <Dest>别放弃。我不知道这儿是否有解药，但我打赌，制作这种毒药的家伙那儿一定有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He should be back though. Always seems to show up whenever I run low on poisons. Hopefully this time's the same.</Source>
      <Dest>不过他应该会回来。每当我快用完毒药的时候他似乎总会出现。希望这次也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If anything, that day I was the fragile one. But I couldn't go to her. I think I almost resented her for taking the life that was meant for me.</Source>
      <Dest>如果有什么的话，那一天我是最脆弱的那个。【但我得不到她。】我几乎把憎恨她当作了我生命的全部意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure, I know you mean well. Tikrid's the same way. She'll always see me as that girl who told the bullies where to stick it.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，我很懂你。剃克瑞德也是。她经常像那个给地痞们通风报信的女孩一样来看我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which is stupid. Knowing her, she probably did it in my honor. But either way, I needed to carve out my own path. That's what made me turn away.</Source>
      <Dest>这很愚蠢。我了解她，她可能是为我才这么干的。但不管怎样，我需要开拓出自己的道路。这就是我拒绝了的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That ship has also sailed. I wanted to serve the Jarl. But now, I'm in business for myself.</Source>
      <Dest>那艘船已经起航了。我是想给贵族服务来着。但现在，我在自己做买卖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But in some ways, Tikrid reminds me of who I used to be. After what happened, it's as if all my dreams became hers.</Source>
      <Dest>但在某些方面，剃克瑞德老让我想起过去的自己。在那件事发生之后，仿佛突然之间，我所有的梦想都变成了她的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Both, I guess. I'm no hero, if that's what's required to join your little club.</Source>
      <Dest>我想，两者都是。我不是英雄，如果这就是加入你小团体的要求的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then so be it.</Source>
      <Dest>那么就这么做吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, now she's like your housecarl, so I guess it worked out.</Source>
      <Dest>好了，现在她就像你的侍卫一样，所以我猜完事儿了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not really. Towns still aren't safe from people like me. Although less guards would definitely make my job easier.</Source>
      <Dest>不是的。城镇对于我这样的人来说还是很危险的。尽管毫无疑问守卫越少我的工作就越容易。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're absolutely right. That's why we're going to kill him, and kill him slow. It won't be pretty, and it won't be clean.</Source>
      <Dest>完全正确。这就是为什么我们要杀了他，而且还得慢慢儿的杀了他。这会让他死的很难看，而且不容易被清理干净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wasn't even sure we'd get along. She became the person I wanted to be, and who was I? I didn't even know anymore.</Source>
      <Dest>我甚至不确定我们曾经相处过，她成为了我想要成为的人，而我又是谁，我甚至什么都不知道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But right now, if you don't mind...I'd appreciate it if you gave me a second to say goodbye to an old friend.</Source>
      <Dest>但现在，如果你不介意的话……我会很感激你给我点时间对一位老朋友道别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But right now, if you don't mind...I'd appreciate it if you gave me a second to say goodbye to an old friend.</Source>
      <Dest>但现在，如果你不介意的话……我会很感激你给我点时间对一位老朋友道别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But right now, if you don't mind...I'd appreciate it if you gave me a second to say goodbye to an old friend.</Source>
      <Dest>但现在，如果你不介意的话……我会很感激你给我点时间对一位老朋友道别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, I know just who. Same guy who made the poison. He lives over in that shack west of Ivarstead.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，我知道是谁。做这种药的是同一个家伙。他就住在紫杉镇西边的窝棚里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Exceptionally weird. But I like how you stick up for her. I guess I just feel like she's grown so much, there's no need to.</Source>
      <Dest>非常不寻常。但是我喜欢你一直坚持帮助她。我猜我刚刚觉得她已经成长了很多，不需要这些帮助了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, strange. It was like looking at an alternate version of myself. Part of me was happy for her, and part of me was, well...jealous.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，真奇怪。这就像看着一个双重的自己。我的一部分为她感到快乐，而另一部分是，好吧......嫉妒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I guess it doesn't matter much if we're traveling together.</Source>
      <Dest>但我想如果我们一起旅行的话，这就不重要了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, he didn't save her, but he damn sure as hell didn't kill her. Only one man is guilty of that crime.</Source>
      <Dest>不，他没有救她，但他妈的肯定没有杀她。只有一个人犯了罪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You write poetry? Because that also makes me cringe.</Source>
      <Dest>你还写诗？那也让我鸡皮疙瘩掉一地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>His shack is west of Ivarstead, just off the main road. We should head there.</Source>
      <Dest>他的窝棚就在瓦斯泰德的西面，离大路不远。我们应该朝这儿走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can see why Tikrid would make a good companion though. After what happened, it's as if all my dreams became hers.</Source>
      <Dest>我能明白为什么Tikrid让一位优秀的战友通过。在发生了这一切之后，我所有的梦想好像全变成了她的一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I knew that life belonged to her, and I couldn't take it away. So I turned around, walked out the inn, and never looked back.</Source>
      <Dest>但我知道那生命是属于她的，而我不能把它夺走。因而我转身，迈出了旅馆，头也不回。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But the truth is, everything's changed. The girl she knew died in that sanctuary.</Source>
      <Dest>可是事实是一切都变了。她知道的那女孩已死在了圣所。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, I know this looks bad, real bad, but there's still a chance. The same guy who crafted this poison might be able to make a fix. </Source>
      <Dest>等等，我知道这看起来挺糟，非常糟，但我们或许还有机会。制造这个毒药的人或许也能够消解它的毒性。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This alchemist, he's some kind of genius. Let's hope for Tikrid's sake, he can outsmart himself.</Source>
      <Dest>这个炼金术士，他某种意义上来说是个天才。让我们以剃克瑞德的名义，祝福他可以战胜自己的智慧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This alchemist, he's some kind of genius. Let's hope for Tikrid's sake, he can outsmart himself.</Source>
      <Dest>这个炼金术士，他某种意义上来说是个天才。让我们以剃克瑞德的名义，祝福他可以战胜自己的智慧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's my girl. She crawls around like a spider, but she bites like one too.</Source>
      <Dest>那是我女儿。她爬来爬去好似蜘蛛，但她咬人的时候更像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't know who that is. But given how often my guy travels, that shack has seen more than its fair share of squatters.</Source>
      <Dest>不知那人是谁。不过以我们的人旅行的频率，那小屋里住过的人相当的多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But that was naive. My parents were gone. So was everyone I knew. And then I walked into the Windpeak Inn and saw her.</Source>
      <Dest>我那时真是太天真。我的家人已经离开。我所认识的人都已离开。然后我走进风岳旅店，然后我就看见了她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or there might not have been a cure to begin with. Forget it. It's not your fault. It's nobody's fault but Deneris'.</Source>
      <Dest>或许根本就没有办法开始治疗。没关系了，不是你的错也不是其他人的错，只能怪丹尼勒斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I didn't give it you. I'm loaning it to you, just to see if that's what they're really after.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有把它给你。不过是把它借你而已。我其实就是想看看这是不是他们真正想找的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Old habits, I guess. I always felt like Tikrid was my kid sister. And it's been a long time since I had any family to poke around.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜是旧习使然。我总觉得剃克瑞德是我妹妹。这是因为我已有好一段时间没有家人，以至于四处闲逛了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was Tikrid, dressed as a guard, and laughing that awkward laugh of hers with people I've never met.</Source>
      <Dest>这是剃克瑞德，打扮得像个守卫，然后在她带着一个我素不相识的人朝我尴尬微笑的时候，剃克瑞德哈哈大笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's an alchemist's shack, over in the Rift. We should head there.</Source>
      <Dest>那里有个炼金术士的屋子，就在裂谷城。我们应该去那里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was the guardsman, protecting the town. And who was I? A killer? A victim? I didn't even know anymore.</Source>
      <Dest>她是守卫，保护着城镇。而我是谁？一个施害者？一个受害者？我都不知道了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe, but for the second time in my life, I was afraid. And all I could do was run. </Source>
      <Dest>也许吧，但这是我一生之中第二次感到了畏惧。而我能做到的唯有跑而已。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Part of me, yes. But I knew they couldn't. It wasn't just me who changed. It's almost as if our lives got switched.</Source>
      <Dest>我一部分是的. 但我知道他们不能. 不是只有我变了. 几乎我们所有都改变了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, I left that part of me all behind, and became what I am now.</Source>
      <Dest>所以，我抛开过去的我，成为现在的我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, I left that part of me all behind, and became what I am now.</Source>
      <Dest>所以，我抛开过去的我，成为现在的我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Everyone dies. It's just more fun when we're the ones who kill them.</Source>
      <Dest>所有人都死了，我们杀了他们只会让事情变得更有趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Everyone dies. It's just more fun when we're the ones who kill them.</Source>
      <Dest>所有人都死了，我们杀了他们只会让事情变得更有趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can have it back, for a price.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以用优惠的价格回收。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Destiny tends to keep me in her hip pocket.</Source>
      <Dest>命运总让我与她紧紧相连。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The ones who died deserved it, either by wickedness or foolishness.</Source>
      <Dest>凡是死掉的都是活该，除了坏死的就是笨死的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought you said you were loaning this sword to me.</Source>
      <Dest>我还以为你说要借这把剑给我呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You sound like you have some regrets. But redemption does not come from death.</Source>
      <Dest>我看起来似乎挺后悔的，但是死亡并不是解脱的方法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You sound like you have some regrets. But redemption does not come from death.</Source>
      <Dest>我看起来似乎挺后悔的，但是死亡并不是解脱的方法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If Tikrid's okay with letting you live, so am I.</Source>
      <Dest>如果剃克瑞德让你走，那我也让你走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If Tikrid's okay with letting you live, so am I.</Source>
      <Dest>如果剃克瑞德让你走，那我也让你走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's fine with me. I'm a killer myself.</Source>
      <Dest>我没那种问题，我自己就是个杀手</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's fine with me. I'm a killer myself.</Source>
      <Dest>我没那种问题，我自己就是个杀手</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what will you do now?</Source>
      <Dest>那你现在怎么办？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what will you do now?</Source>
      <Dest>那你现在怎么办？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This isn't about Deneris. You're thinking about Sahlene.</Source>
      <Dest>这不关丹尼勒斯的事，你脑子里想的是索伦.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know, but I'm not going to change my ways, if that's what you think.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道，但我不会改变我的方式，如果这就是你的想法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You always say you work best under pressure. Well, consider both your lives on the line.</Source>
      <Dest>你总是说你在压力下的工作可以做到最好。嗯，只要同样考虑到你的生活就行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't worry about Tikrid. You take care of Deneris.</Source>
      <Dest>不用担心剃克瑞德了，你照顾好丹尼勒斯吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I feel the same way about death. I grew up wanting to save lives, but whenever I look over my shoulder, all I see is the trail of bodies.</Source>
      <Dest>我对死亡有同样的感觉。我长大想要拯救生命,但是每当我回首往昔的时候，所看到的只是尸体的痕迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then that's where you should go. Your wife and I will follow when she's ready. Although I should probably say "if" she's ready.</Source>
      <Dest>那就是你要去的地方。当她准备好的时候你老婆和我会跟随着。虽然我应该说“如果”她准备好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know how long they kept me in there. I stopped counting the days when I stopped counting the scars. </Source>
      <Dest>我不知道他们把我关在这里多久了。当我不在数着自己伤疤的时候我停止了继续计算日子。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that right? Tikrid has some pretty bad luck with companions.</Source>
      <Dest>是真的吗？剃克瑞德只要跟战友团在一起，运气就会变得特别差。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You look pale. And your eyes...Damnit..this doesn't look good.</Source>
      <Dest>你看起来面色苍白。还有你的眼睛……该死，看起来也不对劲儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When that door spoke, I felt something I never felt before. For the first time in my life, I wasn't invincible. I was afraid.</Source>
      <Dest>当这扇门说话的时候，我有了从未有过的感觉。这是在我人生中第一次发现，我不是无敌的，我也会害怕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Same old Tikrid. I'd tell you to lie down, but trust me, in about an hour, you won't have a choice.</Source>
      <Dest>剃克瑞德还是老样子。我想让你躺下，但是相信我，大约一个小时以后，你不会有选择的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say you should rub them on a knife.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说想要惹恼他们你只需要一把小刀就可以了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You make this potion, and I'll fetch you enough weeds to build you a garden.</Source>
      <Dest>你制作出了这个药剂，我会给你足够的植物来建设你的花园。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I came here ready to die. I thought it was Divines' way of bringing everything full circle. I didn't expect it to turn out like this.</Source>
      <Dest>我抱着必死的决心来到这里。我以为这是圣灵们对世间万物所进行的循环。没想到最后变成这样了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is who I am now. And if that's alright with you, then I think we can work together. We have a mutual enemy. An Elf, named Deneris.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我。如果你觉得可以的话，我想我们可以一起干活儿。因为我们有一个共同的敌人——那个精灵，丹尼勒斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean, only in theory?</Source>
      <Dest>你这话什麽意思，只有理论可行？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, then we won't fight. In fact, from what I hear, you've got a problem with an Elf named Deneris. Maybe I can help.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，那咱就不打了。实际上，据我所知，你跟一个名叫丹尼勒斯的精灵有点过节。也许我能帮上忙呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh no, you're not going anywhere. You need your rest.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，不，你什么地方都不许去。你需要休息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's when we found the door.</Source>
      <Dest>就在那时，我们发现了这个门。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come on. Let's hurry.</Source>
      <Dest>来吧，让我们抓紧时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have a guy in Ivarstead who brews it for me. If it gets in the blood, it's guaranteed to kill.</Source>
      <Dest>我有个能调制这种毒药的伙计在紫杉镇。如果它能溶到血液里，那中毒的人就必死无疑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tikrid?</Source>
      <Dest>剃克瑞德？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Change in plans. We need an antidote.</Source>
      <Dest>计划变动。我们需要一个解毒药剂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know. Anywhere but Dawnstar, I guess. Too many bad memories. I'll probably travel Tamriel, and try and find what's left of my family.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道。除了晨星的任何地方。这里有太多不好的回忆。我可能会旅行泰姆瑞尔，试着找到剩下的我的家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've killed people. Not all of them deserved it. If I know you Tikrid, that's not something you can forgive.</Source>
      <Dest>我杀过人。他们之中，不是所有人都罪该致死。如果我认识你的话，剃克瑞德，这就不是什么你所能原谅的事了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I thought if I could conquer that fear, I could conquer anything. I'd be myself again.</Source>
      <Dest>我想如果我能战胜恐惧的话，我就能战胜一切。我想做回我自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry Tikrid. I never should've left you. But what's done is done. And this is how it ends.</Source>
      <Dest>对不起剃克瑞德。我不该离开你的。但木已成舟，我们也无计可施。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry Tikrid. This wasn't how it was supposed to end. For either of us. </Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉剃克瑞德。这不是本该出现的结果。对我俩而言都不该。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So? What of it? I was once a member of Dark Brotherhood. I've killed men for money.</Source>
      <Dest>所以呢？有什么关系呢？我曾经是黑暗兄弟会的成员。我为钱杀人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know what I said. But there has to be a way to undo the damage.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道我说了什么，但这儿肯定有什么其他方法撤销赔偿金。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But when I broke out of my chains, and I slaughtered them all...I had nothing left to fear.</Source>
      <Dest>但当我挣脱枷锁之时，我就把他们全都宰掉了……我已经没什么好怕的了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know this poison. Chances are he lifted it right off of my belt. And if that's the case, she's in trouble.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道这种药水。他很可能就是从我的皮带上偷走的。如果是那样的话，她就麻烦大了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Huh. I never would have guessed. It's like everything's different.</Source>
      <Dest>嚯。真没想到。好像一切的一切都变了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just hang in there, okay?</Source>
      <Dest>就挂在那儿，好吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Damn that ghost. I should've let you kill him. With the sword, I mean. Just didn't think things through.</Source>
      <Dest>该死的幽灵。我本该让你杀了它才对。我是说用剑。当时没想清楚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then that's where you should go. Tikrid and I will follow when she's ready. Although I should probably say "if" she's ready.</Source>
      <Dest>那就是你要去的地方了。等Tikrid 准备好了我俩就跟上。不过我恐怕只能”假设“她会做好这个准备。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is where it all started. I was over by the lighthouse, looking at the ocean.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是一切之始的地方。当时，我就在灯塔里，凝视着海平面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I did. But maybe I had it backwards. Wouldn't be the first time.</Source>
      <Dest>我是打算那样。但或许我应该把它作为备用品。这不会是第一次的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, you go on ahead. I'll stay here and make sure our friend doesn't run off.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，你去吧。我会留在这里，确保我们的朋友不会逃跑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If we're not gonna fight, then maybe we can work together. We have a mutual enemy. An Elf named Deneris.</Source>
      <Dest>如果不想打架的话我们或许能合作一把。我们有个共同的敌人，一个叫做丹尼勒斯的精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tikrid! Are you alright? I don't know how that bastard slipped by me!</Source>
      <Dest>剃克瑞德！你还好吗？我不知道那个杂种是怎么溜过来的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, what's changed in the last dozen years?</Source>
      <Dest>那么，十几年来有什么改变吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There has to be some sort of mixture it doesn't agree with.</Source>
      <Dest>肯定有某种混合体不适合。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tikrid's already forgiven me. I guess they will too. Maybe, if I live the right way, there'll come a day when I actually deserve it.</Source>
      <Dest>剃克瑞德准备原谅我了。我想他们会那么做的。也许，如果我干得没错的话，当我应该受到原谅的时候，他们会过来找我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If it works as slow as you say, probably about a week. But Tikrid's tough. I'd say she has at least two.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你按照你说的速度来干的话，需要两周。但是剃克瑞德的那群恶棍，我想她只有两天时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I just wish we could've done something about Tikrid.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是希望能为剃克瑞德做些事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I just wish we could've done something about Tikrid.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是希望能为剃克瑞德做些事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>More would have died had Deneris been allowed to live.</Source>
      <Dest>如果让丹尼勒斯活下来，更多人会死去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>More would have died had Deneris been allowed to live.</Source>
      <Dest>如果让丹尼勒斯活下来，更多人会死去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But that's life. You have to live with the choices, even if you aren't the one making them.</Source>
      <Dest>但这就是人生。选择会一直伴随着你，即便你不是那个做出选择的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know. If anything, it should've been me. That girl deserved better.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白。如果有…的话，那个人应该是我。那个女孩应该得到更好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So it's done. Funny, I always thought that sword was part of my destiny. But I guess I was just keeping it safe until you came around.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这就结了。真滑稽，我总以为那把剑是我命中注定。但看来我只是在你来之前暂时保其安全而已。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
