<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, mother.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，母亲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could've gotten that journal. Mother's just holding me back.</Source>
      <Dest>我本可以拿到那本日记的。但妈妈刚才妨碍了我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I bet I could salvage just as well as mother.</Source>
      <Dest>I bet I could salvage just as well as mother.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>See all the fish up here? I caught them. Me.</Source>
      <Dest>看到那些鱼了吗？我会抓到它们的。就靠我一个就够。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes I get a little scared going into deeper waters, but that's natural, right?</Source>
      <Dest>有时候我到了深水区会有点害怕，不过那本来就很自然的对吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In a few years, I'll take over the business. The others will work for me.</Source>
      <Dest>几年后，我将接管生意。其他人将为我工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, alright. Just because we're friends.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧好吧。不就是因为我们是朋友嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There once was a woman as fair as an evening in Springtime of Old Stros M'Kai!</Source>
      <Dest>曾有一个女人像春天夜晚的老斯图尔斯·迈凯一样美丽！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With three beers down, the Orc did frown and bid the Elf goodbye, for none could know twas not for show, and someone had to die!</Source>
      <Dest>三杯啤酒穿肠走，兽人跟精灵要分手。这不是一次表演秀，而是有某人要死咯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With three beers down the Orc goodbye; For none could know twas not for show and someone had to die!</Source>
      <Dest>三杯啤酒穿肠走，兽人提出要分手；这不是一次表演秀，而是有某人要死咯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While most in Tamriel would call us Argonian, we prefer the term Saxhleel.</Source>
      <Dest>大部分塔玛瑞尔的居民叫我们亚龙人，不过我们更喜欢原住民这个称呼。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
