<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An Argonian.</Source>
      <Dest>一个蜥蜴人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Argonians do make fine boots to stand in, but walk on two legs during the day, three if you count the tail.  The answer is a dirty Khajiit thief.</Source>
      <Dest>亚龙人确实能穿上鞋子好好站着，但他们在白天还是用两只脚走路的。光天化日之下把尾巴当作第三只脚走路的，只有肮脏的虎人小偷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An Argonian.</Source>
      <Dest>一个蜥蜴人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It crawls on all fours as a kitty, stands on its toes as it attempts to steal your coin purse, and dies as worthless rug under your feet.</Source>
      <Dest>它就像只小奶猫一样在地上缓慢爬行，在试图偷走你的钱包的时候垫起脚尖，最后如同一块儿一文不值的地毯一样被你踩在脚下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Quit whining.  You don't see Argonians making a fuss.</Source>
      <Dest>别抱怨了，你没看见过亚龙人大惊小怪的样子么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Argonians are a subservient race, content to wag their tails for the Nords like common hounds.</Source>
      <Dest>亚龙人都是些奴才命，冲诺德人摇尾巴摇得高兴着呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Quit whining.  You don't see Argonians making a fuss.</Source>
      <Dest>别抱怨了，你没看见过亚龙人大惊小怪的样子么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And before you suggest they conquered Morrowind, the swamp lizards did nothing of the sort.  The Red Mountain is what felled our people.</Source>
      <Dest>在你建议他们去远征晨风之前, 那些沼泽里泡大的蜥蜴们可从来没有考虑过这种事情。红山可是我们的文明发源地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You Argonians are a subservient race, content to wag your tails for the Nords like common hounds.</Source>
      <Dest>你们这些亚龙人就是劣等种族，就像诺德人的猎狗那样向着他们摇尾巴乞怜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Quit whining.  You don't see Argonians making a fuss.</Source>
      <Dest>别抱怨了，你没看见过亚龙人大惊小怪的样子么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Quit whining.  You don't see Argonians making a fuss.</Source>
      <Dest>别抱怨了，你没看见过亚龙人大惊小怪的样子么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And before you suggest you conquered Morrowind, let me remind you that Red Mountain is what felled our people, not you swamp lizards.</Source>
      <Dest>还有，在你说已经征服了晨风省之前，我不得不提醒你一下，红山是属于我们的，与你们这群沼泽里泡大的蜥蜴无关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's it?  Did you even brawl the person?</Source>
      <Dest>就这些？你甚至没打他？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Brawl?  What purpose would that have served? </Source>
      <Dest>拳赛？这他妈到底有什么用？  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's it?  Did you even brawl the person?</Source>
      <Dest>就这些？你甚至没打他？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you mean to tell me I could tell you Secunda is a great big melon, and if I punched you in the face that would make it so?</Source>
      <Dest>你是想说，假如我跟你说塞康达（第二月亮）是个超大的西瓜，然后再照着你的脸来一拳，那它就成真啦？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's an even dumber reason for winning an argument than shouting.  At least shouting involves words.  But it doesn't surprise me at all.</Source>
      <Dest>这比谁声音大谁就吵赢更让人无语。至少大喊的时候你确实说了点东西。但我一点都不觉得吃惊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's it?  Did you even brawl the person?</Source>
      <Dest>就这些？你甚至没打他？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's it?  Did you even brawl the person?</Source>
      <Dest>就这些？你甚至没打他？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As expected in a land of nitwits, the Nords choose their leaders and their laws based on coin flips, fist size and who can down the most mead.</Source>
      <Dest>这片白痴们的领土果然不出我所料啊，诺德人推举领袖和建立法律的原则无外乎抛硬币看正反，要么就是比拳头、比酒量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's so bad about the Gray Quarter?</Source>
      <Dest>灰民区有什么不好的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For starters, there's leaky roofs, rats under the floorboards, and the Jarl makes no attempt to repair them or the aging stonework.  </Source>
      <Dest>一开始，这儿的屋顶漏水了，而地板下有老鼠跑来跑去。但领主却没有试过修好它们，抑或是那尊老化了的石雕。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's so bad about the Gray Quarter?</Source>
      <Dest>灰民区有什么不好的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose it makes no difference, given how shoddy Nord craftsmanship is.</Source>
      <Dest>考虑到诺德人糟糕的手艺，我想他们修不修也没什么区别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's so bad about the Gray Quarter?</Source>
      <Dest>灰民区有什么不好的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You make one pair of wooden shoes in the Merethic Era and all of a sudden you think you can build a city.</Source>
      <Dest>你做了一双神秘纪元的木头鞋，然后突然就觉得自己能盖起一座城市。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, Nord!  Welcome to Rift Watchtower!</Source>
      <Dest>你好啊，诺德兄弟。欢迎来到裂谷哨塔！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stay for a while, have a drink, but before you leave, don't forget to check out the view from upstairs!  It will take your breath away.</Source>
      <Dest>多歇会儿吧，再喝几口小酒，但在你临走之前，一定别忘了看看楼上的风景！那儿简直美的让人窒息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, fellow Dunmer.  If you've come here seeking refuge, you're more than welcome to stay.</Source>
      <Dest>你好啊，暗精灵伙计。如果你是来这儿寻求保护，那绝对是来对地方啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just stay away from the roof.  There's a nasty Dremora who lives up there that'll beat your face uglier than a Nord family portrait.</Source>
      <Dest>记得离屋顶远一点儿。那地方住着个恶心的魔族，那家伙可是会把你的脸揍得比诺德人的家族肖像画还难看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, fellow outlander.  If you've come here seeking refuge, you're welcome to stay.</Source>
      <Dest>你好，外乡人。如果你来这里说寻求庇护的话，欢迎你留下来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just stay away from the roof.  There's a nasty barbarian who lives up there that'll beat your face uglier than a Nord family portrait.</Source>
      <Dest>离屋顶远一点儿。那地方住着个恶心的野蛮人，那家伙会把你的脸揍得比诺德人的家族肖像画还难看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A spider.</Source>
      <Dest>一只蜘蛛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Spiders are indeed stepped on it death, but wear eight legs during life.  No the answer is a dirty, thieving Khajiit.</Source>
      <Dest>蜘蛛确实能被踩死，但是蜘蛛可是八条腿的。你猜错了，正确答案是一个脏脏，卑劣的虎人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It crawls on all fours as a kitty, stands on its toes as it attempts to steal your coin purse, and dies as worthless rug under your feet.</Source>
      <Dest>它就像只小奶猫一样在地上缓慢爬行，在试图偷走你的钱包的时候垫起脚尖，最后如同一块儿一文不值的地毯一样被你踩在脚下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A spider.</Source>
      <Dest>一只蜘蛛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I suppose given the hundreds of these bearded frost beasts I've sent him, there were bound to be some stronger than he.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊。我想这是因为我断断续续往他那儿送去了数以百计体毛浓密的诺德野兽，那里面肯定有比他强壮的家伙存在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You shouldn't worry. To be honest, Dravos tried to kill me, but I escaped.</Source>
      <Dest>你用不着担心。当然其实 爪佛斯 是想杀我来着。可我逃走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You shouldn't worry. To be honest, Dravos tried to kill me, but I escaped.</Source>
      <Dest>你用不着担心。当然其实 爪佛斯 是想杀我来着。可我逃走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But remember Nord, you may live another day, but as far as we Dunmer are concerned, they are still numbered.</Source>
      <Dest>但要记住，诺德人，你或许能多活几天，但在我们暗精灵看来，他们已然时日无多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, this is a good thing.  Perhaps Dravos has become better at distinguishing these golden-haired baboons from the rest of us mortals.</Source>
      <Dest>不，这是件好事儿。或许这样的话，爪佛斯就能更好的把这些黄毛儿大猩猩跟我们其他的人区分开了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You shouldn't worry. To be honest, Dravos tried to kill me, but I escaped.</Source>
      <Dest>你用不着担心。当然其实 爪佛斯 是想杀我来着。可我逃走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You shouldn't worry. To be honest, Dravos tried to kill me, but I escaped.</Source>
      <Dest>你用不着担心。当然其实 爪佛斯 是想杀我来着。可我逃走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We'll know soon enough the next time a Nord comes to visit.</Source>
      <Dest>一切等下一个诺德人来的时候见分晓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your talk is refreshing.  Finally someone who says what we're all thinking.</Source>
      <Dest>你的话犹如一股清泉沁人心脾。终于有人说出我们的心声了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You flatter me, but it requires no bravery on my part to tell the truth.  And to think, I was once naive enough to believe the lie.</Source>
      <Dest>您高抬我了，对我而言说出真相无需勇气。仔细想想，我曾经也幼稚到相信了这个弥天大谎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your talk is refreshing.  Finally someone who says what we're all thinking.</Source>
      <Dest>你的话犹如一股清泉沁人心脾。终于有人说出我们的心声了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I scoffed when people told me the Nords were barbarians, the Argonians were smelly pondscum, and Imperials were humorless bores.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人都是野蛮人，蜥蜴人闻起来都带着鱼腥味儿，帝国人都是毫无幽默可言的讨厌鬼——每当有人跟我说这么说的时候，我总会嗤之以鼻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only my altruistic nature was constantly thwarted by reality.</Source>
      <Dest>只是我无私的本性不断的被现实挫败。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your talk is refreshing.  Finally someone who says what we're all thinking.</Source>
      <Dest>你的话犹如一股清泉沁人心脾。终于有人说出我们的心声了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your talk is refreshing.  Finally someone who says what we're all thinking.</Source>
      <Dest>你的话犹如一股清泉沁人心脾。终于有人说出我们的心声了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nords are indeed primitive beasts, llizards smell and look like swamp slime, and Imperials are stiffer than a male at his first brothel.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人的确是原始的野兽，亚龙人不管是闻是看都和沼泽泥脱不了干系，而帝国人则比那些第一次逛窑子的家伙还要拘谨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your talk is refreshing.  Finally someone who says what we're all thinking.</Source>
      <Dest>你的话犹如一股清泉沁人心脾。终于有人说出我们的心声了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And no, I don't care if you find that insulting, as facts have no bias.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我才不在乎你是不是感觉受到了侮辱。因为事实就是如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dravos is cheerier than I expected.</Source>
      <Dest>爪佛斯比我想象的更活泼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Cheery?  What in Oblivion has gotten into that fool?  He's not supposed to have a personality!  And you're not supposed to be alive!</Source>
      <Dest>雪莉？那混蛋又他妈做了什么好事？他不应该这么耍性子！而你，更不该活在这个世上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dravos is cheerier than I expected.</Source>
      <Dest>爪佛斯比我想象的更活泼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, you were up there for some time.  So what exactly did Dravos tell you?  Whatever it is, I'll have you know my conscience is clear.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，你已经在那里好几次了。那么爪佛斯到底和你说了什么？不管说了什么，我会让你知道，我问心无愧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Khajiit.</Source>
      <Dest>一个虎人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Correct. A more precisely, a filthy Khajiit thief.</Source>
      <Dest>是的。更准确的来说，是一个肮脏的虎人小偷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It crawls on all fours as a kitty, stands on its toes as it attempts to steal your coin purse, and dies as worthless rug under your feet.</Source>
      <Dest>它就像只小奶猫一样在地上缓慢爬行，在试图偷走你的钱包的时候垫起脚尖，最后如同一块儿一文不值的地毯一样被你踩在脚下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Khajiit.</Source>
      <Dest>一个虎人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You live here?</Source>
      <Dest>你住在这里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I've carved out a little life for myself here.  I provide shelter in exchange for food and supplies, and occasionally hunt game in the woods.</Source>
      <Dest>恩，我在这儿经营着自己的小日子。我提供住宿，以此换取食物和补给，有时也到树林里打打猎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But please, don't let me keep you.  You must see the view.  It's to die for.</Source>
      <Dest>那请吧，别让我妨碍到你。不过你一定得看看那风景。真是美死人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You live here?</Source>
      <Dest>你住在这里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You live here?</Source>
      <Dest>你住在这里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yes, it's been quite profitable setting up here, with all the adventurers wandering by.  </Source>
      <Dest>喔是的，把家安置在这儿确实很来钱，过路的冒险者相当多呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Outside of the occasional run in with some inhospitable Nord troll, life couldn't be better for yours truly.</Source>
      <Dest>外面偶尔有一些不友好的诺德巨魔跑来跑去。对我来说，这种生活再好不过了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You live here?</Source>
      <Dest>你住在这里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords disgust me as well.  Every one of them is a dirty ice baboon.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人同样让我恶心，他们就是一群肮脏的雪猿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then we are of like mind.  I warn you, friend, stay away from the rooftop.</Source>
      <Dest>看来我们的想法差不多。给你提个醒朋友，离屋顶远一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What awaits there is only meant to be seen by the very pale-skinned beasts that hope to enslave us.</Source>
      <Dest>等待于此的只有那些皮肤苍白的野兽渴望奴役我们的欲望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords disgust me as well.  Every one of them is a dirty ice baboon.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人同样让我恶心，他们就是一群肮脏的雪猿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why you...no.  I will not be baited into a fight, Nord.  If you wish to stay in this watchtower, I suggest you stick to the rooftop.  Good day.</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么...不。诺德人，我才不会被激将法弄得和你战斗。如果你希望留在这了望塔里，我建议你呆在屋顶。再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You know gray-skin, being kind won't change the fact that we want you gone.</Source>
      <Dest>听着灰皮人,，慈悲也不会改变我们想让你消失的事实。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You...you came down the steps! What happened up there?  How did you manage to survive?</Source>
      <Dest>你...你居然从台阶上下来了！那上面发生了什么？你到底怎么活下来的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have had a bad experience upon entering Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>想必你在进天际省的时候有过一次糟糕的经历。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My experience here in Skyrim has conformed precisely to my expectations.  </Source>
      <Dest>我在天际的经历一直与我的期望相符。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have had a bad experience upon entering Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>想必你在进天际省的时候有过一次糟糕的经历。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People say the only difference between a Nord and a sack of manure is the sack.  That is an unforgivable insult to manure.</Source>
      <Dest>人们说诺德人和一袋粪便之间唯一的区别就差个麻袋。真是不可饶恕！他们怎么能这么侮辱粪便！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Crops grow from manure.  It replenishes the soil.  And when I drop a load of manure in a bucket, it's generally a pleasurable experience.</Source>
      <Dest>农作物靠肥料生长。肥料能让土地备足营养。每次把肥料舀进粪桶里的时候，对我而言都是愉快的经历。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have had a bad experience upon entering Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>想必你在进天际省的时候有过一次糟糕的经历。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have had a bad experience upon entering Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>想必你在进天际省的时候有过一次糟糕的经历。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Nords, meanwhile, are a blight on this land, drum-beating savages whose existence we'd accept if they weren't so sodding noisy.</Source>
      <Dest>而与之相比的，诺德人是这片土地的祸根，是一群不懂得低调为何物的野蛮人。如果他们没那么该死的吵吵闹闹，我们还能勉强接受。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have had a bad experience upon entering Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>想必你在进天际省的时候有过一次糟糕的经历。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No sooner did I arrive in Windhelm when one such ornery ice bard told me to go back to Morrowind.</Source>
      <Dest>我到风盔城没多久，就有一个冷冰冰的坏脾气吟游诗人要我滚回晨风省。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like all the other horn blowers that infest Skyrim, he was insistent this was Nord land, when Elves were here long before Ysgramor settled.</Source>
      <Dest>就像是其他那些骚扰天际的号手一样，他坚持这里是诺德人的领地，即使是在伊斯格拉谟定居在此处之前精灵统治着这里的时候也是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have had a bad experience upon entering Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>想必你在进天际省的时候有过一次糟糕的经历。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have had a bad experience upon entering Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>想必你在进天际省的时候有过一次糟糕的经历。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, Nord arguments are won by whoever shouts the loudest, and this one clearly had me bested in that regard.</Source>
      <Dest>当然啦，诺德人的道理就是看谁吼的更大声，按这逻辑我绝对是甘拜下风。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have had a bad experience upon entering Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>想必你在进天际省的时候有过一次糟糕的经历。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't need a Dragonborn to tell me that shouting is a frost monkey's greatest weapon.</Source>
      <Dest>你不用找个龙裔来告诉我龙吼是那些诺德猴子的最强的武器。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While nights often call for men to stand on chairs, it hardly has more than four legs.  No, the answer to the riddle is a dirty Khajiit thief.</Source>
      <Dest>夜里的时候我总让几个人靠在椅子上，它不可能比四条腿还多。不，谜题最后的答案是一个卑鄙的虎人小偷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A chair.</Source>
      <Dest>一张椅子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It crawls on all fours as a kitty, stands on its toes as it attempts to steal your coin purse, and dies as worthless rug under your feet.</Source>
      <Dest>它就像只小奶猫一样在地上缓慢爬行，在试图偷走你的钱包的时候垫起脚尖，最后如同一块儿一文不值的地毯一样被你踩在脚下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A chair.</Source>
      <Dest>一张椅子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Nords are a sensitive, insecure lot, overcompensating for their inferiority by treating Dunmer like second class citizens.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人十分敏感，也很缺少安全感，所以他们把黑暗精灵们当做二等公民对待，以此来补偿他们的自卑感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever since we arrived here from Morrowind we have been insulted and derided, treated like the very beasts the Nords undoubtedly are.</Source>
      <Dest>自从我们从晨风来这里之后，就一直遭受着侮辱和嘲笑。那些诺德人无疑把我们当作畜生对待。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose I shouldn't be surprised the bloody frost-huggers are oblivious to facts. </Source>
      <Dest>我想，我真不应该对这些该死的诺德猴子无视事实的把戏感到惊讶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose I shouldn't be surprised the bloody frost-huggers are oblivious to facts. </Source>
      <Dest>我想，我真不应该对这些该死的诺德猴子无视事实的把戏感到惊讶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We are the descendents of the Chimer, acolytes of the Prophet Veloth, wise folk who lived long before the Age of Men.</Source>
      <Dest>我们是北地精灵的后裔，是维勒斯的助手，在人类存在之前就生活着的睿智民族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nords, on the other hand, are not even human, but likely the product of some unholy union between apes and hairless trolls.</Source>
      <Dest>反过来说诺德人，甚至根本就算不上人类，更像是什么猿人和裸巨魔的诡异混种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nords are liars too, boasting of hospitality, warm fires and open arms, but why don't we ask the Gray Quarter just how welcoming Skryim really is.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人也都是骗子，他们总吹牛说他们很好客，会用温暖的火堆和臂膀来欢迎你。但我们为什么不问问看灰民们，在天际，所谓的“好客”究竟是怎样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As far as I'm concerned, the only way we can coexist is to eradicate their very existence.</Source>
      <Dest>就我而言，我们能和平共处的唯一方法就是把他们全都消灭干净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unfortunately, unlike the Khajiit, I can't simply make them disappear by offering them a job.  It takes a little more guile.</Source>
      <Dest>不幸的是，我不像那虎人一样可以直接给你一份工作来让你消失。那样的做法实在是有够狡猾的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You Nords are a sensitive, insecure lot, overcompensating for your inferiority by treating Dunmer like second class citizens.</Source>
      <Dest>从对待黑暗精灵们如二等公民可以看出，你们诺德人太敏感了，毫无安全感，自尊心又很强。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever since we arrived here from Morrowind we have been insulted and derided, treated like the very beasts the Nords undoubtedly are.</Source>
      <Dest>自从我们从晨风来这里之后，就一直遭受着侮辱和嘲笑。那些诺德人无疑把我们当作畜生对待。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose I shouldn't be surprised you bloody frost-huggers are oblivious to facts. </Source>
      <Dest>我想，我真不应该对你这该死的诺德猴子无视事实的把戏感到惊讶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We are the descendents of the Chimer, acolytes of the Prophet Veloth, wise folk who lived long before the Age of Men.</Source>
      <Dest>我们是北地精灵的后裔，是维勒斯的助手，在人类存在之前就生活着的睿智民族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nords, on the other hand, are not even human, but likely the product of some unholy union between apes and hairless trolls.</Source>
      <Dest>反过来说诺德人，甚至根本就算不上人类，更像是什么猿人和裸巨魔的诡异混种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your stories talk of Nord hospitality, of warm fires and open arms, but why don't we ask the Gray Quarter just how welcoming Skryim really is.</Source>
      <Dest>你口中所述的诺德酒馆，有着温暖的篝火和热情的迎接，为什么我们不找个灰民区的人问问，天际省到底是怎么欢迎他的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As far as I'm concerned, the only way we can coexist is to eradicate your very existence.</Source>
      <Dest>就我而言，我们能和平共处的唯一方法就是把他们全都消灭干净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unfortunately, unlike the Khajiit, I can't simply make you disappear by offering you a job.  It takes a little more guile.</Source>
      <Dest>不幸的是，我不像那虎人一样可以直接给你一份工作来让你消失。那样的做法实在是有够狡猾的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Nords are a sensitive, insecure lot, overcompensating for their inferiority by treating Dunmer like second class citizens.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人十分敏感，也很缺少安全感，所以他们把黑暗精灵们当做二等公民对待，以此来补偿他们的自卑感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever since we arrived here from Morrowind we have been insulted and derided, treated like the very beasts the Nords undoubtedly are.</Source>
      <Dest>自从我们从晨风来这里之后，就一直遭受着侮辱和嘲笑。那些诺德人无疑把我们当作畜生对待。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose I shouldn't be surprised the bloody frost-huggers are oblivious to facts.</Source>
      <Dest>我想，我真不应该对这些该死的诺德猴子无视事实的把戏感到惊讶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose I shouldn't be surprised the bloody frost-huggers are oblivious to facts.</Source>
      <Dest>我想，我真不应该对这些该死的诺德猴子无视事实的把戏感到惊讶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We are the descendents of the Chimer, acolytes of the Prophet Veloth, wise folk who lived long before the Age of Men.</Source>
      <Dest>我们是北地精灵的后裔，是维勒斯的助手，在人类存在之前就生活着的睿智民族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nords, on the other hand, are not even human, but likely the product of some unholy union between apes and hairless trolls.</Source>
      <Dest>反过来说诺德人，甚至根本就算不上人类，更像是什么猿人和裸巨魔的诡异混种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nords are liars too, boasting of hospitality, warm fires and open arms, but why don't we ask the Gray Quarter just how welcoming Skryim really is.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人也都是骗子，他们总吹牛说他们很好客，会用温暖的火堆和臂膀来欢迎你。但我们为什么不问问看灰民们，在天际，所谓的“好客”究竟是怎样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As far as I'm concerned, the only way we can coexist is to eradicate their very existence.</Source>
      <Dest>就我而言，我们能和平共处的唯一方法就是把他们全都消灭干净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you trying to kill Nords?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你想要杀诺德人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet unlike with you Khajiit, I can't simply make them disappear by offering them a job.  It takes a little more guile.</Source>
      <Dest>但我跟你可不一样，虎人。我没办法简简单单的给他们派个活儿，就让他们消失无踪。这需要一些手段。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was at the Bee and Barb in Riften plotting my next course of action when I met a man by the name of Sam Guevenne.</Source>
      <Dest>我在裂谷城的蜂与钩策划我的下一步行动的时候，遇到了一个叫做山姆·圭文的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you manage to summon Dravos?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算怎么召唤爪佛斯?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you manage to summon Dravos?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算怎么召唤爪佛斯?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>After a few bottles of mead, I told him of my plan to rid of the world of snow apes once and for all.  Surprisingly, he offered to help.</Source>
      <Dest>我们一起喝了几杯，然我把自己想要一劳永逸地从世界上根除那些诺德猴子的计划告诉了他。令人惊讶的是，他表示愿意帮我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But first, he wanted to play a game.  If I managed to solve his riddle, he told me, he would provide me with a powerful weapon to attain my goal.</Source>
      <Dest>但首先，他想要玩儿个游戏。他告诉我，如果我解开了他的谜题，他就会给我一个强大的武器让我达成我的目标。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you manage to summon Dravos?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算怎么召唤爪佛斯?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you manage to summon Dravos?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算怎么召唤爪佛斯?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With nothing to lose, I accepted his challenge.  In the end, the riddle proved rather easy to solve.</Source>
      <Dest>抱着光脚不怕穿鞋的这种心态，我接受了他的挑战。最终，难题解决得比我想象得要轻松。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you manage to summon Dravos?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算怎么召唤爪佛斯?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm detecting some hostility toward Nords.</Source>
      <Dest>我在找些仇视诺德的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nonsense!  I love those blonde-haired billies, with their pale skins and vapid eyes and beards that smell like wet fur.</Source>
      <Dest>胡说！我爱死那些金发小伙伴儿了，还有他们苍白的皮肤，空洞的眼神，以及那闻起来跟潮湿的毛皮一样酸爽的胡子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm detecting some hostility toward Nords.</Source>
      <Dest>我在找些仇视诺德的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And those accents!  Who wouldn't want to talk to someone who sounds like they have a drum stuck up their nose?</Source>
      <Dest>还有那口音！谁不想跟他们那种鼻音很重的人说话呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm detecting some hostility toward Nords.</Source>
      <Dest>我在找些仇视诺德的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Enough of you!  Perhaps you ought to head upstairs after all.  A Nord lover like yourself may find the view of this barbaric wasteland scenic.</Source>
      <Dest>你够了！你还是自己上去吧。或许像你这样的诺德热爱者才能从这蛮荒之地中找到什么美景。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why shouldn't I be?  You Nords have been nothing but hospitable to us Dunmer since we arrived from Morrowind.</Source>
      <Dest>为什么我不应该这样？你们诺德人在我们丹莫从晨风到这以后除了热情好客啥也没干。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem awfully friendly.</Source>
      <Dest>你真是太友好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem awfully friendly.</Source>
      <Dest>你真是太友好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now please, feel free to visit the rooftop, and I will join you shortly.</Source>
      <Dest>有空欢迎来屋顶走走，我也会陪一陪你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>To be honest, I don't think Dravos has killed anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>老实说，爪佛斯一定杀了什么人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?  You mean to tell me it isn't just you?  Every single one of those bearded horkers I've sent him...is alive?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？你是想告诉我，不光是你一个？ 那些我送给他的大胡子三牙海象……都还活着吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>To be honest, I don't think Dravos has killed anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>老实说，爪佛斯一定杀了什么人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No!  Impossible!  This is the only exit in the watchtower. You're the liar, stranger.  You're the one not to be trusted.</Source>
      <Dest>不！不可能！这是了望塔的唯一出口。你是个骗子，陌生人。我才不信你呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm a Khajiit and not all of us are thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>我是个虎人，但我们并不全是贼啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And next you will tell me Nords aren't a snow-licking, fur-sniffing, bloodthirsty band of bearded apes who carve their butter with a battleaxe.</Source>
      <Dest>接下来你会告诉我，诺德民族不是裹着毛儿舔着雪，用手里的大斧头玩黄油雕的大胡子嗜血猩猩团。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not all Khajiit are thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>并不是所有的虎人都是小偷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And next you will tell me Nords aren't a snow-licking, fur-sniffing, bloodthirsty band of bearded apes who carve their butter with a battleaxe.</Source>
      <Dest>接下来你会告诉我，诺德民族不是裹着毛儿舔着雪，用手里的大斧头玩黄油雕的大胡子嗜血猩猩团。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hold on a second my Dunmer friend.  He's not hostile.  Well, he is, but only because I've told him there are people who want him dead.</Source>
      <Dest>等一下我的丹莫朋友。他没有敌意。呃好吧，有那么一点点，但只是因为我告诉他，有人要他死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This Dremora cannot be allowed to live.</Source>
      <Dest>不能让这魔人活着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Snow-lickers, mainly, but I'm not sure he knows the difference, despite the fact that most Nords bear a striking resemblance to a horse's bottom. </Source>
      <Dest>基本上可以断定是个喜欢舔雪的诺德人，但我不知道他和其他诺德人相比有什么不同之处，毕竟，大多数的诺德人长得都跟马屁股似的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This Dremora cannot be allowed to live.</Source>
      <Dest>不能让这魔人活着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This Dremora cannot be allowed to live.</Source>
      <Dest>不能让这魔人活着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Despite you being of the master race, the fool is blind enough that he might just mistake you for one of them frost monkeys, and attack you on sight.</Source>
      <Dest>不管你是多么了不起的存在，那白痴只会把你跟那些诺德猴子视作一类，并在看见你的第一时间发起攻击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you killed him, it would only be a boon to the very Nords that seek to purge this land of our kind.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你杀了他，只有对那群想要把我们的种族从这片土地上清除干净的诺德人来说，这才算是一件好事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This Dremora cannot be allowed to live.</Source>
      <Dest>不能让这魔人活着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait!  He's not hostile.  Well, he is, but only because I've told him there are people who want him dead.</Source>
      <Dest>等等！他并无敌意。好吧，就算他有，也是因为我之前告诉过他有些人想杀了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think I'll go visit this barbarian and possibly kill him too.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我会去拜访一下这位野蛮人，说不定就把他干掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Snow-lickers, mainly, but I'm not sure he knows the difference, despite the fact that most Nords bear a striking resemblance to a horse's bottom. </Source>
      <Dest>基本上可以断定是个喜欢舔雪的诺德人，但我不知道他和其他诺德人相比有什么不同之处，毕竟，大多数的诺德人长得都跟马屁股似的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think I'll go visit this barbarian and possibly kill him too.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我会去拜访一下这位野蛮人，说不定就把他干掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think I'll go visit this barbarian and possibly kill him too.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我会去拜访一下这位野蛮人，说不定就把他干掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Given your obvious resemblance to the same, he might just attack you on sight. If you somehow managed to kill him, that would put a hitch in my plan.</Source>
      <Dest>鉴于你的长相也十分相似，他可能会在第一时间攻击你。但如果你设法把他杀掉的话，会扰乱我的计划。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unless, of course, you were willing to take his place as this tower's champion.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，除非……你愿意代替他成为这座塔的扞卫者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think I'll go visit this barbarian and possibly kill him too.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我会去拜访一下这位野蛮人，说不定就把他干掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think I will.  Do you wish to join me for drinks later?</Source>
      <Dest>我想我会的。等会儿你想和我一起去喝点什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Later?  Oh, um, yes, of course.  You Nords do enjoy your mead.</Source>
      <Dest>后来呢？哦，嗯，是啊，当然。你这个诺德家伙会享受你的蜜酒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you solved the riddle?</Source>
      <Dest>你解谜后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sam handed me a scroll.  He said that if I used it, I could summon a bound Dremora to this realm for an indefinite amount of time.</Source>
      <Dest>山姆给了我一个卷轴。他说可以用它召唤一个永久的魔族侍从。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you solved the riddle?</Source>
      <Dest>你解谜后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wasn't sure if I believed him, but it wasn't something I could try in the middle of a crowded city.  So I headed west to this watchtower.</Source>
      <Dest>我不确定是否应该相信他，但这不是我能在人声鼎沸的城市正中心所能尝试的事儿。所以我向西走到了这个了望塔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you solved the riddle?</Source>
      <Dest>你解谜后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were a couple of Orc bandits guarding the entrance.  I decided they would make a good test for my Dremora.</Source>
      <Dest>有几个兽人强盗看守着入口，我决定让他们为我的魔人准备个不错的测试。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure enough, the scroll worked, and the Dremora quickly dispatched the Orsimer, and I waited patiently at the bottom of the hill.</Source>
      <Dest>果然，卷轴起作用了。魔族迅速的杀死了兽人，而我耐心的在山低等待着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you solved the riddle?</Source>
      <Dest>你解谜后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you solved the riddle?</Source>
      <Dest>你解谜后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When he didn't return, I walked into the tower to find him on the rooftop, drinking a bottle of ale.</Source>
      <Dest>左等右等也等不到他回来，于是我边喝着麦芽酒边走入堡垒去屋顶上找他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's something funny about this Dremora.  He doesn't respond to all my commands, or any of them for that matter.</Source>
      <Dest>关于魔人有一些有意思的事情。他不会对我所有的命令都做出回应，实际上他对所有命令都不作回应。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you solved the riddle?</Source>
      <Dest>你解谜后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It made no difference to me, as long as he kills the bloody snow monkeys I sent upstairs.  Only now I'm starting to wonder...</Source>
      <Dest>这对我来说没什么区别，只要他们能杀掉那些我哄骗上楼的该死的诺德猴子。只是我现在才开始有点儿好奇……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you solved the riddle?</Source>
      <Dest>你解谜后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should watch your tongue, considering I'm Nord.</Source>
      <Dest>在一个诺德人面前你应该管好你的嘴巴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell me ape, do you know how to make a Nord laugh on Loredas?  Tell him something funny on Morndas. </Source>
      <Dest>告诉我，猴子。你知道怎么在周六的时候逗乐一个诺德人吗？只要把星期一发生的趣事告诉他就行啦。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You Nords are as sharp as an anvil and just as light on your feet.   Too dull to comprehend an insult, too slow to do anything about it.</Source>
      <Dest>这些诺德人还真是像铁砧一样一样敏锐啊，就跟他们的脚步一样轻。他们甚至反应不过来这是种侮辱，他们就是做什么事都要慢一拍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should watch your tongue, considering I'm Nord.</Source>
      <Dest>在一个诺德人面前你应该管好你的嘴巴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should watch your tongue, considering I'm Nord.</Source>
      <Dest>在一个诺德人面前你应该管好你的嘴巴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll say whatever I please and you'll just stand there with your mouth open.</Source>
      <Dest>我会说出自己的请求，而你只要站在那儿大张着嘴就行了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So what?  You should try mocking your friends sometimes.  It's rather liberating.</Source>
      <Dest>那又如何？你也可以试试看取笑你的朋友。这是一种很好的发泄方式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should watch your tongue.  Some of my best friends are Nords.</Source>
      <Dest>你说话注意点，我有些最好的朋友是诺德人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you know how to get a Nord to laugh on Loredas?  Tell him something funny on Morndas. </Source>
      <Dest>你知道怎么在周六的时候逗乐一个诺德人吗？只要把星期一发生的趣事告诉他就行啦。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should watch your tongue.  Some of my best friends are Nords.</Source>
      <Dest>你说话注意点，我有些最好的朋友是诺德人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Nords are as sharp as an anvil and just as light on their feet.   Too dull to comprehend an insult, too slow to do anything about it.</Source>
      <Dest>这些诺德人还真是像铁砧一样敏锐啊，就跟他们的脚步一样轻。他们甚至反应不过来这是种侮辱，他们就是做什么事都要慢一拍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should watch your tongue.  Some of my best friends are Nords.</Source>
      <Dest>你说话注意点，我有些最好的朋友是诺德人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I once offered a Nord 100 septims to smash ten bottles of ale over his head.  When he agreed, I smashed nine and left without paying a single coin.</Source>
      <Dest>有一次我跟个诺德人说，让我在他脑袋上砸10瓶麦芽酒就给他100金币。他同意了，我砸了9瓶转身就走，一块钱也没给他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I once saw a Nord walk into a blacksmith shop and demand a refund.  He placed the sword on the counter, and screamed at the smith.</Source>
      <Dest>有一次我看到个诺德人去铁匠铺要求退货。他把剑丢到店员面前，然后对那个铁匠大吼大叫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The smith sighed and told the Nord to return in an hour.  When the Nord left, he flipped the sword to face the opposite direction.</Source>
      <Dest>铁匠叹了口气，然后告诉诺德人一个小时之后再回来。当诺德人离开之后，他就把剑刃翻了个个儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever hear the one about the Nord who requested to be buried at sea?  His entire family died trying to dig his grave.</Source>
      <Dest>听人说过那个想要被葬在海里的诺德人的事儿吗？他全家都为了给他在海里挖坟墓而死光了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What's the difference between a Nord and a mudcrab?  The crab part.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人和泥蟹的不同之处是什么？诺德人不是蟹，只是滩烂泥。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not just Nords.  Cats too. You know the difference between a sabrecat and a Khajiit?  Sabrecats actually hunt their food instead of stealing it.</Source>
      <Dest>不只是诺德人，那些猫咪也是。你知道剑齿虎和虎人之间的区别吗？实际上剑齿虎是靠自己去猎取食物的，而不是像你们那样去偷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not just Nords.  Lizards too. You know the difference between an Argonian and a horker loaf?  The loaf can feed its family.</Source>
      <Dest>不不仅仅是诺德人，亚龙人也是一样。你知道亚龙人和三牙海象的区别吗？一只海象至少能养活自己的家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not just Nords.  You cats too. You know the difference between a sabrecat and a Khajiit?  Sabrecats actually hunt their food instead of stealing it.</Source>
      <Dest>不只是诺德人。你们这些猫咪也是。你知道剑齿虎和虎人之间的区别吗？实际上剑齿虎是自己猎取食物的，而不是像你们那样去偷。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not just Nords. You lizards too. You know the difference between an Argonian and a horker loaf?  The loaf can feed its family.</Source>
      <Dest>不仅仅是诺德人，你们这些大爬虫也一样！你知道亚龙人和三牙海象的区别吗？一只海象至少能养活自己的家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, which is precisely why I do enjoy listening to their screams.  They're quite raucous.   Sometimes I think I hear two or three at the same time.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，这正是为什么我喜欢听他们的尖叫声。那声音刺耳万分。有时候我想自己同时听到了两三声尖叫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You really hate Nords, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你痛恨诺德人，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which is impossible, but such is the depth of their pain that it rebounds across the walls.</Source>
      <Dest>这是不可能的，那只是他们痛苦的哀嚎从墙壁反射的回声。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dravos told me about what's going on here.</Source>
      <Dest>爪佛斯告诉了我这里发生的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh he did, did he?  Blasted traitor. Don't think you've won yet, you dirty snow ape.  You'll get yours as soon as I figure out how to best give it.</Source>
      <Dest>哦他那么做了，是吗？该死的叛徒。别以为你已经赢了，你个肮脏的雪猴子。等我想出怎么对付你好，我就会把你做的尽数奉还。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dravos and I had a little talk.</Source>
      <Dest>爪佛斯跟我简短地谈过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Talk?  What in Oblivion is he doing talking to people?  What if you were a Nord?  We can't afford to let any of those snow apes loose!</Source>
      <Dest>探讨？他跟这些人废话到底他妈的想干啥啊？如果你是个诺德人你会怎么做？我们不能让这些雪猴子们为所欲为！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dravos and I had a little talk.</Source>
      <Dest>爪佛斯跟我简短地谈过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come to think of it, you were up there for some time. So what exactly did Dravos tell you? Whatever it is, I'll have you know my conscience is clear.</Source>
      <Dest>好好想想吧，到了那里之后你还有些时间。爪佛斯到底跟你说了什么？不管他说了什么，我都问心无愧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Seems like a rather poor justification for murder.</Source>
      <Dest>似乎这场谋杀没有什么正当理由。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only justification I need for sending Nords to their deaths is that they are Nords.  All other argument is invalid.</Source>
      <Dest>我骗诺德人去送死的唯一的理由就因为他们是诺德人。在没别的了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What?  There's a Dremora up there?  Isn't that dangerous?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？那里有一个魔人？  危险吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Extremely.  But Dravos keeps to the roof, and I stay downstairs.  I've convinced him that's the safest place for him to hide.</Source>
      <Dest>对极了！不过爪佛斯守在房顶，而我待在楼下。我已经说服他藏在那里最安全了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then when some foolish, golden-haired monkey of a Nord shows up, I insist that he check out the view.</Source>
      <Dest>每当有些愚蠢的金发诺德猴子出现的时候，我都会坚持劝他上楼看看风景。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What?  There's a Dremora up there?  Isn't that dangerous?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？那里有一个魔人？  危险吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He climbs up the stairs, and never comes back down.  And just like that, one less frost-licker inhabiting Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>他爬上楼梯，再也不会回来了。就这样，天际省又少了一个喜好舔冰的诺德人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What?  There's a Dremora up there?  Isn't that dangerous?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？那里有一个魔人？  危险吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not at all.  Dravos keeps to the roof, and I stay downstairs.  I've convinced him that's the safest place for him to hide.</Source>
      <Dest>一点儿也不。爪佛斯守在房顶，而我待在楼下。我已经说服他藏在那里最安全了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's a barbarian up there?  Isn't that dangerous?</Source>
      <Dest>上面还有个野蛮人？那不是很危险？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, sometimes I can't help it if some greedy snow bard ambushes me and runs up the stairs.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，有时候，一些贪婪的诺德诗人伏击我，然后跑上楼梯，对此我也无能为力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's a barbarian up there?  Isn't that dangerous?</Source>
      <Dest>上面还有个野蛮人？那不是很危险？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's a barbarian up there?  Isn't that dangerous?</Source>
      <Dest>上面还有个野蛮人？那不是很危险？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These frost thieves can smell treasure like a rat smells cheese.  Especially if that treasure belongs to a Dunmer. </Source>
      <Dest>这些诺德贼能像老鼠闻到奶酪一样嗅到财宝的所在。尤其是那些属于暗精灵的宝藏。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's a barbarian up there?  Isn't that dangerous?</Source>
      <Dest>上面还有个野蛮人？那不是很危险？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father always said Nords were masters of arrogation.  They think everything in Skyrim belongs to them, from our souls to our toenail clippings.</Source>
      <Dest>我父亲常说，诺德人是掠夺大师。他们认为天际省的一切都属于他们，上至我们的灵魂，下到我们的脚趾甲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's a barbarian up there?  Isn't that dangerous?</Source>
      <Dest>上面还有个野蛮人？那不是很危险？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dravos has killed more than a dozen white-skins this week.  Riften should send us some boon for cleansing their hold of criminal scum.</Source>
      <Dest>德拉沃斯这星期已经杀了好几群白皮佬了。裂谷应该为我们清洗里这些十恶不赦的渣滓的据点发点奖金。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why, at no other place can you get a clear view of the fall forest, the northern sky, and the chain of mountains that form the spine of the world.</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？再没有其他地方能让你如此清晰的欣赏到如此美景了。秋日的树林，北方的天空，还有从世界之脊绵延而来的群山。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's so great about the view?</Source>
      <Dest>这儿的景色有什么，如此壮观？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's so great about the view?</Source>
      <Dest>这儿的景色有什么，如此壮观？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It would be a shame for a fine Nord such as yourself to come all this way and not take in such a marvelous view of their ancestral homeland.</Source>
      <Dest>对一个像你一样优秀的诺德人来说，大老远过来却没有领略到祖先故乡的美景，真是个遗憾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's so great about the view?</Source>
      <Dest>这儿的景色有什么，如此壮观？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you please, the stairs are right over there.  I swear, the views are so mesmerizing, you may never come back.</Source>
      <Dest>楼梯就在那里，要走的话请随意。我发誓，这里的风景迷人到你都永不会想回来的程度。。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, there's some sort of party going on upstairs.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，楼上正在举行一场聚会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What are you babbling on about?  Party?  Upstairs?  Nonsense, I've heard only screaming!</Source>
      <Dest>你扯啥呢？派对？楼上？扯淡，我只听见了尖叫声！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, there's some sort of party going on upstairs.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，楼上正在举行一场聚会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nevertheless, it's obvious Dravos has been doing far more work with his tongue than his mace.  Well, whatever he's told you, my conscience is clear.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，很明显爪佛斯的舌头比他的锤子利索。好吧，不管他告诉你什么了，我问心无愧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're also stupid ones.  My original plan was to walk into a crowded tavern and throw a well crafted axe on the floor.</Source>
      <Dest>你也是一个蠢货。我原来的计划是走进一家拥挤的小酒馆，然后再往地上扔把做工精良的斧子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords are brave warriors.  Not even a Dremora could kill them all.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人士勇敢的战士，甚至魔人都无法杀光他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was certain you bloodthirsty ice blondes would maul and tear each other to shreds fighting over the axe.</Source>
      <Dest>我很确定你们这些嗜血的金发猴子会为争夺这斧头把彼此撕成碎片。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords are brave warriors.  Not even a Dremora could kill them all.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人士勇敢的战士，甚至魔人都无法杀光他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords are brave warriors.  Not even a Dremora could kill them all.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人士勇敢的战士，甚至魔人都无法杀光他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it turns out I overestimated your people's ability to recognize fine craftsmanship.</Source>
      <Dest>可后来发现我真是高估了他们对精致工艺的鉴别能力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords are brave warriors.  Not even a Dremora could kill them all.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人士勇敢的战士，甚至魔人都无法杀光他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My current strategy has proven far more effective.  I now appeal to your idiotic sense of pride.</Source>
      <Dest>我目前的策略就比那有效得多了。愚蠢的自豪感，那才是他们的死穴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords are brave warriors.  Not even a Dremora could kill them all.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人士勇敢的战士，甚至魔人都无法杀光他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>From my dealings with your people, it seems Nords have an unshakeable attachment to this frozen pool of vomit they call home.</Source>
      <Dest>从我跟你们这些人打交道来看，似乎诺德人都对被他们叫做家乡的这摊冰冻的呕吐物有着不可救药的依恋感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords are brave warriors.  Not even a Dremora could kill them all.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人士勇敢的战士，甚至魔人都无法杀光他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You being a beard-sniffer yourself, you must be perfectly aware of this.</Source>
      <Dest>而你也是个鼻子周围胡子拉碴的家伙，你必须完全意识到这一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords are brave warriors.  Not even a Dremora could kill them all.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人士勇敢的战士，甚至魔人都无法杀光他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're also stupid ones.  My original plan was to walk into a crowded tavern and throw a well crafted axe on the floor.</Source>
      <Dest>他们也都是些蠢货。我原来的计划是走进一家拥挤的小酒馆，然后再往地上扔把做工精良的斧子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords are brave warriors.  Not even a Dremora could kill them all.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人士勇敢的战士，甚至魔人都无法杀光他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was certain the bloodthirsty ice blondes would maul and tear each other to shreds fighting over the axe.</Source>
      <Dest>我确信那些嗜血的金发猴子会为争夺这斧头把彼此撕成碎片。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords are brave warriors.  Not even a Dremora could kill them all.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人士勇敢的战士，甚至魔人都无法杀光他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it turns out I overestimated their ability to recognize fine craftsmanship.</Source>
      <Dest>可后来发现我真是高估了他们对精致工艺的鉴别能力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My current strategy has proven far more effective.  I now appeal to their idiotic sense of pride.</Source>
      <Dest>我目前的策略就比那有效得多了。愚蠢的自豪感，那才是他们的死穴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords are brave warriors.  Not even a Dremora could kill them all.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人士勇敢的战士，甚至魔人都无法杀光他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords are brave warriors.  Not even a Dremora could kill them all.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人士勇敢的战士，甚至魔人都无法杀光他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>From my dealings with them, it seems the Nords have an unshakeable attachment to this frozen pool of vomit they call home.</Source>
      <Dest>从我与他们打的交道来看，似乎诺德人都对被他们叫做家乡的这摊冰冻的呕吐物有着不可救药的依恋感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I suppose that's as good a reason as any.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这是一个好理由。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course.  Now, some of my Dunmer friends think I'm overreacting.  They tell me not to condemn an entire race on the actions of a single drunk.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。这会儿已经有些锻莫朋友觉得我的反应过度了。他们跟我说不要因为一个醉汉的个别行为就谴责整个种族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I suppose that's as good a reason as any.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这是一个好理由。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that wasn't my first encounter with a snow-licker.  I've met Nords from Morrowind to High Rock.</Source>
      <Dest>额，这不是我第一次遇到一个喜欢舔雪的家伙。我从晨风到高岩一路上都碰到诺德人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I suppose that's as good a reason as any.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这是一个好理由。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And in addition to their love of cold winters, smelly furs, and bad poetry, they al have one thing in common.  A superiority complex.</Source>
      <Dest>除了他们对寒冷的冬天，发臭的毛皮，以及糟糕的诗歌的喜爱之外，他们还有一个共同点。优越感十足。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Make it quick.</Source>
      <Dest>快点好吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is it?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you need something?</Source>
      <Dest>你要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Please do check out the view before you go.</Source>
      <Dest>你出发前请先查看下四周。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Be gone.</Source>
      <Dest>滚开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>About time.</Source>
      <Dest>是时候了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
