<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Uh...Berg not know how say without face get punched.  But maybe bard throat itchy, so not sing so good?</Source>
      <Dest>额……伯格不知道怎么说才能不被脸上揍一拳。但也许是吟游诗人喉咙痒痒。也许唱得不好听？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>K'voja!  Berg here for mead sauce.  Bring cheese as trade.</Source>
      <Dest>卡维加！这里的伯格想要些够劲的蜜酒。他想用些奶酪来交换。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Those words you're using don't mean anything.  They're nonsense.</Source>
      <Dest>你说这些话根本没有意义。胡言乱语根本听不懂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg is very sorry.  He does not talk common tongue well.  The Jo'tun say much same of his tries at their words.  </Source>
      <Dest>伯格很抱歉，他不能很好地说这个语言。求伦说什么伯格就去模仿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Those words you're using don't mean anything.  They're nonsense.</Source>
      <Dest>你说这些话根本没有意义。胡言乱语根本听不懂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg spend much time to listen and talk like Jo'tun, Giant men, just as he try very hard to speak tongue of Ha'mari, common man.  </Source>
      <Dest>伯格花了很多时间去聆听求伦——也就是巨人——并像它们一样讲话，就像他也很努力地去学习哈玛里的语言，也就是普通人类的语言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Those words you're using don't mean anything.  They're nonsense.</Source>
      <Dest>你说这些话根本没有意义。胡言乱语根本听不懂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But in end Berg only make sense to Berg.</Source>
      <Dest>但是到头来伯格还是没法让别人明白他是什么意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Noisy bard? How dare you besmirch my lady's honor!  Recant your words, fiend!</Source>
      <Dest>吵杂的吟游诗人？你怎么敢玷污我女士的荣誉！收回那句话，可恶的家伙！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg not know what person say.  This one talk like rabbit in heat.</Source>
      <Dest>Berg not know what person say.  This one talk like rabbit in heat.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's sort of barbaric, don't you think?</Source>
      <Dest>你不觉得这样很野蛮吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg think world of men very strange if killing whole Jo'tun camp okay but keeping Jarl's ears is wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>伯格觉得这个世界的人都好奇怪。杀死求伦营地内的所有人就没问题，但切下领主的耳朵就不行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Giants haven't shown you how to make cheese?</Source>
      <Dest>巨人们有告诉过你怎么做乳酪吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, Jo'tun not trust round-ear like Berg.  They think him sell secret for more mead sauce.  They smell on Berg's breath.</Source>
      <Dest>没有，求伦不信任像伯格一样圆耳朵的人。他们认为他会将这个秘密卖出去换来更蜂蜜酒酱，他们从伯格的呼吸中闻到气味。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Giants haven't shown you how to make cheese?</Source>
      <Dest>巨人们有告诉过你怎么做乳酪吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They let him milk the moh'roktha, mammoth, but do not show him how make cheese.  This Berg's biggest shame.</Source>
      <Dest>他们给他喝莫鲁卡奢奶，猛犸的奶，但就是不教他做奶酪。这是伯格一生最大的耻辱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Giants haven't shown you how to make cheese?</Source>
      <Dest>巨人们有告诉过你怎么做乳酪吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When Berg ready, the Jo'tun will take stone and make mark in chest, to show Berg is man.  </Source>
      <Dest>当伯格准备好，求伦就会拿起石头在胸口画标记，证明伯格是个真男人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where did you learn to speak the common tongue?</Source>
      <Dest>这些平民腔调你是从哪里学来的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg go to Windpeak Inn.  Hear noisy pirate and more noisy bard.  Pick up tongue and mead for drink.</Source>
      <Dest>伯格去了风岳旅店，遇到了到吵的海盗和更吵的诗人，在那学会了说话和喝酒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>But seriously, how many words do you have for mammoth?</Source>
      <Dest>说真的，你们到底有多少长毛象的字词？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Jo'tun have many word for moh'roktha, one called mammoth. Word for one who give best milk, and one for bad milk too.  </Source>
      <Dest>求伦有很多字词是说莫鲁卡奢，也就是长毛象。有个名字的会带来最美味的牛奶，而有的则是带来最差的牛奶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>But seriously, how many words do you have for mammoth?</Source>
      <Dest>说真的，你们到底有多少长毛象的字词？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Word to tell difference with man moh'rothka and beast of wild kind.  And word for one who give meat. Berg not like this word.</Source>
      <Dest>字词告诉人莫鲁卡奢跟野生的野兽有什么不一样。还有一个词是用来叫肉的。伯格不喜欢那个字词。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They do say Nord milk is quite delicious...</Source>
      <Dest>他们确实说诺德牛奶很好喝。。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg thought as much but Nord he know prefer drink milk from cow.</Source>
      <Dest>伯格也是如此想，他认识的诺德人都比较喜欢喝从牛身上搾出来的奶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As far as I'm concerned, Berg needs to shut up and never speak again.</Source>
      <Dest>就我个人的观点来看， 伯格必须闭嘴并永远保持沉默。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Skevragg ragnok!</Source>
      <Dest>撒克佛格罗诺！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can't possibly believe that you're an actual Giant.</Source>
      <Dest>你根本不可能相信你是个真正的巨人吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg born Jo'tun.  Is raised by azgrok.  Clan.  Maybe clan sometime treat Berg bad.  </Source>
      <Dest>伯格生来就是求伦。由阿兹国，一个部落养大。也许部落的人有时候对伯格不是太好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can't possibly believe that you're an actual Giant.</Source>
      <Dest>你根本不可能相信你是个真正的巨人吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Give him metal club from bandit.  Not let him make cheese.  But him still clan.</Source>
      <Dest>给他从强盗拿来的铁棍，不让他造奶酪，但他仍然是部落的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me something about your people.</Source>
      <Dest>给我说说你人民的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Jo'tun, Giant, walk land and hunt.  Head of troll makes good trophy on pelt.  Berg pelt is empty.  Troll head too heavy for puny Berg.</Source>
      <Dest>求伦，巨人，出去狩猎。巨魔的头用来做毛皮是个很好的战利品。伯格没有战利品，巨魔的头对伯格来说太重了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me something about your people.</Source>
      <Dest>给我说说你人民的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some Jo'tun clan color rock in blood.  Nord say it art.  Berg think it trap for vampire.</Source>
      <Dest>Some Jo'tun clan color rock in blood.  Nord say it art.  Berg think it trap for vampire.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me something about your people.</Source>
      <Dest>给我说说你人民的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some say green ones are cousin to Jo'tun.  Berg get angry if green one get chest mark and mate before Berg.</Source>
      <Dest>有些人说绿色的家伙是求伦的亲戚，如果有个绿色的家伙在胸前有标志，还在伯格面前交配的话，伯格会很生气的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why the ears?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么是耳朵？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So dead Jarl hear from grave.  Hear wife moan like wolf at moon when Berg make her woman.</Source>
      <Dest>So dead Jarl hear from grave.  Hear wife moan like wolf at moon when Berg make her woman.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Noisy?  But she's the finest bard in all of Dawnstar.</Source>
      <Dest>噪音？但她是晨星城里最好的吟游诗人耶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg no like. Ta'lak moh'roktha. She grunt like mammoth.  But maybe make better milk.</Source>
      <Dest>伯格就是不喜欢。用莫鲁卡奢来说，她的声就像猛犸一样，但也许可以提供更好的牛奶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There are amulets you can wear to increase your speechcraft.</Source>
      <Dest>这有个护身符，你可以戴上它来增加你的口才。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg not wear shiny trinket like house woman!  He learn man tongue with hard work. </Source>
      <Dest>伯格不会像婊子一样戴那些闪闪发亮的饰物！他是个豪迈的真男人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is a Nord doing living with Giants?</Source>
      <Dest>一个诺德人跟巨人生活在一起是打算做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg is not Nord.  Him Jo'tun, Giant.  Just puny type is all.  Real Nord cranky and hate everyone who not him.</Source>
      <Dest>伯格不是诺德人。他，是求伦，是个巨人，只不过是矮小了一点。真正的诺德人脾气暴躁，讨厌他以外的所有人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Speaking of which, you seem to be covered in them. Big fleas.</Source>
      <Dest>说起这个，你完全被他们蒙蔽了。小丑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, big crowd.  Berg give them new home in big jerk's pants.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，有一大群。伯格给了他们一个新的家，在我的裤裆内。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is this in any way related to the nightmares in Dawnstar?</Source>
      <Dest>这和晨星的噩梦有关吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>T'awas, ut'rah.  Dream change in Dawn's Star. Berg see bad things, scary things.  Things to make him lose sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>吐瓦希，阿喇。晨星城的梦改变了它，但伯格只梦到不好的，恐怖的事，令他失眠的梦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Big one?  You aren't exactly small yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>大个子？你自己一点也不小只。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, Berg is very puny for Giant.  Puny mammoth still is more size than big flea.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，伯格在巨人当中算很矮小的了，但一只猛犸依然比只大跳蚤要大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could train at the Bard's College, but they'd probably just make you fetch.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以在吟游诗人学院接受培训，但他们也许只会让你当个跑腿的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is fetch?  You mean like hound chase stick?  Berg not know why this good for speech.</Source>
      <Dest>什么取东西？你指猎犬追着棒那样？伯格不知道为什么这会让口才变好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So Olga was a cow?</Source>
      <Dest>所以奥尔加是一头牛吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Even cow can be froma.  In this world all nirnook have spirit inside.</Source>
      <Dest>即使牛也可以做成奶酪，在这个世界上所有牛奶中也有灵魂存在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Jarls around here don't seem to tolerate Giant camps.</Source>
      <Dest>在这里领主不喜欢有别的势力</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Jarl is nasty person.  Pays many men to attack Jo'tun home.  Berg defend camp many times with his metal club.</Source>
      <Dest>领主是个令人不快的人物。请了很多人去攻打求伦的家。伯格用他的铁棍保护了营地很多次。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Jarls around here don't seem to tolerate Giant camps.</Source>
      <Dest>在这里领主不喜欢有别的势力</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If he ever met Jarl, he would cut off ears and wear around neck as trophy.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他见到领主，他会切下他的耳朵并当成战利品一样挂在颈上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just the ears?  Why not the eyes?</Source>
      <Dest>只有耳朵？为什么不是眼睛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If Jarl no see, image left to mind.  When Berg mounts woman for first time he will tell Jarl's ears to say hello to wife.</Source>
      <Dest>如果领主看不见，剩下的就只能在心里想像。当伯格骑完他人生中第一个女人，他会对着他的耳朵替他妻子问好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just the ears?  Why not the eyes?</Source>
      <Dest>只有耳朵？为什么不是眼睛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Second time he tell Jarl it sister.  Soon Berg will just slaughter pig and Jarl will think wife is much pleasure.  He will make it true in mind.</Source>
      <Dest>他第二次跟领主说话会是说他妹妹。很快伯格就会杀猪，而领主就会想他的妻子已经很开心了。他会确切地记在心上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Berg...is that your name?</Source>
      <Dest>伯格...是你的名字吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Jo'tun, Giant, give no name.  Ha'mari, Man, give name many moons ago.  Came to Berg inside dra'makr.  Dream.  </Source>
      <Dest>求伦，巨人，没有名字。哈玛里，人类，给名字，在几个月前。梦中人来找伯格，在梦里。梦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Berg...is that your name?</Source>
      <Dest>伯格...是你的名字吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There him met man.  Sun hair, sky eyes.  Talk in Ha'mari tongue.  Give Berg his name.  Bergri...Bergrah...it too long.  Him make short. </Source>
      <Dest>在那儿他和人类见面。太阳色的头发，天空色的眼。跟哈玛里说话。给了伯格一个名字，伯格…伯格拉…太长了，他就说成短的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned a Dream Man.</Source>
      <Dest>你刚刚提到一个梦中情人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sawatt, ut'rah.  Berg talk Dream Man many time.  Dra'markr Ha'mari give Berg name.  Show him friend.  Friend name Olga.</Source>
      <Dest>斯瓦，阿喇。伯格跟梦中人讲过很多次话。在梦中，哈玛里给了伯格名字。介绍了他的朋友奥加给我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't eat meat?</Source>
      <Dest>你不吃肉？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Jo'tun not think moh'roktha, mammoth, is azgrok, clan.  Berg think mammoth is family.  It wrong to eat azgrok when skeever is plenty.</Source>
      <Dest>求伦不认为莫鲁卡奢，长毛象，是阿兹粿部落的。伯格认为猛犸是家人，如果还有恶鼠吃的话，吃自己的族人是不好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't eat meat?</Source>
      <Dest>你不吃肉？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg try save froma, friend.  Him use metal club to smack behind.  But moh'roktha no move.  It make Berg sad to lose friend, but he is not chief yet.</Source>
      <Dest>伯格想救朋友。他用铁棍从背后敲打，但莫鲁卡奢一点反应也没有。这使到伯格因为失去了朋友而很伤心，但他还不是酋长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>K'voja! Well met, big one.</Source>
      <Dest>卡维加！你好，大个子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is the Giant tongue different?  I mean besides the 100 words for mammoth cheese.</Source>
      <Dest>巨人的语法有甚么不一样吗？我是说100个形容长毛象乳酪以外的字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Skevragg! Like stone and fire.  Ha'mari talk with mouth.  Jo'tun talk with stomach.  Muscle like string on lute.  Bones like drum.  Word is song.</Source>
      <Dest>撒克佛格！就像石头和火。哈马里用嘴巴谈话。求伦用胃谈话。肌肉就像鲁特琴的音符。骨头就像鼓。字词是歌曲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting observation, sir. Any thoughts on the other races?</Source>
      <Dest>很有趣的看法，先生。你对其他种族还有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg not know why K'hottra, cat people, wear dead coat on living one.</Source>
      <Dest>伯格不知道为什么虎人，猫人要把死了的生物的毛皮盖在身上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting observation, sir. Any thoughts on the other races?</Source>
      <Dest>很有趣的看法，先生。你对其他种族还有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He think some green one look like big dog and other green one have head so pointy you touch and make bleed.</Source>
      <Dest>他觉得一些绿色的家伙看起来就像只大狗，另一些绿色的家伙的头很尖，摸一下便会流血。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting observation, sir. Any thoughts on the other races?</Source>
      <Dest>很有趣的看法，先生。你对其他种族还有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He think lizard all look same and blue one look like devil.</Source>
      <Dest>他觉得每只蜥蝪都是同一个样子，而蓝色那种看起来就像恶魔一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting observation, sir. Any thoughts on the other races?</Source>
      <Dest>很有趣的看法，先生。你对其他种族还有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He not know why brown one wear tent on head to hide bald spot.  Berg wear no fur on head but he not shamed.  Even if no horns.</Source>
      <Dest>他不知道为什么棕色那个要戴个帐篷在头来隐藏他的秃头。伯格不会在头上放任何东西但他不觉得羞愧，即使他头上没角。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting observation, sir. Any thoughts on the other races?</Source>
      <Dest>很有趣的看法，先生。你对其他种族还有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He think Imperial bossy and brown elf sneaky.  But Berg like Breton.  Has yet to meet one he not like.  Has yet to meet one.</Source>
      <Dest>他认为那些帝国娘娘腔和棕色的精灵都是鬼鬼祟祟的。但伯格喜欢布莱顿人，未见过一个他不喜欢的，没遇过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting observation, sir. Any thoughts on the other races?</Source>
      <Dest>很有趣的看法，先生。你对其他种族还有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg not know why K'hottra, cat people, wear dead coat on living one.</Source>
      <Dest>伯格不知道为什么虎人，猫人要把死了的生物的毛皮盖在身上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting observation, sir. Any thoughts on the other races?</Source>
      <Dest>很有趣的看法，先生。你对其他种族还有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He think some green one look like big dog and other green one have head so pointy you touch and make bleed.</Source>
      <Dest>他觉得一些绿色的家伙看起来就像只大狗，另一些绿色的家伙的头很尖，摸一下便会流血。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting observation, sir. Any thoughts on the other races?</Source>
      <Dest>很有趣的看法，先生。你对其他种族还有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He think lizard all look same and blue one look like devil.</Source>
      <Dest>他觉得每只蜥蝪都是同一个样子，而蓝色那种看起来就像恶魔一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting observation, sir. Any thoughts on the other races?</Source>
      <Dest>很有趣的看法，先生。你对其他种族还有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He not know why brown one wear tent on head to hide bald spot.  Berg wear no fur on head but he not shamed.  Even if no horns.</Source>
      <Dest>他不知道为什么棕色那个要戴个帐篷在头来隐藏他的秃头。伯格不会在头上放任何东西但他不觉得羞愧，即使他头上没角。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting observation, sir. Any thoughts on the other races?</Source>
      <Dest>很有趣的看法，先生。你对其他种族还有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He think Imperial bossy and brown elf sneaky.  But Berg like Breton.  Has yet to meet one he not like.</Source>
      <Dest>他认为那些帝国娘娘腔和棕色的精灵都是鬼鬼祟祟的。但伯格喜欢布莱顿人，未见过一个他不喜欢的，没遇过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry, it was just a dream.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，那只是个梦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I say jakranu, the word of thanks.  Berg not wish to see the dra'makr two time.</Source>
      <Dest>我会说贾克纽，感谢的意思。伯格不想再次见到梦中者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>K'voja! Well met, big one.</Source>
      <Dest>卡维加！你好，大个子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where did the dream man take Olga?</Source>
      <Dest>那个梦游男把奥尔加放哪儿了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dream Man take Olga to Jo'tun.  F'jorok Nah, him say, peace offer.  Dream Man leave Olga with Jo'tun and go home.   He not see boy behind tree. </Source>
      <Dest>梦中人带奥尔加去见求伦。佛乔约克 拿哈，他说道，意为“求和”。梦中人丢下奥尔加和求伦，然后回家了。他没有看到躲在树后面的男孩。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where did the dream man take Olga?</Source>
      <Dest>那个梦游男把奥尔加放哪儿了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Jo'tun, Giant, get club.  Jo'tun try to kill Olga.  Boy run.  He run to Olga.  Throws body in way.  Froma L'hara Vin.  To save a friend.</Source>
      <Dest>求伦，巨人，手中的棍棒落下。求伦试图杀死奥尔加，那孩子跑了。他奔向奥尔加，把尸体扔在路当中。谢天谢地。拯救了一个朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where did the dream man take Olga?</Source>
      <Dest>那个梦游男把奥尔加放哪儿了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Boy eyes wet with sad.  Jo'tun give boy strange look.  But no kill.  Then Berg wake up.  Bad, bad dream.</Source>
      <Dest>男孩的眼睛氤氲着泪光。求伦看着男孩儿，表情有点奇怪。但没有杀人。然后伯格醒来了。那是个噩梦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this dream.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我这个梦的内容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is very strong dream.  Dark night, and cold wind.  Berg sees puny Nord boy shaking in hay bed.</Source>
      <Dest>这是个非常清晰的梦，漆黑的夜晚与冷冽的风。伯格见到那个诺德小男孩在干草床上颤抖着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this dream.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我这个梦的内容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Boy climbs roof of house. Skevragg! Stupid boy. He thinks the light of moons is sun. On ground he sees light. Fire. Dream Man. </Source>
      <Dest>男孩爬上去屋顶。撒克佛格！那个笨蛋，他把月亮当成太阳。在地上他看到光，火，和梦人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this dream.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我这个梦的内容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dream Man smears bright mud on Olga. Olga looks up at boy, but he say nothing.  Olga brown hide now color and no color like pelt of Khott'ra. </Source>
      <Dest>梦中人把一些鲜明的泥涂在奥尔加身上，奥尔加望着那个男孩，但他什么也没有说。奥尔加棕色的兽皮上了色，而且也再没有任何颜色像卡特拉的毛皮一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this dream.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我这个梦的内容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dream Man take Olga from home.  Boy follows.  Boy chase.   Boy face wet with scare.  So cold, but blood is hot like sick.</Source>
      <Dest>梦人把奥尔加从家里带走。小男孩跟踪他们，小男孩追着他们，小男孩吓得脸也湿了。很冷，但血却热得是病了一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I've noticed there are no female giants.</Source>
      <Dest>我发现好像从来没听说过有女的巨人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Jo'tun Fraulen no come when Ha'mari come.  Berg not yet see one either.  Jo'tun, Giant, tell him Fraulen only come when time to mate.</Source>
      <Dest>女求伦在人类来的时候都没来。伯格也没见过。求伦，巨人告诉他女人只会在交配的时候才会出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I've noticed there are no female giants.</Source>
      <Dest>我发现好像从来没听说过有女的巨人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg not know if this joke to make him wait for woman that not there. Berg not want to wait until world ends.  Him has needs.</Source>
      <Dest>伯格不知道这是不是一个笑话，去令他等待一个永远不会出现的女人。伯格不想等到世界结束那天，他也有需要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I can understand you just fine.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以理解你现在很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I say jakranu, word of thanks.</Source>
      <Dest>我会说贾克纽，感谢的意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We seriously need to find you a woman.</Source>
      <Dest>我真的觉得该给你找个女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Berg will not settle for puny Nord.  Him will wait until Jo'tun carve mark in Berg's chest, to say he man and ready to mate.</Source>
      <Dest>伯格不会接受一个弱小的诺德人。他会等到求伦在他的胸上雕上标志，来证明他是个真男人和准备好交配。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Giants I've come across just seem to grunt.</Source>
      <Dest>我遇到的巨人都只会咕噜咕噜的叫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>T'awas, ut'rah.  Berg voice sloppy like wet cheese. Make Jo'tun word sound Ha'mari.  Make Ha'mari word sound like Jo'tun.  Only Berg understand Berg.</Source>
      <Dest>T'awas, ut'rah.  Berg voice sloppy like wet cheese. Make Jo'tun word sound Ha'mari.  Make Ha'mari word sound like Jo'tun.  Only Berg understand Berg.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wow, you hate everyone. Just like a Nord.</Source>
      <Dest>哎哟，你讨厌所有人，就像诺德人一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If Berg were Nord, he hate himself most of all.  But that would make him not Nord.  Nord love himself more than snow like cold.</Source>
      <Dest>如果伯格是诺德人，他会讨厌自己，但那会让他不想当诺德人。诺德人爱自己胜过于冰雪爱寒冷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait, hold on. You think you're a giant?</Source>
      <Dest>等，等一下。你认为你是个巨人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not think.  Am.  Berg is part of Jo'tun azgrok.  Giant clan.  Berg live in what Ha'Mari call Red Road Pass. </Source>
      <Dest>不是我以为，我就是。伯格是求伦阿兹粿的一员，巨人部落。伯格住在哈马里称为红路山隘的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why the inn?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么是旅馆？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Inn make trade with Berg.  He give them milk for mead sauce.  Sauce turn Berg into brave giant. Tell bard what think.</Source>
      <Dest>旅馆与伯格做了个交易，用牛奶来交换蜂蜜酒酱。酱会令伯格变成个勇敢的巨人，告诉诗人他的想法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why the inn?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么是旅馆？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bard hit Berg more hard than rock.  Call him beast man.  Berg think he has much to learn about Fraulen, woman.</Source>
      <Dest>诗人打伯格打得比用石头还要痛，叫他野人。伯格认为他应该多向女人学习。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And that boy is you.</Source>
      <Dest>那男孩是你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>T'awas, ut'rah.  Boy I talk of is Nord.  Berg is Jo'tun.  Not same.</Source>
      <Dest>吐瓦希，阿喇。我说的那个男孩是个诺德人。伯格是求伦。不一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fo'gura.  Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>佛-格拉。再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unh, goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ungh..hngh...goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯…哼…拜拜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>K'voja!</Source>
      <Dest>卡维加！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Huh?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hnngh?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whagh?</Source>
      <Dest>Whagh?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What you want?</Source>
      <Dest>你想要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What Berg do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>What Berg do for you?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What you need from puny Berg?</Source>
      <Dest>你想从卑微的伯格这里得到什么？</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
