<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's all the questions I have.  What next?</Source>
      <Dest>我没有其他问题了，那么接下来呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We rest, and we wait.  Don't worry, I had a good long nap on the way here.  I'll stand watch until tomorrow.</Source>
      <Dest>我们休息，我们等待。不要担心，我在来的路上好好地打了个瞌睡。我会在这里守望到天明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you found the Honorable Eight?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么要创建八圣灵之荣呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To answer that, I must take you back to the Great War.</Source>
      <Dest>要回答这个问题，我必须从世界大战开始讲起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who do you think is responsible for these killings?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为谁应该对这些杀戮负责？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In truth, as of right now, I've decided to stop thinking about it altogether.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，从现在开始，我决定要完全停止思考这件事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who do you think is responsible for these killings?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为谁应该对这些杀戮负责？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Indrel's words were poisonous, even though her intentions were noble.</Source>
      <Dest>英卓尔尽管出发点是高尚的，但他的话语……充满了恶意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who do you think is responsible for these killings?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为谁应该对这些杀戮负责？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The last thing we need is to turn on each other.  The assassin will come to us.  There is no need to divine who he is.</Source>
      <Dest>现在还不是我们自相残杀的时候。那个刺客会来找我们。用不着说他是谁了吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Indrel tell you?</Source>
      <Dest>英卓尔告诉了你什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was adamant that Bodan was a traitor.  She believed he was only in the company for vengeance.</Source>
      <Dest>她固执地地相信波登是个叛徒。她觉得他和我们为伴只是为了复仇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Indrel tell you?</Source>
      <Dest>英卓尔告诉了你什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She also said that Ula-Wei would never let his guard down unless the killer was someone he trusted.</Source>
      <Dest>她也说了，乌拉卫除非看到了他信赖的人，否则是不会放下警觉的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Indrel tell you?</Source>
      <Dest>英卓尔告诉了你什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lastly, the motive.  She said Bodan never forgave us for what happened in that cave.  It made us no different than the ones who killed his wife.</Source>
      <Dest>最后，是动机。她说波登对于山洞里发生的那些事而永远不会原谅我们。那让我们变得跟杀了他妻子的人没什么不同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Indrel tell you?</Source>
      <Dest>英卓尔告诉了你什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I admit, I was tempted to believe it.  However, after talking with you and getting a fresh perspective, it's clear Indrel was wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>确实，我之前被忽悠了。但是在跟你谈完之后，我的智商又回来了……英卓尔肯定错了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Indrel tell you?</Source>
      <Dest>英卓尔告诉了你什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, do you have any questions for me?  I am sure there is much you wish to know.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，你有什么问题要问我吗？我相信你有很多想知道的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, this whole line of questioning is a big waste of time.</Source>
      <Dest>换句话说，这一整段质问就是在浪费时间。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not at all. I am sorry, Companion. I misled the three of you earlier, when I said I could not find Indrel.</Source>
      <Dest>没关系，战友，抱歉，之前当我说我找不到英卓尔的时候，我误导了你们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, this whole line of questioning is a big waste of time.</Source>
      <Dest>换句话说，这一整段质问就是在浪费时间。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I neglected to mention that she was more than eager to find me.</Source>
      <Dest>我当时没有提起她有多么想找到我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, this whole line of questioning is a big waste of time.</Source>
      <Dest>换句话说，这一整段质问就是在浪费时间。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not at all. I am sorry, I misled the three of you earlier, when I said I could not find Indrel.</Source>
      <Dest>没关系，战友，抱歉，之前当我说我找不到英卓尔的时候，我误导了你们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, this whole line of questioning is a big waste of time.</Source>
      <Dest>换句话说，这一整段质问就是在浪费时间。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I neglected to mention that she was more than eager to find me.</Source>
      <Dest>我当时没有提起她有多么想找到我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Still, something must have brought this all on.</Source>
      <Dest>还有，肯定有什么导致了这一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You are perceptive, Companion. You have the makings of a great leader. Yes, I misled the three of you earlier when I said I could not find Indrel.</Source>
      <Dest>你的感知很敏锐，战友。你有领导者的必备素质。是的，之前当我说我找不到英卓尔的时候，我误导了你们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Still, something must have brought this all on.</Source>
      <Dest>还有，肯定有什么导致了这一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I neglected to mention that she was more than eager to find me.</Source>
      <Dest>我当时没有提起她有多么想找到我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Still, something must have brought this all on.</Source>
      <Dest>还有，肯定有什么导致了这一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You are perceptive. You have the makings of a great leader. Yes, I misled the three of you earlier when I said I could not find Indrel.</Source>
      <Dest>你的感知很敏锐，战友。你有领导者的必备素质。是的，之前当我说我找不到英卓尔的时候，我误导了你们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Still, something must have brought this all on.</Source>
      <Dest>还有，肯定有什么导致了这一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I neglected to mention that she was more than eager to find me.</Source>
      <Dest>我当时没有提起她有多么想找到我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why? Do you not trust Bodan?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么？你不信任波登?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No.  I trust him more now than ever.  For you see, the best way to solidify one's beliefs is to challenge them.</Source>
      <Dest>不。我比以前任何时候都更相信他。原因嘛，就是你要坚定一个人的信念的最好办法就是挑战那些信念。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He seems like a true and honest man.</Source>
      <Dest>他看起来是个真实可靠的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You seem absolutely convinced of this fact, even when the one who stands before you has known him far longer.</Source>
      <Dest>看来你已经对这个事实深信不疑了。甚至连站在你面前的人都已经知道他远去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's something I disliked about him from the start.</Source>
      <Dest>打一开始我就不喜欢他的某些方面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, a gut feeling.  I have learned to trust my instincts as well, as they can pick up small things...patterns, facial ticks, that the mind misses.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，就是直觉而已。我现在开始学习遵从我本能的判断了，本能可以发现很多细微的东西...比如一些暗藏其中的细节，难以捕捉的面部表情和头脑的疏忽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anum-La trusts him, and that's good enough for me.</Source>
      <Dest>安努姆菈相信他，就已经够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Remember though, she is naive.  She grew up alone, and we are her family.  She would be blind if Bodan sought to betray her.</Source>
      <Dest>她很纯真，记住这一点。她独自长大，我们就是她的家人。如果波登试图背叛她的话那她还真是看走了眼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't know him well enough to form a judgment.</Source>
      <Dest>以我对他的了解还不足以作出判断。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, you must have an opinion.  Or are you worried how I will react?  In that case, to reserve judgment is almost the same as condemning him.</Source>
      <Dest>不过，你肯定有些想法的。还是你担心我会有什么反应？在这种情况下，保留意见与谴责他无异。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Never, ever trust a bard. That's a good rule to live by.</Source>
      <Dest>绝不相信任何一个吟游诗人。这是能让你受益终生的信条。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you don't have an opinion on him specifically.  I see.  Still, any man who has the gift of speech has the tools to deceive.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你不要对他有意见。我明白。不过，男人除了花言巧语以外也不会别的了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you want to talk about?</Source>
      <Dest>你之前想要说什麽？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wanted to ask you for your thoughts on Bodan.  Do you find him trustworthy?</Source>
      <Dest>我想知道你对波登的看法。你觉得他值得信任么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't do it for free. I expect to be compensated.</Source>
      <Dest>我没打算免费服务。希望你有酬金给我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you have misread who I am, just as I seem to have misread you.  Nevertheless, you have my gratitude, even if your intentions are what they are.</Source>
      <Dest>看来你我之间都互相误解了。不过我感恩不尽，即使你的目的跟他们一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was my pleasure. I consider her a true friend.</Source>
      <Dest>那是我乐意的。我把她当做真正的朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am glad to hear it.  So rare is it to find a true companion in these troubled times.  I mourn the lives of four of my own.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴听到这个消息。在如此乱世寻到一位真正的同伴总归是不易的。我的生命中只有四个那样的人，我为此感到悲哀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Cut the small talk. You didn't bring me out here to thank me.</Source>
      <Dest>别聊家常了。你没以把我带出这里的方式感谢我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're right.  Some see no need for such dressing.  They call it false and tedious.</Source>
      <Dest>你说得对。有些人看不出这种服饰有什么必要。反而觉得又假又傻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Cut the small talk. You didn't bring me out here to thank me.</Source>
      <Dest>别聊家常了。你没以把我带出这里的方式感谢我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I believe making an effort to perform the small courtesies will earn the appreciation of those who receive them.</Source>
      <Dest>但我相信，努力表现出这些小小的礼貌会赢的你所礼貌的对象的欣赏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's no need to thank me. She can hold her own.</Source>
      <Dest>没必要谢我。她可以照顾好她自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, but she has always fought better when she fights for someone other than herself.</Source>
      <Dest>这是真的。但在她为别人而战的时候，总会变得更加强大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>First, I want to thank you once more for protecting Anum-La.  She is like a daughter to me, and had our company survived, I was to leave it to her.</Source>
      <Dest>首先，我得再次感谢你保护了安努姆菈。她对我来说就跟我的女儿一样。而且你还使我们的友谊得以留存，我想把它留给她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Go on.  Have a drink.  I'll be here.</Source>
      <Dest>去吧，喝一杯。我会在这等着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you take Anum-La into your company?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么让安努姆菈加入你的组织？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, a good question.  I don't know if she told you, but I had sent my invitation to another.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，问得好。我不清楚她有没有告诉你，我是已经把我的邀请函递给别人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you take Anum-La into your company?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么让安努姆菈加入你的组织？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She must have found it on a courier, as there was truly no other explanation.</Source>
      <Dest>她一定发现了什么，要不然就没有其他合理的解释了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you take Anum-La into your company?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么让安努姆菈加入你的组织？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bodan seems to think I chose her as a symbol, to be the one member of the company who was truly...clean.</Source>
      <Dest>波登似乎认为我把她当成队里真正...清白的成员的象征。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you take Anum-La into your company?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么让安努姆菈加入你的组织？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is the bard's way of thinking.  A swordsman doesn't consider metaphors and the like.</Source>
      <Dest>这是诗人们的思考方式。一个持剑之人才不会费心去思索该用那种比喻，该用那种情感去表达呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you take Anum-La into your company?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么让安努姆菈加入你的组织？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The truth is I never expected her to stay.  I thought after the first night, she would go scurrying back off into the swamp.</Source>
      <Dest>我也不认为她会留下来，第一晚之后她就会匆匆回到那个沼泽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you take Anum-La into your company?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么让安努姆菈加入你的组织？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Throughout our years together, I kept waiting for her to buckle, waiting for that moment where I would be forced to send her home once and for all.</Source>
      <Dest>我们在一起的时候，我一直在等着她的屈服，等待着我被迫永远地将她送回家的那一刻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you take Anum-La into your company?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么让安努姆菈加入你的组织？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But she never did, and I never had to.</Source>
      <Dest>但她从没那么做，我也就用不着了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, everything's fine.  I have a request, however.  I know you said you would never play that song again.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，一切顺利。但我有个请求。我知道你曾说过你永远不会再演奏那首歌了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet right now, if you would do your old friend a favor...I would like to hear it one last time.  For the ones we lost, and the ones we grieve.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，现在，如果你想帮你的老朋友一个小忙的话...我不想再听到那些了。那些我们失去的人，和我们难以抹去的悲伤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not at all, Bodan.  In fact, I was just about to have our friend summon you.</Source>
      <Dest>别客气，波登。事实上，我差点叫上所有朋友来找你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I understand your anger.  Moon-Tail, Elia, Arnwulf, Ula-Wei, and Bodan.  With every loss, a piece of me died with them.</Source>
      <Dest>我理解你的愤怒。月尾，艾拉，阿恩武夫, 乌拉卫,还有波登。他们的离去……带走了我的一片又一片的灵魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I made a vow when I formed the Honorable Eight.  To stand by what I believed was right, even if it meant slaying our own. </Source>
      <Dest>但当我创立荣光八荣众时，我就发誓会坚定地站在我们所认为的正义一边，即使这意味着牺牲。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is what it means to be a knight!  That is the very definition of honor!</Source>
      <Dest>这就是所谓的骑士！荣誉的象征！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then stand by your vow, Swamp Knight, as I will mine.  Show me my lessons were not in vain.</Source>
      <Dest>让你我遵守各自的誓言吧，沼泽骑士，别让我的努力付诸东流。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For honor!</Source>
      <Dest>为了荣耀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry, little hatchling, I know you loved Bodan, as did I.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉，小家伙，我知道你爱波登，我也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye, my brother.</Source>
      <Dest>再见，我的兄弟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wish it felt that way.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望它那样感觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Rest easy, friend.  It'll be over soon.  When you reach the other side, give Lilliana my regards.</Source>
      <Dest>放轻松，朋友。很快就会结束的。等你到了另一边，替我向莱莉安娜问个好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Before then, most of my experience came in tournaments and the arena.  You risked your life, but there were always rules.  A knight's code.</Source>
      <Dest>在那之前，我大多数的经历都来自于竞赛和角斗场。你虽是冒自己的生命危险，但也总得有规矩——骑士信条。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But war...war is different.  The horrors I've seen, I would wish them on no mortal.</Source>
      <Dest>但是战争...战争是不一样的。我见识过战火的恐怖，我希望战争永远不会降临到人们身上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You learn that under all the pomp and pageantry, we truly are nothing more than beasts.</Source>
      <Dest>你从那些华丽装饰中应该看得出，我们真的不算什么高级动物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet what I couldn't live with was my own guilt.  Countless times I chose my loyalty to the military over doing what was right.</Source>
      <Dest>但我无法忍受这沉重的内疚感。无数次我选择自己效忠的军队，去做正确的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Those horrors, you see, were mine.</Source>
      <Dest>那些恐惧，你知道，都是我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When the war was over, I vowed to never let loyalty cloud my judgment again.  I would do what was honorable, and stay commited to what was right.</Source>
      <Dest>战争结束后，我发誓再也不让忠诚影响我的判断了。我会去做荣誉的事情，遵守正确的承诺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Honorable Eight was a company founded on that principle.  In war, people chase victory at all costs.</Source>
      <Dest>荣光八人众就是一个基于那个原则的组织。在战争中，人们会不顾一切地追求胜利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come death or glory, the one thing we would never do is compromise our beliefs.</Source>
      <Dest>迎接死亡或取得荣耀。我们永远不会背弃自己的信仰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Companion, will you come speak with me outside?</Source>
      <Dest>战友，你能跟我出去说些话吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Will you come speak with me outside?</Source>
      <Dest>你能去外面和我说么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now I hate to delay our reunion, but I would like to speak with the Companion alone.  The two of you order a drink and we'll join you shortly.</Source>
      <Dest>好了我讨厌继续拖延我们的重聚，但是我宁愿单独和战友团谈谈。你们俩先喝着，我们一会就来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now I hate to delay our reunion, but I would like to speak with your companion alone.  The two of you order a drink and we'll join you shortly.</Source>
      <Dest>好了我讨厌继续拖延我们的重聚，但是我宁愿单独和你的同伴谈谈。你们俩先喝着，我们一会就来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wouldn't be the first time, my dear Swamp Knight.  You proved yourself that night in Thorn, and countless times thereafter.</Source>
      <Dest>这不会是第一次，我亲爱的沼泽骑士。那天晚上在索恩你第一次证明了自己，此后也无数次地证明了自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, and I don't suspect we will.  You were right old friend, it was like trying to grasp the wind.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我不怀疑我们会如此。老朋友你是对的，这就像是尝试抓住风一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, it seems we have an even more able warrior in our midst.  I thank you Companion, for keeping Anum-La safe.</Source>
      <Dest>不过呢，看来我们之中居然还有更有能耐的战士。我感谢你，勇士，谢谢你保障了安努姆菈的安全。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, it seems we have an even more able warrior in our midst.  I thank you for keeping Anum-La safe.</Source>
      <Dest>然后，看起来我们之中又出了一位能干的勇士。我由衷地感谢你守护了安努姆菈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anum-La!  Bodan!  It is good to see both of you alive and well.</Source>
      <Dest>安努姆菈！波登！看到你们两个都活蹦乱跳的真是太好了。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
