<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know what I realized? There's four of us and just one of him!</Source>
      <Dest>你知道我发现什么了吗？我们有四个人，而他只有一个人！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well then let's quit!</Source>
      <Dest>好吧那我们离开吧！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With three beers down, the Orc did frown, and bid the Elf goodbye! For none could know, twas not for show, and someone had to die!</Source>
      <Dest>With three beers down, the Orc did frown, and bid the Elf goodbye! For none could know, twas not for show, and someone had to die!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Errrrrrryyargh!</Source>
      <Dest>咿呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm going to kill you.</Source>
      <Dest>我要杀了你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Rrrrrrrrgh!</Source>
      <Dest>啊啊啊啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you sure they were just bandits? Are you sure they weren't vampires too?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为他们只是强盗？你不觉得他们同时也是吸血鬼吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let's show him!</Source>
      <Dest>让我们给他看看！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Looks like one of the bandits got here early! And do you know what the Knights of the Eight do to bandits?</Source>
      <Dest>看来某个强盗已经早一步到这里了。你知道圣灵八骑士怎么处置强盗吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You heard the woman! Pay up unless you all want to end up a bunch of homeless nightwalkers!</Source>
      <Dest>你们都听见这个女人说的了！把钱全都交出来，不然你们就得落得个无家可归的夜盗的下场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think you're right! Some of them had fangs and such. Probably a whole clan of vampire bandits, coming to Kynesgrove to suck everyone's blood!</Source>
      <Dest>I think you're right! Some of them had fangs and such. Probably a whole clan of vampire bandits, coming to Kynesgrove to suck everyone's blood!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, just the other day I think I saw a group of rowdy bandits coming up the river.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道吗，就前几天我想我看到了一群粗暴的强盗正在渡河。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't be sure, but they were saying something about burning your homes and raping all your women.</Source>
      <Dest>我并不确定，但他们所谈论的是烧你家的房子以及强奸你所有的女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, citizens, it's time to pay up! There's a lot of danger out there, and protection doesn't come cheap!</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，公民，是时候交出钱来了！这里有很多危险的存在，保护费可并不便宜！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A handful of guards can't stand up to a couple dozen bandits, and the Jarl's men are stretched thin enough as it is.</Source>
      <Dest>几个卫兵抵挡不住一群强盗的, 再说领主的人就是那样不堪一击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait! Where are you going?</Source>
      <Dest>Wait! Where are you going?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Pardon me, milord, I meant no offense. This group belongs to no Jarl or King.</Source>
      <Dest>对不起,老爷,我无意冒犯。但这个团体不属于领主或国王。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're just a bunch of lowlifes calling themselves the Knights of the Eight. They go around from town to town trying to collect protection money.</Source>
      <Dest>他们只是一伙自称为八骑士的混蛋。他们整天在城镇之间转悠试着收保护费。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Meaning, if we don't pay, they're going to come back tonight and raid the village.</Source>
      <Dest>这意味着，如果我们不给钱，他们今晚会回来抢劫这个村子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Everyone stay inside! Those bloody knights are back again!</Source>
      <Dest>Everyone stay inside! Those bloody knights are back again!</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
