<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I find you and your corpse displeasing.  Away with you!</Source>
      <Dest>我找到了你和你令人讨厌的尸体。带走了你</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Away with me?  But where would we go?  Inside your head maybe.  Or in your bowels.  I wonder, what color are they?</Source>
      <Dest>跟我走？但我们要去哪里？或许去到你的脑子里，要么是肠子里。我想瞅瞅它们到底是啥颜色的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I find you and your corpse displeasing.  Away with you!</Source>
      <Dest>我找到了你和你令人讨厌的尸体。带走了你</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do hope they're red. It would save me the decorating.  One rarely finds a coffin that's just the right color.</Source>
      <Dest>我强烈希望它们是红色的。这能节省我的装饰费用。人们难得能找到颜色正确的棺材。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would be honored to marry Sweetroll, if he'll have me.</Source>
      <Dest>我很荣幸能够嫁给甜甜圈，如果他接受我的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh he'll be more than happy to.  You're the Guildmaster of the Radiant Dark, and he's a corpse.  It's absolutely perfect!</Source>
      <Dest>Oh he'll be more than happy to.  You're the Guildmaster of the Radiant Dark, and he's a corpse.  It's absolutely perfect!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would be honored to marry Sweetroll, if he'll have me.</Source>
      <Dest>我很荣幸能够嫁给甜甜圈，如果他接受我的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And can you just imagine how wonderful your house will smell?  There's far too much wind where we are, but in a hot, stuffy home?</Source>
      <Dest>你能想象你屋子里的气味会有多棒吗？我们站的这地方风太大，可要是在一间温暖的房间里的话呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would be honored to marry Sweetroll, if he'll have me.</Source>
      <Dest>我很荣幸能够嫁给甜甜圈，如果他接受我的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He will rot as fragrantly as any perfume.</Source>
      <Dest>他将像香水的芳香般腐朽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A zombie is a fine pet for any young woman.</Source>
      <Dest>僵尸对于任何年轻女人来说都是一个很不错的宠物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And a mortal is a fine pet for any zombie.  Mortal, morsel, funny how the two are spelled to rhyme.  Sort of like breath, and death.</Source>
      <Dest>凡人只不过是僵尸眼中的美食。Mortal(凡人)，morsel(食物)，这两者的韵实在有意思。就像breath(呼吸)，和death(死亡)一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I appreciate the offer, but no.</Source>
      <Dest>这个条件很诱人，不过我的答案是“否”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you not like dolls?  Or would you rather be one?  Then would Sweetroll be the new Guildmaster?</Source>
      <Dest>你不喜欢玩偶吗？又或者你更想成为一个玩偶？那难道让甜甜圈来当工会老大不成？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I appreciate the offer, but no.</Source>
      <Dest>这个条件很诱人，不过我的答案是“否”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Giggle) He will be someday, but he's not ready yet.  You'll just have to wait.</Source>
      <Dest>(咯咯)有一天他会的，但他还没准备好。你就等着吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I appreciate the offer, but no.</Source>
      <Dest>这个条件很诱人，不过我的答案是“否”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eldawyn may prefer to drink in binges, but I prefer short, little...sips.</Source>
      <Dest>艾德雯或许更喜酣饮狂喝，但我却偏好细品清酌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Pretty much everything smells sweeter than a corpse.</Source>
      <Dest>没有什么比一具死尸更难闻了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, you don't like Sweetroll?  Maybe you'd like to be my new doll then  I promise it will hurt.  Very, very much.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，你不喜欢甜甜圈？也许你会喜欢成为我的新玩偶？我承诺那会很痛苦的。非常，非常痛苦...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thanks, but I already have a spouse.  A living one.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢，不过我已经有配偶了，一个活人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And yet, she'll someday be dead!  She might even be dead already!  How tragic!  Sweetroll here will never make you cry.</Source>
      <Dest>目前来看，她某一天肯定会死去！她已经完全准备好了哦！真奇妙！来，甜甜圈在这里，不哭不哭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thanks, but I already have a spouse.  A living one.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢，不过我已经有配偶了，一个活人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you're not going to marry him, you can at least take him for a walk.  Get to know him, and maybe...(giggle) learn to love him.</Source>
      <Dest>不过你要是不打算嫁给他，至少还是可以带他去散步。慢慢了解他，然后可能……(笑)学着爱上他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thanks, but I plan on marrying someone alive.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢，不过我更想跟活着的生物结婚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And yet, she'll someday be dead!  She might even be dead already!  How tragic!  Sweetroll here will never make you cry.</Source>
      <Dest>目前来看，她某一天肯定会死去！她已经完全准备好了哦！真奇妙！来，甜甜圈在这里，不哭不哭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thanks, but I plan on marrying someone alive.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢，不过我更想跟活着的生物结婚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you're not going to marry him, you can at least take him for a walk.  Get to know him, and maybe...(giggle) learn to love him.</Source>
      <Dest>不过你要是不打算嫁给他，至少还是可以带他去散步。慢慢了解他，然后可能……(笑)学着爱上他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Pleased to meet you, Sweetroll.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴见到你，甜甜圈.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh how nice, the two of you are getting along splendidly.  Sweetroll doesn't have many friends in the guild.  He tends to want to hurt them.</Source>
      <Dest>噢太好了，你们俩相处得很融洽嘛。甜甜圈在公会里没什么朋友。他一般倾向于去伤害他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm already married to a corpse, but the kind that won't shut up.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经嫁给了一具尸体，但却是不会闭嘴的那种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well then, Sweetroll would be a good change of pace.  He knows naught but one word.</Source>
      <Dest>那好吧，甜甜圈会慢慢改变的。除了一个单词以外，他一无所知。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm already married to a corpse, but the kind that won't shut up.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经嫁给了一具尸体，但却是不会闭嘴的那种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for your current spouse, accidents happen.  It's a scary world, master, full of tiny little dangers.  You never see them coming.</Source>
      <Dest>对于你现在的配偶来讲，麻烦很大。多么可怕的世界啊，主人，到处是细枝末节的危险。你根本无从防范。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm married to adventuring.  No spouse is worthy of me.</Source>
      <Dest>没有谁值得我去追求，冒险就是我的伴侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then Sweetroll would make for the perfect spouse!  He's good at adventuring, and he hardly makes a peep.</Source>
      <Dest>甜甜圈先生将是个完美的配偶！他善于冒险，并且几乎不会做出偷窥的举动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm married to adventuring.  No spouse is worthy of me.</Source>
      <Dest>没有谁值得我去追求，冒险就是我的伴侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Most of the time I don't even notice he's there.  He's very tiny for someone so big.</Source>
      <Dest>很多时候我甚至根本注意不到他在那儿。跟别的大块头相比他真是太迷你了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mmm...have you ever smelled anything so sweet as a corpse?  This one's my pet.  I call him "Sweetroll."</Source>
      <Dest>哼嗯嗯......你有闻过什么东西跟尸体一样甜美的吗？这个是我的最爱，我称它为〝甜甜圈〞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Say hello to the nice adventurer Sweetroll.  Well, he's not much for words.</Source>
      <Dest>来跟超优秀的探险家甜甜圈先生打个招呼吧。哦好吧，他这家伙不怎么爱说话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I love it when important people die!  We get a new master, and a new corpse!</Source>
      <Dest>重要人物去世什么的是我的最爱！我们能得到一个新主人，和一具新尸体！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm so happy I might even lend you Sweetroll.  I never even offered Nelos the courtesy.</Source>
      <Dest>我高兴到愿意把我家甜甜圈借给你。我从来没有向纳洛斯客气过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can talk to him, play with him, and even...(giggle), marry him!  Oh, won't that be fun!</Source>
      <Dest>你可以和他聊天，跟他玩，甚至...（咯咯的笑）嫁给他！哦，那不好玩！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that I'm Guildmaster, how can I best use you?</Source>
      <Dest>现在我做了会长，怎样才能发挥你的长处呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By keeping the halls dusty, and my coffins full.  But Vinnius will take care of it.  He's more steward than scholar.</Source>
      <Dest>因为他从不清理大厅，还总是塞满我的棺材。但 维尼乌斯就很会照料一切。比起学者来，他更像一个管家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that I'm Guildmaster, how can I best use you?</Source>
      <Dest>现在我做了会长，怎样才能发挥你的长处呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In time, I may develop a new spell for you, so long as you keep your promise to die for me.</Source>
      <Dest>我迟早会给你而研发一个新法术的，只要你遵守会为我而死的承诺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that I'm Guildmaster, how can I best use you?</Source>
      <Dest>现在我做了会长，怎样才能发挥你的长处呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh?  You don't remember?  Maybe you never said the words to me.  But a little bug told me you talk in your sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>噢？你忘了吗?？可能你没跟我说过。但有个小虫子跟我提起你在梦里说过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that I'm Guildmaster, how can I best use you?</Source>
      <Dest>现在我做了会长，怎样才能发挥你的长处呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gilsi had Nelos, but I have you Dragonborn, and my love begins at the grave.</Source>
      <Dest>歌尔西拥有纳洛斯，而我拥有你，龙裔。我的爱恋始于那座坟墓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think Nelos has 500 years to live.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不信纳洛斯有500年可活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, death comes for him.  Which means, he needs to bite off more than inch.  But that's all you'll ever get.  An inch.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，死亡为他而来。那就意味着，他不止贪图这些。但你永远只能得到那么多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think Nelos has 500 years to live.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不信纳洛斯有500年可活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's about inches and seconds. You might be faster by an second. Taller by inch. Smarter by a brain. That's what separates the good and the great.</Source>
      <Dest>这关乎英寸和秒数。你也许可以快上一秒，高上一英寸，脑子聪明一点儿。这就是区别优秀者和杰出者的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think Nelos has 500 years to live.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不信纳洛斯有500年可活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Once you get that inch, the next mage will need two inches to best you.  The process continues until we are all gods, or we are all dead.</Source>
      <Dest>一旦你领先了一英寸，那么下一个魔法师就需要两英寸来超过你。这样的事情会一直持续到我们全都变成神，或者全部死掉为止。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think Nelos has 500 years to live.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不信纳洛斯有500年可活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Giggle) I can't decide for the life of me which scenario I like better. Although I imagine you can take guess.</Source>
      <Dest>(咯咯笑)我不能决定自己更喜欢的生活情节。虽然我想你也能猜出一二。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Even if they were strong enough, I'd stop him.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管他们已足够强壮，我仍要阻止他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I imagine you could.  A man can kill a man easily enough, and one legend can slay another.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你能行。一个汉子就足以轻松干掉另一个汉子，一个传奇的汉子也可以宰掉另一个传奇的汉子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Even if they were strong enough, I'd stop him.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管他们已足够强壮，我仍要阻止他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But a disease...an acute case of brain rot...so slow that you never even notice it nibbling, nibbling, nibbling at your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>而是一种疾病...一种严重的脑腐蚀......它是如此的缓慢，以致于你几乎永远无法察觉到它在一点，一点，一点地蚕食你的思想。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Even if they were strong enough, I'd stop him.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管他们已足够强壮，我仍要阻止他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every day you feel the same, but you're a little bit slower, a little bit dumber.  Pretty soon you're too dumb to notice anything at all.</Source>
      <Dest>每一天你的感受都差不多，但你的动作有点慢了，有点迟钝了。不久你就迟钝得什么都注意不到了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Even if they were strong enough, I'd stop him.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管他们已足够强壮，我仍要阻止他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vanus' spell is just one nibble. One of a thousand to come.</Source>
      <Dest>万纳斯的法术只是个开胃小菜. 精彩的接着来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why pursue the spells if they're worthless to your cause?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么要为了这种无价值的理由而耗费法力？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're not worthless.  It doesn't matter if Vanus' spells are strong.  It only matters if they're better.  </Source>
      <Dest>它们并不是毫无价值。万纳斯的魔法强大与否都毫无关系。唯一重要的是它们是否更好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why pursue the spells if they're worthless to your cause?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么要为了这种无价值的理由而耗费法力？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For instance, Sweet Roll made me angry the other day.  So I took one of his toes.  He stumbled about, but he found his balance.</Source>
      <Dest>比如说，前几天甜甜圈惹我生气了。所以我剁了他的一根脚趾头。他撞撞跌跌的走，但一会儿就找回了他的平衡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why pursue the spells if they're worthless to your cause?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么要为了这种无价值的理由而耗费法力？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I imagine he'll make me angry again.  And then I'll take another, and another, and eventually, he'll have to crawl on the floor.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜想他会再次惹我生气，这一次我能忍，下一次也能，但总有一天我会让他跪在我面前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why pursue the spells if they're worthless to your cause?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么要为了这种无价值的理由而耗费法力？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vanus' spells don't have to take a leg.  Sometimes, you have to start small.  One toe at a time.</Source>
      <Dest>万纳斯的法术不一定每次要弄一整条腿，有的时候，你还是得从小事做起。每次一根脚趾头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vanus Galerion was a powerful mage.  These spells may change the world.</Source>
      <Dest>万纳斯?加里兰是个强大的的法师。这些法术可能改变这个世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They will.  In time.  It's like the spider I had as a pet.  When I found it, I couldn't help but cut off one of its legs.</Source>
      <Dest>他们会的。只要假以时日。就像我养的那只蜘蛛宠物，我发现它的时候就忍不住卸掉了它的一条腿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vanus Galerion was a powerful mage.  These spells may change the world.</Source>
      <Dest>万纳斯?加里兰是个强大的的法师。这些法术可能改变这个世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It stumbled around a bit, but it learned to walk with a limp.  Then I took another one.</Source>
      <Dest>它有点跌跌撞撞，不过最终适应了跛了一条腿走路。然后我切了它另一条腿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vanus Galerion was a powerful mage.  These spells may change the world.</Source>
      <Dest>万纳斯?加里兰是个强大的的法师。这些法术可能改变这个世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eventually, poor Frosty couldn't walk at all.  But it wasn't until I took the last leg that it lost the will to move.</Source>
      <Dest>最终，可怜的寒霜不再走动。但是似乎并非如此直到我带走最后一个支柱他这才失去移动的意愿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So the prophecy refers to someone else?</Source>
      <Dest>那么预言指向了其他人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm...I know the answer, but do you?  It depends on whether you think mortals live twice.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯……答案我知道，你呢？那取决于你相不相信人有两条命了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So the prophecy refers to someone else?</Source>
      <Dest>那么预言指向了其他人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps it's all part of a cycle.  Dust to flesh, and flesh to dust, through rotting skin, bile and pus.</Source>
      <Dest>也许这就是轮回。尘土变成血肉，血肉又回归尘土，它穿过溃烂的皮肤和发臭的胆汁，回归了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So the prophecy refers to someone else?</Source>
      <Dest>那么预言指向了其他人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But why would anyone want to live again, when death is so wonderful?</Source>
      <Dest>死亡如此美好，为什么有人渴望重获生命？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on the Long Night?</Source>
      <Dest>对于《长夜之谶》你有什么看法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My thoughts...are that Nelos was born 500 years too early.</Source>
      <Dest>在我看来...那个纳洛斯真的是早生了五百年啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on the Long Night?</Source>
      <Dest>对于《长夜之谶》你有什么看法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't think Vanus' spells are strong enough to cause the kind of chaos Nelos wants.  It's a shame, really. He's so intent on making it.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认为万纳斯的咒语不足以强大到造成纳洛斯想要的那种混乱。实话说，这挺丢人的。他似乎是下定决心要达成目的了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of spells can you cast?</Source>
      <Dest>你会放什么魔法?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Giggle) Nothing useful.  Yet.  I'm still learning the craft.  I could just read a tome, but every one Vinnius has is much too large.</Source>
      <Dest>（咯咯地笑）没用的。我依然在学习这技巧，我能阅读一大本书，但每个 维尼乌斯都太大了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of spells can you cast?</Source>
      <Dest>你会放什么魔法?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I tried to rework them best I can, with mixed results.  Well, maybe not so mixed.  I tried to conjure a scamp, and out came an atronach.</Source>
      <Dest>我尽我所能来施放这些魔法，结果很混乱。呃，也不算太混乱。我尝试召唤一个小恶魔，结果出来了一个侍灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of spells can you cast?</Source>
      <Dest>你会放什么魔法?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I tried to conjure diseased rats, and out came two atronachs. I tried to conjure a puppy, and out came a Dremora Lord.</Source>
      <Dest>我想试着召唤出患病的老鼠，结果变出了两只召唤元素。我想召唤出一只小奶狗，结果魔人领主却蹦出来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of spells can you cast?</Source>
      <Dest>你会放什么魔法?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nelos told me to get rid of the tomes and focus on what I do best.  So right now, I conjure little bugs and things.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯让我忘掉那些书卷并专注于自己擅长的事情。于是现在我专注于召唤小虫子和一些小东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of spells can you cast?</Source>
      <Dest>你会放什么魔法?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if one of the other guild members challenged me, I could always bring back the Dremora.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我们同行有人出来挑战我，我恐怕我又要被带回魔人那去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your eyes pulse with light, vampire.  When's the last time you fed?</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼，你眼睛都在放光。你有多久没吸血了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmm...that's a good question.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯……问得好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's brilliant. I would love to be able to conjure and control these bugs.</Source>
      <Dest>真是绝妙的主意阿。我很乐意去召唤和控制这些虫子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, but you can! You just need the right tome. When they say Vanus' conjuration spell could raise an army of dead, that's what he meant.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，你可以的！只要你找对了书。当他们说万纳斯的召唤法术可以组织一支亡灵大军时，他们所言不虚！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's brilliant. I would love to be able to conjure and control these bugs.</Source>
      <Dest>真是绝妙的主意阿。我很乐意去召唤和控制这些虫子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You conjure the purple bugs.  The purple bugs kill everyone.  Then you have all the playthings a girl could ever ask for.</Source>
      <Dest>You conjure the purple bugs.  The purple bugs kill everyone.  Then you have all the playthings a girl could ever ask for.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't see anything.  Maybe if I squint real hard.</Source>
      <Dest>我没看见任何东西，也许是我眼睛斜视的太很了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Squint all you like, Dragonborn, but if you can't see them now, you'll have to wait until death. </Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)随你怎么看，龙裔，但如果你现在不能看到他们，那只能等到你死了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't see anything.  Maybe if I squint real hard.</Source>
      <Dest>我没看见任何东西，也许是我眼睛斜视的太很了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But be patient, you'll get there soon enough.  Then you can be my new doll.</Source>
      <Dest>耐心点儿，你迟早会到达这里。然后你就能成为我的新玩偶了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I squash little bugs before they can ever crawl up my nose.</Source>
      <Dest>没等这些小虫子爬上我的鼻子我就把它们都拍扁了。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You think like Sweetroll. But how can you step on something so small, it fits in the space between your boot and the ground?</Source>
      <Dest>你这想法跟甜甜圈没啥区别。但你是怎么立在这么小的东西上的，它居然能卡在你的靴底和地面之间？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I squash little bugs before they can ever crawl up my nose.</Source>
      <Dest>没等这些小虫子爬上我的鼻子我就把它们都拍扁了。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It will crawl up your boot, and into a scratch.  Then it will eat you, bite by bite, nibble by, nibble...until you're gone.</Source>
      <Dest>它会爬上你的靴子，钻进小缝里。然后它就会吃掉你，慢慢撕咬，静静，啃噬...直到你完全消失。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All I see is a crazy person.</Source>
      <Dest>我的眼里只看到一个疯子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sweetroll, dispose of this infidel.  Sweetroll?  (Giggle) He never listens to me.  Only his heart.  It's where the poison lies.</Source>
      <Dest>甜甜圈，处理掉这异教徒吧。甜甜圈？(咯咯地笑) 他从来不听我的，只听从自己被毒素侵蚀的内心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All I see is a crazy person.</Source>
      <Dest>我的眼里只看到一个疯子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Would you like to be my new doll?  You'd make a fine one.</Source>
      <Dest>你愿意成为我的新玩偶吗？你一定会是个好玩偶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on the Radiant Dark?</Source>
      <Dest>你对黑暗光辉看法如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Quibble, quibble, quibble, that's what we do.  We all want to eat, but there's so many quibbles about what makes a stew.</Source>
      <Dest>挑剔，挑剔，挑剔，我们不停在挑剔。我们都想吃，我们都要吃饭，但是做饭前我们居然为怎么煮饭争吵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on the Radiant Dark?</Source>
      <Dest>你对黑暗光辉看法如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Offryn, for instance, wants magic to move mountains.  But I want something more.  I want to conjure little things.</Source>
      <Dest>欧芙芳，举个例子吧，就像是用法术把山移走一样。但我想要的更多。我想变出一些小东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on the Radiant Dark?</Source>
      <Dest>你对黑暗光辉看法如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tiny bugs that crawl up your nose and nibble on your brain.  Things so small you'll never see them coming until it's already too late.</Source>
      <Dest>小虫子爬进你的鼻子，啃噬你的大脑。变化太过于细微以至于你根本发现不了，待到你发现时为时已晚。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on the Radiant Dark?</Source>
      <Dest>你对黑暗光辉看法如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you see them?  They're dancing in the air, tiny-tiny purple things, riding pods of dust.</Source>
      <Dest>你看见它们了吗？它们在空中飞舞，小小的紫色的东西，就像是骑着豆荚的尘埃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to get my own Sweetroll.  I could use him as a pack mule.</Source>
      <Dest>我想要我自己的甜甜圈。我可以把他当骡子使唤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Giggle) Or you could get an actual pack mule.  I prefer to keep Sweetroll as a pet.  If you died for me, I would never make you carry a thing.</Source>
      <Dest>(咯咯地笑) 要不你就去买匹真正的骡子算啦。我更喜欢把甜甜圈当成宠物。如果你为我而死了，我也不会让你驮东西的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a murderer.  Plain and simple.</Source>
      <Dest>你是个杀人犯！明白无误！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, but death is a comma, a new beginning.  If you died for me, I would show you.  Your flesh would turn such a delightful gray.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，不过死亡并不是终结，而是一个新的开始。如果你为我而死，我会把这点展示给你看。你的身躯将会转变为非常美妙的灰色。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to return to my earlier questions.</Source>
      <Dest>我想回到我刚才的问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fine, but my offer stands.  Be my corpse, Dragonborn.  You would rot so sweetly.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，但我的提议不变。成为我的尸体吧，龙裔。你会腐烂得如此甜蜜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Somehow I don't think Sweetroll will ever love again.</Source>
      <Dest>不知怎么的，我觉得甜甜圈先生不会再爱了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But isn't just once enough?  Isn't a single rose better than a dozen?  Especially when it withers and blackens.</Source>
      <Dest>但一次不就够了吗？一支玫瑰花不亦足矣？何况它也会枯萎，也将凋零。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Somehow I don't think Sweetroll will ever love again.</Source>
      <Dest>不知怎么的，我觉得甜甜圈先生不会再爱了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you died for me, I would make sure to squeeze every ounce of life from you, so that you'd never forget the one you lost.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你为我而死，我保证会把你每一盎司的生命榨干，这样一来你就永远也忘不了那个你失去的人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Doesn't a plant need water?  Sunshine?</Source>
      <Dest>那个植物需要水吗？阳光呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say for Nightshade to grow, it must be watered with blood.  So I could think of no better place for it.</Source>
      <Dest>They say for Nightshade to grow, it must be watered with blood.  So I could think of no better place for it.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Doesn't a plant need water?  Sunshine?</Source>
      <Dest>那个植物需要水吗？阳光呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for light, I made sure to feed him a ball of magelight every morning.</Source>
      <Dest>至于光嘛，我能确保每天早上赏他一记魔光术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you do that?  Conjure things inside people?</Source>
      <Dest>你能做到吗？在人体内召唤东西？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yes, so long as it's very, very small.  I could do it to you, but sadly, you wouldn't die.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，只要它非常、非常小，我就可以把它做出来送给你。可是很遗憾，这样一来你就不会死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you do that?  Conjure things inside people?</Source>
      <Dest>你能做到吗？在人体内召唤东西？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The plants never want to grow.  Not even bloodgrass.  The nightshade I put in Sweetroll is special.  It grew from the blood rivers of Oblivion.</Source>
      <Dest>The plants never want to grow.  Not even bloodgrass.  The nightshade I put in Sweetroll is special.  It grew from the blood rivers of Oblivion.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you do that?  Conjure things inside people?</Source>
      <Dest>你能做到吗？在人体内召唤东西？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And someday, it will leave a seed of it own.  When Sweetroll dies a second time, I could plant it in you.</Source>
      <Dest>然后在将来的某一天，它将留下它自己的种子。当甜甜圈第二次死亡时，我会把它种在你身上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is Sweetroll?  Before he became your pet.</Source>
      <Dest>甜甜圈先生是谁?  在他变成你的宠物之前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An Orc is an Orc, iron and coarse, and never is he wont to be gay. </Source>
      <Dest>兽人就是兽人，又硬又粗，绝不会是他想成为同性恋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is Sweetroll?  Before he became your pet.</Source>
      <Dest>甜甜圈先生是谁?  在他变成你的宠物之前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Giggle) Which is to say, Sweetroll was a poor, poor bandit, who knew not the fairer emotions.</Source>
      <Dest>(咯咯地笑) 也就是说, 甜甜圈是个可悲的，低劣的强盗，不知道诚实是什么样的感情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is Sweetroll?  Before he became your pet.</Source>
      <Dest>甜甜圈先生是谁?  在他变成你的宠物之前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So to show him, I conjured a nightshade seed, and placed it in the belly of his heart.</Source>
      <Dest>所以为了告诉他，我召唤了一颗夜茄子种子，把它放进了他的心室里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is Sweetroll?  Before he became your pet.</Source>
      <Dest>甜甜圈先生是谁?  在他变成你的宠物之前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As the flower bloomed, it trickled tiny drops of poison in his blood...trickle, trickle, trickle...</Source>
      <Dest>在繁花盛开之时，毒药缓缓地流入他的血液…慢慢的，慢慢的，慢慢的…</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is Sweetroll?  Before he became your pet.</Source>
      <Dest>甜甜圈先生是谁?  在他变成你的宠物之前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And every day his knees grew weak, his stomach fluttered, and his head felt faint, and he knew how it felt to love.</Source>
      <Dest>And every day his knees grew weak, his stomach fluttered, and his head felt faint, and he knew how it felt to love.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is Sweetroll?  Before he became your pet.</Source>
      <Dest>甜甜圈先生是谁?  在他变成你的宠物之前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And what better gift for a surly Orc?  The gift of death, of course, of course, but I gave him both.</Source>
      <Dest>那对于一个粗暴的兽人什么才是更好的礼物呢？死亡的礼物，当然，当然，我会把两样都给他的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I take good care of you, don't I Sweetroll?</Source>
      <Dest>我会照顾好你的，对不对啊我的甜甜圈？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He's not sure.</Source>
      <Dest>他不太确定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sweetroll, when's the last time you let me bite you?</Source>
      <Dest>甜甜圈，你多久没那啥我了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not sure yourself, huh.  Well, I believe.  You just have to patient.  It's like torture.</Source>
      <Dest>你自己也不是很确定，嗯？嗯，我信。耐心点，这挺折磨人的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You cut, and you cut, and then you cut some more, and each cut brings you closer and closer to that glorious death.</Source>
      <Dest>一刀，一刀，然后再是一刀，每一刀都会让你距离你所谓的“死得光荣”更近一步。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But the first cut is just as important as the last.  That's what Vanus' spells are Sweetroll, the very...first...cut.</Source>
      <Dest>可是最初的切割和最终的一样重要。最初在甜甜圈身上的切割，就是万纳斯法术的效果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Light eats Shadow, shadow eats the light, everyone will die when we bring the Long Night...</Source>
      <Dest>光明照亮阴影，阴影吞噬光明。当我们带来长夜之时，每个人都会死...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>La, la-la-la, la-la-la-la-la...Sweetroll, do you believe in prophecies?</Source>
      <Dest>啦，啦-啦-啦-，啦-啦-啦-啦-啦...甜甜圈，你相信预言吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until the night is long.</Source>
      <Dest>等过了漫长的夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until the dawn arrives.</Source>
      <Dest>直到黎明的到来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Giggle) Death take us all.</Source>
      <Dest>(咯咯的笑) 人固有一死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, master.</Source>
      <Dest>你好，会长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, won't you die for me!  You know you want to.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，你会为我赴死吗！你知道你会的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How can I serve you, Guildmaster?</Source>
      <Dest>我能为你做些什么，会长？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Giggle) I'm so happy you married Sweetroll!  I hope all went well the night after.</Source>
      <Dest>（偷笑）很高兴你要和斯威特罗结婚了！我希望三天以后一切顺利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
