<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I tell you this for your benefit.  This "connection" you feel is a byproduct.</Source>
      <Dest>我是为了你好才跟你说的：你的这种“连接感”是一种副作用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is true that conjuration magic may have ties to illusion. Yet even illusion magic is but a worm that crawls to the ripest apple.</Source>
      <Dest>召唤系魔法可能真的会有点儿幻术系的既视感。但就算是幻术系魔法也只不过是个爬进成熟苹果里的蠕虫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I tell you this for your benefit.  This "connection" you feel is a byproduct.</Source>
      <Dest>我是为了你好才跟你说的：你的这种“连接感”是一种副作用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is the binding strong because of my feelings?  Or are my feelings strong because I was bound?</Source>
      <Dest>Is the binding strong because of my feelings?  Or are my feelings strong because I was bound?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Come with me, ghost. I could use someone like you as a companion.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我来，幽灵？就算是你这样的家伙，也能成为我的同伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you...No, you are not my Fjona.  Her eyes were as blue as the summer sky, and her hair a wave of chestnut that danced in the breeze.  </Source>
      <Dest>你...不，你不是我的菲欧娜。她的眼睛如夏日的晴空一样湛蓝，她的发丝就像风中的栗色浪花一般飘逸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there any significance to your armor?</Source>
      <Dest>这对你盔甲有什么意义吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think not. There are many warriors who have donned Dwarven armor, as the metal is commonly found in the ruins strewn across Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>我不那样觉得。穿着矮人盔甲的战士有很多，因为制作这种盔甲的材料很容易就能在分布于天际省各处的遗址中找到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there any significance to your armor?</Source>
      <Dest>这对你盔甲有什么意义吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you are implying that the armor was once worn by a Dwarf, well, you forget your history.  Dwarven armor is made for and by man.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你是暗指这具盔甲被矮人穿过，那我得说，你的历史老师死得真早。矮人盔甲都是由人类制作的，而且是按人类身材制作的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're not like the other ghosts.</Source>
      <Dest>你跟别的幽灵不大一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fjona?  I'm here, I...Oh, I apologize.  My thoughts tend to drift, but always it seems, in the same direction.</Source>
      <Dest>菲欧娜？我在这，我...哦，我得道歉。我的心看似飘摇不定，但总有一个方向是固定的，那就是你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you in this abandoned prison?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么会在这个被废弃的监狱?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had come here once before with my master, Fjona.  It is a cold, empty place, and its aura feels much like the void.</Source>
      <Dest>在跟主人菲欧娜一起之前，我曾来过这里。这是一个寒冷而空洞的地方，就像是虚空。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you in this abandoned prison?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么会在这个被废弃的监狱?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I stay in this cell to detach myself from that which is above ground, in hopes that I may forget my sorrow.</Source>
      <Dest>我呆在地牢里面，只是为了摆脱地上所发生的那些过去，希望这样悲伤便不再会逆流成河。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fjona must be a Companion.</Source>
      <Dest>菲欧娜必须成为我的同伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The day she joined was the day we parted.  The Companions forbid the use of magic, and Fjona thought it best that she never conjure me again.</Source>
      <Dest>她加入的那天也是我们分离的日子。战友团禁止使用魔法，而菲欧娜认为，永远不再召唤我才是最好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fjona must be a Companion.</Source>
      <Dest>菲欧娜必须成为我的同伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet my body did not return to the void.  For days I walked the plains of Whiterun Hold, waiting for the end that never came.</Source>
      <Dest>我的身体还没有完全化作虚无。我日日夜夜在白漫领的平原上徘徊，等待着永远不会到来的结局。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fjona must be a Companion.</Source>
      <Dest>菲欧娜必须成为我的同伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Days turned to weeks, and weeks to months, and months to years.</Source>
      <Dest>时光飞逝，天成了星期，接着星期又成了月份，然后月份又成了年。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What memories do you have of Fjona and Whiterun?</Source>
      <Dest>你对菲欧娜与白漫城还留有怎么样的记忆？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I look at the walls I see her on the ledge, mesmerized by the tapestry of stars. </Source>
      <Dest>当我盯着墙壁的时候，我看见她坐在窗台上，沉迷于窗外灿烂的星幕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What memories do you have of Fjona and Whiterun?</Source>
      <Dest>你对菲欧娜与白漫城还留有怎么样的记忆？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I walk through the tundra, I see her chasing the butterflies, entranced by their subtle waltz. </Source>
      <Dest>若我走过苔原，我会见到她追逐蝴蝶的身影，那为蝴蝶们优美华尔兹所吸引的美妙身影。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What memories do you have of Fjona and Whiterun?</Source>
      <Dest>你对菲欧娜与白漫城还留有怎么样的记忆？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Most of all I hear her laughter in the rumble of the river and feel her smile in the warmth of the sun.  </Source>
      <Dest>特别是，我在隆隆的水流声中听到了她的笑声，感觉到了她在温暖阳光下的笑意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What memories do you have of Fjona and Whiterun?</Source>
      <Dest>你对菲欧娜与白漫城还留有怎么样的记忆？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The memories brighten my soul for an instant until they remind me of what I have lost.</Source>
      <Dest>The memories brighten my soul for an instant until they remind me of what I have lost.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That must have been tough on you.</Source>
      <Dest>这对你来说太过粗暴了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was her familiar, her guardian, and above all...her friend. A quick goodbye would have been best.  What happened was...torture.</Source>
      <Dest>I was her familiar, her guardian, and above all...her friend. A quick goodbye would have been best.  What happened was...torture.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That must have been tough on you.</Source>
      <Dest>这对你来说太过粗暴了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I tried to watch from afar, but Whiterun is a place with far too many memories.</Source>
      <Dest>对我而言，远远望着就足够，可白漫城里包含了太多的回忆啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who was Fjona? A loved one?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是菲欧娜? 意中人?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was my master.  I do not recall the name of my wife, or if I had one, for that is a life now twice removed.</Source>
      <Dest>She was my master.  I do not recall the name of my wife, or if I had one, for that is a life now twice removed.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there any way I can help?</Source>
      <Dest>我能帮上什么忙吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I fear not even the world eater could end my torment.</Source>
      <Dest>I fear not even the world eater could end my torment.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why stay in this place?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么呆在这种地方？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is a place for me here, even if it is not the one I long for.</Source>
      <Dest>There is a place for me here, even if it is not the one I long for.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know about the other spirits here?</Source>
      <Dest>关于这里的其他灵魂你知道什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have heard of spirits that are restless, but the ones that haunt this prison sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说过一些不安宁的灵魂，但萦绕着这座监狱的那些已经安息了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where is Fjona now?</Source>
      <Dest>费欧娜现在在哪里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Last I saw her she was in Whiterun, I believe, at the Hall of Jorrvaskr.</Source>
      <Dest>我最后一次见到他是在白漫城，我记得是在月瓦斯卡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The second is not any place I have ever heard of.</Source>
      <Dest>第二这地方我从来没听说过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, it is certainly not the bone bridge to Sovngarde. It could be I leave this realm for a far worse fate, or it could be nothing more than a dream.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，这里肯定不是松嘉德的骨桥。要么我离开这里将会面对更加残酷的命运，要么这里仅只是一场迷梦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The second is not any place I have ever heard of.</Source>
      <Dest>第二这地方我从来没听说过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems, however, the point is moot for the time being.</Source>
      <Dest>总之，这一观点上的争议似乎是暂时的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did she escape?</Source>
      <Dest>她是怎么逃出去的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She does not recall what happened next. But I do. Somehow the girl had raised her hands and conjured my spirit from the void.  </Source>
      <Dest>她不记得接下来发生了什么，但我记得。莫名其妙的，她举起了手把我的精神从虚空中召唤出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did she escape?</Source>
      <Dest>她是怎么逃出去的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bound to her will, I vanquished the Falmer quickly, sensing our link was fading, knowing I had little time.  That is how I met Fjona.</Source>
      <Dest>我们因意愿而彼此连接，我迅速地打败了那只雪精灵，感觉到我们之间的联系正在逐渐消失，我知道我没多少时间了。这就是我怎样遇见费欧娜的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An easy mistake. It's dark and there's a helmet on your face.</Source>
      <Dest>难免的错误。这么黑，你还戴着头盔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose you could be a werecroc and I would still hope that it was Fjona, in need of my services once more.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你大概是个亚龙人吧，我还真希望你是菲欧娜呢，是那个总是需要着我的菲欧娜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Summons typically are very brief. Unusual that you are still here.</Source>
      <Dest>召唤通常是非常短暂的。你还在这里很不寻常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You are right, the link between the conjurer and the conjured is tenuous.  Only a master mage can summon a creature that will remain in perpetuity.</Source>
      <Dest>你说得对, 召唤兽与术士间的联系非常弱。只有大法师召唤出的生物才能永久存在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Summons typically are very brief. Unusual that you are still here.</Source>
      <Dest>召唤通常是非常短暂的。你还在这里很不寻常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fjona, on the other hand, was only a child.</Source>
      <Dest>另一方面，菲欧娜还只是个孩子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Summons typically are very brief. Unusual that you are still here.</Source>
      <Dest>召唤通常是非常短暂的。你还在这里很不寻常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She had not an ounce of magical talent, and yet through sheer will she was able to summon me again and again.</Source>
      <Dest>她没有一丁点儿魔法的天赋，然而通过纯粹的意志力，她可以一次又一次的召唤我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Summons typically are very brief. Unusual that you are still here.</Source>
      <Dest>召唤通常是非常短暂的。你还在这里很不寻常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As the years went on our bond only grew stronger, and as such so did my ties to this world.</Source>
      <Dest>我们的关系随着日久年深越发深厚，同样变强的还有我与这个世界的联结。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there anything about your previous life you remember?</Source>
      <Dest>你前世的记忆还能想起什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just shades, colors, feelings.  The sound of gears churning, a whistle of steam, and a great contraption that mapped the stars.</Source>
      <Dest>只是阴影，颜色，感觉。这齿轮搅拌之声，蒸汽的啸啸之声，一个很棒的奇妙装置在映射星辰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there anything about your previous life you remember?</Source>
      <Dest>你前世的记忆还能想起什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I recall ambling across a great bridge that shimmered like glass...or was that after?  </Source>
      <Dest>我想起曾走过一座大桥，它像玻璃那样闪闪发光...又或者是在那座桥之后的东西在闪闪发光？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you resent the Companions?</Source>
      <Dest>你讨厌同伴吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I do not resent the Companions for their code, nor do I blame Fjona for choosing them over me.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我并不反对战友团的道德准则，也不会怪菲欧娜选择了他们而不是我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you resent the Companions?</Source>
      <Dest>你讨厌同伴吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Her enlistment into their ranks merely brought to light what we both already knew.</Source>
      <Dest>她加入他们的行列，这结果是我们彼此都很清楚的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds to me like you're a stalker.  She should be happy to be rid of you.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来你就像个跟踪狂，她一定很庆幸摆脱了你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You cut me down, but your blade is true.  I must let her go if I am ever to return to the void.</Source>
      <Dest>你让我溃散，但是你的剑却是真的。如果我永远回归虚无我必须得让她也得到解脱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds to me like you're a stalker.  She should be happy to be rid of you.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来你就像个跟踪狂，她一定很庆幸摆脱了你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet how can the mind do what the heart will not?</Source>
      <Dest>头脑怎么可能会做内心不愿意做的事情？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were bound. It's the spell that compelled you to be by her side.</Source>
      <Dest>你被限制了。是法术把你强行带到了她身边。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In the beginning, it was so.  Orphaned at a young age, the child was a lonely one, and I her only companion.  </Source>
      <Dest>开始时是这样的。那孩子很小就成了孤儿，而我是唯一和她作伴的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were bound. It's the spell that compelled you to be by her side.</Source>
      <Dest>你被限制了。是法术把你强行带到了她身边。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For her own sake I wished to leave, but the binding spell would not allow me to.</Source>
      <Dest>为了她着想，我想离开，但约束符咒却不允许我这么做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were bound. It's the spell that compelled you to be by her side.</Source>
      <Dest>你被限制了。是法术把你强行带到了她身边。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If not for I, the other villagers would have adopted her, but my existence forced even the most compassionate of people to maintain their distance.</Source>
      <Dest>要不是我，其他的村民就会接纳她了，但我的存在让那些最热心的人也要和她保持距离。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were bound. It's the spell that compelled you to be by her side.</Source>
      <Dest>你被限制了。是法术把你强行带到了她身边。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A ghost is not a suitable playmate for a young girl, but she left me no choice.  </Source>
      <Dest>幽灵可不是小女孩的好玩伴，可她让我无能为力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were bound. It's the spell that compelled you to be by her side.</Source>
      <Dest>你被限制了。是法术把你强行带到了她身边。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I spoke to her, for silence is a terrible thing to inflict upon a child.</Source>
      <Dest>So I spoke to her, for silence is a terrible thing to inflict upon a child.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And her dependance on you faded, both on and off the battlefield.</Source>
      <Dest>不论在不在战场上，她已经不再那么依赖你了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, just as she had been developing her skill as an archer, she had been maturing as a woman.  </Source>
      <Dest>是的，正如她的箭术愈发娴熟一样，作为一个女人她也逐渐成熟起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And her dependance on you faded, both on and off the battlefield.</Source>
      <Dest>不论在不在战场上，她已经不再那么依赖你了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She would tell me how she spent the day's coin, drinking in the taverns and listening to the bards.</Source>
      <Dest>她也告诉我，她平时的消遣就是在酒馆里喝喝酒，顺便听一听吟游诗人的歌唱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And her dependance on you faded, both on and off the battlefield.</Source>
      <Dest>不论在不在战场上，她已经不再那么依赖你了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She began to hunt on her own, both in the wild and in the city.  Gradually, then suddenly, she ceased to conjure.</Source>
      <Dest>She began to hunt on her own, both in the wild and in the city.  Gradually, then suddenly, she ceased to conjure.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And her dependance on you faded, both on and off the battlefield.</Source>
      <Dest>不论在不在战场上，她已经不再那么依赖你了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was only to tell me she had been accepted into the Companions that she summoned me to say goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>她把我叫了过去，我还以为她是要与我道别，但她却只告诉我，她已经被战友团接纳了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And her dependance on you faded, both on and off the battlefield.</Source>
      <Dest>不论在不在战场上，她已经不再那么依赖你了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She walked into the Hall of Jorrvaskr, and I never saw her again.</Source>
      <Dest>她走进月瓦斯卡大厅，之后我再也没见过她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The first part sounded like an orrery.  Maybe you're a dwarf.</Source>
      <Dest>第一部分听起来像是个太阳仪。也许你是个矮人。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha!  I am no Dwarf, I promise you that.  There are indeed functioning orreries across Tamriel, however, and their descriptions do fit.</Source>
      <Dest>哈！我向你保证我可不是矮人。不过，在泰姆瑞尔大陆确实有还在运转的浑天仪，而他们的描述恰恰相符。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned a Fjona.</Source>
      <Dest>你提到一个叫菲欧娜的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, she was my master.  Just a small girl when I answered her call, bound by the summoning ritual.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，她是我的主人。当她还是一个小女孩的时候，我回应了她的召唤，通过召唤仪式建立了联系，并受其束缚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Falmer.</Source>
      <Dest>女士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As she grew older she would recall with vivid detail the horror of that face, from the rills in its cheeks to the keyhole shape of its snout.</Source>
      <Dest>当她慢慢长大了，她将会清晰地回忆起那张恐怖的脸，回忆起那凹凸不平的面颊与那钥匙孔般的口鼻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Falmer.</Source>
      <Dest>女士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As if it were a door to a dark and foreboding underworld.</Source>
      <Dest>As if it were a door to a dark and foreboding underworld.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me how you met.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲你们是怎么遇见的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The events of the Great War had weakened the guard and the Falmer, once content to ambush caravans, had grown more brazen.</Source>
      <Dest>世界大战的到来削弱了守卫和雪精灵，但那些袭击商队的家伙们也开始变得明目张胆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me how you met.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲你们是怎么遇见的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They were kidnapping children from their homes.  </Source>
      <Dest>他们当时正在把孩子们从他们自己的家里绑走。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me how you met.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲你们是怎么遇见的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A storm came that night. Heavy rain pelted the rooftops.  Thunder shook the earth. The Falmer broke in through the cellar. </Source>
      <Dest>那天晚上，一场风暴袭击了这里。风雨交加，电闪雷鸣。雪精灵闯进了地窖。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me how you met.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲你们是怎么遇见的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They skulked up the stairs and split into two groups.  Two bound for the parents, one for the child.  It was the screams of her mother that woke her.</Source>
      <Dest>他们分成两组溜上楼。两只奔向家长，一只搞定孩子。她妈妈的尖叫声将她惊醒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me how you met.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲你们是怎么遇见的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She opened her eyes to a smell.  A foul vapor emanating from its wormlike mouth, clouding her vision.  Then it slowly began to clear.</Source>
      <Dest>She opened her eyes to a smell.  A foul vapor emanating from its wormlike mouth, clouding her vision.  Then it slowly began to clear.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did the incident with the Falmer affect Fjona?</Source>
      <Dest>雪精灵袭击菲欧娜是怎么个情况？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fjora's childhood steeled her resolve to become strong, but the memory of that Falmer scared her away from melee combat.</Source>
      <Dest>菲欧娜的童年经历让她不得不变得坚强起来，但对雪精灵的恐怖回忆让她对肉搏战敬而远之。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did the incident with the Falmer affect Fjona?</Source>
      <Dest>雪精灵袭击菲欧娜是怎么个情况？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She never showed any other magical ability besides the one, but quickly adapted to another long range weapon.</Source>
      <Dest>除了这以外她再也没显露出其它魔法天赋，但她很快就学会了如何使用远程武器。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did the incident with the Falmer affect Fjona?</Source>
      <Dest>雪精灵袭击菲欧娜是怎么个情况？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She began as a thief, stealing bread and jewelry from the market stalls, trading her profits for a poorly made bow. </Source>
      <Dest>她是干小偷起家的，从街市档位偷点面包首饰什么的，然后拿换来的钱买了一把破烂一样的弓。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did the incident with the Falmer affect Fjona?</Source>
      <Dest>雪精灵袭击菲欧娜是怎么个情况？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did she train to become a Companion?</Source>
      <Dest>她是怎样被培养成一名战友团的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At night she snuck behind the Companion Hall and engaged in target practice, while I kept watch from under the pavilion.</Source>
      <Dest>晚上，她悄悄走到月瓦斯卡后庭对着靶子将自己投入到练习中，而我则在亭子下面一直看着她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did the incident with the Falmer affect Fjona?</Source>
      <Dest>雪精灵袭击菲欧娜是怎么个情况？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did she train to become a Companion?</Source>
      <Dest>她是怎样被培养成一名战友团的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She lacked the strength at first.  Even when she switched from thievery to hunting, it was I who did the fighting on her behalf.</Source>
      <Dest>她一开始就虚了。当她的日常从小偷小摸变成了狩猎之后，只能由我遵循着她的意愿来摆平一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did the incident with the Falmer affect Fjona?</Source>
      <Dest>雪精灵袭击菲欧娜是怎么个情况？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did she train to become a Companion?</Source>
      <Dest>她是怎样被培养成一名战友团的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But slowly that started to change.  An elk would die at my feet before I could strike it with my axe.</Source>
      <Dest>但这种情况慢慢开始改变。在我用斧子砍到猎物之前，它就会死在我的脚下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did the incident with the Falmer affect Fjona?</Source>
      <Dest>雪精灵袭击菲欧娜是怎么个情况？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did she train to become a Companion?</Source>
      <Dest>她是怎样被培养成一名战友团的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In time, the wolves could not even finish howling before she had dropped them to the ground.</Source>
      <Dest>就在一瞬间，狼群还没来得及嚎一声就被她摔在地上了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where do you suppose she is now?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为她现在在哪？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Hall of Jorrvaskr, or the Great Mead Hall of Sovngarde.  Or she may have returned home, to set right what was wronged.</Source>
      <Dest>月瓦斯卡的大厅，或是松加德的蜜酒大厅。又或者她也许回到了家里，去纠正以前犯下的错误。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thank you for the story.  May you find peace in the void.</Source>
      <Dest>多谢你的故事。愿你找到安宁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is I who should thank you.  Sometimes saving a soul requires neither strength nor sorcery.</Source>
      <Dest>我应该感谢你才对。有些时候，要拯救一个灵魂既不需力量也不需魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thank you for the story.  May you find peace in the void.</Source>
      <Dest>多谢你的故事。愿你找到安宁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only your ears, and the compassion to listen. </Source>
      <Dest>只需用耳朵和同情之心去倾听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Psijics used conjured links to talk across great distances.  Perhaps...</Source>
      <Dest>赛伊克人透过召唤术的链接来实现超远距离对话，也许......</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You mean to say I could conjure her?  Or at least, connect our minds?  A tempting thought, but I shudder at the thought of her reply.</Source>
      <Dest>你想说我可以呼唤他？或者至少和她建立精神联系？不错的想法，可是我可不敢回应她的召唤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm a Companion and I use magic.  Routinely.</Source>
      <Dest>我大部分时间是一个随从而且我使用魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, the Companions may abhor magic, but I do not think they are intolerant of it.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，这些同伴可能讨厌魔法，但我并不认为他们完全厌恶它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm a Companion and I use magic.  Routinely.</Source>
      <Dest>我大部分时间是一个随从而且我使用魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, the Warriors of Jorrvaskr did not sever our bond.  It had long ago gone brittle with age.  </Source>
      <Dest>不，月瓦斯卡的战士并没有和我们决裂。但从很久我们之间的关系就变得非常脆弱。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happens if she conjures you again?</Source>
      <Dest>如果她再次conjures你，会发生什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I imagine I will be with her.  I do not know whether to be comforted by the thought, or distraught by the knowledge that I am still here. </Source>
      <Dest>我想我会和她在一起。我不知道这么想是否能感觉些许安慰，或者因为我还在这里的事实而心烦意乱。 </Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
