<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The pleasure is mine, my friend. Say hello to our Elf friend if you see him.</Source>
      <Dest>那是我的荣幸，朋友。下次见到那位精灵朋友的时候请代我问好哦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The pleasure is mine, brave knight.</Source>
      <Dest>那是我的荣幸，勇敢的骑士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He never told me his name, but he was a kind man, and he honored me with this gift.</Source>
      <Dest>他从未告诉过我他的名字，但他是个好人，出于敬佩，他送给了我这个礼物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A fine request. I can play that for you.</Source>
      <Dest>点的好。我可以为你演奏这支曲子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Warrior's Life.</Source>
      <Dest>《战士的一生》</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's a good request. That one always gets the place moving.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，点得好。这曲子很适合活跃气氛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Eyldi the Bear.</Source>
      <Dest>狗熊艾迪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A fine request. That one always gets the place moving.</Source>
      <Dest>点得好。这曲子很适合活跃气氛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Mogo's Mead.</Source>
      <Dest>莫格蜜酒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Wolves of Jorrvaskr.</Source>
      <Dest>月瓦斯卡群狼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A fine request. I can play that for you.</Source>
      <Dest>点的好。我可以为你演奏这支曲子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can I make a request?</Source>
      <Dest>我能点首曲子吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure. What would you like to hear?</Source>
      <Dest>当然。你想听什么呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Certainly. What would you like me to play?</Source>
      <Dest>当然。你想让我演奏什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can I make a request?</Source>
      <Dest>我能点首曲子吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Portraiture. I'll play the lute.</Source>
      <Dest>接下来我会用鲁特琴为大家演奏《肖像》这首曲子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Certainly! That one always gets the place moving.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了！那首曲子经常会让全场为之动容的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Warrior's Life. I'll play the flute.</Source>
      <Dest>《战士的一生》，我来吹奏长笛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Certainly! That one always gets the place moving.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了！那首曲子经常会让全场为之动容的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Warrior's Life. I'll play the flute.</Source>
      <Dest>《战士的一生》，我来吹奏长笛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Certainly! That one always gets the place moving.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了！那首曲子经常会让全场为之动容的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Warrior's Life. I'll play the flute.</Source>
      <Dest>《战士的一生》，我来吹奏长笛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Certainly! That one always gets the place moving.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了！那首曲子经常会让全场为之动容的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Bard) How about we play together?</Source>
      <Dest>(吟游诗人)咱们合奏一曲怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What would you like to play?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算弹奏什么呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Mogo's Mead. If you sing, I can play the lute.</Source>
      <Dest>莫格蜜酒.如果你打算唱歌的话，我可以用鲁特琴给你伴奏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Certainly! That one always gets the place moving.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了！那首曲子经常会让全场为之动容的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That melody you sung. It's not as common as some of the other local favorites.</Source>
      <Dest>你唱的那个旋律。听起来不太像本地的流行曲目啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I imagine it isn't.  Few have ever heard it, and even fewer understand what it's about.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，我猜也不是。很少有人听过它，而能听懂它的人就少之又少了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That melody you sung. It's not as common as some of the other local favorites.</Source>
      <Dest>你唱的那个旋律。听起来不太像本地的流行曲目啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some say it's a quiet song of glory, while others will say it tells the loudest of tragedies.</Source>
      <Dest>有些人说这首轻吟歌颂了荣耀，也有人说它是一曲最为悲怆的哀歌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That melody you sung. It's not as common as some of the other local favorites.</Source>
      <Dest>你唱的那个旋律。听起来不太像本地的流行曲目啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You see, to be a Companion, to be part of the Circle, one must give up a piece of their humanity.  It was not something I was willing to give.</Source>
      <Dest>你也看到了，为了成为一名战友团成员，成为圆环中的一份子，一个人必须要放弃他们的人性。而这恰恰是我不愿放弃的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That melody you sung. It's not as common as some of the other local favorites.</Source>
      <Dest>你唱的那个旋律。听起来不太像本地的流行曲目啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I left my shield-brothers and sisters and set out on my own.  I figured I needed some time to myself, as I've grown weary of saying goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我离开了我的盾牌兄弟姐妹，踏上了自己的道路。我想我需要一些时间，因为我已经厌倦了说再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How about Ragnar the Red?</Source>
      <Dest>红衣拉格纳怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A toast to Matilda then, and all the brave shield-sisters who serve as our brothers' better halves.</Source>
      <Dest>为玛提尔达，以及我们兄弟的另一半——所有勇敢的盾牌姐妹们干杯！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened at the Jarl's tournament?</Source>
      <Dest>领主的比赛上发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was a girl not even flowered, and the crowd behind me laughed and jeered when I requested to enter my name in the archers' list.</Source>
      <Dest>那时的我还是没发育的黄毛丫头，当我请他们把我的名字写进弓箭手名单的时候一群人在背后嘲笑我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened at the Jarl's tournament?</Source>
      <Dest>领主的比赛上发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But all went silent when Eorlund Gray-Mane vouched for me, and paid for my entrance with a dagger from the Sky-Forge.</Source>
      <Dest>但当厄仑德．灰鬃引荐我时，那些家伙都闭嘴了。他也给了我一把由天空熔炉铸造的匕首作为加入的礼物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened at the Jarl's tournament?</Source>
      <Dest>领主的比赛上发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>From his view atop the Sky-Forge, he'd seen me grow from a child who could barely nock an arrow to one who could bulls-eye a flea.</Source>
      <Dest>从他那天空熔炉看下来，他亲眼看着我从一个孩子成长为一个百步穿杨的神射手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think Eorlund vouched for you?</Source>
      <Dest>在你看来，为什么Eorlund要为你担保？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened at the Jarl's tournament?</Source>
      <Dest>领主的比赛上发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think Eorlund vouched for you?</Source>
      <Dest>在你看来，为什么Eorlund要为你担保？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He watched me train outside Jorrvaskr day and night, in the chills of winter and the rains of spring, so that I could one day earn my way inside.</Source>
      <Dest>日复一日地，他在月瓦斯卡外看我修习武艺，风雨未阻，严寒无惧，而这一切都被他收在眼底。于是有朝一日我终得以跻身其中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened at the Jarl's tournament?</Source>
      <Dest>领主的比赛上发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And on that day there was not an archer in Whiterun whose aim was more true. Not Athis or Irileth, not even Aela the Huntress would best me.</Source>
      <Dest>自那天起，在白漫城有了一个未曾失过准头的弓箭手。不是阿蒂斯，不是伊瑞莱斯，甚至也不是那个曾经打败过我的女猎手艾拉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think Eorlund vouched for you?</Source>
      <Dest>在你看来，为什么Eorlund要为你担保？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The "Age of Oppression."</Source>
      <Dest>时代的压迫</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must be a Stormcloak through and through to request that one. Very well, I can sing that for you.</Source>
      <Dest>你一定是个彻头彻尾的风暴斗篷才会点这首曲子。很好，我会唱给你听的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You sound like you almost resent Companion work.</Source>
      <Dest>听你的意思差不多是痛恨战友团的工作了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Resent is probably too strong of a word.  My time with the Wolves was disappointing, but only because I had the false impression of who they were.</Source>
      <Dest>说是气愤也许有点过头了。和这群狼人呆在一块的日子实在是太过于难受，又或许只是因为我分不清他们谁是谁罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You sound like you almost resent Companion work.</Source>
      <Dest>听你的意思差不多是痛恨战友团的工作了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you think the Companions could do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得战友团能为你做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As a child I thought they could protect me. As a young woman I thought they would groom me.  It was naive to think so.</Source>
      <Dest>作为一个孩子，我以为他们会保护我。作为一个年轻女孩，我以为他们会打扮我。我这么想真是太天真了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You sound like you almost resent Companion work.</Source>
      <Dest>听你的意思差不多是痛恨战友团的工作了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you think the Companions could do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得战友团能为你做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wolves may run in packs, but there's a hierarchy, and a competitive one.  Whatever skill or strength I gained I earned on my own.</Source>
      <Dest>狼确实以群体为单位来行动，但他们有着等级制度，有着竞争。无论是技巧还是力量我都得靠自己去学。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything about Riften that you found noteworthy?</Source>
      <Dest>关于裂谷有没有任何你觉得值得一提的事儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I didn't know they had a Temple of Mara here.  I bet a lot a young couples fall victim to the atmosphere.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道他们这里有个玛拉祭坛。我敢打赌很多年轻夫妇都在这里成了婚姻的牺牲品。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything about Riften that you found noteworthy?</Source>
      <Dest>关于裂谷有没有任何你觉得值得一提的事儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The waterfront views are nice, and the market is a nice place to relax and enjoy the weather.</Source>
      <Dest>海滨的视野好极了，而且集市也算得上是一个休养生息的好地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything about Riften that you found noteworthy?</Source>
      <Dest>关于裂谷有没有任何你觉得值得一提的事儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's no one here that I fancy though.  Too many fisherman with skinny legs.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这儿没一个能让我喜欢的。到处都是骨瘦如柴的渔夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And while Riften is beautiful, I think I need a little more sun.  Perhaps I'll head south to Cyrodiil, and maybe just keep going.</Source>
      <Dest>裂谷城已经够美了，但就我个人而言，我还希望能够多晒点太阳。所以或许我会往赛瑞迪尔的南边走，又或者，继续旅途前往下一个地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything about Riften that you found noteworthy?</Source>
      <Dest>关于裂谷有没有任何你觉得值得一提的事儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not sure, but right about now I'd trade both my thumbs for a good massage.</Source>
      <Dest>不确定，不过如果能听到一个好消息的话，让我用我所有的手指去换也无所谓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Don't look at me.  I have no use for a stranger's thumbs.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑声）别指望我了。陌生人的手指对我来说也没什么用处啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you fear the Falmer?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你怕法莫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I grew up in a poor village outside of Whiterun.  It was very small, but full of children, and as such, full of life.</Source>
      <Dest>我是在白漫城外一个贫穷的小村庄里长大的。那里真的非常小，但有许多的孩子，因而也总是充满了生机与活力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you fear the Falmer?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你怕法莫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They said when we played in the yard, the peals of laughter rang all the way to Dragonsreach.  </Source>
      <Dest>他们说当我们在院子里玩时，阵阵欢笑声能一直传到龙临堡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you fear the Falmer?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你怕法莫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet when I think about that village, I can never hear it.  I listen for it, train my ears toward the darkness, but what comes out isn't laughter.</Source>
      <Dest>当我想起那小村庄时，回荡在我脑海中的已不再是那些声音。我把我的耳朵探入黑暗中，努力想要去倾听，但传来的却已不是笑声了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were screams that night.  So many screams.  The Falmer took my mother.  They took my father.  They tried to take me.</Source>
      <Dest>那天夜里只有惨叫声。除了惨叫声还是惨叫声。雪精灵杀了我母亲，也杀了我父亲。还差点杀死我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you fear the Falmer?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你怕法莫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you fear the Falmer?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你怕法莫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Before she tucked me in, my mother used to light a single sconce by my bed, to ward off the dark.</Source>
      <Dest>每次母亲把我撵上床的时候，她总习惯在我床边点一支蜡烛，来驱赶掉黑暗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you escape the Falmer attack?</Source>
      <Dest>你是如何逃脱雪精灵的袭击的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you fear the Falmer?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你怕法莫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you escape the Falmer attack?</Source>
      <Dest>你是如何逃脱雪精灵的袭击的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I remember the way that light wrapped around its face.  How it stood there, tracing its mouth with its tongue...</Source>
      <Dest>我记得光打在它脸上的样子。它就那么站在那里，用舌头轻舔它的嘴唇……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you fear the Falmer?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你怕法莫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you escape the Falmer attack?</Source>
      <Dest>你是如何逃脱雪精灵的袭击的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I...I'm sorry. No more talk about the Falmer.</Source>
      <Dest>我……我很抱歉。但请别再提雪精灵的事了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you fear the Falmer?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你怕法莫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you escape the Falmer attack?</Source>
      <Dest>你是如何逃脱雪精灵的袭击的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're foul creatures, and if I never see another it will be too soon.</Source>
      <Dest>它们是邪恶的生物，我这辈子真是再也不想看到它们了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True love.</Source>
      <Dest>真爱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Please, spare me your sentimental drivel, will you?  I thought we were having a serious conversation.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑声）求你了，多愁善感啊胡言乱语之类的就省省吧，成吗？我想我们这谈话可是很严肃的啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you eventually become a Companion?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么加入战友团的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Wolves will recruit any fighter who is strong and virtuous, for there are few in this world who are both.</Source>
      <Dest>月瓦斯卡的那群狼会招募任何强壮与美德兼备的战士，因为这样的人在世界上就没几个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you eventually become a Companion?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么加入战友团的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My chance came about 7 summers ago, when the city held a tournament to celebrate the birth of the Jarl's son.</Source>
      <Dest>大约7年前，这城市为了庆祝领主儿子的出生而举办了竞技会。我的机会来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree. Other people just get in the way.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。其他人只是在帮倒忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have it backwards. Nobody got in my way. I got in theirs.</Source>
      <Dest>你弄反了。不是别人来给我帮倒忙，而是我总拖别人的后腿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree. Other people just get in the way.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。其他人只是在帮倒忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I once traveled with a companion.  You might even call him a friend.  For years I would rely on him for food, for warmth, and for someone to talk to.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾和一个战友团的人一同去探险，我们也算是朋友。多年来我都是依靠着他来获取食物，取得温暖，排解我心中的寂寞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree. Other people just get in the way.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。其他人只是在帮倒忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But what if the day came when I couldn't summon his aid, and then what would become of me?  No, that wasn't going to be my fate.</Source>
      <Dest>但如果到了再也无法得到他的援助的那天，那我会变成怎样？不，我的命运不该是那样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think you vastly overestimate my magical ability. The summoning of that ghost was an accident.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你高估我的魔法天赋了。能召唤出那个幽灵纯属偶然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could try summoning him and asking him.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以试着把他召唤出来问问看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No, but this place is dirty hovel of thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>不，不过这个地方对于贼来说也太脏了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A lot of thieves steal because they don't want to starve, and are dirty because dirt is the softest bed they can afford.</Source>
      <Dest>大多数贼只为了能够填饱肚子而偷窃，他们总是浑身脏兮兮的，因为他们所能买得起得最柔软的床就是土堆了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Besides, I think the crime here is overstated.  At least, the people getting away with it.</Source>
      <Dest>此外，我觉得所谓的罪恶是被夸大了的。至少，那些真正的罪犯还都逍遥法外。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No, but this place is dirty hovel of thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>不，不过这个地方对于贼来说也太脏了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No, but this place is dirty hovel of thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>不，不过这个地方对于贼来说也太脏了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A thief tried to escape through the market district the other night.  It took less than a minute for the guard to turn him into a pin cushion.</Source>
      <Dest>某天晚上有个小贼偷完东西以后打算从市场区逃走，守卫只花了一分钟都不到的时间就把他给逮住了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Balgruuf's housecarl? I bet Irileth couldn't hit a dragon from inside its belly.</Source>
      <Dest>巴尔古夫的侍卫? 我打赌伊瑞莱斯没法从龙肚子里砍它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, her specialty is destruction magic, but I don't care if it's archery or artwork, she's an intimidating adversary.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，她很擅长毁灭系法术，不过就算她擅长的是箭术或者艺术，都没什么区别，她依旧是一个劲敌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It would require some innate magical ability to summon such a ghost.</Source>
      <Dest>要召唤这样一个幽灵终归是需要点天赋的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I never developed any real magical talent. Didn't learn the finer points of spellcasting.  My only trick was to summon that familiar.</Source>
      <Dest>我身上没有任何真正的魔法天赋，也从未受过系统的魔法训练。我唯一会的把戏就是召唤我那挚友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All I had to do, all I had to be, was scared.  Throughout my youth I was plagued by nightmares, and I would conjure the spirit out of reflex.</Source>
      <Dest>我能做的，就只有躲在角落里瑟瑟发抖罢了。我的青春全被那些噩梦给毁了，它们甚至霸占着我的记忆，赶都赶不走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It would require some innate magical ability to summon such a ghost.</Source>
      <Dest>要召唤这样一个幽灵终归是需要点天赋的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How would you go about summoning it?</Source>
      <Dest>你将如何去召唤它？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It would require some innate magical ability to summon such a ghost.</Source>
      <Dest>要召唤这样一个幽灵终归是需要点天赋的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when I had him near me, saw the way his body lit the darkness, I felt safe.</Source>
      <Dest>每当他在我身边，而我能看到他的身影在暗处屹立时，我就能感到安心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How would you go about summoning it?</Source>
      <Dest>你将如何去召唤它？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It would require some innate magical ability to summon such a ghost.</Source>
      <Dest>要召唤这样一个幽灵终归是需要点天赋的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How would you go about summoning it?</Source>
      <Dest>你将如何去召唤它？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But then I grew up.  Enough time passes, and you forget the things that frightened you in the first place.</Source>
      <Dest>可那之后我就成长了。只要经过足够长的时间，再怎么让你害怕的东西都会被淡忘掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, yes. That cave would've made a perfect underground lair.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯...是的。那个山洞原本可以作为一个完美的地下巢穴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do I look like a necromancer to you?  Besides, even if I was, Greywater Grotto is hardly remote.</Source>
      <Dest>你看我像个亡灵巫师吗？另外就算我曾经做过一阵子亡灵巫师，灰水石窟离这儿也没多远。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Athis? If you asked that Elf to shoot the ground, he'd still miss.</Source>
      <Dest>阿蒂斯?如果你让那个精灵去射地面，他也会脱靶的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, and I imagine he'd accidentally hit your foot.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，而且我想他会不小心打到你的脚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, greetings fellow traveler.  I apologize for my singing, as I didn't realize I had an audience.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你好啊旅行者。真抱歉我正好在唱歌，所以完全没注意到这儿有个听众呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I sometimes fashion myself a bard, or a sword-singer of legend.</Source>
      <Dest>有时候我会装成吟游诗人，或者是传说中的战斗诗人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What marking do you speak of?</Source>
      <Dest>你说的是什么标记？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Falmer mark the entrance to their caves with a sculpture of painted bones.</Source>
      <Dest>雪精灵在他们洞穴入口所做的记号是一支涂过色的骨头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm repulsed by it...but I don't think I could venture into a cave if I wasn't sure those things weren't looming beneath.  The markings help.</Source>
      <Dest>我被它驱逐了……但我不认为在我搞清楚那洞穴里是否有那东西在暗处徘徊之前，我就能直接进去冒险。这些记号帮了忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What marking do you speak of?</Source>
      <Dest>你说的是什么标记？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a beautiful song.</Source>
      <Dest>那是一首美妙的歌曲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's more ominous than beautiful, but I suppose its melody won't lack for suitors.  Maybe not now, but in time.</Source>
      <Dest>悲伤多过美丽，但是应该还是会有人喜欢这种旋律的。或许现在没人喜欢，不过早晚有人会欣赏的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your plans now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在的打算是什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm taking a break from adventuring, but I'll be out there again when I need the coin.  For now, I'm enjoying this city.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经暂时停下冒险的脚步了，不过等我缺钱了我还会继续去冒险的。现在么，还是让我好好享受下这座城市吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, and before that, it was the longboat of Jeek, one of the Captains of the Five Hundred Companions.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，以及在这之前，它可是属于五百勇士中的某位，通称为河之伊克的那位队长，这是他的战船。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Jorrvaskr is the Hall of the Companions.</Source>
      <Dest>月瓦斯卡是战友团的大厅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although how it went from the former to the latter, I can't begin to tell you.</Source>
      <Dest>至于它是怎么逐渐演变成现在这个样子的，那我可就不能对你讲了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Jorrvaskr is the Hall of the Companions.</Source>
      <Dest>月瓦斯卡是战友团的大厅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There should be laws against your howling, dog.</Source>
      <Dest>应该有办法对付你的嚎叫，笨蛋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And do laws apply in such a place?  If so, I suggest you take it up with the Jarl's court.  I've heard they're willing to listen to the unreasonable.</Source>
      <Dest>法律在这种地方也适用吗？如果你这么想，那我建议你去领主的宫殿看看。我猜他们是很乐意听到这样荒唐的评价的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold.  Mountains upon mountains of gold.</Source>
      <Dest>金子，成山成山的金子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anyone who has ever had to beg for food, or steal for it, knows the value of gold.  But you don't look like someone without the means to work.</Source>
      <Dest>任何一个为食物而乞讨过，或者偷窃过的人，都知道金钱的价值。而你不像是那些无力工作的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree.  There's only one thing worth giving up your humanity for...</Source>
      <Dest>我认同。只有一件事情值得放弃你的人性给......</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm almost scared to ask, but too curious not to.  What exactly is worth giving up your humanity?</Source>
      <Dest>虽然这样问不礼貌，但我还是很好奇。究竟是什么东西能让你甚至愿意付出作为人的代价？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I agree. While I believe that every dead man deserves to be mourned, I don't believe I'm the one who should mourn them.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。尽管我认为每个亡魂都应被悼念，但我不觉得我该是那个悼念他们的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While you mourn the death of one bandit, his friends will stab you in the back.</Source>
      <Dest>当你在悼念强盗的时候，他的朋友们会在背后给你一刀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The "Age of Aggression."</Source>
      <Dest>这是"大肆侵略的时代"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must be loyal to the Empire then. Very well, I can sing that for you.</Source>
      <Dest>那你应该是忠于帝国的人。很好，我可以唱给你听了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All my life I'd sought the protection of others, when I should have been learning to protect myself.</Source>
      <Dest>在我的一生中，当我应该学会自我保护的时候，我却一直在寻求他人的庇护。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, and it has nothing to do with the Circle.  That's why I left, but there's a different reason why I won't return.</Source>
      <Dest>不，这跟圆环一点关系都没有。尽管正因为圆环我才选择离开，但让我下定决心永远不再回去的决定因素却不是它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you ever thought of returning to the Companions?</Source>
      <Dest>你想过回归战友团吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you ever thought of returning to the Companions?</Source>
      <Dest>你想过回归战友团吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the reason you won't you return to Jorrvaskr?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么不肯回去月瓦斯卡了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I was a child I thought of nothing else but joining the fabled Companions.</Source>
      <Dest>当我还是个孩子的时候，我别无所想，只想加入那遥不可及的战友团。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I know it must have been difficult.  I myself was asked to make that choice.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道那一定是个艰难的过程，我必须自己做出选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not at all. The choice was easy, as  I've always been suspicious of easy power.  The only strength you can truly rely on is the kind that's earned.</Source>
      <Dest>并不是那样。这个选择很容易，因为我一直相信一个简单的真理。你所能真正依赖的只有力量而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I imagine it would be a difficult choice to make.</Source>
      <Dest>想象得出这个决定有多么艰难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not at all. The choice was easy, as  I've always been suspicious of easy power.  The only strength you can truly rely on is the kind that's earned.</Source>
      <Dest>并不是那样。这个选择很容易，因为我一直相信一个简单的真理。你所能真正依赖的只有力量而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, there are many who share your beliefs, but I would hesitate to call it a gift. </Source>
      <Dest>诚然，有很多人和你持有同样的想法，可是我不能确定那是好事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak of lycanthropy as if it were a curse.  It's a gift.  An honor.</Source>
      <Dest>你谈到狼化病时就像它是个诅咒一样。我可以自豪地说，它是个礼物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't imagine how often Aela has to pluck the fur from her nose just so she can breathe.</Source>
      <Dest>我简直无法想象艾拉居然会那么勤于修剪鼻毛，只为能够顺畅地呼吸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak of lycanthropy as if it were a curse.  It's a gift.  An honor.</Source>
      <Dest>你谈到狼化病时就像它是个诅咒一样。我可以自豪地说，它是个礼物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, there are many who share your beliefs, but I would hesitate to call it a gift. </Source>
      <Dest>诚然，有很多人和你持有同样的想法，可是我不能确定那是好事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One's humanity is a small price to pay for great power.</Source>
      <Dest>爱能赐予你巨大的能量！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't imagine how often Aela has to pluck the fur from her nose just so she can breathe.</Source>
      <Dest>我简直无法想象艾拉居然会那么勤于修剪鼻毛，只为能够顺畅地呼吸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One's humanity is a small price to pay for great power.</Source>
      <Dest>爱能赐予你巨大的能量！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The water attracts nomads crossing to and from Cyrodiil, and draws more than its share of beasts.</Source>
      <Dest>这水吸引了很多从赛瑞迪尔来和到赛瑞迪尔去的游民，也引来了不属于那个区域的野兽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But mortals prefer mead to water, so I ended up here.  Although it's going to take some time for me to get used to this Black-Briar swill.</Source>
      <Dest>可人们对蜂蜜酒比对水有兴趣，所以我就流落到这儿来了。不过我还是需要一段时间才能适应这种黑荆棘脏水。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was a haunting some old prison.</Source>
      <Dest>这是个难以遗忘的老旧监狱。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But how?  How is that even possible?  I know our bond was strong, unusual even, but...well, what did he want?</Source>
      <Dest>但怎么会？这怎么可能？我知道我们的羁绊很深，很不寻常，很……呃，他到底想要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He longs to see you. It's what binds him to this plane.</Source>
      <Dest>他渴望见到你。这是驱使他到这儿来的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I can't. It's not a period of my life I remember often, or care to. I was a child with a doll, one that could speak, but a doll nonetheless.</Source>
      <Dest>不，不行。我不怎么喜欢回忆这一段。小时候我有一个洋娃娃，会说话的洋娃娃，尽管如此，它也只是个洋娃娃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've heard in Cyrodiil, unicorns are prized by the followers of Hircine, but there are no such hunts in Skyrim, not even for a Wolf of Jorrvaskr.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说在赛瑞迪尔，海尔辛的追随者们视独角兽为猎物中的奇珍，但在天际却不然，连月瓦斯卡的群狼都不会去追猎它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A unicorn.</Source>
      <Dest>一只独角兽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Eternal peace.</Source>
      <Dest>永远的和平.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No one will ever ask you to make such a choice.  You might as well say you wouldn't trade it for anything.</Source>
      <Dest>没有人会逼你做出这种决定。你当然还可以拒绝的，就说不管拿什么来你都不会愿意换。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nothing.  Just the usual trinkets surrounded by corpses, blood, and bones.</Source>
      <Dest>啥都没有。尸体上，血泊里，那些骷髅身上，只有些不值钱的寻常饰品罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Found anything of interest here?</Source>
      <Dest>找到什么有趣的东东么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Found anything of interest here?</Source>
      <Dest>找到什么有趣的东东么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The bandit corpse over there is still fresh.  Looks like I arrived here before the wolves could desecrate it.</Source>
      <Dest>躺在那里的强盗尸体还很新鲜。看来那群狼还没来得及亵渎这些尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Found anything of interest here?</Source>
      <Dest>找到什么有趣的东东么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The face on that one looked familiar.  I almost thought it was someone I knew.  A friend's cousin's uncle or something.</Source>
      <Dest>这个人的脸看起来如此似曾相识。我差点以为他是我认识的人了。一个朋友的表姐的叔叔或是其他什么人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What does that make us?  Strangers.  But even the death of a stranger seems like something worth mourning.</Source>
      <Dest>这和我们有什么关系呢？都是些陌生人。但就算是陌生人也应得到哀悼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Found anything of interest here?</Source>
      <Dest>找到什么有趣的东东么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right. We should bury the body.</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的，我们需要把尸体埋了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're welcome to.  It's not something you want to make a habit out of doing though.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴你这么做。尽管你肯定也不愿意那样做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, if I could, I would give them all proper burials, but there isn't enough time in this lifetime and the next.</Source>
      <Dest>如果有可能我也想给他们一个体面的葬礼，但是时间紧迫啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right. We should bury the body.</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的，我们需要把尸体埋了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was fortunate.  Aela's a more skillful archer than I, but on that day she was not at her best, and I was never better.</Source>
      <Dest>我当时挺走运的。艾拉是个比我更有技巧的弓箭手，但是那天她状态有点儿失常，而我则恰好开了挂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Color me impressed.  Besting those three is an impressive feat.</Source>
      <Dest>我太惊讶了！能打败那三位可真是了不起啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Wolves of Jorrvaskr.</Source>
      <Dest>月瓦斯卡群狼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A fine request. I can play that for you.</Source>
      <Dest>点的好。我可以为你演奏这支曲子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every person is worth something to someone.  Even bandits.  But you're right.  Neither of us have any reason to waste our tears.</Source>
      <Dest>每个人对于某人而言都多少有些价值。即使是强盗。不过你是对的，我俩都没有任何理由为他们而悲伤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Looks like just another worthless bandit to me.</Source>
      <Dest>对于我来说这不过是另一个无价值的恶棍罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is that why you cut ties with your familiar?</Source>
      <Dest>这就是你与挚友断交的原因？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My...familiar?  How...how do you know about him?</Source>
      <Dest>我的……挚友？你是……你是怎么知道他的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry to hear that, but I see no reason to.   They say Kodlak Whitemane was a good man, but it was something I always heard second hand.</Source>
      <Dest>我为此感到遗憾，但我认为这并无必要。他们都说克拉科白鬃是个好人，但这也只是据说罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Kodlak Whitemane is dead. You should return and pay your respects.</Source>
      <Dest>克拉科·白鬃死了. 你必须返回并献上你的尊重.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Kodlak I knew was far too consumed with his own demons to pay attention to the likes of me.</Source>
      <Dest>我所知道的克拉科几乎花了一辈子时间在与他自己的心魔斗争，根本多余的精力来关注像我这样的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Kodlak Whitemane is dead. You should return and pay your respects.</Source>
      <Dest>克拉科·白鬃死了. 你必须返回并献上你的尊重.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He will be mourned and he will be honored, and rightly so by the people who loved him.  I don't count myself among them.</Source>
      <Dest>他会被哀悼，也会被称颂，那些爱他的人确实应该这样做。但我并不在其列。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Kodlak Whitemane is dead. You should return and pay your respects.</Source>
      <Dest>克拉科·白鬃死了. 你必须返回并献上你的尊重.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I met him in a prison in Eastmarch. Your name, the accent, it has to be you.</Source>
      <Dest>我在东陲领的牢里见过他。你的名字，口音，一定是你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But how?  How is that even possible?  I know our bond was strong, unusual even, but...well, what did he want?</Source>
      <Dest>但怎么会？这怎么可能？我知道我们的羁绊很深，很不寻常，很……呃，他到底想要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And to think I once thought he was a figment of my imagination. Now he's a figment of everyone else's.  But don't worry, I have no desire to see him.</Source>
      <Dest>想来我曾以为他仅仅存在于我的臆想当中。现在看来他成了所有人的臆想。不过别担心，我不想见他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Best to leave it alone. Conjuration magic can be dangerous.</Source>
      <Dest>最好让它单独呆着，召唤系魔法可能有危险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Tale of the Tongues.</Source>
      <Dest>龙语传说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's one of my favorites. To the Dragonborn, the savior of Skyrim!</Source>
      <Dest>这是我最喜欢的曲子之一。献给天际的救世主——龙裔！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whatever bond we shared is best left to memory. And memories always seem beautiful because well...they're imperfect.</Source>
      <Dest>把我们团结在一起的是共同的回忆。回忆总是美好的，因为它们……不完美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You won't considering seeing him again?</Source>
      <Dest>你不考虑再看看他吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You won't considering seeing him again?</Source>
      <Dest>你不考虑再看看他吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The reality is my familiar was a crutch. A substitute. For a time he served a purpose, but at some point he only served to make me weak.</Source>
      <Dest>现实是，我的挚友只是支撑，是一个替代品。在某些时候他确实能够帮上忙，但有些时候他只会拖累我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, there are many times where I have relied on the strength of others, and each time it has only served to hinder my own development.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，有好几次我试图依赖别人的力量，结果每次都是吃了那帮队友的亏，他们只会帮倒忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We all need to rely on others. Surely you have not come this far without help.</Source>
      <Dest>我们都需要相互扶持，想想你如果一切只靠自己也走不到今天吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We all need to rely on others. Surely you have not come this far without help.</Source>
      <Dest>我们都需要相互扶持，想想你如果一切只靠自己也走不到今天吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I once traveled with a companion.  You might even call him a friend.  For years I would rely on him for food, for warmth, and for someone to talk to.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾和一个战友团的人一同去探险，我们也算是朋友。多年来我都是依靠着他来获取食物，取得温暖，排解我心中的寂寞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But what if the day came when I couldn't summon his aid, and then what would become of me?  No, that wasn't going to be my fate.</Source>
      <Dest>但如果到了再也无法得到他的援助的那天，那我会变成怎样？不，我的命运不该是那样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We all need to rely on others. Surely you have not come this far without help.</Source>
      <Dest>我们都需要相互扶持，想想你如果一切只靠自己也走不到今天吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Didn't expect to find you here.</Source>
      <Dest>真没想到在这儿找到你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What, did you think I would spend the rest of my days in that cavern?</Source>
      <Dest>什么，你以为我会在那个洞穴里度过余生吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm in the mood to hear something new.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在有心情听听新玩意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmm...there is one ballad I can play for you.  It was given to me by a bard traveling north to Morthal.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯……有一首民谣我可以演奏给你听，是一个向北部旅行前往莫萨尔的吟游诗人给我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He sat in this tavern and listened to me play, and when I had finished, he asked if I would honor a dying man's last request.</Source>
      <Dest>他坐在旅馆里听着我演奏，等我奏完一曲，他问我能否满足一个将死之人的最后请求。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm in the mood to hear something new.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在有心情听听新玩意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm in the mood to hear something new.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在有心情听听新玩意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then, without another word, he played this song.</Source>
      <Dest>然后他没说一句话，就演奏了这首曲子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to hear you play "Tears of the Hist."</Source>
      <Dest>我想听你演奏一曲《希斯的眼泪》</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A sad and moving ballad. I can play that for you.</Source>
      <Dest>一首哀伤而感人的歌谣。请听好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must really love food, and have an excellent memory.  Even then, it seems like a poor trade.  You'd be much better off with a steak.</Source>
      <Dest>你一定是个吃货，记性也不错。不过即便如此，这笔交易看起来还是不太划算。牛排都比那个要好吃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Gourmet's legendary potage.</Source>
      <Dest>美食家的传奇肉羹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Falmer are hairless vermin in need of a tan.  Nothing to be afraid of.</Source>
      <Dest>雪精灵只是一群秃头且需要接受日光浴的害虫,根本没什么好怕的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fear is a funny thing.  A great warrior might slay a giant as big as a mountain, but shriek like a handmaiden when a spider crawls up his arm.</Source>
      <Dest>恐惧是很有趣的东西。一位伟大的战士可以杀死山一样高的巨人，也会在蜘蛛爬到胳膊上时像个少女一样尖叫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Falmer are hairless vermin in need of a tan.  Nothing to be afraid of.</Source>
      <Dest>雪精灵只是一群秃头且需要接受日光浴的害虫,根本没什么好怕的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wish I could say my fear of Falmer was just as random.</Source>
      <Dest>我也希望我能说我对雪精灵并没有那么害怕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's enough for now. Take a break.</Source>
      <Dest>现在已经够了，休息一下吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you. Let me know if you wish to hear another song.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你。如果你想听其他歌曲的话就告诉我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I love that song, mostly because Mikael hated it. Couldn't stand singing about someone other than him.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢这首曲子，最大的原因是米凯尔讨厌这种曲子。我简直爱死了站他面前唱这首曲子的那种感觉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Dragonborn Comes.</Source>
      <Dest>龙裔降临。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what does that make you?</Source>
      <Dest>所以，这事儿让你感觉如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know, but I don't have the skills to survive as an adventurer.  You need to know which mushrooms are food, and which ones are poison.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道。但我没有可以作为一名冒险家生存下去的技能。你得能搞得清哪些蘑菇是食物，哪些有剧毒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what does that make you?</Source>
      <Dest>所以，这事儿让你感觉如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have to learn how to sleep on a bed of rock, and with one eye open.  And as a hunter, you have to get used to the idea of being prey.</Source>
      <Dest>你必须习惯夜晚睡在石头上，并且得始终保持警惕。此外，作为一个猎人，你必须得适应被当成狩猎目标的状况。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what does that make you?</Source>
      <Dest>所以，这事儿让你感觉如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The worst part is you might spend a week in some crypt, and have no treasure to show for it. So you also have to learn to handle disappointment.</Source>
      <Dest>最糟糕的是你可能会在某些地穴里呆上一周，却没找到与此付出成正比的宝藏。所以你也要学会接受失望的痛苦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what does that make you?</Source>
      <Dest>所以，这事儿让你感觉如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet it's not the size of a cave that worries me, but what lives inside it.  Particularly, the caves marked by the Falmer.</Source>
      <Dest>我倒不是因为这洞穴的大小而不敢进去，这洞穴里生活着的生物才让我感到害怕。特别是这洞穴里住着的可是雪精灵啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, but there's a certain type of skillset you need to survive. You need to know which mushrooms are food and which ones are poison.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，可是要生存下来你需要有特定的技能。你得能搞得清哪些蘑菇是食物，哪些有剧毒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem like you can handle yourself in a fight.</Source>
      <Dest>看你的样子像是有自卫能力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem like you can handle yourself in a fight.</Source>
      <Dest>看你的样子像是有自卫能力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have to learn how to sleep on a bed of rock, and with one eye open.  And as a hunter, you have to get used to the idea of being prey.</Source>
      <Dest>你必须习惯夜晚睡在石头上，并且得始终保持警惕。此外，作为一个猎人，你必须得适应被当成狩猎目标的状况。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem like you can handle yourself in a fight.</Source>
      <Dest>看你的样子像是有自卫能力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The worst part is you might spend a week in some crypt, and have no treasure to show for it. So you also have to learn to handle disappointment.</Source>
      <Dest>最糟糕的是你可能会在某些地穴里呆上一周，却没找到与此付出成正比的宝藏。所以你也要学会接受失望的痛苦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet it's not the size of a cave that worries me, but what lives inside it.  Particularly, the caves marked by the Falmer.</Source>
      <Dest>我倒不是因为这洞穴的大小而不敢进去，这洞穴里生活着的生物才让我感到害怕。特别是这洞穴里住着的可是雪精灵啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem like you can handle yourself in a fight.</Source>
      <Dest>看你的样子像是有自卫能力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you an adventurer of some sort?</Source>
      <Dest>你是某种冒险者么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hardly. In my time with the Wolves, I did a lot of small favors.  Pest control, muscle jobs, or hunting down petty thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>几乎没有。在我和群狼相处的时间里，我做过许多小趣事。驱除害虫，强健体魄，或者追寻讨厌的贼们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As someone who's spent half her life in the slums, and the other half tracking and hunting forest game, this work was easy.</Source>
      <Dest>对于一个半辈子在贫民窟半辈子在森林里玩狩猎游戏的人来说，这工作不过是小菜一碟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you an adventurer of some sort?</Source>
      <Dest>你是某种冒险者么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unfortunately, raiding caves, Draugr crypts, ghost ships and spider dens are another matter entirely.</Source>
      <Dest>但不幸的是，要清扫那些强盗窝，装满尸鬼的洞穴，幽灵船还有蜘蛛巢可就完全不是同一回事了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you an adventurer of some sort?</Source>
      <Dest>你是某种冒险者么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>La la la la la la...</Source>
      <Dest>啦 啦 啦 啦 啦 啦 ...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>La la la la la la...</Source>
      <Dest>啦 啦 啦 啦 啦 啦 ...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not out of some desire to be a hero, but because I believed there was no safer place to live than inside the great mead hall of Jorrvaskr.</Source>
      <Dest>并不是想要做个英雄什么的，而是因为我坚信没有比宏伟的月瓦斯卡更安全的住所了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I remember kneeling on the steps, drenched in wet rags, the clouds practically screaming the rain.</Source>
      <Dest>我记得我跪在台阶上，穿着湿透的破衣服，天上的云倾下了瓢泼大雨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I must've looked so pitiful, begging Skjor to take me in. Yet it wasn't pity he gave me, but scorn.</Source>
      <Dest>我看起来一定是可怜极了所以斯科月才会收留我。然而他给予我的却不是同情，而是轻蔑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I knew meself a maiden fair, with em'rald eyes and fire-red hair!  She owned a tavern by the sea, and served warm drinks of mellow honey!</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】少女如花正美貌，赤发碧眼秋波长！海边开家小酒馆儿，蜜酒下肚口芬香！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Drink ye merry, drink ye thirsty, bring thy crew 'n revel freely!  For on one thing we're all agreed, that Mogo made the finest mead!</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】喝个痛快，喝个大饱，让你的船员们自由狂欢吧！我们一致认为，莫戈的蜂蜜酒天下无双！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mogo's mead, Mogo's mead, the only drink we'd e'er need! Take a flask and take a seat, and drink thyself a sweety-treat!</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】莫戈莫戈的蜂蜜酒，莫戈莫戈的蜂蜜酒，人只要这酒就够！找个座来拿一瓶，醍醐灌顶百病走！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Clouds sweep over the sky; Floods the swamps of my eyes; Rain falls on Black Marsh, year after year, but the Hist sheds not a tear.</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】阴云掠过无际的天垂；如洪流般在我眼中积堆。年复一年，雨点降落在黑沼泽省，但希斯特却从不垂泪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Forests of green slowly fade; Mists like ghosts of the day; Storms rage through Black Marsh, year after year, but the Hist sheds not a tear;</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】绿色的森林逐渐消退；每日的迷雾庞若鬼魂；暴风咆哮着穿过黑泽，年复一年，但希斯特却不曾流泪；</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Death comes for all we hold dear, but for the Hist shed not a tear.</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】死亡终会夺去我们所珍视的一切，但希斯特却不曾流泪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>.</Source>
      <Dest>。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We drink to our youth, and to days come and gone. For the Age of Aggression is now nearly done.</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】为青春干杯，为那些逝去的和将来的日子干杯。因为好战的年代已经结束。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We'll drive out the Stormcloaks and restore what we own. With our blood and our steel we will take back our home.</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】我们将驱逐风暴斗篷并恢复我们拥有的一切。用我们的鲜血和武器夺回家园。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Down with Ulfric!  The killer of kings!  On the day of your death, we'll drink and we'll sing!</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】乌弗瑞克这跳梁小丑！是杀害至高王的凶手！当你终于被湮灭带走，我们会欢唱会喝酒！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We're the children of Skyrim, and we fight all our lives. And when Sovngarde beckons, every one of us dies!</Source>
      <Dest>我们是天际的子民，我们一辈子都在战斗，只要松加德传来召唤，我们就英勇赴义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But this land is ours and we'll see it wiped clean. Of the scourge that has sullied our hopes and our dreams.</Source>
      <Dest>这片大地是我们的，洁白而干净。任何灾难只会加强我们的信念跟梦想！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>.</Source>
      <Dest>。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We drink to our youth, and to days come and gone. For the Age of Oppression is now nearly done.</Source>
      <Dest>为我们的年少举酒，为过去和到来的日子干杯。为压迫的年代将要成为过往的旧岁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We drink to our youth, and to days come and gone. For the Age of Oppression is now nearly done.</Source>
      <Dest>为了我们的青春，为了那些逝去的和将来的日子，我们干杯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We'll drive out the Empire from this land that we own. With our blood and our steel we will take back our home.</Source>
      <Dest>驱逐帝国找回自我，用鲜血和盔甲重建家国。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All hail to Ulfric! You are the High King! In your great honor we drink and we sing.</Source>
      <Dest>向乌弗瑞克欢呼！您是至高王！我们为你的荣耀举杯欢庆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We're the children of Skyrim, and we fight all our lives. And when Sovngarde beckons, every one of us dies!</Source>
      <Dest>我们是天际的子民，我们一辈子都在战斗，只要松加德传来召唤，我们就英勇赴义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But this land is ours and we'll see it wiped clean. Of the scourge that has sullied our hopes and our dreams.</Source>
      <Dest>这片大地是我们的，洁白而干净。任何灾难只会加强我们的信念跟梦想！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>.</Source>
      <Dest>。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Wolf strode upon great Jorrvaskr, to meet the sons of Ysgramor; They said what are you but a harbinger, to leave us hopeless and forlorn;</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】这条狼大步踏入伟大的月瓦斯卡，去寻找伊斯格拉谟之子；他们说，你就是一个把我们弃于绝望与无助的预言者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Wolf bore its fangs and spread its claws, and tore at its own hide;  Drink the blood, and become my sons, or by dawn you'll not survive;</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】那匹狼张开利爪亮出獠牙，然后撕下了它自己的皮；喝下这血，成为我的孩子吧。否则黎明到来之时你就命不长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so the pack was born again as the Wolves of Jorrvaskr; To rule in life and serve in death, as the moonlight bound hunter.</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】重生时已是月瓦斯卡之群狼。身为生者却宛若行尸走肉，化为与月光永伴的猎手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so the pack was born again as the Wolves of Jorrvaskr; To rule in life and serve in death, as the moonlight's dark hunter.</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】重生时已是月瓦斯卡之群狼。身为生者却宛若行尸走肉，化为与月光永伴的猎手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>.</Source>
      <Dest>。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alduin's wings they did darken the sky; His roar fury's fire and his scales sharpened scythes;</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因其翼遮天蔽日，其吼怒焰四溢，其鳞利如刀锋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Men ran and they cowered and they fought and they died; They burned and they bled as they issued their cries;</Source>
      <Dest>人类退缩、逃跑，战斗、死亡。人类受伤、流血，痛哭、哀嚎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We need saviors to free us from Alduin's rage; Heroes on the field of this new war to wage;</Source>
      <Dest>我们需要救世主将我们从奥杜因的愤怒中解放。这片大地上的英雄们要踏入新的战场上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And if Alduin wins, men is gone from this world; Lost in the shadows of the black wings unfurled;</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因的胜利，将带来人类的灭亡，黑色双翼的阴影下无处可藏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But then came the Tongues on that terrible day; Steadfast as winter they entered the fray;</Source>
      <Dest>可怕的岁月里，发声者们加入战斗，踏着坚定的步伐，凯歌高奏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And all heard the music of Alduin's doom; The sweet song of Skyrim, sky-shattering Thu'um;</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】奥杜因拉下了的命运之幕，那是天际的赞歌，是响彻天际的吐目。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so the Tongues freed us from Alduin's rage; Gave the gift of the Voice, ushered in a new age;</Source>
      <Dest>发声者从奥杜因的愤怒之中解救了我们，龙吼的天赐，引领我们进入新的时代。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If Alduin's eternal then eternity's done; For his story is over and the dragons are gone.</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因的永恒，已然不在。奥杜因的故事，已经终结。龙也消失于天外。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>.</Source>
      <Dest>。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Our hero, our hero, claims a warrior's heart!  I tell you, I tell you, the Dragonborn comes;</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】英雄，英雄，勇者无惧。我告诉你，我告诉你，龙裔已降临。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With a Voice wielding power of the ancient Nord art;  Believe, believe the Dragornborn comes;</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】诺德技艺，龙吼回归。没错，没错，他是龙裔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's an end to the evil, of all Skyrim's foes; Beware, beware the Dragonborn comes;</Source>
      <Dest>终结邪恶，敌人的末日。当心，当心，龙裔出世。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For the darkness has passed and the legend yet grows; You'll know, you'll know the Dragonborn comes.</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】黑暗消逝，传奇之曲正在编织。你会发现，你会发现，龙裔已降临。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>.</Source>
      <Dest>。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, there once was a hero named Ragnar the Red, who came riding to Whiterun from ole Rorikstead!</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】哦，曾经有位名叫“红衣拉格纳”的英雄，他从美丽的洛利克镇一路骑马来到白漫城！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And the braggart did swagger and brandish his blade, as he told of bold battles and gold he had made!</Source>
      <Dest>大话精吹嘘他身经百战，炫耀着金币还有他的剑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But then he went quiet, did Ragnar the Red, when he met the shield-maiden Matilda who said;</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】红衣拉格纳后来变了哑巴，全因他遇到盾牌女仆玛提尔达，她说……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, you talk and you lie and you drink all our mead! Now I think it's high time that you lie down and bleed!</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】噢，你吹牛喝酒耍活宝！真有种就不要跑！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so then came the clashing and slashing of steel, as the brave lass Matilda charged in full of zeal!</Source>
      <Dest>一阵金属碰撞叮叮当当，勇敢的女孩玛提尔达战意高涨！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And the braggart named Ragnar was boastful no more!  When his ugly red head rolled around on the floor!</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】自大狂拉格纳再也没法在那吹牛了！因为他那丑陋的红毛脑袋掉在地上摔成了一堆渣！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>.</Source>
      <Dest>。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Wolf strode upon great Jorrvaskr, to meet the sons of Ysgramor; They said what are you but a harbinger, to leave us hopeless and forlorn;</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】这条狼大步踏入伟大的月瓦斯卡，去寻找伊斯格拉谟之子；他们说，你就是一个把我们弃于绝望与无助的预言者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so the pack was born again as the Wolves of Jorrvaskr; To rule in life and serve in death, as the moonlight bound hunter.</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】重生时已是月瓦斯卡之群狼。身为生者却宛若行尸走肉，化为与月光永伴的猎手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Wolf bore its fangs and spread its claws, and tore at its own hide;  Drink the blood, and become my sons, or by dawn you'll not survive;</Source>
      <Dest>【原版歌词替换】那匹狼张开利爪亮出獠牙，然后撕下了它自己的皮；喝下这血，成为我的孩子吧。否则黎明到来之时你就命不长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Clouds sweep over the skies; And floods the swamps of my eyes; Rain falls on Black Marsh, year after year, but the Hist sheds not a tear.</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】流云扫过天空，盖住了我的眼睛；大雨年复一年地落在黑沼省的土地上，但是希斯特从未流过一滴泪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Forests of green slowly fade; As mists like ghosts of the day; Storms rage through Black Marsh, year after year, but the Hist sheds not a tear;</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】绿色的森林逐渐消退；每日的迷雾庞若鬼魂；暴风咆哮着穿过黑泽，年复一年，但希斯特却从不流泪；</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Death comes for all we hold dear, but for the Hist shed not a tear.</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词待校对】死亡终会夺去我们所珍视的一切，但希斯特却不曾流泪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>.</Source>
      <Dest>。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Drum - Medley}</Source>
      <Dest>{鼓声 - 混奏}</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Lute - Wolves of Jorrvaskr}</Source>
      <Dest>{鲁特琴 -月瓦斯卡群狼}</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Lute - Medley}</Source>
      <Dest>{鲁特琴混奏}</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Lute - Medley}</Source>
      <Dest>{鲁特琴混奏}</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Lute - Tale of the Tongues}</Source>
      <Dest>{鲁特琴——《龙吼传奇》</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Lute - Tale of the Tongues}</Source>
      <Dest>{鲁特琴——《龙吼传奇》</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Flute Medley}</Source>
      <Dest>{长笛乐曲}</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Flute Medley}</Source>
      <Dest>{长笛乐曲}</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Flute Medley}</Source>
      <Dest>{长笛乐曲}</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Flute Medley}</Source>
      <Dest>{长笛乐曲}</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Flute Medley}</Source>
      <Dest>{长笛乐曲}</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>La la la la la la...</Source>
      <Dest>啦 啦 啦 啦 啦 啦 ...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>La la la la la la...</Source>
      <Dest>啦 啦 啦 啦 啦 啦 ...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>La la la la la la...</Source>
      <Dest>啦 啦 啦 啦 啦 啦 ...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I dedicate to Mikael, to Jorrvaskr, and the ego that was bigger than both!</Source>
      <Dest>我赞扬米凯尔，赞扬月瓦斯卡，但是自尊比这两者都要重要！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Bard Play}</Source>
      <Dest>{吟游诗人演奏}</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until next time.</Source>
      <Dest>下回见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right then.</Source>
      <Dest>那好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is it?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that Skjarn with you? I'll just pretend I'm not here.</Source>
      <Dest>史卡盎和你在一起？我马上消失，就当我不在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We need a bard who can handle herself in case things get messy.</Source>
      <Dest>我们需要在混战中能够自保的诗人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It sounds to me you don't need a bard at all. If it's a Giant you're after, what makes you think things won't get messy?</Source>
      <Dest>这话听着让我觉得你压根不需要什么诗人。如果你追杀的是一个巨人，那是什么让你觉得事情不会变得一塌糊涂呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's not about belonging to any faction. You can sing and you can fight.</Source>
      <Dest>和从属于任何阵营无关。你想唱就唱，想打就打。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I confess, I have a love for strings, whether they be on bows or lutes. Yet I doubt my arrows can fell or Giant, nor can my song appease one.</Source>
      <Dest>我承认，我对弦有一种爱恋，不管它们是被做成了弓还是被做成了鲁特琴。不过我觉得我的箭是无法射杀巨人的，我的歌曲也无法安抚它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, it's either you or Aela, and chances are she sings like a cow.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，无论是你还是艾拉，多半都会觉得她唱得像头牛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Then you might be better off going with her. I can't recall ever hearing a Giant sing, but imagine their music to be a little off key.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑声）那你最好还是带着她离开吧。我不记得我是不是有听过巨人唱歌了，不过我猜它们唱起歌来八成会有点跑调。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I doubt any bard can soothe the heart of a Giant. It's more likely they will use your head as a drum.</Source>
      <Dest>我不觉得会有能够安抚巨人心灵的吟游诗人，大部分时候他们只会拿你的脑袋当鼓来敲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, it's either you or Aela, and chances are she sings like a cow.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，无论是你还是艾拉，多半都会觉得她唱得像头牛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You sing beautifully. You are no bard, but something far greater.</Source>
      <Dest>你的歌声真美极了，虽然不是诗人，胜似诗人！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I apologize, but flattery is wasted on me. Besides, how can a song soothe the heart of a Giant? You've read far too many children's tales.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉，不过奉承对我不起效。此外，怎么可能会有能安抚巨人的歌曲？你这是还活在童话世界里么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We need a bard to soothe the heart of a Giant.</Source>
      <Dest>我们需要一个吟游诗人来安抚巨人的心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A Giant? I'm afraid that sounds like a job for the Companions, and I am no longer that.</Source>
      <Dest>处理巨人？这难道不是战友团的工作吗，我已经不是战友团的人啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nor do I consider myself a bard. So it seems you have come up empty on both counts.</Source>
      <Dest>我也不认为自己算什么吟游诗人。所以看起来你两头的打算都落空了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We need a bard to soothe the heart of a Giant.</Source>
      <Dest>我们需要一个吟游诗人来安抚巨人的心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) I beg to differ, but I suppose it matters not. That's all in the past.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑声）我不敢苟同，但这并不重要。一切都过去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That armor looked terrible on you anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>那身盔甲穿在你身上怎么看都难看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That armor looked terrible on you anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>那身盔甲穿在你身上怎么看都难看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, I'm sure you didn't come here to listen to me argue over nothing. What business do you have here in Whiterun?</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我确信你不是来听我瞎扯的。你来雪漫城有何贵干？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As I've told you before, we all have weaknesses. The others fill in the gaps.</Source>
      <Dest>我跟你说过，人人都有弱点。可以由其他人来填补。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is where you and I differ, friend. I train every day to rid myself of weaknesses, or at the very least, so I can mask them with my strength.</Source>
      <Dest>伙计，这便是你我不同的地方。至少于我而言，我每天都是不断地努力去克服自己的弱点，至少我不会秀自己的下限。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As I've told you before, we all have weaknesses. The others fill in the gaps.</Source>
      <Dest>我跟你说过，人人都有弱点。可以由其他人来填补。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, I'm sure you didn't come here to listen to me argue over nothing. What business do you have here in Whiterun?</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我确信你不是来听我瞎扯的。你来雪漫城有何贵干？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You may have strength in battle, but you lack resolve if you yearn for the company of others. But they cannot be with you forever.</Source>
      <Dest>你可能在战场上颇有一手。但如果你仍然渴望着他人的帮助，那你下手时就无法干净利落。因为他们无法永远与你相伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My strength is unmatched, but even a strong warrior needs good company.</Source>
      <Dest>我的力量无人可比，不过再强的战士也需要出色的班底。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My strength is unmatched, but even a strong warrior needs good company.</Source>
      <Dest>我的力量无人可比，不过再强的战士也需要出色的班底。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, I'm sure you didn't come here to listen to me argue over nothing. What business do you have here in Whiterun?</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我确信你不是来听我瞎扯的。你来雪漫城有何贵干？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We've had this conversation, but I agree. Others will only let you down.</Source>
      <Dest>我们讨论过了，其他人只会让你失望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And yet you come to me with companions in tow. Your business here in Whiterun must be urgent, for you to defy your own words.</Source>
      <Dest>现在你带着你的战友团同僚来找我了。你在白漫城一定有很紧急的事情要做，以至于你连誓言都能违背。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you're well, Fjona.</Source>
      <Dest>看见你平安无恙真是太好了，菲欧娜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>More than well. I feel lighter. Spry, even. I wish I had shed my old Companions armor sooner.</Source>
      <Dest>真是棒极了。我现在的感觉不仅是轻松，甚至还充满了活力。要知道如此，我早点脱掉这老旧的战友团盔甲就好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you're well, Fjona.</Source>
      <Dest>看见你平安无恙真是太好了，菲欧娜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You see, all my life I've worn heavy armor. It always felt safe. But after we spoke, I realized it was just another crutch.</Source>
      <Dest>你看，我这辈子一直都穿着重甲。它总让我很有安全感。但在与你交谈之后，我意识到它或许只是另一个精神寄托。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you're well, Fjona.</Source>
      <Dest>看见你平安无恙真是太好了，菲欧娜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't need Eorlund's armor to protect me. All I need is my own strength.</Source>
      <Dest>我不需要用厄伦德的盔甲来保护自己，我有我力量就够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought you didn't want to come back to this place.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜大概你不想重回此地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I didn't come back to join. I came back to return something. You see, all my life I've worn heavy armor.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是来归队的。我回来是送还一些东西的。你看，我一辈子都穿着重甲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought you didn't want to come back to this place.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜大概你不想重回此地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It just felt more comfortable. Safe. But after we spoke...I started to wonder...maybe it was just another crutch.</Source>
      <Dest>那让人感觉更舒服。安全。可当我们谈过之后……我开始疑心……也许那只是另一个精神寄托。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought you didn't want to come back to this place.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜大概你不想重回此地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't need Eorlund's armor to protect me. All I need is my own strength.</Source>
      <Dest>我不需要用厄伦德的盔甲来保护自己，我有我力量就够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, there you are. For some reason I had a feeling I'd run into you here. </Source>
      <Dest>啊，你在这里啊。我总有种预感，似乎在这儿就一定能遇上你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I'm glad someone got to take home something.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，很高兴看到终于有人往家里带点什么了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) So what was the point of all this, anyway?</Source>
      <Dest>（叹气）话说回来，那这一切究竟有什么意义呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I-I...no, this is all a mistake!</Source>
      <Dest>我——我……不，这一切都是个误会！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wasn't me, it was him!</Source>
      <Dest>那不是我，那是他！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I-I...no, this is all a mistake!</Source>
      <Dest>我——我……不，这一切都是个误会！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wasn't me, it was her!</Source>
      <Dest>那不是我，那是她！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Am I the only one who's curious about the treasure? Someone should jump into that lake.</Source>
      <Dest>我是唯一那个对宝藏好奇的人吗？总该有人跳进湖里去看看吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Lute}</Source>
      <Dest>{鲁特琴声}</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, wish me luck.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧,祝我好运。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the Nine! It's enormous!</Source>
      <Dest>九圣灵在上！真是壮观！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We'll need to clear a space for me to play. The last thing I need is a critique from an angry bear.</Source>
      <Dest>我们得清出一块空地来让我表演。我最讨厌的就是中途蹦出只发怒的巨熊来打断我的演出了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know. It seems like you could just as easily run out of magicka and end up fighting with your dagger.</Source>
      <Dest>我不清楚。看来你总是随随便便就用光你的法力，然后就不得不用你的匕首来结束战斗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't relate. I've always preferred being on my own.</Source>
      <Dest>我没办法与别人合作。我宁愿孤身一人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've always felt like I understood Argonian ballads. Not just their sadness, but their strength.</Source>
      <Dest>我总是觉得我能理解亚龙人的歌谣。那不只是他们的悲伤，更是他们的力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you talking about the lute or the bow? Although I supposed the answer is "yes" to both.</Source>
      <Dest>你是在谈论鲁特琴或弓吗？虽然我已经猜到两者的答案都是“是”了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Uh...I think it's best if I play alone.</Source>
      <Dest>噢……我觉得独奏要更好一些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) I'll go get my lute.</Source>
      <Dest>（叹息）我还是去拿我的鲁特琴吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In other words, you have no idea what song I need to play.</Source>
      <Dest>换句话说，你不知道我要弹奏什么歌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You left out the most important detail. Do you even know what song is the key to this spell?</Source>
      <Dest>你忘记了最重要的细节。你到底知不知道什么曲调是这个魔咒的关键？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I imagine it won't do us any good to sing something like "Mogo's Mead."</Source>
      <Dest>我认为唱像“莫戈的蜂蜜酒”那样的歌于我们毫无裨益。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
