<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course it was you, boy. The others were not so foolish. Nor were they as brave.</Source>
      <Dest>当然是你，孩子。其他人没有那么愚蠢。也没那么勇敢。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course it would be you.</Source>
      <Dest>我当然会与你在一起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I challenged the Gods themselves, and neither Daedric Prince nor the makers of the realm could fell me.</Source>
      <Dest>我对神灵本身发起了挑战，不管是魔神还是创世者都不是我的对手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As have I, boy. Don't disappoint me now.</Source>
      <Dest>这是因为有我，孩子。现在别让我失望了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In my time, I have challenged Jarls and Kings, armies and Empires.</Source>
      <Dest>想当年，领主、国王、军队和帝国我都挑战过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I told you idiots I didn't want to be disturbed!</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉你，白痴，我不想被打扰！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha! Don't be absurd. I haven't the slightest idea what you're talking about.</Source>
      <Dest>哈！简直荒谬！我不知道你在说什么！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know who you are, but I know what you are, and what you are not.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道你是谁。但我却知道你是怎样的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have been targeted by everyone from the Brotherhood to the remnants of old the Morag Tong.</Source>
      <Dest>因为是莫拉格帮会的残余我已经被兄弟会的每一个人追杀过了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
