<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Too bad.  It looks like fate took him first.</Source>
      <Dest>太糟糕了。看来他第一次遇到这种事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Too bad.  It looks like fate took him first.</Source>
      <Dest>太糟糕了。看来他第一次遇到这种事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait, what?  I thought you loved him.</Source>
      <Dest>等等，啥？我还以为你爱着他呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait, what?  I thought you loved him.</Source>
      <Dest>等等，啥？我还以为你爱着他呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't really pay too much attention to anything he had to say.</Source>
      <Dest>我确实没有特别留意他所说的那些话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't really pay too much attention to anything he had to say.</Source>
      <Dest>我确实没有特别留意他所说的那些话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't really pay too much attention to anything he had to say.</Source>
      <Dest>我确实没有特别留意他所说的那些话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, he couldn't stop talking about you.  It was really too much.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，他不停地谈论你。真是谈的太多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, he couldn't stop talking about you.  It was really too much.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，他不停地谈论你。真是谈的太多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where is Vanus' research laboratory?</Source>
      <Dest>维纳斯的研究室在哪？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where is Vanus' research laboratory?</Source>
      <Dest>维纳斯的研究室在哪？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, he didn't mention you once.</Source>
      <Dest>其实他从没提到过你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, he didn't mention you once.</Source>
      <Dest>其实他从没提到过你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, he didn't mention you once.</Source>
      <Dest>其实他从没提到过你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't I seduce your Elf friend and take her out of the picture?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么我不能引诱你的精灵朋友然后带她离开这画呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't I seduce your Elf friend and take her out of the picture?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么我不能引诱你的精灵朋友然后带她离开这画呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't give a sodding nirnroot about your love life.  Take me to Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>我不会迁怒于你可爱的生命。带我去见納洛斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly does Nelos have planned?</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯到底是在计划着什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly does Nelos have planned?</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯到底是在计划着什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what if I side with Olivia?</Source>
      <Dest>那么我支持奥利维亚如何?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what if I side with Olivia?</Source>
      <Dest>那么我支持奥利维亚如何?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what if I side with Olivia?</Source>
      <Dest>那么我支持奥利维亚如何?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm willing to listen to his proposal.</Source>
      <Dest>我很乐意听他的建议。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Face it Gilsi, he just doesn't like you.</Source>
      <Dest>面对现实吧歌尔西,他没那么喜欢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Face it Gilsi, he just doesn't like you.</Source>
      <Dest>面对现实吧歌尔西,他没那么喜欢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not to worry.  I'm just getting started killing you fools.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心。我现在就杀了你们这些白痴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not to worry.  I'm just getting started killing you fools.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心。我现在就杀了你们这些白痴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They're your comrades.  You shouldn't wish them ill will.</Source>
      <Dest>他们是你的伙伴。 你不该希望他们持有憎恨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They're your comrades.  You shouldn't wish them ill will.</Source>
      <Dest>他们是你的伙伴。 你不该希望他们持有憎恨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nelos killed Jadro'Ra.  I would never join your ranks.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯杀了驹卓拉。我永远不会加入你们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nelos killed Jadro'Ra.  I would never join your ranks.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯杀了驹卓拉。我永远不会加入你们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Get over it.  I need you and your magic with me.</Source>
      <Dest>结束吧。我需要你和你的魔法的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Get over it.  I need you and your magic with me.</Source>
      <Dest>结束吧。我需要你和你的魔法的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Frankly, I haven't decided yet.</Source>
      <Dest>坦白地说，我还没决定呢.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Frankly, I haven't decided yet.</Source>
      <Dest>坦白地说，我还没决定呢.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Frankly, I haven't decided yet.</Source>
      <Dest>坦白地说，我还没决定呢.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright. I'm ready to see Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，我准备好去见纳洛斯了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, now you have a new leader to worship.  Me.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，现在你有了一个新的应该崇拜的领袖，就是我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, now you have a new leader to worship.  Me.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，现在你有了一个新的应该崇拜的领袖，就是我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I always suspected your motives were a bit unusual.</Source>
      <Dest>我总觉得你的动机有点不同寻常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I always suspected your motives were a bit unusual.</Source>
      <Dest>我总觉得你的动机有点不同寻常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then why are you out here.  It seems Nelos doesn't care for you at all.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你现在在这儿。看来纳洛斯根本不在乎你啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then why are you out here.  It seems Nelos doesn't care for you at all.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你现在在这儿。看来纳洛斯根本不在乎你啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Neither Olivia or Nelos have sway over what I do.</Source>
      <Dest>奥利维亚和纳洛斯都改变不了我要做的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Neither Olivia or Nelos have sway over what I do.</Source>
      <Dest>奥利维亚和纳洛斯都改变不了我要做的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Neither Olivia or Nelos have sway over what I do.</Source>
      <Dest>奥利维亚和纳洛斯都改变不了我要做的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well...it's about time.  You've made Nelos wait quite a while.  It was rather poor manners on your part.  You're almost as bad as that Elf!</Source>
      <Dest>喔……到时候了。你让纳洛斯等了好一会儿了。这非常失礼。你简直跟那个精灵一样差劲！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You forget, I prefer an Elf that's cold and frigid.   And his intentions are as clear as ice.</Source>
      <Dest>你忘了，我更喜欢如冰霜般无情的精灵。而他的内心也像冰一样透明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, I trust your meeting with Nelos went well?  How many times did he mention me?  Seven?  Eight?</Source>
      <Dest>那么，我相信你与纳洛斯的会面还算顺利？他提到了我几次？七次？还是八次？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then obviously you're a fool.  Luckily, Winterhold is on the other side of Skyrim.  So you have a week's journey to reconsider your foolishness.</Source>
      <Dest>很显然你是个傻瓜。幸运的是冬堡远在天际省的另一端。所以你可以利用差不多一个星期的旅程时间来反省自己的愚蠢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nelos is the preeminent thinker in all of Tamriel.  You would do well to at least listen to what he has to say.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯是整个泰姆瑞尔大陆里最杰出的思想家。哪怕只是听他说的话，也会让你做的更好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You sound like the old hag.  Nelos encourages us to channel our passions.</Source>
      <Dest>你这话听起来就像个老巫婆。纳洛斯鼓励我们释放自己的激情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source> No, I am more than equipped to handle that firestarter on my own.  And for the record, she is not my friend.</Source>
      <Dest> 不，我已经做好万全准备来独自解决那个纵火者。还有声明一下，她可不是我的朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have no idea how much I've fantasized about kissing Nelos, and feeling his body go cold and limp in my arms.  </Source>
      <Dest>你不知道我有多想亲吻纳洛斯，然后看着他的尸体在我怀里慢慢变冷，失去生机。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Soon will come the passing of the Long Night, and with it, a new dawn.  That's all I'll say for now.  Nelos will fill you in on the rest.</Source>
      <Dest>漫漫长夜即将过去，在这之后，将是一个崭新的黎明。这就是我要说的了。纳洛斯会为你提供休息的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And what of the other thing?  The guild business and such.  Are you one of us now?</Source>
      <Dest>那其他的事情呢？如公会生意之类的。你现在算是我们的一员吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Would you ask the farmer to fight your wars?  Or the guardsman to grow your beets?</Source>
      <Dest>你想让农夫去帮你打仗？或者干脆让卫兵帮你种甜菜得了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He knew that old hag would burst a vein in her forehead and send you right to us.  After all, it's time you fought for the winning side.</Source>
      <Dest>他知道那个老巫婆会脑门儿上的血管都会爆开，然后把你送来我们这。毕竟，是时候你该为注定胜利的一方而战了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And what of the other thing?  Are you one of us now?  Is it time to give the old hag a cold, icy death?</Source>
      <Dest>其他的事情呢？你现在是我们中的一员了吗？是时候给那个老女巫一个冰酷无情的了断了吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know what you're talking about. There's nothing more romantic than a warm body going cold in your arms.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道你在说什么。没什么比一具温暖的身躯在你怀里渐渐变冷更加浪漫的事情了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, I suggest you take his offer.  You are going to take his offer, aren't you?</Source>
      <Dest>所以，我建议你答应他的条件。你会答应的，对吧？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I told him it should be her that should stand watch, but he insisted I do it.  After all, I'm the only one he can truly rely on.</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉他，应该站岗的人其实是她，但他还是坚持要我站岗。毕竟，我可是唯一一个他可以真正可以依靠的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wanted to savor his death in my mouth, feel the life seep out of him.</Source>
      <Dest>我想在亲口品尝他死亡的滋味，感觉生命是如何从他身体里流失的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like I told you at Dragon Bridge, that is impossible.  You can plainly see how stunning I am.  Are you suggesting my Nelos prefers males?</Source>
      <Dest>就像我在龙桥告诉你的那样，这是不可能的。你明白我有多吃惊吧。你难道在暗示我的纳洛斯更喜欢男人吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But while you may be cold, Nelos is colder, and my touch is the coldest of all.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管你可能很冷酷，但纳洛斯会比你更甚，而我的轻触则会寒彻骨髓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, we recognize your value.  You would be wise to do the same.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我们承认你的价值，如果你也一样说明你还不算太笨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My, aren't we the cold one.  They say the one who cares less is the one with the power.</Source>
      <Dest>天哪，我们才不是无情的人。人们说拥有力量的人才能对一切都漠不关心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good.  You'll find he is a reasonable Elf, and not at all what the old hag paints him to be.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。你会发现他其实是个很理性的精灵，完全不是老巫婆所描绘的那种人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just up the stairs and down the trap door.  You musn't keep him waiting.</Source>
      <Dest>赶紧从楼上的暗门里进去。你可不能让他久等。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you should start with that wretched drunk. Make it look like an accident.  Or don't.  I really don't care.</Source>
      <Dest>那你就从那个可悲的酒鬼开始吧。可以伪装成一场事故。不这么干也行。我无所谓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course I loved him.  I've only loved two mortals in my life.  The first I killed with a kiss.  I was going to do the same to Nelos. </Source>
      <Dest>我当然爱他。在我的一生中，我只爱过两个凡人。第一个被我的吻所杀。现在我也要对待纳洛斯做同样的事情。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It can be a bit too much at times, but you can't blame him.  (Sigh) It's such a burden to be so beautiful.  </Source>
      <Dest>也许是多花了些时间，但是你不要责怪他。（叹气）长的美丽还真是个负担。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, he prefers beauty and power.  I am brimming with both.</Source>
      <Dest>不，他喜欢的是既美丽又强壮。而我两者皆备。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, he prefers beauty and power.  I am brimming with both.</Source>
      <Dest>不，他喜欢的是既美丽又强壮。而我两者皆备。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No.  I will not get over it.  But yes, I will accompany you.  Besides, you want me angry.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我是迈不过这道坎了。但没错，我会协助你的。此外，你是想要我生气啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I plan to die in the arms of my beloved.  So if you're going to make trouble, at least wait until we're inside.</Source>
      <Dest>我打算死在我恋人的怀中。所以如果你想找麻烦，至少等我们都进来了再说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No.  Not if you aren't going to ask nicely.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你不打算更礼貌的提问，答案是不。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You fancy yourself a free thinker?  That isn't the wisest course.</Source>
      <Dest>你幻想自己是个无神论者？真是不明智。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And what about my fate?  My destiny?  Do you know how often I thought of blowing him a deathly kiss, but held back?</Source>
      <Dest>我的命运又会怎么样？我的宿命？你知道我有多少次想给他一个死亡之吻，又多少次忍住了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you do side with that old hag, know this:</Source>
      <Dest>但如果你还打算站在老巫婆那边的话，你得知道……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you do side with that old hag, know this:</Source>
      <Dest>但如果你还打算站在老巫婆那边的话，你得知道……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that's ridiculous.  The choice is clear.  One side is led by an ugly, feeble old witch, and the other is a pure as the winter snow.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，这真是荒唐。选择很明了，一边是听命于一个蹒跚的，丑陋老巫婆，另一边则如同冬雪般的纯净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Seduce...Eldawyn?  Oh Gods no, I wouldn't ask my worst enemy to subject themselves to such horrors. </Source>
      <Dest>勾引……艾德温？噢不，天哪，就算是我最痛恨的敌人，我也不会要他去做这么可憎的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Everything is happening as Nelos envisioned it.  I think he planned for you to interfere with Vanus' spells.  There's really no other explanation.</Source>
      <Dest>所有事情皆如纳洛斯所预见的那般发展。我想他打算让你去干扰万纳斯的咒语。除此之外没有其他解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've always said my touch is coldest when my insides burn.  You might as well just step out of the way and let me do all the work.</Source>
      <Dest>我说过在怒火中烧时我的碰触是最为残酷的。你也许应该站到一旁，让我独自完成这事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you think you're deserving of my love, then you're mistaken.  But Skyrim is a vast, cold place.  We may find another.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你认为你值得我去爱，那你就大错特错了。但天际省是如此广阔的地方。我们可以找到另一个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're lying.  You can plainly see how stunning I am.  Are you suggesting my Nelos prefers males?</Source>
      <Dest>你在撒谎。你能清清楚楚的看到我有多大的魅力。而你却说我的纳洛斯更喜欢男人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, I don't like the idea of them being alone together, even for one second.  Far be it for any of the others to make their presence known.</Source>
      <Dest>我还是觉得让他们俩独处不是个好主意，哪怕一小会儿也很不妥。绝不能让任何人知道他们的存在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, don't tell me you bought that troll manure.  Nelos, in his infinite wisdom, placed this location in Vanus' texts.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，别告诉我那块巨魔粪便是你买的。纳洛斯，利用他的无穷睿智，将这个放在万纳斯的书中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only person I ever kissed died of frost.  And while I would never give you a kiss, if you cross us, well...I can always blow you one.</Source>
      <Dest>唯一被我吻过的人冻死在寒风中。我可不会亲你的，但如果你背叛了我们，试试看……我随时都能朝你呼出寒风。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only person I ever kissed died of frost.  And while I would never give you a kiss, if you cross us, well...I can always blow you one.</Source>
      <Dest>唯一被我吻过的人冻死在寒风中。我可不会亲你的，但如果你背叛了我们，试试看……我随时都能朝你呼出寒风。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For the Elf, it's her burning desire to be hideously ugly.  For myself, its praying for her cold, icy death.</Source>
      <Dest>就那个精灵而言，因她自己的渴望而变成一个可怖的丑八怪。就我而言，只能为她凄凉无情的下场而祈祷了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These hands and these lips are yours, Guildmaster, even though you will never know their touch.</Source>
      <Dest>这双手和这嘴唇属于你了，工会大师，虽然你永远也不知道它们会碰哪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And you killed five of ours...or was it four?  In any event, you don't see us whining and moaning about it.</Source>
      <Dest>你杀了我们的五个……也许是四个？不管在什么情况下，你都不会看见我们因为这个发牢骚或者抱怨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wanted to hold him close to me and feel his body go limp, and his soft, tender lips turn hard as ice.   </Source>
      <Dest>我想紧拥着他，感受着他的身体慢慢失去生机。还有他那柔软，温柔的嘴唇变得如坚冰般僵硬。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How could Nelos just die like that?  I was supposed to kill him!</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯怎么会这么死去？我该亲手了结他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're his star pupil, and he wants to make me jealous.  But there's no need for either of us to be.  Although I wouldn't blame you if you were.</Source>
      <Dest>你是他的得意门生，他希望我嫉妒你。但是我们俩没有必要嫉妒彼此。即使你有这种感觉我也不会责怪你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In Skyrim life is short and courtship shorter.</Source>
      <Dest>在天际，生命是短暂的，爱情就更是短暂的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In Skyrim life is short and courtship shorter.</Source>
      <Dest>在天际，生命是短暂的，爱情就更是短暂的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nelos looked a bit sickly.  Did you know he's dying?</Source>
      <Dest>Nelos 看起来有点憔悴.  你知道他正步向死亡么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nelos looked a bit sickly.  Did you know he's dying?</Source>
      <Dest>Nelos 看起来有点憔悴.  你知道他正步向死亡么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here for a moment.</Source>
      <Dest>在这儿等一下.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need you to do something for me.</Source>
      <Dest>我需要你为我做件事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry for your loss.  Nelos loved you deeply.</Source>
      <Dest>我为你的失败感到遗憾。纳洛斯曾经深爱着你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry for your loss.  Nelos loved you deeply.</Source>
      <Dest>我为你的失败感到遗憾。纳洛斯曾经深爱着你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why frost magic?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么是冰霜魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why frost magic?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么是冰霜魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why frost magic?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么是冰霜魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned there were others.</Source>
      <Dest>你是说当时还有其他人在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned there were others.</Source>
      <Dest>你是说当时还有其他人在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He obviously sees you as just a friend.</Source>
      <Dest>他明显是把你当做一个朋友看待的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He obviously sees you as just a friend.</Source>
      <Dest>他明显是把你当做一个朋友看待的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You've been expecting me?</Source>
      <Dest>你一直在等我？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You've been expecting me?</Source>
      <Dest>你一直在等我？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Naturally.</Source>
      <Dest>自然地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Naturally.</Source>
      <Dest>自然地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Naturally.</Source>
      <Dest>自然地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Naturally.</Source>
      <Dest>自然地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I know Gerrod.  Still dodging the gaze of his wives?</Source>
      <Dest>我知道杰瑞。他还在躲着他的老婆们？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. He probably would've never spoken again otherwise.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。否则他可能再也不会说了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. He probably would've never spoken again otherwise.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。否则他可能再也不会说了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. He probably would've never spoken again otherwise.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。否则他可能再也不会说了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. He probably would've never spoken again otherwise.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。否则他可能再也不会说了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here.</Source>
      <Dest>在这里等着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not familiar with any of those names.</Source>
      <Dest>我没听过那些名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not familiar with any of those names.</Source>
      <Dest>我没听过那些名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Using frost magic to preserve youth? How would that work?</Source>
      <Dest>使用冰霜魔法来永葆青春？那能行吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Using frost magic to preserve youth? How would that work?</Source>
      <Dest>使用冰霜魔法来永葆青春？那能行吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Using frost magic to preserve youth? How would that work?</Source>
      <Dest>使用冰霜魔法来永葆青春？那能行吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Using frost magic to preserve youth? How would that work?</Source>
      <Dest>使用冰霜魔法来永葆青春？那能行吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Using frost magic to preserve youth? How would that work?</Source>
      <Dest>使用冰霜魔法来永葆青春？那能行吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Go on. This couldn't have possibly ended well.</Source>
      <Dest>继续。这恐怕不会有好结果了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Go on. This couldn't have possibly ended well.</Source>
      <Dest>继续。这恐怕不会有好结果了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Go on. This couldn't have possibly ended well.</Source>
      <Dest>继续。这恐怕不会有好结果了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Go on. This couldn't have possibly ended well.</Source>
      <Dest>继续。这恐怕不会有好结果了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Go on. This couldn't have possibly ended well.</Source>
      <Dest>继续。这恐怕不会有好结果了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was so special about the tome?</Source>
      <Dest>这个坟墓有什么特别之处？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was so special about the tome?</Source>
      <Dest>这个坟墓有什么特别之处？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was so special about the tome?</Source>
      <Dest>这个坟墓有什么特别之处？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was so special about the tome?</Source>
      <Dest>这个坟墓有什么特别之处？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I plan on tricking Olivia into returning here alone.</Source>
      <Dest>我打算把奥利维亚单独骗回这里来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I plan on tricking Olivia into returning here alone.</Source>
      <Dest>我打算把奥利维亚单独骗回这里来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I plan on tricking Olivia into returning here alone.</Source>
      <Dest>我打算把奥利维亚单独骗回这里来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>When nights are long and winters are cold, mortals die.  This I like.</Source>
      <Dest>夜晚变得漫长之时，凛冬来临，凡人们接二连三的死去。我喜欢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Let's stop and trade some things.</Source>
      <Dest>我们停一下，我想跟你交换点东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet it only left her skin cracked and dry, and whiter than a Nord's.  She was a living ghost.</Source>
      <Dest>但这只留给她比任何诺德人还要干燥苍白的皮肤。她是一个活生生的幽灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet it only left her skin cracked and dry, and whiter than a Nord's.  She was a living ghost.</Source>
      <Dest>但这只留给她比任何诺德人还要干燥苍白的皮肤。她是一个活生生的幽灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then look at the way catfish come to the surface when the earth is about to quake, or how rodents scurry indoors days before winter.</Source>
      <Dest>他们看起来就像地震前浮出水面的鲶鱼，或者入冬前躲进洞里的动物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then look at the way catfish come to the surface when the earth is about to quake, or how rodents scurry indoors days before winter.</Source>
      <Dest>他们看起来就像地震前浮出水面的鲶鱼，或者入冬前躲进洞里的动物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What can I do for you master?</Source>
      <Dest>我能为你做些什么，主人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You see, fire scorches and lightning shocks, but ice is a paradox, for it can both destroy and preserve.</Source>
      <Dest>你看，火能灼烧一切而电则毁灭他物，可是冰却是个矛盾体，一方面可以造成毁灭，一方面又能给予保护。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was completely mad, of course.  Should a child always listen to her elders? Was it wrong for me to end her miserable existence?</Source>
      <Dest>毫无疑问她完全失去理智了。难道一个孩子总得听长辈们的话？我结束掉她那凄惨的生命难道错了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was completely mad, of course.  Should a child always listen to her elders? Was it wrong for me to end her miserable existence?</Source>
      <Dest>毫无疑问她完全失去理智了。难道一个孩子总得听长辈们的话？我结束掉她那凄惨的生命难道错了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, he told me how the answer lied in the beasts of the wild, and the world around us.  </Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样，他告诉我，如何从荒野中的野兽身上，以及周围的世界之中寻找答案。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, he told me how the answer lied in the beasts of the wild, and the world around us.  </Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样，他告诉我，如何从荒野中的野兽身上，以及周围的世界之中寻找答案。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dying?  You're mistaken.  He's suffering from a permanent case of frost poisoning.  I have that effect on him.</Source>
      <Dest>快死了？你弄错了。他只是在忍受我的冰霜毒药所带来的永久性痛苦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nelos says you're the most important piece on the board.  It's a lie, naturally, but he likes to keep me humble.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯说你是棋盘上最重要的一个棋子。这当然是瞎扯淡，但是他喜欢让我保持谦逊。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) It will take some time to get over this.  Maybe I'll blow Vinnius a kiss just so it doesn't go to waste.</Source>
      <Dest>(叹气)需要花一段时间来克服它。或许我会吹给威恩斯一个吻，这样努力才不会被浪费掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good.  Try telling her that Nelos is sick and dying, and that we all left him out in the cold.  Then lead her to the throne room.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，可以试试告诉她纳洛斯病重垂死，而且我们遗弃了他，任由他在寒冷中受折磨。也许能把她引到王座之室去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, so you know about that! Scandalous, isn't it?  That's what happens when you don't have a long courtship.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，看来你知道！真丢人，不是么？这就是你短暂的热恋期里发生的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Soon her health began to fail, and she no longer could muster up the magicka for her daily treatment. That's when she brought me a tome on Frostbite.</Source>
      <Dest>很快她的健康状况就开始恶化，这让负责她日常治疗的祭司很泄气。也就在那个时候，她给了我记载霜噬术的法术书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Soon her health began to fail, and she no longer could muster up the magicka for her daily treatment. That's when she brought me a tome on Frostbite.</Source>
      <Dest>很快她的健康状况就开始恶化，这让负责她日常治疗的祭司很泄气。也就在那个时候，她给了我记载霜噬术的法术书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nature knows what's real.  And it will react to a coming storm in the same fashion, whether it made by mortals or gods.</Source>
      <Dest>大自然知道什么是真实的。它将以同样的方式对即将到来的风暴做出反应。不论那风暴是被凡人创造的，还是诸神所致。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nature knows what's real.  And it will react to a coming storm in the same fashion, whether it made by mortals or gods.</Source>
      <Dest>大自然知道什么是真实的。它将以同样的方式对即将到来的风暴做出反应。不论那风暴是被凡人创造的，还是诸神所致。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course.  The old hag is nothing but predictable.  You, on the other hand, are less so.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，这个老巫婆的下场是可以预见的。而你，则与其不同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Problems with the former spouses.  He had three of them, and none of them knew.</Source>
      <Dest>问题出自他的前任老婆们。他结过三次婚，而他的前任老婆们之中没有一个人知道这件事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then may the Radiant Dark count you as an ally when the time comes for true power to flex its might.</Source>
      <Dest>当神威降临之时，黑暗光辉就会把你当成是他们的一员。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, Guildmaster.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，会长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, Guildmaster.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，会长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, Guildmaster.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，会长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, Guildmaster.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，会长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't worry, he'll be more than well enough to kill the old hag when the time comes.  I trust you'll be delivering her to us?</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，等时机成熟了，他干掉那个老巫婆绰绰有余。我相信你会把她交给我们的，对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't know that!  You haven't seen the way he looks at me, the way all males look at me.</Source>
      <Dest>你不懂！你没见到他看着我的那种神态，简直跟其他男人看着我时一模一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll be back at Hall of the Radiant if you need me.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你需要我，我就在光明之厅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why yes, he's standing right in front of me.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，他正站在我的面前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't think they've already...no, that's impossible!  I followed Nelos here and saw no sight of that Low Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>你不会认为他们已经......哦，不，这不可能！我一路跟着纳洛斯过来根本没有看见那个低等精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was a book recommended to me by the librarian's apprentice on the nature of destruction magic.</Source>
      <Dest>这本关于毁灭魔法的书是一个图书管理员的学徒推荐给我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For that you have my eternal gratitude.  I wish the rest of them would die so easily.</Source>
      <Dest>在这件事情上，我永远都对你感激不尽。我希望余下的他们会更容易杀死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right, because I've always wanted a man who combs his eyebrows.</Source>
      <Dest>对的, 因为我一直想要一个会自己修眉毛的男人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you harness the elements, do you draw them from nature, or manifest them?  When heat is drawn to make fire, does the air lose warmth?</Source>
      <Dest>当你控制元素的时候，你是从自然中吸取，还是直接幻化出元素？当热量被用来制造火焰时，空气的温度会降低吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, maybe you aren't so bad after all.  I may just blow you a kiss if you're lucky.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道，你可能没有那么糟。如果你幸运的话，也许我会吻你一下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's the kind of look that makes you nervous and excited, in control and yet completely powerless.  I'd recognize it anywhere, especially on him.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是那种让你看起来紧张和兴奋，受控而且完全无力的眼神。我在任何地方都能发现这种眼神，尤其是在他身上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, Gerrod, Offryn, Faleen...and the rest of those footstools.  I stopped bothering with their names after you killed most of them.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道， 杰瑞, 欧芙芳, 法琳……还有其他的小喽罗。自从你干掉了大部分人后我就再也没因为想不起他们的破名字而烦恼了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You married Felena's corpse? Oh, I'm not judging, master.  I think you two make a perfect couple.</Source>
      <Dest>你和妃乐娜的尸体结婚了？ 噢，我没有别的意思，主人。 我觉得你们俩简直是天生一对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you shouldn't.  Offryn and Faleen just arrived.  Gerrod's been hiding out at that old Cliffside Retreat.  </Source>
      <Dest>你不该出现的。 欧芙芳和法琳刚刚抵达。 杰瑞还躲在那个什么克里夫塞德的隐居处里面</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While some schools attempt to mimic reality and others try to alter it, it was unclear whether destruction was doing one or the other.</Source>
      <Dest>在那些从学院里出来的家伙中，有些人试图去模仿现实，另一些人则试图去改造现实，尚不清楚毁灭法术究竟是前一种还是后一种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hail, Guildmaster.</Source>
      <Dest>万岁，工会大师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've heard Eldawyn is in Whiterun, and my dear Nelos is somewhere to the north of here.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说艾德温在白漫城，而我亲爱的纳洛斯则是这以北的某地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't really fancy females, but you do have power.  I may just blow you a kiss if you're lucky.</Source>
      <Dest>我并不喜欢女人，但你很有能力。要是你运气好我也许会给你一个吻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every day she cast frost spells on herself, trying to delay the appointment the wrinkles had with her neck.</Source>
      <Dest>她每天都对自己施放冰霜法术，试图延缓脖子上的皱纹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every day she cast frost spells on herself, trying to delay the appointment the wrinkles had with her neck.</Source>
      <Dest>她每天都对自己施放冰霜法术，试图延缓脖子上的皱纹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, the old bat thought if she slowed the heart and the body, she could slow the aging process itself.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，这个老蝙蝠还以为如果他能减缓心跳和身体代谢，她就可以延缓自己的老化过程。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, the old bat thought if she slowed the heart and the body, she could slow the aging process itself.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，这个老蝙蝠还以为如果他能减缓心跳和身体代谢，她就可以延缓自己的老化过程。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When plants fail to grow in magelight, it's proof alteration is not natural.  When the invisible can be touched, it proves that illusion is not real.</Source>
      <Dest>植物不能在法术制造的光芒下生长，这证明了变换系不是符合自然规律的。虚幻之物却可以触摸，这证明了幻术系不是真实的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When plants fail to grow in magelight, it's proof alteration is not natural.  When the invisible can be touched, it proves that illusion is not real.</Source>
      <Dest>植物不能在法术制造的光芒下生长，这证明了变换系不是符合自然规律的。虚幻之物却可以触摸，这证明了幻术系不是真实的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, my grandmother once believed frost magic was the key to eternal youth.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我的祖母曾经相信冰霜法术是青春永驻的关键。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, it's a long way to Winterhold.  A long time for second thoughts.  If you do manage to have them, know this:</Source>
      <Dest>当然，这离冬堡还有很长的一段路要走。你有足够的时间再想个主意出来。如果你成功了，要知道：</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's no way to be certain why the Divines blessed me with such a specific gift, but I do know how.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道为何圣灵赐予我这样一个特殊的礼物，但我很清楚该怎么做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I suppose the loss is his, then, dying so soon like that.  It was the fire, of course, he never could stay away.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我想损失是属于他的，那么，就像这样的死去吧。这是团火焰，当然，他永远也不能离开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only person I ever kissed died of frost.  And while I would never give you a kiss, if you cross us, well...I can always blow you one.</Source>
      <Dest>唯一被我吻过的人冻死在寒风中。我可不会亲你的，但如果你背叛了我们，试试看……我随时都能朝你呼出寒风。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Much of this was explained to me by Nelos, not that I needed him to.  I understood it just fine.  I just wanted to hear his voice.</Source>
      <Dest>大部分的事情，纳洛斯都跟我解释了，并不是我需要他这么做的。我理解这还不错。我只是想听到他的声音。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not use restoration spells?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么不使用恢复法术?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not use restoration spells?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么不使用恢复法术?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not use restoration spells?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么不使用恢复法术?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Eldawyn?  Never heard of her.</Source>
      <Dest>Eldawyn?  从没听说过她</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Eldawyn?  Never heard of her.</Source>
      <Dest>Eldawyn?  从没听说过她</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You always listen to your elders.</Source>
      <Dest>你总对长辈言听计从。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've heard rumors about Eldawyn, but she seemed pleasant enough.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经听到了关于Eldawyn的流言，但她似乎满不在乎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've heard rumors about Eldawyn, but she seemed pleasant enough.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经听到了关于Eldawyn的流言，但她似乎满不在乎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hate questions like this.  I'll say yes, and you'll think I'm just being nice.</Source>
      <Dest>我讨厌这样的问题。因为我会说是的，然后你就会以为我真的没事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hate questions like this.  I'll say yes, and you'll think I'm just being nice.</Source>
      <Dest>我讨厌这样的问题。因为我会说是的，然后你就会以为我真的没事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hate questions like this.  I'll say yes, and you'll think I'm just being nice.</Source>
      <Dest>我讨厌这样的问题。因为我会说是的，然后你就会以为我真的没事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hate questions like this.  I'll say yes, and you'll think I'm just being nice.</Source>
      <Dest>我讨厌这样的问题。因为我会说是的，然后你就会以为我真的没事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hate questions like this.  I'll say yes, and you'll think I'm just being nice.</Source>
      <Dest>我讨厌这样的问题。因为我会说是的，然后你就会以为我真的没事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hate questions like this.  I'll say yes, and you'll think I'm just being nice.</Source>
      <Dest>我讨厌这样的问题。因为我会说是的，然后你就会以为我真的没事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In this case, no.</Source>
      <Dest>在这种情况下，没有??。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In this case, no.</Source>
      <Dest>在这种情况下，没有??。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A handsome Dunmer?  You better not introduce us lest he fall for me.</Source>
      <Dest>一个英俊的Dunmer？你最好不要向我们介绍了，免得他爱上我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've heard of the name Eldawyn, but I've yet to meet her.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说过艾德雯这个名字，但是至今我没见过她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've heard of the name Eldawyn, but I've yet to meet her.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说过艾德雯这个名字，但是至今我没见过她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You left a fine institution to follow this rogue mage.  But you won't be missed.</Source>
      <Dest>你认贼作父，跟随了这个流氓法师。但我们不会放过你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You left a fine institution to follow this rogue mage.  But you won't be missed.</Source>
      <Dest>你认贼作父，跟随了这个流氓法师。但我们不会放过你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You left a fine institution to follow this rogue mage.  But you won't be missed.</Source>
      <Dest>你认贼作父，跟随了这个流氓法师。但我们不会放过你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You left a fine institution to follow this rogue mage.  But you won't be missed.</Source>
      <Dest>你认贼作父，跟随了这个流氓法师。但我们不会放过你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've met Eldawyn.  She never mentioned a Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经见过艾德雯。她从来没提过什么纳洛斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've met Eldawyn.  She never mentioned a Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经见过艾德雯。她从来没提过什么纳洛斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I object to that.  I am far more handsome than anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>我表示抗议。我比你们任何一个都帅的多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about your guild.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我说说你们公会的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about your guild.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我说说你们公会的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about your guild.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我说说你们公会的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about your guild.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我说说你们公会的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Long Night.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于那漫长的一夜。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Long Night.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于那漫长的一夜。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Long Night.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于那漫长的一夜。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Long Night.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于那漫长的一夜。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Long Night.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于那漫长的一夜。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Long Night.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于那漫长的一夜。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Nelos?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是 纳洛斯?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Nelos?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是 纳洛斯?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Nelos?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是 纳洛斯?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Nelos?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是 纳洛斯?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the long night.</Source>
      <Dest>请告诉我关于”长夜“的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the long night.</Source>
      <Dest>请告诉我关于”长夜“的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the long night.</Source>
      <Dest>请告诉我关于”长夜“的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the long night.</Source>
      <Dest>请告诉我关于”长夜“的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the long night.</Source>
      <Dest>请告诉我关于”长夜“的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the long night.</Source>
      <Dest>请告诉我关于”长夜“的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Power should be used to defend the powerless.</Source>
      <Dest>力量应该用来保护弱者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Power should be used to defend the powerless.</Source>
      <Dest>力量应该用来保护弱者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Power should be used to defend the powerless.</Source>
      <Dest>力量应该用来保护弱者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Say no more. Where do I sign up?</Source>
      <Dest>废话少说。我在哪儿签？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Say no more. Where do I sign up?</Source>
      <Dest>废话少说。我在哪儿签？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Say no more. Where do I sign up?</Source>
      <Dest>废话少说。我在哪儿签？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Say no more. Where do I sign up?</Source>
      <Dest>废话少说。我在哪儿签？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Say no more. Where do I sign up?</Source>
      <Dest>废话少说。我在哪儿签？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure you have a wonderful personality.</Source>
      <Dest>我能肯定你有一个很棒的人格。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure you have a wonderful personality.</Source>
      <Dest>我能肯定你有一个很棒的人格。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could use some ice yourself on those bags under your eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以自己来点冰块，就在你眼前那些袋子里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could use some ice yourself on those bags under your eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以自己来点冰块，就在你眼前那些袋子里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could use some ice yourself on those bags under your eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以自己来点冰块，就在你眼前那些袋子里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>People can fall in love rather quickly.  Take us for example.</Source>
      <Dest>有些人坠入情网的速度可快了，比如，咱们俩……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>People can fall in love rather quickly.  Take us for example.</Source>
      <Dest>有些人坠入情网的速度可快了，比如，咱们俩……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For all those who serve the guild, he is our leader, our mentor, our muse. </Source>
      <Dest>对于那些为工会服务的人来说，他就是我们的领袖、我们的导师、我们的灵魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only if you did know it, you would've answered "yes" right away.  Which must mean you're jealous and don't want to admit you wish you were me.</Source>
      <Dest>你要是知道的话，就决不会那么快说是。这就表示你嫉妒我而又不敢承认自己想成为我这样的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You!  Tell me, do you think I'm attractive?</Source>
      <Dest>你！快告诉我，你觉得我有吸引力吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You aren't half as handsome as a mudcrab, and not even worth comparing to Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>你的相貌还赶不上泥沼蟹的一半。更别提跟纳洛斯相比了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A night born for unholy rituals, hushed whispers, and shivers down the spine of children and men.  </Source>
      <Dest>一个为邪恶仪式而生的夜晚,低声的耳语,让孩子和男人们的背脊发凉。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's a miracle you didn't collapse and die from the horror of seeing her.  No doubt she left the house that morning with her face in a veil.</Source>
      <Dest>真是个奇迹啊你看到她的第一眼居然没给吓死。看来她那天早上出门是带了面纱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only if you did know it, you would've answered "yes" right away.  Which must mean you're shy and don't want to admit you're in love with me.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你才知道，请你立刻回答“是”。 这意味着你在害羞的不敢承认你已经爱上了我了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bags?  No, that can't be, I'm still young!  And also a Dunmer.  I'm pretty sure we're born this way.  Some people find it attractive.</Source>
      <Dest>下垂？不，这怎么可能，我还年轻着呢！我是个暗精灵，我很确定我们天生就长成这样。有些人觉得这样还挺有魅力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?  I thought I was doing her a favor.  Although granted, I may be a bit biased.</Source>
      <Dest>真的？我还以为我帮了她一个大忙了。虽然得承认，我也许有些偏见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The sort of nights made for long shadows and dark phantoms.  For quick daggers and hot blood.</Source>
      <Dest>这样的夜晚适合狭长的阴影和黑暗的幽灵。也适合迅疾的匕首和滚烫的鲜血。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like my guild mate Gerrod, you make a compelling argument, but so do Nelos' eyes.  They're positively enchanting.</Source>
      <Dest>和我的公会同伴杰瑞一样，你提出一个令人信服的论点，就跟纳洛斯的双眼一样。它们真迷人。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've often thought of how it will come.  Dreamt of it. </Source>
      <Dest>我总是在想怎样它才会来。梦见它就行了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Radiant Dark is open to all who possess skill with magic, whether the light you cast shines brightly, or darkly.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗光辉欢迎所有精通法术的人，不管你的光芒是黑暗的还是明亮的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A night when the end of all things is possible.  A wonderful night to have a curse.</Source>
      <Dest>一个万物可能终结的夜晚，也是一个美妙的诅咒之夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) You're handsome for a sload, but my heart belongs to Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 你比斯洛德人还帅，但是我的心已经属於纳洛斯了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He is a Dunmer of average height but immeasurable stature, his eyes burning with the fire of the Red Mountain itself.</Source>
      <Dest>他是个身高普通的黑暗精灵却有着崇高的地位，他的眼中燃烧着红山的烈焰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That only serves to validate my point.  The stupid Altmer bitch doesn't love Nelos.  Meanwhile, I can't go two sentences without mentioning him.</Source>
      <Dest>那只是为了证实我的观点。这个愚蠢的高精灵婊子不爱纳洛斯。而且，就算只说两句话我也免不了要提起他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eldawyn may have the face of a slaughterfish, but her hands know fire better than her mouth knows wine.</Source>
      <Dest>艾德温也许有张食人鱼似的脸，但她对火焰之术的运用，远超于其对酒的鉴赏能力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, and we both got what we wanted.  She was indeed very well preserved in the coffin of ice I made for her.  Dead, but preserved.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我们都得到了彼此想要的东西。她确实被完好的保存在我为之打造的冰棺中。没有生命，但却拥有着永恒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As if your beauty, or lack thereof, could ever compare to mine.  You're as pretty as sabrecats are gentle.</Source>
      <Dest>你不管是相貌，还是其他方面，都无法和我相比。你这能叫漂亮的话，剑齿虎都是温柔了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which reminds me of a certain High Elf I hate so much.</Source>
      <Dest>这让我想起了一个我特别讨厌的高精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The one written on the face of all who fear us, for Nelos himself wrote it.</Source>
      <Dest>这个人把对我们的害怕都写在了脸上，那也是为了纳洛斯而写的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Synod is too political. The College of Whispers is too shortsighted.  The Psijics are too close-minded and let's face it...Winterhold is a wreck.</Source>
      <Dest>希诺太政治了。学院的领袖太短视了。赛伊克人意见颇深,让我们面对现实吧……冬堡就是一个烂摊子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Arguably the greatest mage in all of Tamriel, but when it comes to who is most dashing, I will tolerate no argument.</Source>
      <Dest>整个泰姆瑞尔大陆最伟大的法师的人选有待争议。但如果说谁是最活跃的那个，我就不会容忍任何争论了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know that! That wasn't what I asked you.  I asked you if you thought I was attractive. Pretty. Adorable. Cute.</Source>
      <Dest>这个我知道！我没问你这个。我问你的是，你觉得我有吸引力吗，觉得我既迷人还可爱吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) You're cute for a sload, my lady, but you are not my Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)你是个可爱的蛞蝓人，我的夫人，但你不是我的纳洛斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When the long night comes, powerful mages and mighty warriors alike will rise and find their true calling.</Source>
      <Dest>當漫長的黑夜降臨時,強大的法師和勇敢的战士都將出現,找到自己真正的宿命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's the same reason why Nelos pays so much attention to the High Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯如此注意这个高精灵也是出于同样的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And this does not even include the five acolytes of Nelos' personal guard, one for each school of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>这还没算上纳洛斯个人侍卫的五个跟班呢，每一个都代表着各自的魔法学院……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I did quite enjoy the way the frost nibbled on her skin.  So much so I might have overdid the treatment. She was, however, well preserved in the end.</Source>
      <Dest>我还挺喜欢看到冰霜蚕食她的皮肤，因此我对她也许有点过分了。不过她最后会被好好保存的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This, of course, didn't stop my grandmother from holding an ice spike to her face every night.</Source>
      <Dest>这个，当然，这并没能阻止我的祖母每天晚上拿着一根冰锥对着自己的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Consider yourself lucky to have never had the displeasure of meeting the ugliest witch in all of Tamriel.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说你都没见过整个泰姆瑞尔大陆丑得最让人累感不爱的人啦，想想你有多幸运吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We are a small group of mages, whose ideals do not always align with the hundred or so guilds that now roam Tamriel in place of the one.</Source>
      <Dest>我们是一个理念与泰瑞姆大陆上某个大型法师公会略有不同的小型法师团体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, you can't just ask to be in the guild.  Nelos has to select you, and he has a very discerning eye.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，你不能想加就加啊。必须由纳洛斯来选中你，而他有一双敏锐的眼睛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Those spells restore the body to their natural state.  Aging is natural.  Death is natural.  So restoration would only undo what the frost had done.</Source>
      <Dest>那些魔法可以让身体回复到正常状态。老化是正常的。死亡是正常的。恢复系魔法可以解除霜冻带来的影响。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eldawyn, the bards cry, a Mer so hideous that her very face is a crime, with so much hair on her back her priest is a kennel master.</Source>
      <Dest>艾德温, 吟游诗人叹道,这精灵如此可怕，甚至连她的脸都像是灾难，她的背上有如此多的毛，她的牧师一定是个狗场主人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eldawyn, the bards cry, a Mer so hideous that her very face is a crime, with so much hair on her back her priest is a kennel master.</Source>
      <Dest>艾德温, 吟游诗人叹道,这精灵如此可怕，甚至连她的脸都像是灾难，她的背上有如此多的毛，她的牧师一定是个狗场主人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eldawyn, the bards cry, a Mer so hideous that her very face is a crime, with so much hair on her back her priest is a kennel master.</Source>
      <Dest>艾德温, 吟游诗人叹道,这精灵如此可怕，甚至连她的脸都像是灾难，她的背上有如此多的毛，她的牧师一定是个狗场主人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, frost spells, they will undoubtedly kill you, as they killed her.  On the other hand, her corpse is very well preserved.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，冰霜法术，他们无疑会杀了你，正如他们杀掉了她一样。话说回来，她的尸体保存得真好啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And according to him, power is something that must be exercised.  For there is nothing sadder than a great warrior born in a time of peace.</Source>
      <Dest>而据他所言，力量是要通过时常锻炼来保持的。没有比伟大的战士却诞生于和平的世代更悲哀的事情了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps if I was some ancient relic or magical staff, the professors might have actually bothered to recognize my existence.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我是什么远古遗迹或者魔杖的话，教授们或许就会注意到我的存在了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only one who did stop to notice me was that old letch Sergius.  His attention was not the kind I wanted, however, even if it was inevitable.</Source>
      <Dest>唯一停下并注意到我的人是瑟吉尔斯那个老色鬼。我可不想引起这一类人的注意，但事已至此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And an answer like that is as good as saying "no."  Except that can't possibly be right, because I'm a ravishing beauty and we both know it.</Source>
      <Dest>而这样的回答与“不。”无异。这不太可能是对的，因为我是个特别漂亮的美人，我们都知道的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And an answer like that is as good as saying "no."  Except that can't possibly be right, because I'm a ravishing beauty and we both know it.</Source>
      <Dest>而这样的回答与“不。”无异。这不太可能是对的，因为我是个特别漂亮的美人，我们都知道的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He is the hand and we are the fingers, waiting for the long night when we clutch all of Nirn in our palm.</Source>
      <Dest>他是手掌而我们就是手指，等待着长夜到来，而那时我们会将世界握在手里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It doesn't surprise me.  If I had as much hair on her back as she did, I'd probably fancy a Khajiit.</Source>
      <Dest>我并不惊讶。如果我也有如同她背上那么多的毛，也许我也会看上一个虎人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Those who have power, seek it.  Not for politics or justice, knowledge or peace, but for power itself.</Source>
      <Dest>那些拥有力量的人，追求的不是政治，不是正义，亦不是知识与和平，只为力量本身。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Imagine a cool winter night, when the only sound you hear is the wind threading through the trees.</Source>
      <Dest>想象在一个寒冷的冬夜，寒风穿过树林的呼声是你唯一能听见的声音。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When they recover the knowledge that was lost, we will be that much closer to the day of the long night.</Source>
      <Dest>当他们找回失落的古老知识时，我们将离长夜的到来更近了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I'm sure it's common for her name to arise when people debate who is the ugliest, sleaziest harlot in all of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我确信当人们争论谁是天际最丑陋、肮脏的妓女时，她的名字是最常被提及的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An institution that cared more about itself than its students. </Source>
      <Dest>一项关心自己多于关心学生的制度。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It didn't do much for the wrinkles, but I found it does do well in slowing the heart.  Stopping it, in fact.</Source>
      <Dest>这对皱纹没有什么作用，但我发现减慢心跳速度对去除皱纹很有效。事实上，停止心跳更有效。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gerrod may ramble on like a fool, but his talent for alteration can bend city walls as easily as it bends spoons.  </Source>
      <Dest>也许杰瑞聊天时像个傻瓜，但他的天赋用来拆城墙时就像弄弯勺子一样简单。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In this instance, it might've saved her life, but it would not have made her young.</Source>
      <Dest>在这种情况下，那大概可以挽救她的性命，但不会使她变得年轻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm fairly sure I'm all four of those things, and the High Elf is none.</Source>
      <Dest>我很确信我拥有全部的四样东西，而那个高等精灵连一个没有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such are the perils of beauty.  Males want and repeatedly ask for that which they do not deserve.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是冒险的迷人之处。男人们总是想方设法的想要得到那些他们不应得的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak in metaphors and folk tales. What's this long night really about?</Source>
      <Dest>你老玩隐喻和民间故事，这个漫漫长夜到底是关于什么的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak in metaphors and folk tales. What's this long night really about?</Source>
      <Dest>你老玩隐喻和民间故事，这个漫漫长夜到底是关于什么的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak in metaphors and folk tales. What's this long night really about?</Source>
      <Dest>你老玩隐喻和民间故事，这个漫漫长夜到底是关于什么的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak in metaphors and folk tales. What's this long night really about?</Source>
      <Dest>你老玩隐喻和民间故事，这个漫漫长夜到底是关于什么的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Destruction magic is a poor substitute for the thrill of destroying by hand.</Source>
      <Dest>直接动手制造破坏的快感，毁灭系魔法根本比不了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Destruction magic is a poor substitute for the thrill of destroying by hand.</Source>
      <Dest>直接动手制造破坏的快感，毁灭系魔法根本比不了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Destruction magic is a poor substitute for the thrill of destroying by hand.</Source>
      <Dest>直接动手制造破坏的快感，毁灭系魔法根本比不了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. You've made it abudantly clear you are wonderful at everything.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。毫无疑问，你完美无缺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. You've made it abudantly clear you are wonderful at everything.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。毫无疑问，你完美无缺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. You've made it abudantly clear you are wonderful at everything.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。毫无疑问，你完美无缺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. You've made it abudantly clear you are wonderful at everything.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。毫无疑问，你完美无缺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. You've made it abudantly clear you are wonderful at everything.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。毫无疑问，你完美无缺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. You've made it abudantly clear you are wonderful at everything.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。毫无疑问，你完美无缺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Nelos want from you?</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯想从你这里得到什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Nelos want from you?</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯想从你这里得到什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Nelos want from you?</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯想从你这里得到什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Nelos want from you?</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯想从你这里得到什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Arch-Mage is the greatest mage in Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest> Arch-Mage是天际最伟大的法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is this High Elf?</Source>
      <Dest>这个高精灵是谁?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is this High Elf?</Source>
      <Dest>这个高精灵是谁?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is this High Elf?</Source>
      <Dest>这个高精灵是谁?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is this High Elf?</Source>
      <Dest>这个高精灵是谁?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds ominous. Not to mention malicious.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来有点不详。不要特意说它了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds ominous. Not to mention malicious.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来有点不详。不要特意说它了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds ominous. Not to mention malicious.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来有点不详。不要特意说它了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds ominous. Not to mention malicious.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来有点不详。不要特意说它了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Dragon Bridge?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来龙桥的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Dragon Bridge?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来龙桥的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Dragon Bridge?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来龙桥的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Dragon Bridge?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来龙桥的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Arch-Mage is the greatest mage in Skyrim.  Oh wait, that's me.</Source>
      <Dest>大法师是整个天际最伟大的法师，啊等等，那不就是我吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Arch-Mage is the greatest mage in Skyrim.  Oh wait, that's me.</Source>
      <Dest>大法师是整个天际最伟大的法师，啊等等，那不就是我吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you consider yourself a prodigy.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你把自己当做天才。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you consider yourself a prodigy.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你把自己当做天才。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you consider yourself a prodigy.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你把自己当做天才。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you consider yourself a prodigy.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你把自己当做天才。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you consider yourself a prodigy.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你把自己当做天才。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you consider yourself a prodigy.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你把自己当做天才。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why yes, you are.</Source>
      <Dest>对，你就是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why yes, you are.</Source>
      <Dest>对，你就是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned you were a mage.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说你做过法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned you were a mage.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说你做过法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned you were a mage.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说你做过法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Guilds are all well and good, but I prefer to work alone.</Source>
      <Dest>公会当然是很好很强大，不过我还是喜欢独自行事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Guilds are all well and good, but I prefer to work alone.</Source>
      <Dest>公会当然是很好很强大，不过我还是喜欢独自行事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't know.  I like males.</Source>
      <Dest>不知道，我是喜欢男的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't know.  I like males.</Source>
      <Dest>不知道，我是喜欢男的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't know.  I like males.</Source>
      <Dest>不知道，我是喜欢男的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I killed Eldawyn. You can thank me with gold.</Source>
      <Dest>其实我已经杀了艾德雯。要谢我的话金币拿来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I killed Eldawyn. You can thank me with gold.</Source>
      <Dest>其实我已经杀了艾德雯。要谢我的话金币拿来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>When I cast destruction spells people cower in fear.  As they should.</Source>
      <Dest>当我施放毁灭法术的时候，人们因恐惧而颤抖。他们就应该这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>When I cast destruction spells people cower in fear.  As they should.</Source>
      <Dest>当我施放毁灭法术的时候，人们因恐惧而颤抖。他们就应该这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>When I cast destruction spells people cower in fear.  As they should.</Source>
      <Dest>当我施放毁灭法术的时候，人们因恐惧而颤抖。他们就应该这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I didn't realize it at the time, but I think they were insulting me! Although to be fair, I am a good enchanter.  The best.</Source>
      <Dest>我当时还无法理解，但我认为他们是在侮辱我！说句实在话，我是个优秀的法师，而且是最优秀的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And the worst part is they just met!  How can he value the counsel of that drunk over his companion of five years?</Source>
      <Dest>他们的碰面是整件事最糟糕的部分了！他怎么会因为一个醉鬼的醉话而拒绝和他并肩作战了五年的战友呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh this is wonderful news indeed!  Although I won't dare break the news to Nelos myself.  It'll look far too suspicious.  Best to say we never met.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，这确实是好消息！虽然我自己不敢把这个消息告诉纳洛斯。这听起来太可疑了。最好还是当做不知道吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you've tasted the power of destruction at your fingertips.  I was addicted from the start.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你试过让毁灭之力浮动于你的指尖之上吗？我试过一次就上瘾了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eldawyn is my arch enemy, my nemesis in love.  Nelos is always talking to her, confiding in her, when he should be doing those things with me.</Source>
      <Dest>艾德温是我的死对头， 我的情敌。 纳洛斯一直在谈论她，信任她，而他应该谈论和信任的人是我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wait here now in hopes that he might return, and in fear that she will be with him when he does.</Source>
      <Dest>我守在这里奢望他也许会回来，但很担心他回来时会带着她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or not.  It may be that we fly too close to the gods and burn in their fire.  Yet I, for one, plan on keeping my Nelos nice and cool.</Source>
      <Dest>或者并非如此。如果我们飞的离圣灵太近了，会被圣灵之火而焚烧。而就我个人来讲，我还是打算保持我的纳洛斯的美好和残酷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, he wouldn't accept me into his guild without first passing three additional tests.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，他并不接受我加入了公会而没有先通过三项附加测试。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I used to prefer working alone myself, but then I met Nelos and realized I rather not be lonely.</Source>
      <Dest>我过去总喜欢独来独往，但后来我遇到了纳洛斯，我才意识到自己并不孤单。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nelos recognized my talent for destruction and chose to cultivate it, whereas Mirabelle wanted me to train under the Master Enchanter.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯认可了我毁灭魔法的才能并想要培养我, 然而蜜拉贝儿则想把我训练成一位附魔大师</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Truly? I only wish I could've been there to watch.  Was there stabbing?  I hope there was lots of stabbing.</Source>
      <Dest>真的？我当时不在现场真是太可惜了。是用戳的吗？我希望你当时多戳几下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, but I found where I truly excel is with spells of frost and cold.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，但我发现是真正擅长的是冰霜魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, but I found where I truly excel is with spells of frost and cold.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，但我发现是真正擅长的是冰霜魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, but I found where I truly excel is with spells of frost and cold. </Source>
      <Dest>是啊。但我发现我真正擅长的是冰霜魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, but I found where I truly excel is with spells of frost and cold. </Source>
      <Dest>是啊。但我发现我真正擅长的是冰霜魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It must be out of pity.  Or hunger.  I've always said her nose reminds me of a giant turnip.</Source>
      <Dest>这一定是出于同情。或饥饿。我总是说她的鼻子让我想起一个巨大的萝卜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But no feeling can ever equate to the cold, blue blast of air on your skin, fresh and clean as the morning dew.</Source>
      <Dest>但没有什么感觉能跟寒冷感相提并论，冰蓝色的空气刮得你皮肤生疼，空气闻起来清新得如清晨的露珠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It makes no sense why he prefers her company.  Unlike that Summerset eyesore, I'm a fellow Dunmer.</Source>
      <Dest>真弄不懂为什么他更喜欢她的陪伴。跟夏景群岛省那帮丑东西不一样，我可是个黑暗精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not to mention I'm cuter, funnier, and by far the more talented mage.</Source>
      <Dest>更不用说我还比较可爱、有趣，而且在魔法天赋上厉害的多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well sure, so do I.  That doesn't mean you aren't above having an opinion on the fairer sex.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，我也是。可这不意味着你可以在性别歧视上发表意见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The first was to still his heart, the second was to make him smile, and the third was to take his breath away.</Source>
      <Dest>首先要让他平静下来，然后让他开心一点，最后就该宰了他了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>His questions turned out to be a sort of audition. One that I naturally passed with flying colors.</Source>
      <Dest>他的问题原来是一种测试。我自然而然的的就成功通过了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>His questions turned out to be a sort of audition. One that I naturally passed with flying colors.</Source>
      <Dest>他的问题原来是一种测试。我自然而然的的就成功通过了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I couldn't get enough of the tingle of lightning spells, or the hot breath of a fireball on the back of my palms.  </Source>
      <Dest>我的手背丝毫感受不到到闪电魔法带来的刺痛，亦或是火球术炙热的气息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suspected this might be some clever attempt for him and Eldawyn to escape on some tryst, which neither I nor the laws of decency could abide by.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这恐怕是他和艾德雯为了跑出去约会而耍的小伎俩。这种勾当，不论是是从传统角度还是我个人来说，都是无法容忍的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And how may I ask was that decided?  A vote?  Titles don't determine one's skill, nor do they speak to one's power.</Source>
      <Dest>我能问下是怎么决定的吗？投票？头衔可不能说明一个人的实力，也不能证明一个人的力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Despite Nelos having sailed under false ones.</Source>
      <Dest>轻视纳洛斯就已经是误入歧途了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Despite Nelos having sailed under false ones.</Source>
      <Dest>轻视纳洛斯就已经是误入歧途了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When the spells that were lost are found, when the relics of forgotten magic are restored, not even the sun itself will bring light to our shadow.</Source>
      <Dest>当失落的咒文再次被吟唱，当被人遗忘的魔法圣物再次现世，就算是太阳的光芒也无法驱散我们的阴影。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only thing the Radiant Dark does not brook is turning on each other.  A tenet I find most difficult when in the presence of Eldawyn.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗光辉里唯一没有被打破的规则就是禁止内讧，这条规矩在艾德温而很难执行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The actions do indeed result in death and destruction, but there is no malice. It is a test of mortal power.</Source>
      <Dest>这中行为确实导致了伤亡和破坏，但是并非出于恶意。这只是个对凡人力量的测试。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How can the extent of one's power be tested without a land to dominate?</Source>
      <Dest>在没有区域限制的情况下，怎么才能测试一个人的能力范围有多大？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was in the Arcanaeum studying a tome on that very subject when I first met Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>我第一次遇见纳洛斯的时候，就在秘藏馆里研读这个科目的书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was in the Arcanaeum studying a tome on that very subject when I first met Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>我第一次遇见纳洛斯的时候，就在秘藏馆里研读这个科目的书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am, and I'll have you know it wasn't all talent.  I worked very hard to become the mage I am, a mage not everyone thought I could be.</Source>
      <Dest>我付出了卓绝的努力，打破了众人的成见成为了一名魔法师，我正用我的行动，在现在与将来向你证明这一切与天赋毫无关系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, so maybe those tests were self-imposed, but I still plan on passing them.</Source>
      <Dest>好啦，就算那些试炼是自找麻烦，但我还是想测试一下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When the long night arrives, I will be at his side, and somewhere far, far behind us will be Gerrod and Eldawyn, laying waste to those who defy us.</Source>
      <Dest>当长夜来临，我会在他身旁，而在远方某处，杰瑞和艾德温会朝那些反对我们的人扔大便。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Those who are righteous may seek to dominate the wicked, and those who are wicked may seek to dominate the righteous.</Source>
      <Dest>正义消灭邪恶，抑或邪恶颠覆正义。大抵如是！大抵！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I bet you've never felt the tingle of lightning spells, or the hot breath of a fireball on the back of your palms.  </Source>
      <Dest>我敢打赌说，你从来没有感受过掌心中闪电魔法的震颤，抑或火球术灼热的呼吸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I still remember when I was but a novice at the college, whenever I cast a destruction spell everyone would comment on what a good enchanter I was.</Source>
      <Dest>我仍然记得在学院里的日子里，当时的我不过是个学徒，哪怕我施展一个小小的毁灭法术大家也会称赞我是个多么厉害的法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For instance, one of the mages in my guild, a female High Elf, is very, very unattractive.  </Source>
      <Dest>打个比方，一个在我公会的女性高精灵法师，非常，非常没有吸引力。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As I said, we at the Radiant Dark seek only power, and the means to exercise it.  What good is ice without something to cool?</Source>
      <Dest>就像我说的，我们在黑暗光辉唯一寻求的是力量，以及如何使用这种力量。如果一块冰不冷，那它还有什么用呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I followed Nelos to Haafingar, but only got as far as Dragon Bridge before I lost track of him.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我跟踪纳洛斯去了海芬加，可是才到龙桥那里我就跟丢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you!  I suspected as much.  Which makes it all the more confusing why Nelos ignores me for that horse of a High Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢！我心里也不踏实。奇怪的就是纳洛斯居然会因为那头高精灵母马而忽视我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He asked me if I understood the tome I read.  I could only nod what remained of my head as my body melted into the floor.</Source>
      <Dest>他问我能不能理解我所阅读的法术书。我当时浑身无力都快瘫软在地上了所以我只能点头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He asked me if I understood the tome I read.  I could only nod what remained of my head as my body melted into the floor.</Source>
      <Dest>他问我能不能理解我所阅读的法术书。我当时浑身无力都快瘫软在地上了所以我只能点头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He looked so menacing with that lick of hair and blades of war paint slashed across his face.  Yet his voice was gentle.</Source>
      <Dest>他卷曲的头发和脸上刀刻般的战纹让他看上去此勇悍。而他的声音却很温柔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He looked so menacing with that lick of hair and blades of war paint slashed across his face.  Yet his voice was gentle.</Source>
      <Dest>他卷曲的头发和脸上刀刻般的战纹让他看上去此勇悍。而他的声音却很温柔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Savos may have once been a powerful mage, but now he is nothing more than an administrator, more adept at delegating duties than casting spells.</Source>
      <Dest>萨沃斯也许曾经是个强大的法师，但现在他只不过是个管理者，比起施法，他更善于发号施令。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I do admire her strength.  Her neck must be so strong to hold up that boulder she calls a chin.</Source>
      <Dest>不过我十分钦佩她的力量。她的脖子该有多强壮才能支撑住那块儿她叫做下巴的大石头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I was destined to be a cryomancer, and true to fate's word, it's the chill of cold air that I love most of all.</Source>
      <Dest>但是我注定是一个寒霜术士，正如命运所言，我最喜欢的是冰冷空气带来的寒意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Away with you.</Source>
      <Dest>和你一起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Spoken like someone who has no idea what they're missing.</Source>
      <Dest>这话就像那些都不知道自己错过什么了的人说的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When the guild I belong to last met, Nelos instructed us to refrain from contact for the time being.</Source>
      <Dest>我上次去自己公会的时候，纳洛斯要我们暂时不要联系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If he joined the college today, my dear Nelos would be called a novice, despite being more powerful and more handsome than any of the masters.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他今天才加入学院，那么即使是我亲爱的纳洛斯也会被称作一个菜鸟，就算他比任何大师级法师更加强大和英俊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The ugly harlot aside, the long night will be ominous to all those who crave peace, but pure felicity to all who yearn for battle.  </Source>
      <Dest>这丑陋的婊子站在一旁，漫长的夜晚对渴望平静的人将是灾难，而对渴望战斗的人来说则是纯粹的杀戮盛宴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>About time.</Source>
      <Dest>是时候了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me. I need your help.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着我。我需要你的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me. I need your help.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着我。我需要你的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么心事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, Guildmaster, let the frost guide you.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，会长。愿冰霜的力量引导着你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry, but I couldn't care less about your peasant customs and their various modes of succession.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉，但我一点也在乎你向农民的税和他们各种各样的继承问题。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't play second to anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>我从来不会屈居任何人之下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Make it quick.</Source>
      <Dest>有话快说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is it?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
