<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you by chance lost?</Source>
      <Dest>你失去机会吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was.  My mother taught me the ways of the wilderness, but I never imagined it would be so difficult in practice.</Source>
      <Dest>我是。我母亲教我明白这荒野中的法则，但我从没想过实际上这么艰难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you by chance lost?</Source>
      <Dest>你失去机会吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The moss grows on all sides of the tree.  The stars are too numerous to count.  The wind blows in all directions.</Source>
      <Dest>【歌词疑似】苔藓长满树的全身。星子繁多不可胜数。风则往四面八方流动吹拂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you by chance lost?</Source>
      <Dest>你失去机会吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If not for the turn of the moons, I'd have no sense of where I am.</Source>
      <Dest>如果没有月亮，我可就真的找不着北了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She may not be here, but she'll come home.</Source>
      <Dest>她可能不在这里，但她终究会回家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You words are kind.  Thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>你很会安慰人。谢谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Wood Elf living in the woods. Predictable.</Source>
      <Dest>一个住在森林里的木精灵。可以想象。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't live here.  I didn't intend to, anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>我不在这里住，也没有这种打算。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>By the gods, I've met houseplants that were more talkative than you.</Source>
      <Dest>天哪，我可没见过比你还话唠的盆栽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Forgive me. It's just...forget it.  I won't add to your burdens any longer.</Source>
      <Dest>对不起。这太…当我没说过。我不想再为你添负担了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't really know much about Bosmer history.</Source>
      <Dest>我真的不大清楚木精灵的历史。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I confess, I'm not the best source to rely on, but I can relate to you some of what my mother told me.</Source>
      <Dest>我承认，我的消息不一定可靠，但我可以向你透露一些我母亲告诉我的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't really know much about Bosmer history.</Source>
      <Dest>我真的不大清楚木精灵的历史。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Basically near the time of creation, the forest people of Nirn lived as something of a hybrid between Man and Beast.  </Source>
      <Dest>在被创造出来之后的一段时间，奈恩星上的人们以一种介于人兽之间的状态活着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't really know much about Bosmer history.</Source>
      <Dest>我真的不大清楚木精灵的历史。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's by Y'ffre's grace that we were made into Bosmer, yet the ritual of The Wild Hunt allows us to return to our beast forms to defend our homes.</Source>
      <Dest>伊弗里眷顾之下我们变成了木精灵，但荒野狩猎的仪式让我们能变回野兽型态以保卫我们的家园。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't really know much about Bosmer history.</Source>
      <Dest>我真的不大清楚木精灵的历史。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My mother used to tell me stories of the transformation, how during the war hordes of our kind consumed the bodies of the invading Khajiit.</Source>
      <Dest>我母亲以前常跟我说变身的故事，诉说着在战时我们部族是如何吞噬虎人侵略者的尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't really know much about Bosmer history.</Source>
      <Dest>我真的不大清楚木精灵的历史。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If somehow she knew the ritual, and she's out there...I must find her.  I have to do something.</Source>
      <Dest>如果她真的知道那个仪式，她一定会在那儿。我必须把她找出来。我得做点什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry, I've combed through this forest. There are no Bosmer bodies.</Source>
      <Dest>不要担心，我会通过这森林，那里没木精灵的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I imagine there wouldn't be.  It's not exactly her safety that worries me.</Source>
      <Dest>我想也不会有。我并不是担心她的安危。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've heard worse.</Source>
      <Dest>我听过更糟的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Somehow I doubt that.  But thanks.</Source>
      <Dest>不知为何，我不是很相信你说的。但还是谢谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not much of a talker, are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你不是一个爱说话的人，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No.</Source>
      <Dest>不。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It might be dangerous.  In the story they consume everything.  Even themselves.</Source>
      <Dest>这可能会很危险。在这个故事中，他们牺牲一切，甚至包括自己的命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know, and if it's my fate to be consumed, then so be it.  I may not be from Valenwood, but I'm still a Bosmer.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白，如果消逝就是我的命运的话，那就随它去吧。也许我并非来自威木省，但我仍是个木精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vampires?  We should hunt them down!</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼？我们应猎捕他们！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But then I'll have to chop my own wood.  My mother told me that's not allowed.</Source>
      <Dest>但是我母亲告诉我那样不行。那个时候我将必须砍我用的木柴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then I wish you luck with your search.</Source>
      <Dest>那我祝你好运，找到你母亲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you.  May Y'ffre bless you in your travels though the wood.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你。愿伊弗里在旅途中庇佑着你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hold the courier.  You know Lisette?</Source>
      <Dest>等等，信使。你认识丽赛特吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course. She'd probably tell you I used to follow her around like a dog.  Which isn't exactly true.  I don't bark or pee on the rug.</Source>
      <Dest>当然认识。她可能会跟你说我以前像条狗似的跟着她。那可不对。至少我不乱吠或是在地毯上尿尿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hold the courier.  You know Lisette?</Source>
      <Dest>等等，信使。你认识丽赛特吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes I hung around because the boys loved her. Everyone did.  She was always so good with people.  It made things easier for me.</Source>
      <Dest>有时我待在这儿，因为男孩子都喜欢她。大家都这样。她总是那么善于跟人交往。这让我做事情容易多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Spent the night?  Interesting.</Source>
      <Dest>在那过夜了 ？有意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh no, nothing like that!  He was a wanderer that didn't know heads from tails and Masser from Secunda.  </Source>
      <Dest>噢，不对，完全不对！他是个不知天高地厚、东南西北的流浪汉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Spent the night?  Interesting.</Source>
      <Dest>在那过夜了 ？有意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had just cooked some venison, and I think he was following the smell.  </Source>
      <Dest>我刚煮了些鹿肉，我想他是问着香味来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Spent the night?  Interesting.</Source>
      <Dest>在那过夜了 ？有意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I took pity on him and fed him, and in return he told me stories of his adventures. He was truly gifted, with a tongue that rivaled Y'ffre himself.</Source>
      <Dest>我同情他而且给他点东西吃，他告诉我他的冒险的故事作为回报。他真是个天才，拥有媲美伊弗里的口才。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right.  You would probably just butcher it.</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的。或许你就是应该肢解了它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't have to be so mean.</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么这么卑鄙！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Face it, your mother left you.  Probably for some man who didn't love her.</Source>
      <Dest>面对现实吧，你母亲抛弃你了，也许是因为某个男人不再爱她了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't anything about her.  Get away from me.</Source>
      <Dest>她跟你没有任何关系。离我远点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who was your father?</Source>
      <Dest>你爸是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I never knew him.  Sometimes I think she chose Solitude because it was the last place he'd look for us.</Source>
      <Dest>我完全不了解他。有时我觉得她选择独孤城，是因为那是最不可能被他找到的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's complicated, but I need your spirit to help me learn a master technique.</Source>
      <Dest>这很复杂，但是我需要你的灵魂来帮助我学习一个大师级的技巧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That sounds a bit scary.  But if you think I can help, then I'm willing to go through with it.</Source>
      <Dest>这听起来有点吓人。但如果你认为我能帮上忙的话，我愿意去做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just do exactly as I say from here on out and I might consider this debt paid.</Source>
      <Dest>从这里开始，只要完全按照我所说的去做，我可能会考虑付这笔债务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No.  But I will help if I can.</Source>
      <Dest>不。不过如果可以的话，我愿意帮忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need your assistance in a Trial of the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>在诸神的审判中我会需要你的援手</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then this truly must be fate, for all that's happened, and for you to bring me this bow.  I will do as you ask.</Source>
      <Dest>所发生的这一切都一定是冥冥中命运的安排，你带给我弓也是。有什么要求就尽管提，我会照办的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned the bow was important to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你说过那把弓对你很重要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When my mother lived in Valenwood, she came across an old tree that made for the perfect home, if not for a single wayward limb.</Source>
      <Dest>那时候我妈妈还住在威木省，她无意间发现了一棵古树，要不是一个别扭的树杈的话，那里可以改造成一个完美的家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned the bow was important to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你说过那把弓对你很重要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A traveling outsider offered to cut it down, and from the wood, he fashioned a bow.  Together, they formed a village.</Source>
      <Dest>一个外来的旅行者帮忙把它伐倒了，他用那木头做了一把弓。之后他们齐心协力建成了一个村庄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned the bow was important to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你说过那把弓对你很重要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wasn't the best wood, and it isn't much of a bow, but for mother, it was piece of home.</Source>
      <Dest>这把弓不是最好的木头，也没多少木头。但对母亲来说，这是家的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned the bow was important to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你说过那把弓对你很重要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For me, this bow is a piece of her.  I...I thank you for returning it.  If there is anything you need, I will do my best to help.</Source>
      <Dest>对于我来说，这把弓是她的一部分。我……我十分感谢你让它回到我身边。如果你有什么需要，我会尽我所能帮助你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I require Kynareth's blessing, for she gives life to Y'ffre's plants.</Source>
      <Dest>我请求凯娜瑞斯的祝福，希望她给予伊弗里的植物生命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  As a city Elf, this feels a bit odd, but I give you her blessing, and mine.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。作为一个城市里长大的精灵，我觉得这有点奇怪，不过我还是要给你她的祝福，嗯还有我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dead, most likely, given what I saw.</Source>
      <Dest>死了，八成是，就我所见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dead?  No...I...I never...</Source>
      <Dest>我…不能…死…</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dead, most likely, given what I saw.</Source>
      <Dest>死了，八成是，就我所见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wasn't supposed to happen this way!  Not like this...</Source>
      <Dest>不应该是这样的！不应该啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She must have fled.  One of the hunters wasn't...consumed.</Source>
      <Dest>她肯定逃跑了。猎人们都安然无恙。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you think she's safe?  (Sigh) Listen to me, worried about her when so many our dead.  Y'ffre forgive me.</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得她很安全？（叹息）听我说，当我们死了这么多人的时候，我真的很担心她。愿伊弗里原谅我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No trace of her.  Well, unless you count all the blood and gore.</Source>
      <Dest>没有她的踪迹。好吧，如果你把那些血和血块也给算上的话，还是有一点线索的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then she must have escaped.  Maybe the Gods haven't abandoned her yet.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说她肯定逃出去了。也许圣灵还没有遗弃她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's only one way to find out.</Source>
      <Dest>那只有一个方法能让这一切水落石出了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Y'ffre forgive me, but I pray you don't find her.  Yet...if you are headed south, I'd appreciate it if you could look for my bow.</Source>
      <Dest>伊弗里原谅我, 但我恳求你不要找到她。但…如果你向南走, 帮我找到我的弓我会感激不尽的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's only one way to find out.</Source>
      <Dest>那只有一个方法能让这一切水落石出了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I dropped it when I ran and...it's very important to me.  But I dare not go back into those woods.</Source>
      <Dest>那是在我逃跑的时候掉的…它对我来说非常重要。但我不敢回到那些林子里去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't have time for this, get to the point.  Why kill your own mother?</Source>
      <Dest>我时间不多，说重点，为什么要杀你亲妈?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry.  It was because...I had to.  She was my responsibility.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉。这是因为…我不得不那样做…我必须对她负责。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't have time for this, get to the point.  Why kill your own mother?</Source>
      <Dest>我时间不多，说重点，为什么要杀你亲妈?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I couldn't.  Wouldn't.  It was still her.  The hunters, the Gods, they gave me a chance to make things right, and I failed them.</Source>
      <Dest>但我做不到，根本做不到。她还是她。猎人，神明，他们给了我改正错误的机会，但我却辜负了他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't have time for this, get to the point.  Why kill your own mother?</Source>
      <Dest>我时间不多，说重点，为什么要杀你亲妈?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The hunters stormed off into the woods to finish the job and...she's...she's dead now, isn't she?</Source>
      <Dest>猎人们冲进了树林去进行猎杀…她…她现在已经死了，是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can talk to me. Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以跟我说，告诉我发生了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was easy for me to track the blood...the carnage.</Source>
      <Dest>对我来说那并不难，追踪血迹或者…杀戮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can talk to me. Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以跟我说，告诉我发生了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The forest was so loud...the cicadas beating their wings like a thousand tiny drums.  It was a frenzy.  </Source>
      <Dest>森林如此喧吵……蝉敲打着它们的翅膀小鼓。一场狂欢。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can talk to me. Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以跟我说，告诉我发生了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I found her in that old barrow south of here.  She had turned into something else.  Some kind of monster.  </Source>
      <Dest>我在南边的古坟那里找到了她。她变成了嗯…某种…怪物。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can talk to me. Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以跟我说，告诉我发生了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I shot that first arrow out of reflex, but I wounded her.  But when it came time to kill her I...I couldn't do it.  I just...ran.  </Source>
      <Dest>我第一箭是下意识射出的，但却伤到了她。可到了真要杀她的时候我……我下不了手。我只是……跑掉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can talk to me. Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以跟我说，告诉我发生了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I returned, the hunters stormed off into the woods to finish the job.</Source>
      <Dest>当我返回时，猎人们匆匆地进入森林开始猎杀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can talk to me. Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以跟我说，告诉我发生了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't want to say it but...she's...she's dead now, isn't she.</Source>
      <Dest>我不想这么说可她…她…她是不是…死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Never mind that, what happened with your mother?</Source>
      <Dest>别在意，你母亲出什么事了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I...I was supposed to slay her. The hunters...they said she was killing their own.</Source>
      <Dest>我…我本来是打算杀死她。那些猎人…他们说是她杀了他们的同伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who were you talking to?</Source>
      <Dest>你跟谁讲话呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Jorik.  It's the name I've given this Nord carving.  It helps sometimes, having someone there, even if he isn't real.</Source>
      <Dest>乔瑞克，我给这个诺德雕像起的名字。有其他人到那里的时候能起点作用，尽管他只是个雕像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I came to see Jorik, obviously.</Source>
      <Dest>显然我是来看乔瑞克的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I didn't notice it was you.  I thought you were one of the hunters.  They came here, for my mother.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，我没注意到是你。我以为是一个追踪我母亲猎人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Last time I checked, you didn't own this forest.</Source>
      <Dest>我最后一次检查的时候，你没有自己的这片森林。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh...I thought you were one of them.  The hunters that were after my mother.</Source>
      <Dest>哦…我还以为你跟那些在追我妈的猎人是一伙的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What...What are you doing here?</Source>
      <Dest>什么…你在这儿干什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My bow...you found it...and my mother?</Source>
      <Dest>我的弓…你找到它了…那…我妈妈呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>哈啰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The spiced wine.</Source>
      <Dest>因为美酒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's so good, isn't it?  Evette is a talented winemaker.  Lacks business sense though.</Source>
      <Dest>它很棒，对吧？爱芙缇是一位天才酿酒师，虽然没什么生意头脑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It must be very lonely out here.</Source>
      <Dest>我得一个人到外面待会儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have the trees and the flower beds to keep me company.  There's also Jorrik.</Source>
      <Dest>我有树木和花丛的相陪。还有乔欧克。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did this person leave Solitude often?</Source>
      <Dest>这人经常离开独孤城吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She went on the road sometimes.  In Solitude, she would complain about the coldness of the stone and traveled to the southern holds.</Source>
      <Dest>有时她在路上走走。在孤独城的时候，她会抱怨石头的寒冷然。接着就向南边的领地前进了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did this person leave Solitude often?</Source>
      <Dest>这人经常离开独孤城吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Other times an adventurer might come and whisk her away for weeks, but she always came home.</Source>
      <Dest>有时她会跟着一个冒险家离开几周，但她总会回家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did this person leave Solitude often?</Source>
      <Dest>这人经常离开独孤城吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something must have happened to her.  She wouldn't just leave.</Source>
      <Dest>她身上一定发生了什么，她不会就那么走了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not until you find the person you're looking for, I take it.</Source>
      <Dest>直到你找到你要找的人，我要了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's right.  She has to be here.  She always talked about how green the pines were, how lush the grass was.  </Source>
      <Dest>没错。她一定在这里。她总是提到松树有多么苍绿，青草有多么茂盛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not until you find the person you're looking for, I take it.</Source>
      <Dest>直到你找到你要找的人，我要了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How if you listened closely to the chorus of insects, you could almost make out the words.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你仔细聆听虫子的合鸣，你就可以写诗了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not until you find the person you're looking for, I take it.</Source>
      <Dest>直到你找到你要找的人，我要了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How the forests here couldn't be more different, yet somehow reminded her so much of Valenwood.</Source>
      <Dest>这儿的森林没有一星半点的相似之处，这一特征勾起了她对威木省的许多回忆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm just glad the author wasn't here to listen to you set fire to his tale.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是很高兴那个作者没在这里听你毁了他的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I said I was sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>我说我很抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Blue Palace is amazing.</Source>
      <Dest>蓝色宫殿真是壮观啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That it is. Although the people inside could use a makeover.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊。虽然里面的人似乎却不是这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Blue Palace is amazing.</Source>
      <Dest>蓝色宫殿真是壮观啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sorry.  I shouldn't talk bad about people who aren't here.  I've been told trees like to gossip.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉。我不该在别人背后说人是非。我告诫过那些爱说是非的树了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Aside from rumors, what makes you so certain she transformed?</Source>
      <Dest>除了谣言作为根据以外，还有别的什么让你如此确信她有所改变？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In the stories they say that only a shaman can initate The Wild Hunt.  Yet they also say it's a response to extreme peril.</Source>
      <Dest>在故事里只有萨满能发起荒野狩猎，但故事里也提到这是为了应对极其严重的灾祸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Aside from rumors, what makes you so certain she transformed?</Source>
      <Dest>除了谣言作为根据以外，还有别的什么让你如此确信她有所改变？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What if the transformation was also instinctual?  Something driven by a deep desire to protect something you love?</Source>
      <Dest>如果说变身也是种本能呢？一种想保护所爱之人的强烈渴望所激起的本能呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is a dangerous spot for a camp.</Source>
      <Dest>这个营地是个危险的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can take care of myself.</Source>
      <Dest>我能照顾好自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you ever visit Evergreen Grove?</Source>
      <Dest>你经常常春树林吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do. It's very peaceful.  Sometimes I pass through there to borrow wood from Hert and Hern.  They're vampires.</Source>
      <Dest>我去过。那里非常宁静。有时我会经过那里去向赫特还有赫恩借点木材。他们是血族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Have you ever heard of the Green Pact and the Wild Hunt?</Source>
      <Dest>你有听说过绿色条约和荒野狩猎吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Jorrik?</Source>
      <Dest>乔欧克？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The big stone head by the campfire.</Source>
      <Dest>在营火旁的巨大石首。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who exactly are you looking for?</Source>
      <Dest>你到底要找谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My mother.</Source>
      <Dest>我妈妈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么不呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry, do I know you?</Source>
      <Dest>对不起，我认识你吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Only what I've read in stories.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我唯一在故事看到过的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Remember what I told you about the travelers?  They say they saw a Sload, a Werewolf, and a Naga.  Yet their descriptions matched none.</Source>
      <Dest>还记得我告诉你的旅人吗？他们说，他们看见一个蛞蝓人、狼人和纳珈。他们的根本完全不一样嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Only what I've read in stories.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我唯一在故事看到过的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The travelers' accounts were...strange and conflicting.  One claimed there were spikes jutting from the beast's back.</Source>
      <Dest>旅人们的描述说法是…奇怪又矛盾的。有人宣称那野兽的背部有尖锐物突出。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Only what I've read in stories.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我唯一在故事看到过的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The other said it had horns like tusks of a mammoth and a silver stripe running down its hide.</Source>
      <Dest>其他人说它有着如长毛象牙般的角，且毛皮上有条银色的斑纹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Only what I've read in stories.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我唯一在故事看到过的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The third claimed it had a forked tongue, and three eyes that hissed with blue vapor.  This was no beast of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>第三个人宣称它有分叉的舌头，还有三个发出嘶嘶蓝色蒸气的眼睛。这不是天际的怪物啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Only what I've read in stories.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我唯一在故事看到过的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only tales of The Wild Hunt account for anything remotely matching these descriptions.</Source>
      <Dest>唯有荒野狩猎的传说才能解释这样的诡异东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Only what I've read in stories.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我唯一在故事看到过的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If there's a chance that this thing was...is...my mother, maybe I can help her. Reach her somehow.</Source>
      <Dest>如果这个可能是...是...我妈妈的话，也许我可以为她做点什么。想办法到她那里去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now I get it.  You're completely mad.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我懂了，你完全疯了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, not completely.</Source>
      <Dest>不，不完全是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Jorrik.  I like it.  Sounds strong, but gentle.</Source>
      <Dest>乔欧克。我喜欢。听起来既强壮又文雅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know if it's a proper Nord name, but he doesn't really have a say.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道这是不是一个适当的诺德名字，反正他不会说话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I suppose you *do* get the occasional visitor on their way to Evergreen Grove.</Source>
      <Dest>我姑且相信你确实是在那些不速之客前往常青苑的路上发现他们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>None that bother to stop.  Although there was that Nord from Riften who spent the night.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然那个来自裂谷城的诺德人走了一整晚，仍然不能停下脚步来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where do you normally live?</Source>
      <Dest>那你本来住哪？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm from Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>我来自独孤城。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Unless you tell me, I can't help you.  But you have to provide more details.</Source>
      <Dest>除非你告诉我,否则我没法帮你.你必须提供更多的细节.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I...I'm sorry.  It's been so long and I've almost lost all hope.</Source>
      <Dest>抱…抱歉。实在是太久，我已经快要失去希望了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Unless you tell me, I can't help you.  But you have to provide more details.</Source>
      <Dest>除非你告诉我,否则我没法帮你.你必须提供更多的细节.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe telling a stranger will do me some good.   So I'll tell you why, if you'll listen.</Source>
      <Dest>也许告诉一个陌生人会让我好受点吧。如果你想听的话，我就告诉你原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any visitors lately?</Source>
      <Dest>最近有任何访客吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Does the bear that just attacked me count?</Source>
      <Dest>刚刚有只熊攻击我算吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any visitors lately?</Source>
      <Dest>最近有任何访客吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just a mudcrab.  I had him over for dinner.</Source>
      <Dest>还有只泥螃蟹。我把它弄来当晚餐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any visitors lately?</Source>
      <Dest>最近有任何访客吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not lately.  Unless you count that alchemist.  But he's kind of dead.</Source>
      <Dest>最近没有。除非连那个炼金术师也算。但是他死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any visitors lately?</Source>
      <Dest>最近有任何访客吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, there's a really annoying person standing right in front of me.  Not that I mind.</Source>
      <Dest>对啊，就有一个很讨厌的人站在我面前。虽然我不介意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about her.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于她的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was a fiery woman, nothing like me. Yet she could be graceful when she wanted to.  And kind when I needed her to.</Source>
      <Dest>她是一个热情的女人，一点都不像我。不过在有需要的时候，她也是可以婀娜优雅的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about her.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于她的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She loved to tell me stories about Valenwood, about cities that walked and strange creatuers that croaked in the night.</Source>
      <Dest>她喜欢告诉我关于威木省的故事，还有会移动的城市和在夜里低吼的奇怪生物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about her.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于她的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were beetles the size of horse carts, she said, and plants so colorful they put the aurora to shame.</Source>
      <Dest>她说那里有马车大小的甲虫，缤纷艳丽连极光都相形失色的卉木植披。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about her.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于她的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She loved Valenwood so much, I never understood why we lived in place like Skyrim.  I think it has to do with my father.</Source>
      <Dest>她如此喜爱威木省，我不明白我们为什么会住在像天际省这样的地方。我猜这是我父亲决定的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm just amazed you managed to talk for so long.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是惊讶你们谈了这么久。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now you see why I don't.</Source>
      <Dest>现在知道我为什么不这么干了吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the rumor?</Source>
      <Dest>什么样的传言？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One said he saw a werewolf.  Another claimed it was a Sload. The third said it was a Naga. They could only agree on one thing.  It was once a person.</Source>
      <Dest>有个人说他看见了狼人。另一个人声称看到了蛞蝓人。第三个说那个是娜迦。他们说的有一点相同，那儿有个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the rumor?</Source>
      <Dest>什么样的传言？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lisette said it was the ale talking.  She said men exaggerate when they want attention.</Source>
      <Dest>丽赛特说那些都是胡言乱语，男人们总是喜欢哗众取宠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the rumor?</Source>
      <Dest>什么样的传言？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She could always see through the follies of men, so maybe she was right.  But if there's a chance...I won't leave.  I can't.</Source>
      <Dest>她总能看穿人的愚蠢，所以她也许是对的。但是如果有机会的话……我不会离开的。我无法离开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what's bothering you.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我是什么困扰着你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was many months ago, at The Winking Skeever back in Solitude.  Many visitors had come for the Burning of King Olaf.</Source>
      <Dest>几个月前，就在独孤城眨眼雪鼠旅馆后面，许多游客来参加火烧国王奥拉夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what's bothering you.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我是什么困扰着你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were three different men from three separate holds.  All had passed through this forest.  All with a similar story.</Source>
      <Dest>三个人来自不同的地方。他们全都穿越了这片森林。他们说了相似的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what's bothering you.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我是什么困扰着你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mother always said once is a fluke, twice is a coincidence.  Three times meant a rumor was worth your ear.</Source>
      <Dest>母亲总是说谣言这种事啊，第一次听到是偶然，第两次听到是巧合，第三次就值得注意了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The festivals.</Source>
      <Dest>节日</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Me too.  Although I never really understood why King Olaf had to burn.  Wasn't he a hero?</Source>
      <Dest>我也是。虽然我从没真正理解过为何奥拉夫国王非得烧掉不可。他不是个英雄吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You still haven't told me why you're out here.</Source>
      <Dest>你还没有告诉我你为什么在这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd rather not.  It's a long story, and I'm not much for words.</Source>
      <Dest>我不太想说。这是个很长的故事，而我又不善言辞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Solitude, huh?  Maybe you can tell me what in Oblivion a Winking Skeever is.</Source>
      <Dest>独孤城对吧?或者你可以告诉我另一个坐落于湮灭的眨眼雪鼠在哪儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Y'ffre's Bones, The Winking Skeever!  Now that brings back memories.  Lisette used to love performing there.  She's a friend.</Source>
      <Dest>哦天哪，在眨眼雪鼠！我想起来了。丽赛特过去一直喜欢在那里表演。她是朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh I see. Nice to meet you Jorrik.</Source>
      <Dest>喔~我懂了。很高兴认识你，乔欧克。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't think he's going to respond.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认为他会有什么反应。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you tell me one of his stories?</Source>
      <Dest>你能告诉我一个关于他的故事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can try.  But I'm warning you, you won't like how I tell it.</Source>
      <Dest>我试试看。不过丑话说在前头，你不会喜欢听我讲的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure the story's fine.  The telling needs a little work.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢肯定这个故事不错。只要花点心思讲好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think I'd rather just listen to stories instead of tell them. Mother always said I was a good listener.</Source>
      <Dest>比起讲故事，我更喜欢听故事。我的母亲总说我是个好听众。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure the story's fine.  The telling needs a little work.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢肯定这个故事不错。只要花点心思讲好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although maybe that's just a nice way of saying I'm quiet.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然那可能只是说我很安静。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you say Solitude?  I love Solitude!</Source>
      <Dest>你刚刚说独孤城？我爱独孤城！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?  What about it do you love?</Source>
      <Dest>真的？你爱它哪一点？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was awful.</Source>
      <Dest>那真是糟糕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Small world.</Source>
      <Dest>世界真小。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Say hi to her for me if you're ever in Solitude.  </Source>
      <Dest>若你有路过独孤城，帮我跟他打个招呼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure you'll tell it just fine.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你会说"一切都好"。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, but don't say I didn't warn you.</Source>
      <Dest>好，别怪我没提醒你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure you'll tell it just fine.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你会说"一切都好"。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The tale I remember best was about his adventure in The Reach.  One night it was very dark and cold, and he was frightened.</Source>
      <Dest>我最难忘的故事是关于他在瑞驰的冒险。那天晚上又黑又冷，他吓坏了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure you'll tell it just fine.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你会说"一切都好"。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then when he felt all was lost, a voice shouted out, "The blood's all below your waist!"</Source>
      <Dest>然后当他觉得一切都完了，一个声音喊道"跑，快跑！"。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure you'll tell it just fine.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你会说"一切都好"。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh wait.  That part comes later.  Y'ffre's Bones, I really messed it up, didn't I.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，等一下。那块应该在后面。天啊，我搞砸了，对吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I enjoy the public executions.</Source>
      <Dest>我挺喜欢公开处刑的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you sure you aren't thinking of Helgen?  Executions are all that city has.  Or all it used to have.</Source>
      <Dest>你确定？想想海尔根的事。城市只有处决，从来就只有处决。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think I know who you're talking about.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我知道你在说谁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I forget his name, but it sounded like "Hagraven."  What an odd thing to name a boy.</Source>
      <Dest>我记不清他的名字了，那个名字听起来有点像"乌鸦鬼婆"。一个小子用这种名字真的很怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you're not going to finish?</Source>
      <Dest>我可以把这理解成你不打算停手？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, it's too late.  It wasn't that great of story anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>不，太迟了。不管怎样，这故事没那么了不起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>哈啰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I...I couldn't do it Jorik.  She was there, right in front of me.</Source>
      <Dest>我...我做不了，乔瑞克。当时她就在那，我的右前方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I begged Y'ffre to give me courage, and still, it wasn't enough.</Source>
      <Dest>我恳请伊弗里赐予我勇气，但这还不够。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gods forgive me, I couldn't do it.  Even if it had to be done.</Source>
      <Dest>愿神灵宽恕我，我做不到。即使这件事必须做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't care what she's become...it's not fair to ask a child to slay her own mother.</Source>
      <Dest>我不在乎她变成了什么……但要求一个孩子去杀死她的亲生母亲，这本身就是不合理的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
