<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you implying you're hundreds of years old?</Source>
      <Dest>你是在说你已经活了几百年了么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you implying you're hundreds of years old?</Source>
      <Dest>你是在说你已经活了几百年了么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not sure Elder Scrolls work that way.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得上古卷轴不是那样用的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not sure Elder Scrolls work that way.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得上古卷轴不是那样用的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That doesn't explain how he became Jarl of Windhelm.</Source>
      <Dest>这并不能解释他是如何成为风舵城领主的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That doesn't explain how he became Jarl of Windhelm.</Source>
      <Dest>这并不能解释他是如何成为风舵城领主的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That doesn't explain how he became Jarl of Windhelm.</Source>
      <Dest>这并不能解释他是如何成为风舵城领主的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anyways, you were saying about Ulfric?</Source>
      <Dest>总之，你是在说乌弗瑞克吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who used to live here?</Source>
      <Dest>曾经住在这里的人是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright, that explains the face, but shape-shifters aren't immortal.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，这至少解释了那张脸，但变种到也不是不道德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright, that explains the face, but shape-shifters aren't immortal.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，这至少解释了那张脸，但变种到也不是不道德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maybe Tiber Septim is Alduin, too.</Source>
      <Dest>很有可能泰伯赛普丁就是奥杜因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I suppose that's a reasonable criticism.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为这批评是合理的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I suppose that's a reasonable criticism.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为这批评是合理的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I suppose that's a reasonable criticism.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为这批评是合理的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd say you look a few days over twenty.  And by few I mean a million.</Source>
      <Dest>你看上去也就二十出头的样子，我说的出头呢也就出个上百万天吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That I was crazy to imply you're hundreds of years old.</Source>
      <Dest>我真是疯了才会觉得你有好几百岁了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That I was crazy to imply you're hundreds of years old.</Source>
      <Dest>我真是疯了才会觉得你有好几百岁了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That I was crazy to imply you're hundreds of years old.</Source>
      <Dest>我真是疯了才会觉得你有好几百岁了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hello again.</Source>
      <Dest>又见面啦！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly is your role as a Stormcloak?</Source>
      <Dest>你到底在风暴斗篷里扮演什么角色？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly is your role as a Stormcloak?</Source>
      <Dest>你到底在风暴斗篷里扮演什么角色？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly is your role as a Stormcloak?</Source>
      <Dest>你到底在风暴斗篷里扮演什么角色？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>But in the story, Gyna wasn't actually Princess Talara. That's the twist.</Source>
      <Dest>但在这个故事中，实际上吉纳并不是塔拉让公主。这是扭曲事实。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a matter of fact...I'm not.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上呢...我不是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a matter of fact...I'm not.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上呢...我不是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a matter of fact...I'm not.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上呢...我不是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A man your age must have some family to speak of.</Source>
      <Dest>像你这样年纪的男人通常会谈及家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A man your age must have some family to speak of.</Source>
      <Dest>像你这样年纪的男人通常会谈及家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A man your age must have some family to speak of.</Source>
      <Dest>像你这样年纪的男人通常会谈及家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I can deliver your next letter for you.</Source>
      <Dest>我能把下一封信送给你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why yes, yes I am.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，就是我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've heard enough from you.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经受够你了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've heard enough from you.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经受够你了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about how you went back in time.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你怎么能及时赶回来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about how you went back in time.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你怎么能及时赶回来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about how you went back in time.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你怎么能及时赶回来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about how you went back in time.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你怎么能及时赶回来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure the Empire will crumble under the weight of your letters.  Literally.</Source>
      <Dest>不夸张地说，我确定帝国会在你的来信之下崩溃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course! I was a fool not to see it myself.</Source>
      <Dest>当然！我真是个傻瓜，竟然没发觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course! I was a fool not to see it myself.</Source>
      <Dest>当然！我真是个傻瓜，竟然没发觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think those are vegetables.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认为那些是蔬菜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait, go back. There are Elves on the moon?</Source>
      <Dest>等等，回来。在月亮上真有精灵？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait, go back. There are Elves on the moon?</Source>
      <Dest>等等，回来。在月亮上真有精灵？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a Stormcloak?</Source>
      <Dest>你是个风暴斗篷？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a Stormcloak?</Source>
      <Dest>你是个风暴斗篷？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a Stormcloak?</Source>
      <Dest>你是个风暴斗篷？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually Centaurs are quite common in the West.</Source>
      <Dest>半人马在西部真的很常见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ulfric is Talos?</Source>
      <Dest>乌夫瑞克就是塔洛斯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The last guy was shaking in his stupid red dress saying something like I was more valuable to the cause alive.  </Source>
      <Dest>上一个家伙在他那可笑的红衣服里面发抖，说着"您定能将革命火种洒遍全天际"这类话。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some plant mage.  Probably wasn't a very good one either, using a stove for an alchemy table.</Source>
      <Dest>某些处男法师。半桶水的那种, 用炉子当炼金台.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lies perpetuated by plant mages who sniffed one too many deathbells. Ulfric isn't the second coming of Talos. He is Talos.  </Source>
      <Dest>就是那些吸多了死亡丧钟的草药术士们让谎言延续至今，蒙蔽了世人。乌弗瑞克不是塔洛斯的转世，他就是塔洛斯。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lies perpetuated by plant mages who sniffed one too many deathbells. Ulfric isn't the second coming of Talos. He is Talos.  </Source>
      <Dest>就是那些吸多了死亡丧钟的草药术士们让谎言延续至今，蒙蔽了世人。乌弗瑞克不是塔洛斯的转世，他就是塔洛斯。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course! Not officially, but I follow the one true king of Skyrim.  Not that harlot widow, whats-her-face, General Tullius.</Source>
      <Dest>当然！虽然不被承认，但我只追随天际省真正的至高王。才不是那婊子寡妇，她叫什么名字？将军·图留斯是吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Remember that the next time you visit the Palace of the Kings.</Source>
      <Dest>下次再来拜访众王之殿的时候给我记住这一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why?  Because of my gray beard?  My wrinkles?  My age spots? Those aren't indicators of age, but rather a man's grooming habits. Mine are impeccable.</Source>
      <Dest>为什么？因为我那已经灰白的胡须？我的皱纹？我的老年斑？这些并不代表着衰老，只是一个人的修饰品味罢了，我的可是无懈可击的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's Elves, taking root like a creep cluster.  Elves can live in any climate, on account they aren't actually Elves, but Shades.  </Source>
      <Dest>精灵族都那样，殖民的本事跟藤蔓丛一样强。他们什么气候都能生存，因为他们不是真的精灵，而是阴影。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think it's a like a Minotaur, with the head of a Centurion. </Source>
      <Dest>我觉得它像一个长着百夫长头的神兽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or spent his days at the docks, hammering down bottles of skooma.  Nobody says that about me.  I'm not mad.</Source>
      <Dest>或在码头上度过时日，锤击着斯库玛的瓶子。但没人这样说我。我没有发疯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only an Imperial agent would be so cunning.  Which is surprising because they're normally so stupid.</Source>
      <Dest>只有帝国密探才会如此狡猾。这也太奇怪了，他们不都很蠢吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But Vampires are.  That's right, Ulfric Stormcloak is actually Tiber Septim, a shape-shifting vampire.  </Source>
      <Dest>但他是个吸血鬼。对，乌佛瑞克·暴风斗篷确实是个吸血鬼。他吸的是金币，他是个变种的吸血鬼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And that's when I realized to avoid assassination, Tiber Septim was secretly living in the Imperial City as a prostitute named Gyna.</Source>
      <Dest>泰伯赛普汀以吉纳的名字秘密入主皇城，从那时起，我意识到需要提防暗杀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which is a bunch of chicken feathers.  Another thing dreamt up by mages who need courage spells to confront the fact they're all miserable failures!</Source>
      <Dest>那只是一堆鸡毛。是被那些法师空想出来的东西。那些法师一无是处，甚至需要施展勇气魔法才能面对这个事实。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All I have to do is look into your eyes and...wait for it...waaait for it...there!  </Source>
      <Dest>我需要做的就是看着你的眼睛...等...等啊等啊等啊等...在那里！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, but it does.  You see, Tiber Septim is a shape-shifter.  He is no man, and every man at once.</Source>
      <Dest>哦。但确实如此，你看，泰伯塞普汀是一个变种人。这一刻他不是人类，不再是任何一个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Scathing missives that mock her figure and the vast emptiness that fills the halls of her pink palace.</Source>
      <Dest>尖酸的信件嘲讽着她的体型，巨大的空虚充斥在她的粉色宫殿大厅之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What kind of name is that for a Jarl?  Or a woman?  General.</Source>
      <Dest>这还能叫领主的名字吗？这还能叫女人的名字吗？居然还有叫"将军"的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh right.  Like I said, you ought to get your eyes checked.  I'm not a day over twenty.   What happened is, I got my hand on this thing.  </Source>
      <Dest>噢是啊。我说过的，你这眼神儿该去检查一下了。我的20岁还没超过一天呢。现在呢，我正全神贯注在这件东西上呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Haven't you been paying attention to a word I've said? The Stormcloaks are my family.</Source>
      <Dest>你没注意到我说的话吗？我的家人就是风暴斗篷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You better believe it!  They live on the sun, the moons, and even...inside you.  Ever have a sore throat?   </Source>
      <Dest>你最好相信它！他们活在太阳里，月亮里，甚至是...你的身体里。你喉咙疼过吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Got what you needed, did you, you Imperial agent?  Too bad for you, the Moon Elves taught me a spell that will erase your memory!  </Source>
      <Dest>已经得到了你想要的，对不？你个帝国密探？不幸的是，月亮精灵教会我了一个能抹去你记忆的咒语！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?  Have you been sticking fire salts up your ass? Well you shouldn't. Sure, it feels good, but it'll give you the meanest rash.  </Source>
      <Dest>什么？你一直把火盐贴到你的屁股上？呃，你没那么做。当然，这感觉不错，但也会让你患上最坏的皮疹。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why, have you ever used one?  Ever even seen one?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么会那样觉得...你用过上古卷轴吗？还是说曾见到过它？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We all were, we all were. Tiber Septim, you see, is what you call a shape-shifter.  </Source>
      <Dest>我们都是，我们都是。你看，泰伯赛普丁就是所谓的易形者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not that that'll stop children from doing it. Children are the worst breed of fungus. I should know, I used to own one.</Source>
      <Dest>这都没法让这些孩子不做这事儿。熊孩子是最难种的蘑菇。我早该知道的，我也曾养过一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What a bunch of bull-horker!  Not even a shape-shifter can be in two places at once!  Alduin is more likely one of the Uriels or Pelagiuses.</Source>
      <Dest>它的体积堪比一群雄性海象的集合！仅仅是一次翼展就能遮蔽大片天空！奥杜因简直就是尤瑞尔或者佩拉吉奥斯的化身。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I send letters to that false queen, Jarl Tullius. </Source>
      <Dest>我寄了封信给那个假女王——图留斯领主。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings and salutations, my name is...wait a minute...are you an Imperial agent?</Source>
      <Dest>向你致敬，我的名字是...等等...你是个帝国密探？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's about a princess who lost her identity following a royal murder plot.</Source>
      <Dest>这是有关一位公主如何在一场皇室谋杀的阴谋发生后痛失她的身份与地位的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some people even go so far as to say that Ulfric Stormcloak is Talos reborn.  That's ridiculous.  </Source>
      <Dest>有些人甚至直到现在还认为乌弗瑞克·风暴斗篷是塔洛斯重生。这太荒谬了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some people even go so far as to say that Ulfric Stormcloak is Talos reborn.  That's ridiculous.  </Source>
      <Dest>有些人甚至直到现在还认为乌弗瑞克·风暴斗篷是塔洛斯重生。这太荒谬了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean by that, literally?  Paper can't beat stone.  Don't be stupid.</Source>
      <Dest>你这是什么意思，字面上的意思？纸可赢不了石头。别犯傻了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Haven't we met before?  Wait...you're that Imperial agent I keep telling myself about!</Source>
      <Dest>我们以前是不是见过？等等...你是那个我一直提防着的帝国密探！！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now Ulfric, that's a strong Nord name. A strong Nord name for a strong Nord man. </Source>
      <Dest>乌弗瑞克，还真是个听着就很强力的诺德名字啊。正是人如其名。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now Ulfric, that's a strong Nord name. A strong Nord name for a strong Nord man. </Source>
      <Dest>乌弗瑞克，还真是个听着就很强力的诺德名字啊。正是人如其名。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's exactly what an Imperial slug would say!  You're the second patrol to come here in the last week.  My letters must be working.</Source>
      <Dest>果然是帝国狗腿子说的屁话！你是这周之内第二批来这儿的巡查。看来我写的信起作用了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source> Some even think it was he who seduced Barenziah as the battlemage Jagar Tharn.  </Source>
      <Dest>有些人甚至认为是他引诱巴兰兹娅成为了战斗法师贾加·萨恩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had a father once, Thornvar the Hammer.  People used to say he must've took a hammer to the head.</Source>
      <Dest>我父亲活着的时候，被称作铁锤琮瓦。人们常说他脑袋肯定是被锤子敲过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've got three in my pocket, and six more that I plan on designing myself using charcoal and paper made from the Eldergleam.</Source>
      <Dest>我口袋里就有三个卷轴，另外还有六个我打算用从古藤圣所取来的木炭和纸自己制作呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, two can play at that game.  So can three.  Pretty much any number less than twelve.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，两个人可以玩这个游戏。三个也行。只要不多于十二个人，都可以。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At the bottom I sometimes scribble drawings of a pornographic nature, just to further illustrate my point.</Source>
      <Dest>在结尾处我有些时候会用笔草草地画上一些自然春光图，只为了能够在未来进一步阐述我的观点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?  Then it's already begun.</Source>
      <Dest>什么？那这已经开始了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure they are!  There's corn, artichokes, and that nightshade-looking thing over there is some kind of Dwarven onion.</Source>
      <Dest>就在这儿！这里有玉米，洋蓟，还有某种和夜茄类似的矮人洋葱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And he's right!  I'm the most valuable soldier in the whole Stormcloak army.</Source>
      <Dest>他说得太对了！我就是整个风暴斗篷军队里最有价值的士兵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not some illusionist like Jagar Tharn, but a real shape-shifter, the kind that can transform into a dragon or a bale of hay.</Source>
      <Dest>不是某些像贾格•萨恩一样的幻术师，而是那种能够变成一头龙或一捆干草的真正变形者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's called an Elder Scroll.  And I used it to travel to another dimension, where they had invented time travel and something called "a centaur." </Source>
      <Dest>这是上古卷轴。我曾经去过另一个位面，在那儿他们发明了时间旅行和一种叫做"半人马"的玩意儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just like the real Gyna isn't actually the Jarl of Windhelm.  She's Tiber Septim, Ulfric's cousin, first emperor of Tamriel.</Source>
      <Dest>就好像真正的吉纳不是风舵城实际上的领主。她是泰伯·赛普汀，乌佛瑞克的堂姐，泰姆瑞尔大陆的第一个统治者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right, so the Moon Elves sent me to the dawn of the 3rd Era.</Source>
      <Dest>对啊, 所以说是月亮精灵把我送到了第三纪元的黎明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Huh?  What was I saying?</Source>
      <Dest>哈？我刚才说了啥？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And trust such an important message to an amateur?  Never.  The letter stays in my pocket, until I can find an official courier.</Source>
      <Dest>把这么重要的信件托付给一个外行人？想都别想。我会把这封信留在我自己这儿，直到我找到一个正式的通讯员为止。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's right. Tiber Septim has been in hiding ever since he faked his death in the 38th year of the 3rd Era.  I can prove it. I was there.</Source>
      <Dest>那就对了。泰伯·赛普汀从第三纪元三十八年假死开始一直隐藏到现在。我能证明。我当时就在现场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What if the owner comes back?</Source>
      <Dest>如果那个主人回来了该怎么办？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll be more careful when I sit on a bale of hay then.  It might be a Divine.</Source>
      <Dest>如果是我的话，坐在这堆干草堆上是会更加小心的。说不定这就是个圣灵呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where will you go?</Source>
      <Dest>你要去哪儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where will you go?</Source>
      <Dest>你要去哪儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait, go back. There are Elves on the moon?</Source>
      <Dest>等等，回来。在月亮上真有精灵？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a surprisingly dignified response.</Source>
      <Dest>这种正经的回应真是令人惊讶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a surprisingly dignified response.</Source>
      <Dest>这种正经的回应真是令人惊讶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you own this shack?</Source>
      <Dest>这间小屋是你的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I think the outcome of the war is pretty much decided.</Source>
      <Dest>其实我觉得，这场战争的结果差不多已经确定了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to go back to what you said about Ulfric.</Source>
      <Dest>我想回到你刚刚谈乌佛瑞克的话题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or maybe I am.  I'm a Son of Skyrim.  Even our bowel movements are majestic.</Source>
      <Dest>又或许我是。我是天际之子。连我们的五脏六腑都是高贵的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's a war going on, and I have letters to write.  I don't have time to be civil to someone who bays like a horse every time he takes a nap.</Source>
      <Dest>泰姆瑞尔战火四起，我有许多东西要写。我可没有这个闲功夫专门每次在某人打盹的时候像匹马那样嘶叫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're the ones who taught Tiber Septim the art of shape-shifting.  </Source>
      <Dest>他们便是授予泰伯‧赛普汀吼声之道的人。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll let him move back in.</Source>
      <Dest>我会让他搬回来住的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I said I'd let him move back in, I didn't say I was moving out.   I'll let him sleep on the chair out back, unless he snores.  Then it's the axe.</Source>
      <Dest>我说我会让他搬回来，我没说我要搬出去。如果他打呼噜的话，我会让他睡在室外房子后面的椅子上。然后就是斧子的事了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And blow their cover? You really are bad at this.</Source>
      <Dest>然后揭穿圣灵们的伪装？你对这个真是不在行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This dump?  Are you out of your mind? I just sleep here, live here, and use the vegetable garden on occasion. No, this all belongs to someone else.</Source>
      <Dest>这个仓库？你疯了吗？我只是睡在这里，住在这里，有时用用这里的菜园。没错，这一切都属于别人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course it is!  That just shows my letters are working.</Source>
      <Dest>当然是的！它证明了我的信管用了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You mean Talos?</Source>
      <Dest>你是说塔洛斯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sounds like something I'd name a store, or the assortment of crap that collects under my foot.</Source>
      <Dest>这听起来简直就是商店的名字嘛，就像我脚下这垃圾堆一样垃圾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I take it you have a different opinion of the name Ulfric.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜你对乌夫瑞克这个名字也有些别的看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>General isn't his name, and Tullius isn't even the Jarl.</Source>
      <Dest>他不叫"将军"，图留斯也不是领主。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think you mean the Jarl of Solitude, Elisif the Fair.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你说的应该是独孤城的领主，金发艾利西弗吧。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
