<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some call it the right of first night. As if men in power need to justify their rape with laws.  No, they just took what they wanted.  </Source>
      <Dest>有人称那是“初夜权”。就好像手握权势的人就可以利用法律让强奸变得合理。不，他们只是在为所欲为。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some call it the right of first night. As if men in power need to justify their rape with laws.  No, they just took what they wanted.  </Source>
      <Dest>有人称那是“初夜权”。就好像手握权势的人可以利用法律让强奸变得合理。不，他们只是在为所欲为。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Two of Gabania's men were dragging my sister into the cottage when they passed me by. One of them turned to look at me, and our eyes met.</Source>
      <Dest>当两个卡贝尼亚的人把我姐姐拖进小屋的时候，他们与我擦肩而过。其中的一个看了我一眼，我们的眼神交汇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There wasn't a drop of emotion in that face. That's what I remember most from that night.  Not the murder or the rape or the screams.</Source>
      <Dest>在那张脸上没有一丝表情。这就是那个夜晚我记得最清楚的。而不是谋杀、强奸或尖叫声。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was the face on that guardsman.   The face of apathy.  That I couldn't forgive.</Source>
      <Dest>而是那张守卫的脸。那张充满冷漠的脸。我永远不会原谅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll be waiting.</Source>
      <Dest>我会等你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Maybe you're right.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑声）或许你是对的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Morrigan, are you alright?</Source>
      <Dest>茉莉甘，你还好吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dark Brotherhood! What happened?</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗兄弟会！发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Morrigan!  No...</Source>
      <Dest>茉莉甘！不……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Please...Leave me.</Source>
      <Dest>请你……离我远些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I said leave!</Source>
      <Dest>我说了！离开！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A Draugr?</Source>
      <Dest>一个尸鬼?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What? But how...</Source>
      <Dest>什么？怎么可能……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Morrigan!</Source>
      <Dest>茉莉甘！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>...</Source>
      <Dest>……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've waited my entire life for this moment.</Source>
      <Dest>I've waited my entire life for this moment.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you do remember.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你还记得咯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was twenty years ago. There was a small town in Cyrodiil that blended into the countryside.</Source>
      <Dest>那是二十年前。在赛洛迪尔的乡间有一个小镇子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father always joked that it was too small to be on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父亲总是开玩笑说，它太小了以至于不能出现在任何地图上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when the visitors came by, they felt like explorers, discovering the town for the first time.</Source>
      <Dest>而当旅人们路过时，他们感觉自己像是探险家，头一次发现这座小镇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But for me, it was the only place that felt like home.</Source>
      <Dest>但是对我而言，那里是我唯一能称为家的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet after that day, I realized the whole thing was just a ruse.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，那天之后，我意识到整件事只是个诡计。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You made those maps. And you never put our town there for a reason.</Source>
      <Dest>你绘制了那些地图。而且你还出于某个理由在地图上漏绘了我们的城镇。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't worry. In about a minute, we'll be gone, and you'll be dead.</Source>
      <Dest>Don't worry. In about a minute, we'll be gone, and you'll be dead.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The way these ships are designed, the captain's quarters are on the lower deck. We'll probably have to fight our way down.</Source>
      <Dest>这船就是这么设计的，船长的宿舍在甲板下面。我们可能得一路杀到下面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That makes two of us kid. But he'll keep you safe. </Source>
      <Dest>我和你一样，孩子。但他会保护你安全的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, he's got one thing going for him. He's not the ugliest one on this ship.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，有件事对他来说挺有利的。他不是这艘船上最丑的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't. But I owe it to Morrigan to try.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有。不过看在茉莉甘的份上我应该试试。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is it?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't get it. That face. They all wore it. The people I killed for the Brotherhood, they wore it too.</Source>
      <Dest>你没明白。那张脸。他们都是那张脸。那些我为兄弟会杀的人，也是那张脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gabania...his men...and everyone I've killed since. To me, they're all one and the same.</Source>
      <Dest>卡贝尼亚……他的部下……还有被我所杀的所有人。在我看来，他们没什么区别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't need to kill anyone. But those men, the people who stand by and do nothing, while all around them the world suffers...</Source>
      <Dest>我不必杀任何人。但是那些人，那些站在一旁，看着自己周围哀鸿遍野却无动于衷的人……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're better off dead. And I'm the one to kill them.</Source>
      <Dest>他们死了更好。最好是我能亲手杀掉他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you believe that, then both your eyes are blind.</Source>
      <Dest>要是你相信那个，那你是两只眼睛都瞎了 。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know much about raising children, but I know better than to take your advice.</Source>
      <Dest>我确实在如何养育孩子这方面懂得不多，但我至少比你懂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, let's go.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我们走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It'll just be for a little while.  I promise.  If anyone comes near, stay behind the Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>一会儿就好，我保证。要是有人过来，你就躲在那精灵身后。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good girl.</Source>
      <Dest>好女孩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It'll just be for a little while.  I promise.  If anyone comes near remember what I told you.</Source>
      <Dest>就一会儿。我保证。如果有人走近，记得我告诉你的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Morrigan. I'm going to be gone a little while, like we talked about.</Source>
      <Dest>茉莉甘。就像我说的，我需要离开一小会。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've thought of that.  But I don't trust anyone to protect her but me.</Source>
      <Dest>我考虑过。但我不相信任何人能保护她，除了我自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You afraid of mercs, Elf? Because I'll go through a thousand sellswords to kill that bastard!</Source>
      <Dest>你在担心雇佣兵吗，精灵？因为我将会穿过一千个佣兵去做掉那个混账！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So he decided to get on his ship and sail to Windhelm. That ship is now docked at the harbor.</Source>
      <Dest>所以他决定把他的船航驶到风盔城。这艘船也就是现在停泊在码头的那艘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Turns out, the whole plan wasn't going too well, and our Baron was more than a bit agitated.</Source>
      <Dest>结果，整个计划的进展不顺利, 然后我们的男爵变得焦躁不安。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The one I heard was about a rich Baron, using the war as a way to gain influence with the new Jarls, or the weakened ones.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说过有这么个富有的男爵，依靠战争获得对新任领主或弱势领主的影响力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As a drifter, you get in earshot of all sorts of crazy rumors. You hear the same one enough, and you start paying attention.</Source>
      <Dest>作为流浪汉，你总会耳闻各种各样的的奇怪传闻。不过有一个传闻听了很多次，你就会开始注意那件事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Shut your mouth and I'll tell you, one-eye.</Source>
      <Dest>闭上你的嘴我就告诉你，独眼龙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wouldn't dream of it.</Source>
      <Dest>我不会再梦见它了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah? So what does that make us? </Source>
      <Dest>是吗？那这和我们有什么关系？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gabania.</Source>
      <Dest>Gabania.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I just do.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道又如何。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Quiet, kid. It's nobody's business but ours.</Source>
      <Dest>安静，孩子。这是我们之间的私事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're one to talk.  You're going to need a bigger bandage to cover up that Ogre you call a face.</Source>
      <Dest>你还真是能说会道。你应该拿一副更大的绑带盖住你称之为脸的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Morrigan...</Source>
      <Dest>茉莉甘……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd like to see you try.</Source>
      <Dest>我想让你试试看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who wants to know?</Source>
      <Dest>谁想知道?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You talk big, but you have a blind spot, one-eye.  You best watch it.</Source>
      <Dest>你光说大话，却没看见存在的缺陷，独眼龙。你最好能正视它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You say you follow the law. The law is what murdered my family.</Source>
      <Dest>你说自己是守法的。而法律就是谋杀我家人的元凶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who says there has to be one?  We're alive.  Maybe that's enough.</Source>
      <Dest>谁说必须有呢？我们还活着。也许这就足够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was wise, especially given what happened. How did you kill him?</Source>
      <Dest>那确实很明智，尤其以当时的情况来说。你是怎么杀死他的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I started out by pretending to be a beggar. Nagging the guards for coin and bread.  Not that it required much acting.  My hunger was real.</Source>
      <Dest>我从装扮一个乞丐开始。到处跟守卫乞求金币和食物。这并不需要什么演技。我的饥饿可不是装出来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was wise, especially given what happened. How did you kill him?</Source>
      <Dest>那确实很明智，尤其以当时的情况来说。你是怎么杀死他的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I pestered Gabinia's men one by one until I found that face.  He didn't recognize me.  Of course he didn't.</Source>
      <Dest>我一个个地纠缠卡贝尼亚的手下，直到我找到了那个人。他没有认出我。当然没有认出我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was wise, especially given what happened. How did you kill him?</Source>
      <Dest>那确实很明智，尤其以当时的情况来说。你是怎么杀死他的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I tracked him day and night, from the barracks to the brothels.  It was outside the inn where he was most vulnerable, unloading his mead.</Source>
      <Dest>我没日没夜地跟踪他，从营房到妓院。他喝完蜜酒出去撒尿的时候最好下手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was wise, especially given what happened. How did you kill him?</Source>
      <Dest>那确实很明智，尤其以当时的情况来说。你是怎么杀死他的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That night, I hid behind a stack of hay piles. The twin moons were out, and there was no mistaking that face.</Source>
      <Dest>那一晚，我躲在一摞稻草堆后面。双月升起，那张脸沐浴在月光之下，让我根本无法错认。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was wise, especially given what happened. How did you kill him?</Source>
      <Dest>那确实很明智，尤其以当时的情况来说。你是怎么杀死他的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I crept up behind him as he was pissing on the wall, the sound of the stream masking my footsteps.  Then I slid the dagger into his heart.</Source>
      <Dest>当他对着墙角撒尿的时候，我悄悄靠近了他，水流的声响隐藏了我的脚步。然后我把匕首刺进了他的心脏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was wise, especially given what happened. How did you kill him?</Source>
      <Dest>那确实很明智，尤其以当时的情况来说。你是怎么杀死他的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when he fell to the ground, I turned his face over and cut his mouth into a smile.</Source>
      <Dest>他摔到地上的以后，我把他弄成面朝上，并让他做出微笑的表情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I started out by pretending to be a beggar. Nagging the guards for coin and bread.  Not that it required much acting.  My hunger was real.</Source>
      <Dest>我从装扮一个乞丐开始。到处跟守卫乞求金币和食物。这并不需要什么演技。我的饥饿可不是装出来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I pestered Gabinia's men one by one until I found that face.  He didn't recognize me.  Of course he didn't.</Source>
      <Dest>我一个个地纠缠卡贝尼亚的手下，直到我找到了那个人。他没有认出我。当然没有认出我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I tracked him day and night, from the barracks to the brothels.  It was outside the inn where he was most vulnerable, unloading his mead.</Source>
      <Dest>我没日没夜地跟踪他，从营房到妓院。他喝完蜜酒出去撒尿的时候最好下手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That night, I hid behind a stack of hay piles. The twin moons were out, and there was no mistaking that face.</Source>
      <Dest>那一晚，我躲在一摞稻草堆后面。双月升起，那张脸沐浴在月光之下，让我根本无法错认。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I crept up behind him as he was pissing on the wall, the sound of the stream masking my footsteps.  Then I slid the dagger into his heart.</Source>
      <Dest>当他对着墙角撒尿的时候，我悄悄靠近了他，水流的声响隐藏了我的脚步。然后我把匕首刺进了他的心脏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when he fell to the ground, I turned his face over and cut his mouth into a smile.</Source>
      <Dest>他摔到地上的以后，我把他弄成面朝上，并让他做出微笑的表情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Killing the guardsman couldn't have been easy.</Source>
      <Dest>那个卫兵也不是太容易杀的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No. Looking back, I was lucky I wasn't a man grown.  My size and build forced me to cling to the shadows.  </Source>
      <Dest>确实不容易。现在想起来，幸亏我那时还很小。我的矮个子和瘦身材迫使我始终躲在阴影里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Killing the guardsman couldn't have been easy.</Source>
      <Dest>那个卫兵也不是太容易杀的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A grown man would have used the sword that felled my father to seek some sort of poetic justice.  A boy was forced to abandon that for a dagger.</Source>
      <Dest>一个长成的男人会拿起杀死他父亲的利剑来寻求诗歌中的正义。而一个男孩却只能拾起一把匕首，然后抛弃正义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An assassin with a heart of gold.  I'll take a coin purse full of gold instead.</Source>
      <Dest>一个有着金灿灿的善心的杀手。我更喜欢把我的钱袋塞满金灿灿的金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't have a heart of gold.  Some people deserve to die.  Others don't.  And you'd be surprised at the range of people I feel are deserving.</Source>
      <Dest>我可没有一颗金灿灿的善心。有些人该死。有些不。你会惊讶于我觉得有多少人该死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An assassin with a heart of gold.  I'll take a coin purse full of gold instead.</Source>
      <Dest>一个有着金灿灿的善心的杀手。我更喜欢把我的钱袋塞满金灿灿的金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I drew the line at Morrigan.  Children in general are too young to be corrupted like the rest of us.</Source>
      <Dest>我刻意和茉莉甘划开界线。孩子们太小，不应该受我们这样的人污染。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You broke a tenet?  Oh, you foolish fool.</Source>
      <Dest>你居然打破了教条？哦，你这个蠢透了的蠢货。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All of Astrid's talk of the new ways, I didn't think it would happen.  I was wrong. The Dark Brotherhood will always be under the eyes of Sithis.</Source>
      <Dest>所有阿斯垂德所讲的“新的教条”，我以为绝不会成真。但我错了。黑暗兄弟会永远都在西斯帝的注视之下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She isn't yours, and thus not your responsibility.</Source>
      <Dest>她并不是你的所有物，所以你不用负责任。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For now she is.  Has to be.  She's got no one else.  Now, eventually she'll come of age, and no longer be the girl she once was.</Source>
      <Dest>现在她是。必须是。她没有别的人了。然后，她终会成年，不再是曾经那个小女孩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She isn't yours, and thus not your responsibility.</Source>
      <Dest>她并不是你的所有物，所以你不用负责任。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And the only thing connecting her to her past will be me.  That's when I'll say goodbye.  Not a second before.</Source>
      <Dest>到时我就是她与她过去的唯一联系。直到那时我才会和她道别。一秒也不会提前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How hard could it be?  Like raising an oversized hamster.</Source>
      <Dest>那能有什么难度？就像养活一只超大号仓鼠一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You obviously don't have children, to say something like that.  No, I'm not cut out to be a father.</Source>
      <Dest>你显然没有孩子，凭什么说出那样的话？不，我不适合做一个父亲 。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How hard could it be?  Like raising an oversized hamster.</Source>
      <Dest>那能有什么难度？就像养活一只超大号仓鼠一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe an uncle.  The kind that drops in from time to time bearing gifts.  Can't even do that.  Can't chance them following me.  </Source>
      <Dest>也许可以是叔叔。时不时带着礼物来串门的叔叔。不，我甚至不能这么做。不能给他们跟踪我的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How hard could it be?  Like raising an oversized hamster.</Source>
      <Dest>那能有什么难度？就像养活一只超大号仓鼠一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd lead them straight to her.  And a contract is always open until it's fulfilled.</Source>
      <Dest>我会把他们引到她那儿。契约在完成前不会失效。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've already met the little scamp.  Her name's Morrigan.  She spoke well of you.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经见过那小家伙了，她的名字是茉莉甘。她对你的评价不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did she? (Sigh) I told her not to talk to strangers. What did she tell you?</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗？（叹气）我告诉过她不要和陌生人讲话。她和你说了些什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, yes. Children are useless scum.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯没错，小孩的都是些没用废物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then stay away from this one.</Source>
      <Dest>那就离这孩子远一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This whole arrangement is suspicious.  Explain yourself, or I call the guard.</Source>
      <Dest>这一切都很可疑。你得解释一下，要么我就叫守卫来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hold on, there's no need for that.  It's not what you think.  The girl's under my protection.</Source>
      <Dest>等等，不必这么做。事情不是你想的那样。我正在保护这个女孩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, well.  Looks like Gilfre's got herself a couple of dirty squatters.</Source>
      <Dest>喔，喔。看来吉福雷惹上了几个脏兮兮的流浪汉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We aren't staying.  Just passing through.  And we aren't looking for trouble.</Source>
      <Dest>我们不会久留。只是路过这里。而且我们不想招惹麻烦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for me?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah. Don't join the Dark Brotherhood. The road it'll take you will be covered in not only the blood of your victims, but of your friends, as well.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊。我奉劝你不要加入黑暗兄弟会。那条道路上沾满的不仅仅是你受害者的鲜血，也会染上你朋友的血。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for me?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah. Quit the Dark Brotherhood. The road it'll take you will be covered in not only the blood of your victims, but of your friends, as well.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊。我劝你退出暗黑兄弟会。那条道路上沾满的不仅仅是你受害者的鲜血，也会染上你朋友的血。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for me?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May you be dead ten minutes before Sithis knows it.</Source>
      <Dest>但愿在被西帝斯知晓前，你已死了十分钟有余。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for me?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Truly know who you are killing, and what you kill for, before you make the killing blow.</Source>
      <Dest>下手之前，搞清楚要杀的是谁，为什么要杀他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any advice for me?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么建议吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Kill every nobleman you see.</Source>
      <Dest>杀掉所有贵族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You only make her weak by protecting her.</Source>
      <Dest>你对她的保护只能使她更脆弱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There will come a time when I will teach her what she needs to know, and nothing more.</Source>
      <Dest>终有一天我会告诉她她必须知道的事，仅此而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Put yourself in my shoes.  Young girl, empty house, darkly dressed man...</Source>
      <Dest>站在我的立场想想。少女，空房，打扮黑暗的男人……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I was that kind of man, the girl's hands would be bound, and you'd be dead.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我是那种人，这女孩的手会被绑住，而你现在已经死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Put yourself in my shoes.  Young girl, empty house, darkly dressed man...</Source>
      <Dest>站在我的立场想想。少女，空房，打扮黑暗的男人……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Even now, I'm still not sure whether I should let you live.  So choose your words carefully.</Source>
      <Dest>就算现在，我也不确定该不该留你活口。所以开口时注意点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maybe I'll ask her who her guardian is.  Pray she says "That guy."</Source>
      <Dest>也许我会问她谁是她的监护人。希望她会说“是那家伙”。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She'll tell you all you need know.  Which is why she won't say a word.</Source>
      <Dest>她只会告诉你你该知道的部分。所以她才不肯多说一个字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your parents must be so proud to have raised such a dutiful killer.</Source>
      <Dest>你的父母一定为养育了你这样一个孝顺的杀手而自豪。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe they weren't proud, but I can't say they'd be disappointed.  I know, because it felt so good to do it.</Source>
      <Dest>也许他们并不感觉骄傲，但我不能说他们会失望。我知道，因为这么做感觉太棒了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your parents must be so proud to have raised such a dutiful killer.</Source>
      <Dest>你的父母一定为养育了你这样一个孝顺的杀手而自豪。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wasn't until I heard that slow, condescending clap that I woke up from my trance. Then I looked up, and saw Astrid.</Source>
      <Dest>直到几声缓慢，和蔼的掌声将我从恍惚中惊醒。于是我抬起头，看到了阿斯垂德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I myself enjoy the company of children.</Source>
      <Dest>我自己倒是挺喜欢有孩子陪着的感觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But not in that way, I take it.  Otherwise, I'm sure they'll come a time and place where we meet again, under different circumstances.</Source>
      <Dest>但不是以那种方式，这我认了。另外，我确信总有一天我们会在不同的情境下不期而遇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you take her if he was dead?</Source>
      <Dest>既然他已经死了，你为什么还要带上她？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dark Brotherhood would eventually try to find her. Once the black sacrament has been performed, the mark is eternally cursed by Sithis.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗兄弟会最终肯定会试图找到她的。黑暗圣礼一旦完成，被要求歼灭的对象将一辈子受到西帝斯的诅咒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you take her if he was dead?</Source>
      <Dest>既然他已经死了，你为什么还要带上她？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The sacrament demands blood and they will not stop until that blood has been spilled. </Source>
      <Dest>圣礼渴求鲜血，在血债血偿之前，他们不会停手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you take her if he was dead?</Source>
      <Dest>既然他已经死了，你为什么还要带上她？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've killed so many of my brothers and sisters.   Some I even considered friends.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经杀了很多兄弟姐妹。还有一些我甚至认为是朋友的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's with the girl?</Source>
      <Dest>那女孩儿怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm her guardian. Lets just leave it at that.</Source>
      <Dest>我是她的护卫。言止于此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I just wanted to talk.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是想谈谈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sorry, but I'm not looking for company.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉，但我现在不需要同伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What will you do now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在有什么打算？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Keep wandering. Maybe head back to the old mill. It's probably best we both stay clear of Windhelm, and each other.</Source>
      <Dest>继续游荡。或者回去那个旧农场。我们最好都别再接近风盔城，也别再见面了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What will you do now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在有什么打算？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That goes for your friend as well, unless he wants to try and collect on that bounty.</Source>
      <Dest>你的朋友也一样，除非他想用我来换赏金。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>With Gabania dead, you can focus on being a father.</Source>
      <Dest>卡贝尼亚死了以后，你终于可以专注于作为父亲的职责了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah. I'm going to have to get her to stop calling me that.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊。我让她别那么叫我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>With Gabania dead, you can focus on being a father.</Source>
      <Dest>卡贝尼亚死了以后，你终于可以专注于作为父亲的职责了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for you, here. I took these from a summoner I was contracted to kill. They've served me well. I hope they help you on your journeys. </Source>
      <Dest>至于你呢，给。这是我在契约里杀掉的召唤师身上找到的。它们都很有用，希望能对你的旅途有所帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your desire for revenge could have cost Morrigan her life.</Source>
      <Dest>你对复仇的渴望可能会赔掉茉莉甘的性命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was always a risk. But there's going to be more days like this. If I am...her father, I guess there'll come a time I have to let go.</Source>
      <Dest>风险总是会有的。但像这样的日子以后还会有很多。如果我是……她的父亲，我想总有一天我必须结束这一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your desire for revenge could have cost Morrigan her life.</Source>
      <Dest>你对复仇的渴望可能会赔掉茉莉甘的性命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for you, here. I took these from a summoner I was contracted to kill. They've served me well. I hope they help you on your journeys. </Source>
      <Dest>至于你呢，给。这是我在契约里杀掉的召唤师身上找到的。它们都很有用，希望能对你的旅途有所帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't encourage her. I don't think Draugr have names. Dead ones, anyway. But whoever it was, I owe them.</Source>
      <Dest>别鼓励她。我可不认为尸鬼也有名字。那些死了的家伙也一样。但不管它是什么，我都欠着它们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's likely this Draugr's name is Moris.</Source>
      <Dest>很可能这只尸鬼的名字就叫莫里斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for you, here. I took these from a summoner I was contracted to kill. They've served me well. I hope they help you on your journeys. </Source>
      <Dest>至于你呢，给。这是我在契约里杀掉的召唤师身上找到的。它们都很有用，希望能对你的旅途有所帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's likely this Draugr's name is Moris.</Source>
      <Dest>很可能这只尸鬼的名字就叫莫里斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You could be right. But with Gabania dead, there's no reason to leave her side again.</Source>
      <Dest>你可能是对的。但是随着卡贝尼亚的死，我再也没有离她而去的理由。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This just proves you need to rely on others beside yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>这只证明了你需要依靠自己身边的人。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for you, here. I took these from a summoner I was contracted to kill. They've served me well. I hope they help you on your journeys. </Source>
      <Dest>至于你呢，给。这是我在契约里杀掉的召唤师身上找到的。它们都很有用，希望能对你的旅途有所帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This just proves you need to rely on others beside yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>这只证明了你需要依靠自己身边的人。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wouldn't go that far. I owe him one. That will have to do.</Source>
      <Dest>我不会那么过份。我欠他一次，一定会还的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I believe you owe Raynes an apology.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为你欠瑞纳斯一声抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for you, here. I took these from a summoner I was contracted to kill. They've served me well. I hope they help you on your journeys.</Source>
      <Dest>至于你呢，给。这是我在契约里杀掉的召唤师身上找到的。它们都很有用，希望能对你的旅途有所帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I believe you owe Raynes an apology.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为你欠瑞纳斯一声抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I always knew the day would come where I wouldn't have to protect her. I just didn't expect it to come so soon.</Source>
      <Dest>我一直都知道她不再需要我保护的日子总会到来。我只是没想到它来得这么快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It seems to me Morrigan can take care of herself.</Source>
      <Dest>就我看来，茉莉甘似乎可以自己照顾自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here. I took these from a summoner I was contracted to kill. They've served me well. I hope they help you on your journeys. </Source>
      <Dest>至于你呢，给。这是我在契约里杀掉的召唤师身上找到的。它们都很有用，希望能对你的旅途有所帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It seems to me Morrigan can take care of herself.</Source>
      <Dest>就我看来，茉莉甘似乎可以自己照顾自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It won't bring your family back, but I hope you found some measure of peace.</Source>
      <Dest>这不会让你的家人死而复生，不过我希望你能够找到一些平静。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We'll see.  But it wasn't just me. I had a lot of help. Not just today, but back at the mill. </Source>
      <Dest>我们会知道的。但那将不光是我。我得过很多帮助。不止是今天，还有在农场的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It won't bring your family back, but I hope you found some measure of peace.</Source>
      <Dest>这不会让你的家人死而复生，不过我希望你能够找到一些平静。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, let's get back to the inn. Morrigan might get fidgety without me there.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说，先回旅馆吧。没有我在茉莉甘会着急的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It is a noble's birthright to treat commoners like ants.</Source>
      <Dest>生而高贵的人自然有权利视平民如蝼蚁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With that attitude, you and Gabania may share the same fate. But you and I have no quarrel. Not after today.</Source>
      <Dest>这样的态度，也许你能和卡贝尼亚遭受同样的命运。但我还不想跟你打。今天还不想。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It is a noble's birthright to treat commoners like ants.</Source>
      <Dest>生而高贵的人自然有权利视平民如蝼蚁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, let's get back to the inn. Morrigan might get fidgety without me there.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说，先回旅馆吧。没有我在茉莉甘会着急的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He remembered. Maybe not you, but all the poor villagers he's hurt.</Source>
      <Dest>他全都记得。也许他不记得你，但是他记得他伤害过的可怜的村民。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And he didn't care. I guess if he did, he would be more like me. A man, and not a monster.</Source>
      <Dest>而他不在乎。我猜如果他在乎，他会更像我。是一个人，而不是一头怪物。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He remembered. Maybe not you, but all the poor villagers he's hurt.</Source>
      <Dest>他全都记得。也许他不记得你，但是他记得他伤害过的可怜的村民。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, let's get back to the inn. Morrigan might get fidgety without me there.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说，先回旅馆吧。没有我在茉莉甘会着急的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you feel?</Source>
      <Dest>感觉如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Worried. We better hurry back. Right now, I just want to make sure Morrigan's okay.</Source>
      <Dest>很担心。我们最好快点回去。马上，我只想确定茉莉甘安然无恙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what's the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么计划？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what's the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>那么计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gabania is too paranoid to leave his ship. It's likely he has people delivered to him. But don't get any ideas. I'm not wearing a noble's robes.</Source>
      <Dest>卡贝尼亚太多疑，所以不会离开他的船。很可能会有人给他通风报信。但我没想出任何主意，我又没穿着贵族长袍</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what's the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么计划？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what's the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>那么计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What I'm saying is, we'll have to sneak our way past the guard. Either that, or muscle our way in.</Source>
      <Dest>我想说的是，我们估计得潜行着从警卫面前走过了。要么就强行开道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what's the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么计划？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what's the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>那么计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gabania is too paranoid to leave his ship. It's likely he has people delivered to him. But don't get any ideas. I'm not wearing a noble's robes.</Source>
      <Dest>卡贝尼亚太多疑，所以不会离开他的船。很可能会有人给他通风报信。但我没想出任何主意，我又没穿着贵族长袍</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what's the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么计划？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what's the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>那么计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What I'm saying is, we'll have to sneak our way past the guards. Either that, or muscle our way in.</Source>
      <Dest>我想说的是，我们估计得潜行着从警卫面前走过了。要么就强行开道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what's the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么计划？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what's the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>那么计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I prefer stealth, but I'm guessing your friend isn't the type.  I'll let you figure it out. You know each of our strengths, and how best to use us.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢秘密行动，但我猜你的朋友不擅长这个。我会让你来做决定。你知道我们每个人的优势，以及如何发挥我们的优势。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned Morrigan has some magical skill. Can she defend herself?</Source>
      <Dest>你提过茉莉甘会两下魔法。她能保护好自己吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She's a child. It's better if she hides. I've given her a potion that will make her invisible, but with an assassin, she won't have time to drink it.</Source>
      <Dest>她是个孩子。如果她能藏起来更好。我给过她一个让她隐形的药水，但如果遇到了一名刺客，她不会有时间喝药水的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned Morrigan has some magical skill. Can she defend herself?</Source>
      <Dest>你提过茉莉甘会两下魔法。她能保护好自己吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But again, she's a child. It's her one weakness, and her one advantage.</Source>
      <Dest>但是，她只是个孩子。这是她的弱点，也是她的优势。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned Morrigan has some magical skill. Can she defend herself?</Source>
      <Dest>你提过茉莉甘会两下魔法。她能保护好自己吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We've talked about her learning a spell. Maybe she can catch an unwitting assassin off guard, and give her enough time to drink the potion.</Source>
      <Dest>我们谈过让她学习咒语的事。或许她能趁一个昏头傻脑的刺客疏于防备之际喝下隐身药水。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned Morrigan has some magical skill. Can she defend herself?</Source>
      <Dest>你提过茉莉甘会两下魔法。她能保护好自己吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) The more I think about it, the more it seems like a bad idea. I would feel better if you stayed, but I doubt me and the Elf can work together.</Source>
      <Dest>（叹气）我越想，越觉得是个坏主意。如果你肯留下来我会感觉好很多，但是我不确定能否和那个精灵相处愉快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It sounds like it'll take a group effort to make any headway on that ship.</Source>
      <Dest>看来想在那艘船上杀出条血路就必须依靠团队合作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's what I feared. In a way, it doesn't seem like much of a risk if we left her alone for one night.</Source>
      <Dest>这正是我所担心的。某种程度上，似乎让她独处一晚不会有太大危险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It sounds like it'll take a group effort to make any headway on that ship.</Source>
      <Dest>看来想在那艘船上杀出条血路就必须依靠团队合作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've done my best to keep the Brotherhood off our trail, and the odds of something happening are slim to none.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经竭尽全力甩掉暗黑兄弟会，而且平安无事的可能性也远大于发生意外。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It sounds like it'll take a group effort to make any headway on that ship.</Source>
      <Dest>看来想在那艘船上杀出条血路就必须依靠团队合作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if it did happen, if Morrigan wasn't safe...I could never forgive myself.</Source>
      <Dest>然而如果意外真的发生了，如果茉莉甘遇上了危险……那我永远也不会原谅我自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It sounds like it'll take a group effort to make any headway on that ship.</Source>
      <Dest>看来想在那艘船上杀出条血路就必须依靠团队合作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And yet, every night I go to sleep, I see that face. The guardsman...and the one who made him.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，每天晚上我入梦之后，都会看见那张脸。那个守卫……和那个元凶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right. I don't think it's a good idea either.</Source>
      <Dest>你说得对。我也认为这不是个好主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Failure) No, it's a terrible idea. Hopefully you have some that aren't.</Source>
      <Dest>（失败）不，这主意糟透了。希望你有不那么糟的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That ship will be well guarded. The weakest link should stay with the girl.</Source>
      <Dest>那艘船肯定会被严加把守。所以就让最弱的人来照顾那个女孩吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Failure) You have a point. But something makes me think she'd be better off coming with us than staying with him.</Source>
      <Dest>（失败）确实是个主意。但我总觉得她最好和我们一起走，而不是和他呆在一起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would stay, but think about it. You and Raynes alone together?</Source>
      <Dest>我会留下来的，但仔细想想。你和瑞纳斯单独在一起？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Success) Yeah. It wouldn't end well, for him anyway. And if Gabania's men are worth half the gold he pays them, I'll need your help.</Source>
      <Dest>（成功）是啊。对他来说，这无论如何都不会有好的结果。如果卡贝尼亚的人能值他们雇佣金的一半的话，我就得要你来帮忙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Success) You're right. Maybe I'm not thinking clearly on this either. If that's what's best for Morrigan, then okay.</Source>
      <Dest>（成功）你说得对。也许我也没有想清楚。只要是对茉莉甘好的，那就好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you sure you aren't letting your anger affect you?</Source>
      <Dest>你确定自己不会被愤怒冲昏头脑吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Honestly, I was going to suggest you stay, but then that would leave me with him. It wouldn't be pretty.</Source>
      <Dest>老实说，我想建议你留下，但那可就让我跟他呆在一起了。这可不好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you sure you aren't letting your anger affect you?</Source>
      <Dest>你确定自己不会被愤怒冲昏头脑吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Failure) That doesn't make any sense. If he's insane, he's not someone you can trust to maintain a code.</Source>
      <Dest>（失败）这说不通。要是他真是个疯子，那你就不能确保他会坚守信条。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He's ruthless. Crazy. But he protects the innocent.</Source>
      <Dest>他残忍。疯狂。但他保护无辜者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't expect you to tell Morrigan. That's a bit heavy for a child to hear.</Source>
      <Dest>我本来不想让你告诉茉莉甘。这件事对一个孩子来说略显沉重。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wasn't something I wanted to do. But I had to. Because where my head was at, I couldn't trust my own decisions.</Source>
      <Dest>我不想这么做。但我却必须这么做。考虑到我正把注意力放在其他地方，我没法相信自己的决断。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't expect you to tell Morrigan. That's a bit heavy for a child to hear.</Source>
      <Dest>我本来不想让你告诉茉莉甘。这件事对一个孩子来说略显沉重。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know why I have to do this. Why I can't let him live.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道我为什么必须这么做。我为什么不能留他苟活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't expect you to tell Morrigan. That's a bit heavy for a child to hear.</Source>
      <Dest>我本来不想让你告诉茉莉甘。这件事对一个孩子来说略显沉重。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But she didn't. And as she always does, the girl asked why. So I told her. And if my needs ever made her feel unsafe, to let me know.</Source>
      <Dest>但她不知道。就像平时那样，小女孩我问为什么。所以我就告诉她。如果我的需求让她感到不安，请告诉我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't expect you to tell Morrigan. That's a bit heavy for a child to hear.</Source>
      <Dest>我本来不想让你告诉茉莉甘。这件事对一个孩子来说略显沉重。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's another reason Gabania has to die. I can't protect Morrigan like this. Not when all I see are the faces from that day.</Source>
      <Dest>卡贝尼亚之所以必须死还有另一个原因。如果我脑海中一直萦绕着那天那张脸孔，我将无法保护好茉莉甘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think it was good for you to be honest with Morrigan about your past.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你如果能坦率地将你的过去告诉茉莉甘，那会好一些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wasn't something I wanted to do. But I had to. Because where my head was at, I couldn't trust my own decisions.</Source>
      <Dest>我不想这么做。但我却必须这么做。考虑到我正把注意力放在其他地方，我没法相信自己的决断。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think it was good for you to be honest with Morrigan about your past.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你如果能坦率地将你的过去告诉茉莉甘，那会好一些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know why I have to do this. Why I can't let him live.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道我为什么必须这么做。我为什么不能留他苟活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think it was good for you to be honest with Morrigan about your past.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你如果能坦率地将你的过去告诉茉莉甘，那会好一些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But she didn't. And as she always does, the girl asked why. So I told her. And if my needs ever made her feel unsafe, to let me know.</Source>
      <Dest>但她不知道。就像平时那样，小女孩我问为什么。所以我就告诉她。如果我的需求让她感到不安，请告诉我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think it was good for you to be honest with Morrigan about your past.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你如果能坦率地将你的过去告诉茉莉甘，那会好一些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's another reason Gabania has to die. I can't protect Morrigan like this. Not when all I see are the faces from that day.</Source>
      <Dest>卡贝尼亚之所以必须死还有另一个原因。如果我脑海中一直萦绕着那天那张脸孔，我将无法保护好茉莉甘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is something you deserve, and the Gods have obliged.</Source>
      <Dest>这是你应得的, 众神已赐与你.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know about that. Seems the Gods could have done me a favor and never let it happen.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道。看起来神灵帮我永远的避免了这个麻烦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is something you deserve, and the Gods have obliged.</Source>
      <Dest>这是你应得的, 众神已赐与你.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But maybe then, Morrigan wouldn't be alive today.  So if the price of that is letting Gabania live, it's one I'm willing to pay.</Source>
      <Dest>但也许茉莉甘活不过今天。所以如果代价只是放卡贝尼亚一条生路，那么我很愿意支付它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Raynes should stay with Morrigan.</Source>
      <Dest>瑞纳斯应该和茉莉甘呆在一起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No. Absolutely not.</Source>
      <Dest>不。绝对不行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your revenge would be sweet. It's too bad Raynes is going to kill him first.</Source>
      <Dest>你的复仇会很美妙。但如果瑞纳斯抢先杀掉他就太糟了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Him? That hot-headed milk-drinker would charge headfirst into a spear.</Source>
      <Dest>他？那个头脑发热的懦夫会一头撞上矛尖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your revenge would be sweet. It's too bad Raynes is going to kill him first.</Source>
      <Dest>你的复仇会很美妙。但如果瑞纳斯抢先杀掉他就太糟了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, it has to be me.  I'm the only one who can put the fear in those faces. But I won't do it unless I know Morrigan will be safe.</Source>
      <Dest>不，那人必须是我。我是唯一一个能让他们感到恐惧的人。但除非让我得知茉莉甘不会有事，否则我不会行动的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your revenge would be sweet. It's too bad Raynes is going to kill him first.</Source>
      <Dest>你的复仇会很美妙。但如果瑞纳斯抢先杀掉他就太糟了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Killing Gabania will not bring my family back. But I can still protect her.</Source>
      <Dest>杀了卡贝尼亚并不能挽回我的家人。但至少我仍能保护她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about Morrigan?</Source>
      <Dest>茉莉甘呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's what I've been thinking about. I can't leave her alone, and I can't bring her with me.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我一直在思考的事。我不能把她留下来，也不能带她走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about Morrigan?</Source>
      <Dest>茉莉甘呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And if it's one or the other...him, or her...it will always be her.</Source>
      <Dest>如果必须二者选其一……他，或者她……我一定会选她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you're finally going to get revenge?</Source>
      <Dest>所以你最后决定去复仇？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe. I got a lead. Whispers mostly, but when it comes to that name, I've been trained to listen.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊。我得到了些线索。一般是些耳语，但出现那个名字的时候，我已经习惯了仔细聆听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned a lead on Gabania.</Source>
      <Dest>你提到有卡贝尼亚的线索。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, might be something, might be nothing. Whispers mostly, but when it comes to that name, I've been trained to listen.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，也许是什么，也许什么都不是。一般是些耳语，但出现那个名字的时候，我已经习惯了仔细聆听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Leave me.</Source>
      <Dest>别来烦我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It looks like she's going to be okay.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来她很快就会好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You've got the wrong house stranger.  The mill owner lives on the other side of the road.  I suggest you leave.</Source>
      <Dest>陌生人你认错门了，磨坊主住在路的另一边。我建议你离开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You've been awfully quiet. I wasn't sure what to make of this, you bringing this maniac here.</Source>
      <Dest>你一直很安静。我不确定你在干些什么，你居然把这疯子带到这儿来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can tell he's not with the Brotherhood though. But that won't guarantee Morrigan's safety.</Source>
      <Dest>不过我能肯定他不是兄弟会的人。但这也不能保证茉莉甘的安全。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not a chance. There's got to be another way. What do you think?</Source>
      <Dest>绝不可能。肯定还有其他办法。你认为呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I should have figured he wouldn't remember. They never do.</Source>
      <Dest>我早该知道他不会记得的。他们从来都是这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you serving as her guardian?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么要做她的守卫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I need a reason to protect a child?</Source>
      <Dest>我保护一个孩子难道还需要理由？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That must have been cathartic.</Source>
      <Dest>这一定很解恨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was.  I stared into that face for what seemed like forever, my body tingling with sensation.  </Source>
      <Dest>没错。我死死盯着那张脸，那一刻对我而言如永恒一般漫长，我的身体也因激动而颤栗。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That must have been cathartic.</Source>
      <Dest>这一定很解恨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wasn't until I heard that slow, condescending clap that I woke up from my trance. Then I looked up, and saw Astrid.</Source>
      <Dest>直到几声缓慢，和蔼的掌声将我从恍惚中惊醒。于是我抬起头，看到了阿斯垂德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you her father?</Source>
      <Dest>你是她爸？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No.</Source>
      <Dest>不。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There must be more to it than that.</Source>
      <Dest>事情不会是这么简单。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah.  The Dark Brotherhood aren't just hunting a killer.  They're hunting one of their own.  Me.</Source>
      <Dest>对。暗黑兄弟会不只是在追猎一个杀手。他们是在猎杀一个同类。我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There must be more to it than that.</Source>
      <Dest>事情不会是这么简单。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's a long story. Not one I really care to tell.</Source>
      <Dest>那是一个很长的故事。不是太值得讲的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are you two doing here?</Source>
      <Dest>你们两个在这里干嘛？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's none of your business.</Source>
      <Dest>这不关你的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's none of your business.</Source>
      <Dest>不关你的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A stranger. Just like you. Let's keep it that way.</Source>
      <Dest>一个陌生人。就跟你一样。暂时先这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sithis sounds formidable.  Better to kill the girl and be done with it.</Source>
      <Dest>西帝斯听上去很强大。最好杀了那个女孩儿，然后结束这一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I was that sort of person, I would've never come this far.  </Source>
      <Dest>如果我是那种人，我不可能会撑这么久。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your parents were powerless, but I imagine they tried to stop it.</Source>
      <Dest>你的父母无力还手，但我猜他们曾试图阻止这件事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My mother pleaded for mercy, my father reached for his axe.  When one of the guards gutted him, all anyone could do was weep.</Source>
      <Dest>我的母亲不停地求饶，而父亲起身去拿他的斧头。当一个警卫把他开膛破肚的时候，我们唯一能做到的只是哭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your parents were powerless, but I imagine they tried to stop it.</Source>
      <Dest>你的父母无力还手，但我猜他们曾试图阻止这件事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Two of Gabania's men were dragging my sister into the cottage when they passed me by.  One of them turned to look at me, and our eyes met.</Source>
      <Dest>两个卡贝尼亚的手下把我姐姐拽进小屋的时候，我正和他们擦身而过。他们中的一个抬起头看了看我，我们目光交错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your parents were powerless, but I imagine they tried to stop it.</Source>
      <Dest>你的父母无力还手，但我猜他们曾试图阻止这件事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There wasn't a drop of emotion in that face. That's what I remember most from that night.  Not the murder or the rape or the screams.</Source>
      <Dest>在那张脸上没有一丝表情。这就是那个夜晚我记得最清楚的。而不是谋杀、强奸或尖叫声。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your parents were powerless, but I imagine they tried to stop it.</Source>
      <Dest>你的父母无力还手，但我猜他们曾试图阻止这件事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was the face on that guardsman. The face of apathy. That I couldn't forgive.</Source>
      <Dest>而是那张守卫的脸。那张充满冷漠的脸。我永远不会原谅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My mother pleaded for mercy, my father reached for his axe. When one of the guards gutted him, all anyone could do was weep.</Source>
      <Dest>我的母亲不停地求饶，而父亲起身去拿他的斧头。当一个警卫把他开膛破肚的时候，我们唯一能做到的只是哭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Two of Gabania's men were dragging my sister into the cottage when they passed me by. One of them turned to look at me, and our eyes met.</Source>
      <Dest>当两个卡贝尼亚的人把我姐姐拖进小屋的时候，他们与我擦肩而过。其中的一个看了我一眼，我们的眼神交汇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There wasn't a drop of emotion in that face. That's what I remember most from that night.  Not the murder or the rape or the screams.</Source>
      <Dest>在那张脸上没有一丝表情。这就是那个夜晚我记得最清楚的。而不是谋杀、强奸或尖叫声。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was the face on that guardsman. The face of apathy. That I couldn't forgive.</Source>
      <Dest>而是那张守卫的脸。那张充满冷漠的脸。我永远不会原谅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was a young boy, living in an old cottage with my parents and older sister. She was about five years older than Morrigan, and promised to marry.</Source>
      <Dest>那时我是个小男孩儿，跟我的父母和姐姐住在一所旧屋子里。那时她比茉莉甘年长五岁，已经许人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want Raynes to hear the story of why we're doing this, and what Gabania did.</Source>
      <Dest>我要让瑞纳斯听到我们这么做的来龙去脉，还有卡贝尼亚的所作所为。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was the day of her wedding when Lord Gabania's men came riding into field.  </Source>
      <Dest>就在她婚礼的那一天，领主卡贝尼亚的人骑马冲进了那里。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want Raynes to hear the story of why we're doing this, and what Gabania did.</Source>
      <Dest>我要让瑞纳斯听到我们这么做的来龙去脉，还有卡贝尼亚的所作所为。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was a young boy, living in an old cottage with my parents and older sister. </Source>
      <Dest>我那时是一个小男孩，和我的姐姐以及父母生活在一间破旧的小屋里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you end up in the Dark Brotherhood?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么会加入暗黑兄弟会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was the face on that guardsman. The face of apathy. That I couldn't forgive.</Source>
      <Dest>而是那张守卫的脸。那张充满冷漠的脸。我永远不会原谅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why is the Dark Brotherhood after you?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么会被黑暗兄弟会盯上的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I killed one of their contracts.</Source>
      <Dest>我杀了他们契约上的一个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If that were the case, I imagine I'd already be dead.  Which means there are things even the Listener can't hear, or doesn't choose to.</Source>
      <Dest>如果是那样的话，我想我本应该已被杀掉多时了。而现在的情况说明有些东西连聆听者也听不到，或者选择不去听到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What a coincidence. I'm the Listener.</Source>
      <Dest>真巧啊，我就是聆听者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If it's the latter, then perhaps you and I aren't so different.</Source>
      <Dest>如果是后者，那么也许你我之间也没有什么太大的不同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What a coincidence. I'm the Listener.</Source>
      <Dest>真巧啊，我就是聆听者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If that were the case, I imagine you'd have drawn your weapon.  Which means you don't know, or don't care to.</Source>
      <Dest>如果是这样的话，我想你本应该抽出武器。而现在的情况说明你并不知情，亦或是根本不在乎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What a coincidence. I'm a member.</Source>
      <Dest>好巧啊，我是一名兄弟会成员。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If it's the latter, then perhaps you and I aren't so different.</Source>
      <Dest>如果是后者，那么也许你我之间也没有什么太大的不同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What a coincidence. I'm a member.</Source>
      <Dest>好巧啊，我是一名兄弟会成员。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you know how it is. Always looking over your shoulder, never getting a good night's sleep, never knowing if this is the last time.</Source>
      <Dest>那你应该懂这感觉吧。时刻警惕你的背后，夜晚从不沉眠，永远不知道你是否能看到第二天的太阳。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've been hunted myself.</Source>
      <Dest>我自己就曾被追杀过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The last time I see the sun.  Or taste a ripe apple.  Or get pinched by the girl.   Everything has a finality to it.  </Source>
      <Dest>我最后一次看见太阳。或者最后一次尝到熟透的苹果。或者最后一次被小女孩掐疼。万事皆会有尽头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've been hunted myself.</Source>
      <Dest>我自己就曾被追杀过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It all feels so tense.  So grave.  I'd probably lose myself, fall into old habits, if the kid weren't depending on me.</Source>
      <Dest>这感觉如此紧张，如此沉重。如果这个孩子不再依赖于我，我可能会迷失自我，故态复萌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've been hunted myself.</Source>
      <Dest>我自己就曾被追杀过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Agreed. The question is how to purge it.</Source>
      <Dest>同意。问题在于如何净化他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I gained their trust, and offered them drink.  The liquor was a paralysis poison.  Then I bound them and interrogated them until I found it.</Source>
      <Dest>我取得他们的信任，再请他们喝一杯。烈酒是很好的麻痹药。然后我把他们捆住，审问他们，直到我得到我想要的答案。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Agreed. The question is how to purge it.</Source>
      <Dest>同意。问题在于如何净化他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was a game. I asked them to name their killer. They always assumed I was talking about me.</Source>
      <Dest>那是一个游戏，我叫他们说出杀手的名字，但他们总是认为我在说我自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you kill your victims?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎样杀死你的目标的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I gained their trust, and offered them drink.  The liquor was a paralysis poison.  Then I bound them and interrogated them until I found it.</Source>
      <Dest>我取得他们的信任，再请他们喝一杯。烈酒是很好的麻痹药。然后我把他们捆住，审问他们，直到我得到我想要的答案。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you kill your victims?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎样杀死你的目标的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was a game. I asked them to name their killer. They always assumed I was talking about me.</Source>
      <Dest>那是一个游戏，我叫他们说出杀手的名字，但他们总是认为我在说我自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You needed to know there was some morality behind each kill.</Source>
      <Dest>你需要确认每次杀戮背后都有些道德意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe.  At least that's the way I see it now.  Not so much before.  The Dark Brotherhood doesn't take sides.</Source>
      <Dest>可能吧。至少我现在会这么想。以前我不会想这么多。毕竟暗黑兄弟会从不站队。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You needed to know there was some morality behind each kill.</Source>
      <Dest>你需要确认每次杀戮背后都有些道德意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When a hunter tracks game for the butcher, it's not his place to ask if the deer deserves it.</Source>
      <Dest>当一名猎人替屠夫打猎时，他就不应质疑猎物该不该死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You needed to know there was some morality behind each kill.</Source>
      <Dest>你需要确认每次杀戮背后都有些道德意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet for some reason in the back of my mind, I always assumed they did.  Some were less guilty than others, but all were guilty of indifference.</Source>
      <Dest>然而出于某些原因，我总认为他们该死。也许有些人的罪孽比其他人更轻，但无动于衷是他们共有的罪行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You needed to know there was some morality behind each kill.</Source>
      <Dest>你需要确认每次杀戮背后都有些道德意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Everyday people driven to murder, and your average target never gave two septims about what they'd done.  Some of them even relished it.</Source>
      <Dest>每一天都有人被迫进行杀戮，但你盯上的人对自己的作为却总是不屑一顾。有些人甚至会享受杀戮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You needed to know there was some morality behind each kill.</Source>
      <Dest>你需要确认每次杀戮背后都有些道德意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This attitude, this unfeeling apathy that infects everyone around us, it needed to purged.</Source>
      <Dest>这种态度，这种冷漠无情感染了我们周围每一个人，它必须得到净化。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And I wasn't looking for a milk-drinker, but it looks like I've found one.</Source>
      <Dest>我本来没打算找一个懦夫，但似乎我已经找到了一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then leave the milk-drinker be.</Source>
      <Dest>那就离开那个懦夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who or what is Sithis?</Source>
      <Dest>西帝斯是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Imagine if you will a room of complete darkness. You have a torch in your hands, but there's no light to speak of. </Source>
      <Dest>想象下如果你在一个伸手不见五指的房间里。你手上有支火把，但却找不到任何光明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who or what is Sithis?</Source>
      <Dest>西帝斯是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The entire room is as black and cold as the midnight sky.</Source>
      <Dest>整个房间又黑又冷宛如午夜的天空。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who or what is Sithis?</Source>
      <Dest>西帝斯是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now imagine that darkness reaching out to you. Embracing you into the very void itself.  That's Sithis. </Source>
      <Dest>现在想象黑暗涌向了你。拥抱着你坠入永恒的虚空。这就是西帝斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who or what is Sithis?</Source>
      <Dest>西帝斯是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nothingness and everything all in the same form.</Source>
      <Dest>化为一体的万物和虚无。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're not just any killer.  Takes one to know one.</Source>
      <Dest>你不是简单的杀手。同类能认出彼此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That obvious, huh? Alright. I was once a member of the same organization that hunts me.  The Dark Brotherhood.</Source>
      <Dest>这很明显，哼？好吧。我曾隶属于现在追杀我的组织。暗黑兄弟会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're not just any killer.  Takes one to know one.</Source>
      <Dest>你不是简单的杀手。同类能认出彼此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But to be honest, it's not really a story I like to tell.</Source>
      <Dest>但老实说，我不太喜欢讲这段往事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In the end, it was all you ever wanted.  To kill with conscience.</Source>
      <Dest>最后，这就是你想要的。凭着良心杀人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not entirely.  True, killing criminals and those who deserve it, it was easy, but the easy thing is never satisfying.</Source>
      <Dest>不尽然。确实，杀死那些应得此报应的罪犯易如反掌，但是这样简单的事情从不会令我满足。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In the end, it was all you ever wanted.  To kill with conscience.</Source>
      <Dest>最后，这就是你想要的。凭着良心杀人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do indeed loathe apathy.  In some ways I felt it was the greater crime.  The kind made with a level head.</Source>
      <Dest>我确实痛恨冷漠。我觉得在某种程度上这是更重的罪行。一种由冷静的头脑策划出的罪行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The girl's too trusting for her own good.  What of it?</Source>
      <Dest>那女孩太过信任别人了。是又如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Morrigan said there were people after you.</Source>
      <Dest>茉莉甘说过有人在追你们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah?  And what of it?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？这有什么关系呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Seems to me like you two are being sought after.</Source>
      <Dest>看来你俩一直在被追杀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does the girl know about all of this?</Source>
      <Dest>那个女孩知道这些事情吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No. I've tried to keep her as far in the dark about it all as I can. She's a smart girl, though. I think she's beginning to piece things together.</Source>
      <Dest>不。我用尽一切试图对她隐瞒事实。但她是个聪明的女孩儿。我想她已经开始拼凑出事情的真相了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then I apologize for my intrusion sir.  Good day.</Source>
      <Dest>那么很抱歉打扰到您了先生。祝好运！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're polite. Too polite. As if you got what you came here for, and now you're in a hurry to leave.  </Source>
      <Dest>你很有礼貌，过于礼貌。就像你已经达到了来此的目的，现在想快些脱身。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then I apologize for my intrusion sir.  Good day.</Source>
      <Dest>那么很抱歉打扰到您了先生。祝好运！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who are you?  What are you doing here?  You're not with them, are you? </Source>
      <Dest>你是谁？你来这干什么？你和他们不是一伙的，对吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Maybe I'll ask the child what she thinks about her guardian the killer.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。也许我应该问问那女孩她对她的杀手护卫有什么看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, alright.  Leave her out of this.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，好吧。别让她知道这些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Maybe I'll ask the child what she thinks about her guardian the killer.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。也许我应该问问那女孩她对她的杀手护卫有什么看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As I said, I was once an assassin for the Dark Brotherhood.  One of the best they had.  Only murder wasn't enough for me.</Source>
      <Dest>如我所说，我曾是黑暗兄弟会的刺客。他们中最好的那个。只是我不满足于单调的杀戮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Maybe I'll ask the child what she thinks about her guardian the killer.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。也许我应该问问那女孩她对她的杀手护卫有什么看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When a target is marked, a typical assassin kills without question or remorse.  The murder is efficient.  A transaction.  </Source>
      <Dest>当盯上一个目标时，典型的杀手会不问缘由地把他杀掉。这种谋杀显然很有效率。这就是生意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Maybe I'll ask the child what she thinks about her guardian the killer.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。也许我应该问问那女孩她对她的杀手护卫有什么看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No different than going to the market.  Only I took things a little bit further.</Source>
      <Dest>这与进市场购物无异。只是我做得更进了一步。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Maybe I'll ask the child what she thinks about her guardian the killer.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。也许我应该问问那女孩她对她的杀手护卫有什么看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had what you call a procedure.  I didn't just stalk my targets, I approached them.  I even befriended them.  I needed to know the man I killed.</Source>
      <Dest>只是我有你们所谓的“过程” 。我不是单纯地追踪那些人，我会接近他们。我甚至与他们结交朋友。我需要了解我要杀的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Please?</Source>
      <Dest>请？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I see you're not going to give up until I tell you.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。看来我不说你就不会罢休。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Please?</Source>
      <Dest>请？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was once an assassin for the Dark Brotherhood.  One of the best they had.  Only murder wasn't enough for me.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾是黑暗兄弟会的刺客。他们中最好的那个。只是我不满足于单调的杀戮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Please?</Source>
      <Dest>请？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When a target is marked, a typical assassin kills without question or remorse.  The murder is efficient.  A transaction.  </Source>
      <Dest>当盯上一个目标时，典型的杀手会不问缘由地把他杀掉。这种谋杀显然很有效率。这就是生意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Please?</Source>
      <Dest>请？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No different than going to the market.  Only I took things a little bit further.</Source>
      <Dest>这与进市场购物无异。只是我做得更进了一步。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Please?</Source>
      <Dest>请？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had what you call a procedure.  I didn't just stalk my targets, I approached them.  I even befriended them.  I needed to know the man I killed.</Source>
      <Dest>只是我有你们所谓的“过程” 。我不是单纯地追踪那些人，我会接近他们。我甚至与他们结交朋友。我需要了解我要杀的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wasn't asking for it.</Source>
      <Dest>我没在问这个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You certainly have an odd way of showing that stranger.  Do you also ask for mead when you're not thirsty?</Source>
      <Dest>你说话的方法真是奇怪，陌生人。难道当你不口渴的时候你也会要蜂蜜酒？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maybe you ought to tell me "what" before I lose my patience and kill you both.</Source>
      <Dest>也许你们应该告诉我些什么，在我失去耐心杀掉你们两个之前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you want a fight stranger, I'm more than happy to oblige.  But leave the girl out of it.  She's got no blood on her hands.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你想打架，陌生人，我随时奉陪。但是别把女孩扯进来。她是清白的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you kill the ones who don't realize they're hurting people.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你杀了那些没有意识到正在伤害别人的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, these people and their attitudes disgusted me.  It needed to be purged.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，这些人和他们的态度让我感到恶心。这些都需要被净化。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you kill the ones who don't realize they're hurting people.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你杀了那些没有意识到正在伤害别人的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I gained their trust and offered them drink.  The liquor was a paralysis poison.  Then I bound them and interrogated them until I found it.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我取得他们的信任，再请他们喝一杯。烈酒是很好的麻痹药。然后我把他们捆住，审问他们，直到我得到我想要的答案。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you kill the ones who don't realize they're hurting people.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你杀了那些没有意识到正在伤害别人的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was a game. I asked them to name their killer. They always assumed I was talking about me.</Source>
      <Dest>那是一个游戏，我叫他们说出杀手的名字，但他们总是认为我在说我自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain.</Source>
      <Dest>请解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The bard doesn't care whose ears are bleeding.  The lover is oblivious to the man she's betrayed.  </Source>
      <Dest>吟游诗人毫不在乎听众的耳朵是不是在滴血。出轨的情人对她背叛的男人漠不关心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain.</Source>
      <Dest>请解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These people and their attitudes disgusted me.  It needed to be purged.</Source>
      <Dest>这些人和他们的态度让我感到恶心。它需要被清除。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain.</Source>
      <Dest>请解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I gained their trust and offered them drink.  The liquor was a paralysis poison.  Then I bound them and interrogated them until I found it.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我取得他们的信任，再请他们喝一杯。烈酒是很好的麻痹药。然后我把他们捆住，审问他们，直到我得到我想要的答案。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain.</Source>
      <Dest>请解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was a game. I asked them to name their killer. They always assumed I was talking about me.</Source>
      <Dest>那是一个游戏，我叫他们说出杀手的名字，但他们总是认为我在说我自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds to me like a ritual.</Source>
      <Dest>在我听来像个仪式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hate that word.  Makes it sound religious or something.  It was a procedure.  A potion for the conscience.</Source>
      <Dest>我讨厌这个词。听起来像是宗教之类的。这是一个过程。一剂给良知的药。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds to me like a ritual.</Source>
      <Dest>在我听来像个仪式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dark Brotherhood isn't about good and evil.  You'll find in this world, people want others dead for the most trivial of reasons.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗的兄弟无关善恶。你会发现在这个世界上，人们会为了一个最微不足道的原因而想置他人于死地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds to me like a ritual.</Source>
      <Dest>在我听来像个仪式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're a bard who sings off key?  You're dead.  You jilted a lover?  Buy a headstone.  Looked at someone the wrong way?  Maggot food.</Source>
      <Dest>你是个唱歌跑调的吟游诗人？你死定了。你抛弃了情人？墓碑自备。看别人的眼神不对了？杀掉养蛆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds to me like a ritual.</Source>
      <Dest>在我听来像个仪式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can't try to justify the reasons because the reasons are moronic. But if I got to know them, I could always find it. My reason. The apathy.</Source>
      <Dest>你不可能正当化那些理由，因为那些理由是如此愚蠢。但如果我了解了他们，我就总能找到理由。我自己的理由。冷漠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She does seem to idolize you a lot.</Source>
      <Dest>看来她对你崇拜极了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I try not to read too much into in it.  Children get attached easily.  Stay here long enough and she'll probably begin to idolize you.</Source>
      <Dest>我会当作没听懂这句话。孩子总是容易被吸引。在这里呆久一些，她也会崇拜你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's better if you just tell the truth. Who's after you?</Source>
      <Dest>你最好说实话。是谁在找你们？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dark Brotherhood. They're after us. Her and me.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗兄弟会。他们在找我们。找我和她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Dark Brotherhood is not what it once was. Perhaps you can escape.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗兄弟会已经不复当年。也许你能逃脱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It isn't just the Dark Brotherhood.  The one who pursues me is Sithis.  I broke a tenet, and in doing so betrayed him.</Source>
      <Dest>不单单是暗黑兄弟会。是西帝斯在追杀我。我违背了教条，因而我背叛了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Dark Brotherhood is not what it once was. Perhaps you can escape.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗兄弟会已经不复当年。也许你能逃脱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now every night I am left to face his wrath.</Source>
      <Dest>现在每天晚上我都得留下来面对他的愤怒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A good one.</Source>
      <Dest>一个好父亲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh. Maybe you're right.  But there will come a time when it's safer for us to be apart.</Source>
      <Dest>啊。也许你是对的。但总有一天我们分道扬镳反而会对彼此更好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Meaning, you were going to kill her.</Source>
      <Dest>这意味着，你将要去干掉她。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tracking her down was easy. She was staying in some bunkhouse near the Jarl's Keep.</Source>
      <Dest>跟踪她不是件难事。她一直住在领主要塞附近的一些工棚里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Meaning, you were going to kill her.</Source>
      <Dest>这意味着，你将要去干掉她。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She wasn't a harlot. She wasn't even a woman. She was just a girl.</Source>
      <Dest>她不是个妓女，甚至连女人都不是。她只是个小女孩儿。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Meaning, you were going to kill her.</Source>
      <Dest>这意味着，你将要去干掉她。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Inside her wasn't apathy.  It was innocence.  The child wasn't even old enough to understand love.</Source>
      <Dest>她的内心不是冷漠。而是天真。这孩子甚至没有成长到足够明白什么是爱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Meaning, you were going to kill her.</Source>
      <Dest>这意味着，你将要去干掉她。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At first I thought there must have been mistake. Only when I confronted the man he confirmed her identity. The sick bastard was in love with a child.</Source>
      <Dest>一开始我以为搞错了。直到我找到那个男人，他确认了她的身份。那恶心的混账居然搞上了一个孩子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Meaning, you were going to kill her.</Source>
      <Dest>这意味着，你将要去干掉她。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so that night I killed a mortal not for apathy, but for passion, and took the child from Honorhall.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我不是由于他的冷漠，而是他的肉欲，杀了他。然后我带着那孩子离开了荣耀厅孤儿院。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you find her?</Source>
      <Dest>那你是怎么找到她的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tracking her down was easy. She was staying in some bunkhouse near the Jarl's Keep.</Source>
      <Dest>跟踪她不是件难事。她一直住在领主要塞附近的一些工棚里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you find her?</Source>
      <Dest>那你是怎么找到她的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She wasn't a harlot. She wasn't even a woman. She was just a girl.</Source>
      <Dest>她不是个妓女，甚至连女人都不是。她只是个小女孩儿。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you find her?</Source>
      <Dest>那你是怎么找到她的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Inside her wasn't apathy.  It was innocence.  The child wasn't even old enough to understand love.</Source>
      <Dest>她的内心不是冷漠。而是天真。这孩子甚至没有成长到足够明白什么是爱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you find her?</Source>
      <Dest>那你是怎么找到她的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At first I thought there must have been mistake. Only when I confronted the man he confirmed her identity. The sick bastard was in love with a child.</Source>
      <Dest>一开始我以为搞错了。直到我找到那个男人，他确认了她的身份。那恶心的混账居然搞上了一个孩子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you find her?</Source>
      <Dest>那你是怎么找到她的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so that night I killed a mortal not for apathy, but for passion, and took the child from Honorhall.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我不是由于他的冷漠，而是他的肉欲，杀了他。然后我带着那孩子离开了荣耀厅孤儿院。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does the girl fit in to all of this?</Source>
      <Dest>这女孩是怎么卷进这一切中去的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One night, we received word of a man performing the black sacrament in the Riften Ratway. </Source>
      <Dest>某个晚上，我们收到了在裂谷城鼠道中进行黑暗仪式的某个人所发来的消息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does the girl fit in to all of this?</Source>
      <Dest>这女孩是怎么卷进这一切中去的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was to arrange a meeting with him to get information on the target.</Source>
      <Dest>为了得到关于目标的更多信息，我安排与他进行了一场会面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does the girl fit in to all of this?</Source>
      <Dest>这女孩是怎么卷进这一切中去的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The man told me a story of a harlot who had taken everything from him. He wanted her to know the pain and anguish she caused him.</Source>
      <Dest>这个男人告诉了我一个关于夺走他一切的妓女的故事。他想让她知道她给他造成的痛苦和心酸。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does the girl fit in to all of this?</Source>
      <Dest>这女孩是怎么卷进这一切中去的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Another jilted lover, I thought. Another uncaring woman.  My specialty.  So I accepted the contract on behalf of the Brotherhood.</Source>
      <Dest>又一个无情的情人，我想。又一个不长心的女人。我的专长。所以我代表黑暗兄弟会接受了这个契约。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not adopt the child yourself?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你不自己领养那个孩子？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll admit I have grown fond of her. Despite all that's happened, she can still make me laugh.</Source>
      <Dest>我要承认我越来越喜欢她了。尽管发生了这么多事情，她还是能让我笑得出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not adopt the child yourself?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你不自己领养那个孩子？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My time with her has made me rethink my purpose in life. Perhaps I wasn't meant to be a killer, after all.</Source>
      <Dest>我和她相处的日子促使我反思人生的意义。毕竟，也许我本不想成为一名杀手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not adopt the child yourself?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你不自己领养那个孩子？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She even has the same dark hair and pale skin, like me...</Source>
      <Dest>她甚至有同样乌黑的头发，苍白的皮肤，像我一样……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not adopt the child yourself?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你不自己领养那个孩子？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She could even pass off as my real daughter. But what kind of father could I possibly be? </Source>
      <Dest>她甚至可以被当作是我的女儿。但我又能是怎样的父亲呢？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you had a motive, but not the means.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你有动机，但是没手段。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was just a boy.  My anger alone would never be enough to kill a noble.  I performed the Black Sacrament, but the Brotherhood never answered.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是个男孩。仅凭一腔怒火不可能杀掉一个贵族。我举行了黑暗圣礼，但兄弟会却从未回应我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you had a motive, but not the means.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你有动机，但是没手段。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I knew then that I was truly alone. And if I wanted vengeance, I had to do it myself.  </Source>
      <Dest>我知道自己已经真真正正的孑然一身了。如果我要复仇，我要自己去做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you had a motive, but not the means.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你有动机，但是没手段。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gabania was beyond my reach.  But that guard.  The one whose face was burned into my memory.  That was a man I could kill.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经找不到卡贝尼亚了，但我能找到那个守卫。那张脸已经深深地烙在了我的脑海里。那是我不共戴天的仇人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you had a motive, but not the means.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你有动机，但是没手段。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I pulled the sword from my own father's belly and watched him spill all over the ground.</Source>
      <Dest>我把剑从父亲的腹部拔了出来，看着他的血流满一地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you had a motive, but not the means.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你有动机，但是没手段。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I kept that sword as a reminder.  The blood had dried and crusted over the blade, but I never bothered to polish it.</Source>
      <Dest>我把那把剑当做一个警醒。血已经干了，剑锋也生锈了，但我从来也不去磨光它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't blame you, considering what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>考虑到发生了这样的事，我不怪你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I was just a boy.  My anger alone would never be enough to kill a noble.  I performed the Black Sacrament, but the Brotherhood never answered.</Source>
      <Dest>然而我那时只是个男孩。仅凭一腔怒火不可能杀掉一个贵族。我举行了黑暗圣礼，但兄弟会却从未回应我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't blame you, considering what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>考虑到发生了这样的事，我不怪你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I knew then that I was truly alone.  And if I wanted vengeance, I had to do it myself.  </Source>
      <Dest>我知道自己已经真真正正的孑然一身了。如果我要复仇，我要自己去做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't blame you, considering what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>考虑到发生了这样的事，我不怪你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gabania was beyond my reach.  But that guard.  The one whose face was burned into my memory.  That was a man I could kill.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经找不到卡贝尼亚了，但我能找到那个守卫。那张脸已经深深地烙在了我的脑海里。那是我不共戴天的仇人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't blame you, considering what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>考虑到发生了这样的事，我不怪你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I pulled the sword from my own father's belly and watched him spill all over the ground.</Source>
      <Dest>我把剑从父亲的腹部拔了出来，看着他的血流满一地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't blame you, considering what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>考虑到发生了这样的事，我不怪你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I kept that sword as a reminder.  The blood had dried and crusted over the blade, but I never bothered to polish it.</Source>
      <Dest>我把那把剑当做一个警醒。血已经干了，剑锋也生锈了，但我从来也不去磨光它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after they killed your family?</Source>
      <Dest>他们杀死你的家人之后呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They razed the town. Gabania really just wanted the land and the peasants cleared. When his lot forced themselves on the women, it was just for fun.</Source>
      <Dest>他们把这个小镇夷为了平地。卡贝尼亚只是想要这片土地并想清理这些农民。而当他的手下胁迫那些妇女时，却只是为了娱乐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after they killed your family?</Source>
      <Dest>他们杀死你的家人之后呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, not forced.  Toyed with them, defiled them, and murdered their spirit.  And when they killed them all they...they just left me there to watch.</Source>
      <Dest>不，不只是胁迫。玩弄她们，玷污她们，毁灭她们的意志。当他们把她们全杀了的时候……他们只是留我在那儿看着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after they killed your family?</Source>
      <Dest>他们杀死你的家人之后呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mourned them for days. But my mourning quickly turned to anger. I thirsted for revenge.</Source>
      <Dest>我为他们悲痛了好几天。但是我的悲痛很快变成了愤怒，我渴望复仇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't have to be so rude.</Source>
      <Dest>你没必要这么粗鲁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't have to be.  I need to be.  Leave us.</Source>
      <Dest>不是必要，而是需要。离开这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There wasn't a drop of emotion in that face. That's what I remember most from that night.  Not the murder or the rape or the screams.</Source>
      <Dest>在那张脸上没有一丝表情。这就是那个夜晚我记得最清楚的。而不是谋杀、强奸或尖叫声。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some call it the right of first night. As if men in power need to justify their rape with laws.  No, they just took what they wanted.</Source>
      <Dest>有人称那是“初夜权”。就好像手握权势的人就可以利用法律让强奸变得合理。不，他们只是在为所欲为。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some call it the right of first night. As if men in power need to justify their rape with laws.  No, they just took what they wanted.</Source>
      <Dest>有人称那是“初夜权”。就好像手握权势的人可以利用法律让强奸变得合理。不，他们只是在为所欲为。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My mother pleaded for mercy, my father reached for his axe. When one of the guards gutted him, all anyone could do was weep.</Source>
      <Dest>我的母亲不停地求饶，而父亲起身去拿他的斧头。当一个警卫把他开膛破肚的时候，我们唯一能做到的只是哭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Two of Gabania's men were dragging my sister into the cottage when they passed me by. One of them turned to look at me, and our eyes met.</Source>
      <Dest>当两个卡贝尼亚的人把我姐姐拖进小屋的时候，他们与我擦肩而过。其中的一个看了我一眼，我们的眼神交汇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was about five years older than Morrigan, and promised to marry.</Source>
      <Dest>她比茉莉甘大5岁, 已经许人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was the day of her wedding when Lord Gabania's men came riding into the field.  </Source>
      <Dest>在她结婚的那天，卡贝尼亚领主的士兵闯进了领地。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll never forget the way their horses grunted and seethed, as if ready for war. Then the nobleman descended from his horse, and made his demands.</Source>
      <Dest>我永远忘不了他们的战马嘶鸣奔腾，准备作战的样子。然后那个贵族跳下他的马，提出了他的要求。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take care.</Source>
      <Dest>多保重。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Shadow hide you.</Source>
      <Dest>愿阴影庇佑你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah?</Source>
      <Dest>啊?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd like that.</Source>
      <Dest>我……希望我能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd like that.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢这个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Sorry, but I'm a little too old for you.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑）抱歉，但是我对于你老说有点太老了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They wear it to tell people they want to get married.  </Source>
      <Dest>他们戴上它，以此告诉人们他们想要结婚。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
