<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm an adult and I killed her. A child told me to do it.</Source>
      <Dest>作为一个成年人，我杀了她。一个小孩让我这么干的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm an adult and I killed her. A child told me to do it.</Source>
      <Dest>作为一个成年人，我杀了她。一个小孩让我这么干的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any stories from your days in the Orphanage?</Source>
      <Dest>说说你在孤儿院时候的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry. I swear on Grelod's life she will be just fine.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心。我拿桂罗的命发誓，她会很好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you're another pilgrim on your way to High Hrothgar.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜你是另一个在前往高吼峰上的朝圣者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting stories from your travels?</Source>
      <Dest>您的旅行有沒有一些有趣的事?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting stories from your travels?</Source>
      <Dest>您的旅行有沒有一些有趣的事?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She had been beaten and tortured, yet through it all she faces those who greet her with dignity and pride.  </Source>
      <Dest>她一直被殴打和折磨着，但当这一切过去后，她找到了那些会对她尊敬和自豪的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The air is thicker than a Jarl's waistline, and the wind rumbles like the breath of a dragon.  </Source>
      <Dest>那气氛就好比贵族的腰围一般粗厚，那阵风也好像巨龙的气息一样隆隆地响。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have a few, if you'll indulge me. In my journeys to the north, for instance, I found a palace with domes painted like the night sky.</Source>
      <Dest>有些吧，如果你会容许我的话。比如说，在我到北方的旅途中，发现了一个宫殿。殿中的穹顶画得如同夜空一般。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I guess that's why they call it "ole" Rorikstead.  Must have had another name, unless the song isn't as old as I think. </Source>
      <Dest>我想这就是为什么他们会叫这个城镇做"古"洛利克镇。它一定有别的名字，除非这首歌不如我想像中那么古老。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That doesn't raise my confidence, but I suppose we all have our own fate.  Good luck, traveler.  May all your adventures be worthy of a song.</Source>
      <Dest>你这句话并没有给予我更大的信心，但我想我们每个人都有自己的命运吧。祝你好运，旅行者。愿您的冒险精彩得可换来一首赞歌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Either way, I have enjoyed our talk.  May you craft your own stories as you continue your travels.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样，我很高兴和你聊天。希望你在之后的旅途中创造出属于自己的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In the end, I'm thankful the guard didn't turn me in right then.  How foolish a child I was, to think I could convince an adult to commit murder.</Source>
      <Dest>最终，我很感激那名守卫没有举报我。多么地愚蠢，我在想我一个小孩可以说服一个成年人去谋杀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Inside one of the cells is the most beautiful damsel you will ever lay your eyes upon, but her voice is dirty with pain.</Source>
      <Dest>在一个房间内有一个你永远都不想闭上眼，永远直视着，最美丽的少女，但她的话却是狠毒得像带刺一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Names do not make a city, and they do not make the man.</Source>
      <Dest>名字无法成就一座城市，也不会成就一个男人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To the west, at the source of a river, I found a mast jutting out from the surface.  If I knew how to swim, I'd see what's attached to it.</Source>
      <Dest>在西边，我在一条河流的源头处见到一枝桅杆从河面上伸出来。如果我懂得游泳，我真想看看它到底是连接着些什么东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then a voice came cutting through the silence. It said, "You can shoot him in the neck, but he won't bleed. The blood's all below the waist!"</Source>
      <Dest>这时，一把声音打破了沉默。它说："你可以射他的脖子，但他可不会流血。他的血全都流到去跨下了。"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was lost in the clutches of night, with only the blood moon to guide me. That is, until I saw a fire and a circle of tents tucked below the rock.</Source>
      <Dest>我在黑夜的魔掌中迷了路，只剩下血红色的月亮引导着我。直到我看到了在岩石縫隙之下的营火与帐篷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Does it describe the dampness of the air as it wafts in from the canals, or the leaves that roll down the sky like autumn tears?</Source>
      <Dest>难道名字能形容那些从河道那里吹来的湿气，或者那些像天空落泪般随风帘卷的秋叶？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then let's hold off on the drinks, lest we both end up in bed with Spriggans.</Source>
      <Dest>我们晚点再喝这些酒吧，免得醉醒后发现我们和树精上床了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha! You are either a very funny person, or a very disturbed one.  I dare not ask which.  </Source>
      <Dest>哈！你要不是一个有趣的人，就是个令人烦厌的家伙。嘿！你不用回答我你是哪一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was wrong of you, but what's done is done, and it makes for a good story.</Source>
      <Dest>那是你的错，但那已过去了，况且它成就了一个好故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is the orphanage why you left Riften?</Source>
      <Dest>是因为孤儿院让你想离开裂谷城？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You think fighting a Hagraven's scary, try being engaged to one.</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得跟乌鸦鬼婆打斗是件恐怖的事，那试试看跟她们一战再说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You think fighting a Hagraven's scary, try being engaged to one.</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得跟乌鸦鬼婆打斗是件恐怖的事，那试试看跟她们一战再说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It looks emptier in here.</Source>
      <Dest>似乎这里更干净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It looks emptier in here.</Source>
      <Dest>似乎这里更干净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've been to the orphanage. Quaint little place.</Source>
      <Dest>我去过孤儿院。古色古香的小地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've been to the orphanage. Quaint little place.</Source>
      <Dest>我去过孤儿院。古色古香的小地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can I help you?</Source>
      <Dest>我能为你效劳吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps someone finally gave him an answer.  Sometimes the right answers are the wrong ones.</Source>
      <Dest>也许有人最终给他一个答案了吧。有些时候错误的答案可能就是最终的正确答案。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hail.</Source>
      <Dest>万岁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're right. I have enjoyed our talk. May you craft your own stories as you continue your travels.</Source>
      <Dest>你说得对。我很享受和你聊天。也许你在继续你的旅途的时候，可以写一个你自己的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Safe travels.</Source>
      <Dest>旅途安全。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, you know the funny Khajiit fellow who liked to count the steps?  We found him dead the other day.  Took his own life.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，你知道那有趣而且喜欢跟踪人的虎人家伙么?  后来我们发现他死了. 就是栽这上面了吧.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可以的理由，是他被迫留在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until next we meet.</Source>
      <Dest>下次再见。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
