<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You fought gallantly, adventurer. I must now return to Cheydinhal. The Countess will be pleased to know the Knight-Commander is well.</Source>
      <Dest>You fought gallantly, adventurer. I must now return to Cheydinhal. The Countess will be pleased to know the Knight-Commander is well.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry. I'm ready to face whatever comes.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心。我已经准备好面对要发生的一切了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have no doubt you are, and with the Knight-Commander guarding our rear flank, our defense is practically impenetrable.</Source>
      <Dest>我不怀疑你的身份，有了骑士长监视着我们的侧翼，我们的防御是牢不可破的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry. I'm ready to face whatever comes.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心。我已经准备好面对要发生的一切了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you again for convincing him to join the fight. I believe he asked to speak with you. You'll find him up there on the hillside.</Source>
      <Dest>我衷心的感谢你再一次信任他，并为他加入那场战斗。我想他应该有话要和你说。你可以在那边的山坡上找到他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I slept well, but I should have been here to help.</Source>
      <Dest>我睡得很好，但我应该过来帮忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, spoken like a true Knight of the Rose. With you and the return of the Knight-Commander, it seems the reports of chivalry's death were premature.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，说的真的跟护花使者一样。那么骑士教条和你一起回归了, 似乎关于骑士精神之死的报告还是言之过早的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I slept well, but I should have been here to help.</Source>
      <Dest>我睡得很好，但我应该过来帮忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you again for convincing him to join the fight. I believe he asked to speak with you. You'll find him up there on the hillside.</Source>
      <Dest>我衷心的感谢你再一次信任他，并为他加入那场战斗。我想他应该有话要和你说。你可以在那边的山坡上找到他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The bed was cold and uncomfortable, but I managed.</Source>
      <Dest>那床又冷又硬，不过我挺过去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) That's Nord hospitality for you, but it has its charm. The Knight-Commander seems to enjoy it though.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 那是诺德人的待客之道，你会发现它的魅力的。你看，骑士队长就很享受。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The bed was cold and uncomfortable, but I managed.</Source>
      <Dest>那床又冷又硬，不过我挺过去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He's up on the hill, guarding our rear flank by his lonesome. In fact, I believed he asked for you, but he didn't wish to disturb your slumber.</Source>
      <Dest>躺在床上的时候他一定以为自己正孤军奋战为我们殿后呢。哦不过老实说，我猜他肯定想找你帮忙，但又怕搅了你的清梦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Never mind that. How are the preparations?</Source>
      <Dest>别介意。准备的怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As well as can be expected. The Knight-Commander insisted he guard the rear flank. That leaves every available body to guard our front.</Source>
      <Dest>值得期待的是，骑士队长决定去守住退路，这样所有的有生力量都能拉到正面去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Never mind that. How are the preparations?</Source>
      <Dest>别介意。准备的怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you again for convincing him to join the fight. I believe he asked to speak with you. You'll find him up there on the hillside.</Source>
      <Dest>我衷心的感谢你再一次信任他，并为他加入那场战斗。我想他应该有话要和你说。你可以在那边的山坡上找到他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All that stuff just gets in the way. Better to have them focus on training.</Source>
      <Dest>所有的事情已经在掌握当中，现在最好让他们集中精力在训练上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Understood. Fortunately, it seems this village is not without a few capable fighters. As for the children, they should be escorted to the mine.</Source>
      <Dest>明白了。很不幸，这座村子里已经有些好斗士了。而对于孩子们来说，他们应该被送到矿里去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Barricades will slow their charge, and give us time for strategic adjustments.</Source>
      <Dest>路障会放慢它们的攻击，并给我们时间进行战略性的调整。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Indeed. More importantly, it will allow us to divert most of our defense to the rear flank, which is our most vulnerable point of entry.</Source>
      <Dest>的确。 重要的是那可使我们把兵力转移到最近的侧面， 那地方是我们最易受攻击的入口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Traps. Bandits charge ahead, and barricades are worthless without archers.</Source>
      <Dest>陷阱。强盗们攻过来了，那些路障在没有弓箭手的情况下完全就是摆设。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I see you know a bit about military strategy. True enough. I will teach the miners how to fashion bear traps.</Source>
      <Dest>I see you know a bit about military strategy. True enough. I will teach the miners how to fashion bear traps.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm afraid the Knight-Commander is a hopeless drunk. We can't count on him.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得骑士长是个无可救药的醉汉，我们不能指望他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, so you wager that the darkness in his soul outweighs the light. I cannot disagree more.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，所以你担保他灵魂中的黑暗面远远超过光明。我也这么想。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm afraid the Knight-Commander is a hopeless drunk. We can't count on him.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得骑士长是个无可救药的醉汉，我们不能指望他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, I fear my presence only reminds him of the past, and prevents him from shedding the shame of his exile.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我害怕我的存在只会让他想起过去，成为他从流亡的耻辱中解脱出来的绊脚石。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm afraid the Knight-Commander is a hopeless drunk. We can't count on him.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得骑士长是个无可救药的醉汉，我们不能指望他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you would speak with him, perhaps somewhere in that field of gloom you will find a stray petal of white.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你想跟他说话,也许在某个黑暗的角落,你会发现一只飘落的花瓣白色。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll try convincing Erevan to aid the townsfolk.</Source>
      <Dest>我会试着说服艾里温去帮助市民们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Would you? I appreciate your assistance. I fear my presence only serves to remind him of what he has lost.</Source>
      <Dest>是吗？我很感谢你的协助。但是恐怕我的存在，只会提醒他，他曾经失去了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you fear 3 bandits, then the Order of the Rose is truly worthless.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你连3个强盗都怕，那么玫瑰教团也太没用了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>On the contrary, a Knight of the Rose is trained to take on as many as seven warriors by his lonesome.</Source>
      <Dest>正相反，一名玫瑰骑士被训练为只身一人就有着七名以上的战士的战斗力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you fear 3 bandits, then the Order of the Rose is truly worthless.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你连3个强盗都怕，那么玫瑰教团也太没用了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, that would only make the townsfolk more reliant on outsiders, and bury their own heroism under a veneer of shame.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，这只会让他们更加依赖于外人，并将自己的英雄气概埋葬于耻辱的表象之下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you fear 3 bandits, then the Order of the Rose is truly worthless.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你连3个强盗都怕，那么玫瑰教团也太没用了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's the Knight-Commander who taught me that one can inspire in defeat as well as in victory. If only he could be reminded of his own words.</Source>
      <Dest>It's the Knight-Commander who taught me that one can inspire in defeat as well as in victory. If only he could be reminded of his own words.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I reckon you could have vanquished them without much help.</Source>
      <Dest>我估计你本来可以无需多少帮助就征服他们</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's true, in the Order we often train against multiple combatants.</Source>
      <Dest>我确实可以。在教团里我们经常进行一对多的战斗训练。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I reckon you could have vanquished them without much help.</Source>
      <Dest>我估计你本来可以无需多少帮助就征服他们</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, to say I could vanquish all three would diminish the heroism of you and the townsfolk.</Source>
      <Dest>不过，要是说我就能解决那三个，就会贬低你和村民们的英勇事迹啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I reckon you could have vanquished them without much help.</Source>
      <Dest>我估计你本来可以无需多少帮助就征服他们</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's the Knight-Commander who taught me that one can inspire in defeat as well as in victory. If only he could be reminded of his own words.</Source>
      <Dest>It's the Knight-Commander who taught me that one can inspire in defeat as well as in victory. If only he could be reminded of his own words.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your actions were brave, and your faith rewarded.</Source>
      <Dest>你的行为很英勇，你的信念也值得褒奖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your words do me great honor, but on this day it is you and the people of Kynesgrove that are the true heroes.</Source>
      <Dest>你的赞美让我无比荣幸, 但在这段时间以来只有你和基耐森林的人民才是真正的英雄.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your actions were brave, and your faith rewarded.</Source>
      <Dest>你的行为很英勇，你的信念也值得褒奖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I merely provided the impetus for your heroism. The ember that lit the heart of justice aflame.</Source>
      <Dest>我仅仅为你的英雄品质提供了动力。余烬照亮那燃烧的正义之心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your actions were brave, and your faith rewarded.</Source>
      <Dest>你的行为很英勇，你的信念也值得褒奖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's the Knight-Commander who taught me that one can inspire in defeat as well as in victory. If only he could be reminded of his own words.</Source>
      <Dest>It's the Knight-Commander who taught me that one can inspire in defeat as well as in victory. If only he could be reminded of his own words.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was a risky gambit.</Source>
      <Dest>那可真是一招险棋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not at all, sera. For I have wagered on the mortal soul countless times, knowing that the scales always tip toward the righteous.</Source>
      <Dest>一点也不，先生。因为我在无数次对凡人人性的赌局中了解到：心灵的天平总会向公正倾斜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was a risky gambit.</Source>
      <Dest>那可真是一招险棋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I believe the same is true of the Knight-Commander. Perhaps this will be the cause that restores his memory.</Source>
      <Dest>我相信骑士指挥官也是如此。或许这能帮他恢复记忆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You fool. When the bandits realize what happened, they'll return with an army.</Source>
      <Dest>你个傻瓜！等到强盗们发现了事情的真相，回来的时候会带上一个军队的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Undoubtedly. However, we will have ample time to prepare for their assault.</Source>
      <Dest>毫无疑问。但是，我们也有足够的时间来为他们的攻击做准备。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You fool. When the bandits realize what happened, they'll return with an army.</Source>
      <Dest>你个傻瓜！等到强盗们发现了事情的真相，回来的时候会带上一个军队的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If we can somehow convince the Knight-Commander to join us, our victory is all but guaranteed.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我们能用某种方法说服骑士指挥官加入我们的话，我们的胜利就十拿九稳了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think he's happier now. You should try a bit of debauchery yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>我想他现在快乐多了。你应试着多放纵自己一点才好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is best for some is not best for all. The Knight-Commander prided himself on his conduct.</Source>
      <Dest>对某物来说最好的，并不意味着对所有的都是最好的。骑士指挥官对他的行为感到自豪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think he's happier now. You should try a bit of debauchery yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>我想他现在快乐多了。你应试着多放纵自己一点才好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As I have always fashioned myself in his image, I have no desire to stain my armor in pursuit of such transient comforts.</Source>
      <Dest>鉴于在他的印象中我已经把自己打扮的够时髦了，我也懒得再为一时的高兴来给我的盔甲染色了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think he's happier now. You should try a bit of debauchery yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>我想他现在快乐多了。你应试着多放纵自己一点才好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My fear is that the Knight-Commander feels he is already stained, and that gives him an excuse to act below his own standards.</Source>
      <Dest>我所担心的是骑士长发现自己已经被玷污了，这给他了一个借口来掩饰他的办事不利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think you can prove his innocence?</Source>
      <Dest>你以为你能证明他的清白？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) It is unlikely I can do much of anything.</Source>
      <Dest>（叹气）很不幸我没法做多少事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think you can prove his innocence?</Source>
      <Dest>你以为你能证明他的清白？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet the Countess begged me to investigate the matter in secret, and to check on the Knight-Commander's well-being.</Source>
      <Dest>然而伯爵夫人乞求我偷偷调查这件事，让我去看看骑士指挥官是否幸福。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think you can prove his innocence?</Source>
      <Dest>你以为你能证明他的清白？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems I will have dismal news to report on both fronts.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来我会报道这两方面的阴暗新闻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would rather be known as the Knight of Thorns than some milk-drinking rose.</Source>
      <Dest>比起乳臭未干的玫瑰花，我更愿意被称为荆棘骑士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is best for some is not best for all. The Knight-Commander prided himself on his conduct.</Source>
      <Dest>对某物来说最好的，并不意味着对所有的都是最好的。骑士指挥官对他的行为感到自豪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would rather be known as the Knight of Thorns than some milk-drinking rose.</Source>
      <Dest>比起乳臭未干的玫瑰花，我更愿意被称为荆棘骑士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You, on the other hand, have much to learn about chivalry. I suggest you stay away from this inn, lest you influence him further.</Source>
      <Dest>不过从另一方面来说，你对骑士精神也还知之甚少。我建议你离这座旅馆远一点儿，以免再影响他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If he wishes to remain in exile, you do him no favors by bringing up the past.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他想继续流浪，你仅仅提及过去对他毫无影响。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) Yes, he insists on acting out of character because he believes such actions are noble.</Source>
      <Dest>(叹气)是啊，他坚持扮演那个角色是因为他相信这样的行为是高尚的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If he wishes to remain in exile, you do him no favors by bringing up the past.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他想继续流浪，你仅仅提及过去对他毫无影响。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If he were to profess his innocence, such a scandal would not only divide the public, but damage the credibility of the court.</Source>
      <Dest>若他还要继续表明他的无知，那这样的丑闻不仅会让公众失望，还会使法庭的信用受损。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If he wishes to remain in exile, you do him no favors by bringing up the past.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他想继续流浪，你仅仅提及过去对他毫无影响。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why we must find undeniable proof of his innocence! But I admit, at this point, I am grasping at straws.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是为什么我们必须找到能证明他无罪的证据！但我承认，在这一点上，我其实是孤注一掷了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Knight-Commander has been pleasant company. I prefer him this way.</Source>
      <Dest>那个骑士指挥官挺好相处的，我选择站在他那边。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alas, I have heard  there are many in this province who conduct themselves in such a manner. However, it is not befitting a Knight of the Rose.</Source>
      <Dest>唉，我听说这个省有很多家伙就是如此为人处世的。无论如何，这不适合玫瑰骑士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Knight-Commander has been pleasant company. I prefer him this way.</Source>
      <Dest>那个骑士指挥官挺好相处的，我选择站在他那边。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And despite his protests, in my eyes he is still our commander. </Source>
      <Dest>虽然他反对，但在我眼里他仍然是我们的指挥官。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is a shame that he will forever be known as the Knight of Thorns, and not the White Rose of legend.</Source>
      <Dest>作为索恩的骑士而非传奇白玫瑰被大家所铭记就是个耻辱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you for your assistance. Your skill in battle is praiseworthy. However, we were not alone.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你的帮助。 你的战斗技能值得称赞。无论如何，我们并不孤单。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you can see, the townsfolk are ready to defend Kynesgrove. They simply require someone to lead them.</Source>
      <Dest>As you can see, the townsfolk are ready to defend Kynesgrove. They simply require someone to lead them.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is for that reason I risked taking on three bandits, knowing that mortals are inherently virtuous, and that reinforcements would soon arrive.</Source>
      <Dest>就是因为这个原因我才能与三个强盗相对抗，我知道人性本善，并且援军也快来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No luck, I see. (Sigh) I am still hopeful the Knight-Commander will join us, but for now, we need to prepare without him.</Source>
      <Dest>并不幸运，我知道。（叹气）我仍然指望骑士首领能加入我们，但就现在而言，我们需要做没有他的打算。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have recruited some of the townsfolk to help build a few rudimentary defenses, although we only have so much time.</Source>
      <Dest>我招募了一些镇民来帮忙建立一些基本的防御工事，虽然我们有很多时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wanted to get your opinion, before we begin. Do you think it would be wiser to construct barricades or traps?</Source>
      <Dest>我想听听你的意见，然后再开始。你觉得做点路障或者陷阱是不是比较保险？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I trust you had a good sleep?</Source>
      <Dest>我相信你睡的还不错？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your recollections of the night the Countess was assaulted?</Source>
      <Dest>伯爵夫人遇袭的那晚的事你能记起什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We were fast asleep at the Lodge when it happened.</Source>
      <Dest>那时候我们正在小屋里呼呼大睡呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your recollections of the night the Countess was assaulted?</Source>
      <Dest>伯爵夫人遇袭的那晚的事你能记起什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The guards claim he approached them that night, indicating he had trouble sleeping, and asked if he could relieve them of their posts.</Source>
      <Dest>The guards claim he approached them that night, indicating he had trouble sleeping, and asked if he could relieve them of their posts.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your recollections of the night the Countess was assaulted?</Source>
      <Dest>伯爵夫人遇袭的那晚的事你能记起什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The assault occurred about an hour later, with the guards at the tavern, by a knight in white armor. Only the Steward witnessed the attack.</Source>
      <Dest>袭击发生在大约一个小时后，一个穿着白色铠甲的骑士与守卫在小酒馆发生了冲突。只有管​​家目击了这场袭击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your recollections of the night the Countess was assaulted?</Source>
      <Dest>伯爵夫人遇袭的那晚的事你能记起什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>None of us believed it. The Knight-Commander would not act so recklessly. However, the armor the assailant wore was indeed his.</Source>
      <Dest>那个骑士指挥官居然表现得如此不计后果，这让我们都难以相信。不过，那个袭击者穿得确实与其身份相符。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your recollections of the night the Countess was assaulted?</Source>
      <Dest>伯爵夫人遇袭的那晚的事你能记起什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was no mistaking the blood that covered its breastplate when we found it the next morning.</Source>
      <Dest>毫无疑问，当我们隔天早上发现它的时候，鲜血会覆盖它的胸甲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about Erevan.</Source>
      <Dest>跟讲讲艾里温的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They called him the White Rose. In the Order, there are those who have flawless technique, and those who simply get results.</Source>
      <Dest>他们称他为白玫瑰. 按照惯例, 这通常是那些拥有完美技巧的人们所得到的惠赠.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about Erevan.</Source>
      <Dest>跟讲讲艾里温的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With the Knight-Commander, it was more than just his skill with the blade. It was the elegance with which he wielded it.</Source>
      <Dest>身为领骑士，不仅要精于剑术，亦要于手持兵器时表现出相应的优雅风范。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about Erevan.</Source>
      <Dest>跟讲讲艾里温的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every movement was poetry, like a dance of swords. Not only that, but it carried over into everything he did.</Source>
      <Dest>每一个动作都蕴含着诗韵，就像是在刀光剑影中沉着的舞蹈。不止如此，他做每件事都带有着这种味道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about Erevan.</Source>
      <Dest>跟讲讲艾里温的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>His clothes were spotless. His manners were pristine. He spoke with a dictation that would make nobles sound like paupers. </Source>
      <Dest>他的衣着完美无瑕。他的举止古典而文雅。他言谈中流露的领袖气息能让贵族如平民一般恭敬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about Erevan.</Source>
      <Dest>跟讲讲艾里温的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He was more than just our leader, and he was more than just a knight. He was immaculate.  Divine.</Source>
      <Dest>他不仅仅是我们的领袖，也不仅仅是一个骑士。他是完美的，是神圣的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What will you do now, Knight-Commander?</Source>
      <Dest>指挥官，那么你现在要怎么办？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The credit goes to you. As I have all my life, when faced with a decision, I needed only follow your example.</Source>
      <Dest>这些都归功于你。我这一辈子，每当遇到任何事需要做决定，我都只需按你的样子做就好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Knight-Commander! The town is safe with nary a casualty!</Source>
      <Dest>报告领骑士大人！城镇安全了，乡亲们个个元气满满的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for you, I suggest you get some sleep. We'll need all our warriors well rested and focused on the battle.</Source>
      <Dest>至于你，我建议你去睡会儿觉。我们得让所有的战士好好休息，这样才能在战斗中集中注意力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright everyone, you have your orders!</Source>
      <Dest>好了大伙儿，你们都有自己的命令！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, Knight-Commander. You will have your place on the front lines, as always.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，骑士指挥官。在前线将有你的位置，一如既往。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Knight-Commander! I always believed that virtue would win out in the end!</Source>
      <Dest>Knight-Commander! I always believed that virtue would win out in the end!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dravynea, we need your alteration talents to protect those on the front line. Defense of the villagers is the priority.</Source>
      <Dest>Dravynea，我们需要你的变换天赋来保护前线的这些东西。防着村民们是第一要务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Roggi, I need you to gather any weapons you can find. We can't have these miners fighting with pickaxes.</Source>
      <Dest>罗吉，我要你收集一切你能找到的武器。我们不能让矿工们就拿着鹤嘴镐去战斗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Roggi, I need you to gather the other miners and bring them here so we can start building our defenses.</Source>
      <Dest>Roggi，我要你去把那些矿工集合起来带到这儿来，我们好开始建造防御。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Remove your weapons and surrender yourself to the guard, and I will refrain from removing your heads.</Source>
      <Dest>交出武器并且卸下你们的护甲，我可能会放你们一马。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you ruffians are through listing your demands, allow me to propose a counter offer.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你们这些暴徒在直接提要求，允许我讨一下价吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What about the town guard? I saw a few patrols when I entered.</Source>
      <Dest>城里的守卫呢？我进城的时候看见有一些在巡逻啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then fortune favors our meeting. I am a member of the Order of the Rose, the personal guard of the Count of Cheydinhal.</Source>
      <Dest>天佑我们的会议。我是玫瑰教团成员，香丁赫尔伯爵的的个人守卫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will see to it that these brigands are brought to justice.</Source>
      <Dest>我一定会让那些强盗被绳之以法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Knights? What warrior sworn to service would do the townsfolk harm?</Source>
      <Dest>骑士？一个发誓要保护大家的战士会去伤害平民？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nevertheless, I assure you, the Elf you see there is not the one I know. Erevan was a true knight, a paladin without peer.</Source>
      <Dest>然而我向你保证，你看到的精灵绝不是我所认识的那位。埃里温是个真正的骑士，无人可比的圣骑士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) I am sorry if the Knight-Commander has been a bother to you stranger.  </Source>
      <Dest>（叹息）如果骑士指挥官打扰到了你的话，我很抱歉，陌生人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Knight-Commander, I know you do not wish to defy the Countess' decree, but you cannot sit here and perpetuate this injustice!</Source>
      <Dest>指挥官，我知道你不想违背伯爵夫人的命令，但是你不能坐在这里让这种不公继续下去！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You are an honorable knight, and the most gallant Elf I have ever known.</Source>
      <Dest>你是个高贵的骑士，也是我所见过的最勇敢的精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, Knight-Commander?</Source>
      <Dest>骑士长?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Knight-Commander, please! I will do everything I can to exonerate you, but you must tell me what really happened that night!</Source>
      <Dest>求你了骑士长。 我会尽一切努力让你无罪，但你必须要告诉我那晚发生了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good luck. Hopefully you can convince him to be true to himself.</Source>
      <Dest>祝你好运。希望你能说服他去做真实的自己。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
