<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What's that?  I-Is something ahead?  Bandits?  Beasts?  W-Where's my sword?  I think I forgot my sword!</Source>
      <Dest>那是什么？是……什么尸体吧？强盗？还是野兽？我……我的剑去哪了？我找不到我的剑了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the Nine...</Source>
      <Dest>以九圣灵之名……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, a Dwarven city.  Is it true their machines use steam blades that bend around your shields?  Don't worry, I'm already devising a defense.</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，一个矮人城市。这些机器真的能用蒸汽刀片切碎你的盾牌吗？别担心，我已经设计出一种防御方法了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder how old this ruin is.  You're not thinking of raiding it are you?  Heroes like us should respect the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知这遗迹有多古老。你该不会想洗劫这里吧你？吾辈英雄应当尊重死者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A cave.  Was I supposed to bring a torch?  I forget.</Source>
      <Dest>一个山洞。我应该带个火把的吗？我忘了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>哈啰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here.  I got this for you.  Just a small token of my gratitude.</Source>
      <Dest>来，这个送给你，只是个表达我心意的小礼物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any siblings?</Source>
      <Dest>任何兄弟姐妹？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just one. A sister. A real snobby bitch, and obsessed with gold. Saving it to be precise.  Which would be fine, if she had a sense of humor about it.</Source>
      <Dest>就一个。一个姐姐。绝对的势利泼妇，就是爱钱。或者说爱存钱更准确吧。存钱不是坏毛病，问题是她一点幽默感也没有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whenever we went to the market in Whiterun, she'd always harass the vendors until they gave her a discount just to make her leave.</Source>
      <Dest>每次我们去白漫城市场的时候，她会一直缠着商人，直到商人不得不给她打个折好让她滚蛋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any siblings?</Source>
      <Dest>任何兄弟姐妹？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any siblings?</Source>
      <Dest>任何兄弟姐妹？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Poor Carlotta. Here she was trying everything in her power to feed her children, and my sister shakes her down for every last septim.</Source>
      <Dest>可怜的卡洛塔。她用尽一切办法只为了养活她的孩子们，而我的姐姐为了几个金币甚至想把她搜个一干二净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any siblings?</Source>
      <Dest>任何兄弟姐妹？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When we left, I told my sister, if there was one thing she didn't need any amulet or potion for, it was to become a master of cheapcraft.</Source>
      <Dest>当我们离开时，我告诉我的姐姐，要说有件工作她不用护符或者药水的帮助就能胜任，那就是成为一个砍价大师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That pretty much severed whatever relationship we had.  My sister holds a grudge as tight as she holds her coin purse.</Source>
      <Dest>那几乎让我们断绝了所有的往来。我姐妹一直也因此对我怀恨在心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any siblings?</Source>
      <Dest>任何兄弟姐妹？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings stranger, the name's Hjoromir, and I'm at your service.</Source>
      <Dest>你好，陌生人，我的名字是肖罗密尔，很高兴为你服务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let me know if there's anything I can help you with.  Perhaps you need your boots shined, or your tunic washed, or need a letter delivered?</Source>
      <Dest>如果有什么我可以帮忙的请告诉我。也许你需要人擦鞋，洗衣服，或是帮你跑腿送信？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Those who reject marriage typically are people no one wants to marry.</Source>
      <Dest>那些拒绝结婚的通常是些没人要的货色。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's not true.  I-I've got plenty suitors, it just wouldn't be chivalrous of me to lead them on.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是真的。我……我有很多的追求者，如果我把她们都给骗了是不是有点不符合骑士精神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's enough about your family.</Source>
      <Dest>关于他的家庭那足够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I've had enough of talking about them, as it were.  At least, to anyone who isn't a patron.</Source>
      <Dest>我可是受够谈论他们了。至少是受够了谈论那些不是客人的家伙们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Unfortunately lad, I need no such services.</Source>
      <Dest>很不幸，小伙子，我不需要这样的服务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, maybe you need someone to chop you some firewood.  Or brew you an alchemy potion.  I think I have a recipe lying around somewhere...</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，那或许你需要有人帮你砍一些木材。或配制一些炼金药剂。我记得我有一个配方在哪来着……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, if that's what you need.  I can be your personal jester, and you can mock me for your amusement.   </Source>
      <Dest>是的，如果你有需要的话，我还可以当你专属小丑，让你尽情的嘲笑我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Confound it boy, are you daft?  No one is this slow.</Source>
      <Dest>该死的熊孩子，你脑子进水了吗？没人这么慢！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Confound it boy, are you daft?  No one is this slow.</Source>
      <Dest>该死的熊孩子，你脑子进水了吗？没人这么慢！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I can be much more than that.  I can polish your boots, gather your kindling, and carry your quiver, handing you arrows as you shoot them.</Source>
      <Dest>但我会做的不只如此。我还可以帮你擦鞋，捡柴火，背弓箭袋，当你射击的时候为你递弓箭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your words are true.  You are a master without ever having picked up a sword.</Source>
      <Dest>你说的真对。你是个从未拿过剑的大师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Well, I wouldn't go that far.  I'm not a master.  Yet.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 好吧，我不会走那么远。我还不是个大师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, at least you're showing initiative.</Source>
      <Dest>还不赖。至少，你已经掌握了主动权。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's right, and I assure you, every service I offer will earn your complete satisfaction.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，而且我向你保证，我所提供的每一项服务都会让你满意至极。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, at least you're showing initiative.</Source>
      <Dest>还不赖。至少，你已经掌握了主动权。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, I could be your personal assistant.  I could wash your clothes and carry your equipment.  Consider me your personal pack mule.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我可以做你的私人助手。我可以帮你洗衣服，替你拿装备。把我当你的驮骡使唤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I don't really have a letter to write.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，我还真没有信要写。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, maybe you need someone to chop you some firewood.  Or brew you an alchemy potion.  I think I have a recipe lying around somewhere...</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，那或许你需要有人帮你砍一些木材。或配制一些炼金药剂。我记得我有一个配方在哪来着……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here I thought you were a boot-licker.  You're actually sort of arrogant.</Source>
      <Dest>原来你是表达一种傲慢,我特么还以为你是在拍马屁.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, I don't mind doing peasant stuff, because I know it's only temporary, and I've never been one who's needed a lot of gold to survive.</Source>
      <Dest>哈哈，我并不介意用乡下人的东西，因为我知道这只是暂时的。而我绝对不会成为口袋里没几个子儿就活不下去的人！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about your mother?</Source>
      <Dest>那你的母亲呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, my mother is a kind woman.  She always compliments me on my meals, and tells me how proud she is to have me for a son.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，我的母亲是一个善良的女人。她总是赞美我做的饭，告诉我她多么我这样的儿子而感到自豪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about your mother?</Source>
      <Dest>那你的母亲呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's it's own dilemma.  When even I can tell my potage has no flavor, it's tough to appreciate the kindness of her words.</Source>
      <Dest>当时真是处于进退两难的境地，当我发现自己做的肉汤没放盐的时候，我很难接受她善意的赞美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about your mother?</Source>
      <Dest>那你的母亲呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While lies of deceit are born as spiders and die as flies, white lies can wilt like a rose and leave nothing but thorns.  </Source>
      <Dest>诡计的谎言就如同蜘蛛一般出生像苍蝇一样死去，而善意的谎言就像一株枯萎的玫瑰，除了荆棘以外什么也没有留下。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>When I lick boots, I focus on every piece of dirt, and will even lick twice.</Source>
      <Dest>当我舔靴子的时候，我专注于每一片泥土，甚至会舔两次。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) And when you're done, I supposed you move to your lord's bottom then?  Hopefully he makes you rinse your mouth first.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 当你搞定之后，我想你会躲在你老大的身后。希望他会先让你洗干净你的嘴巴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>When I lick boots, I focus on every piece of dirt, and will even lick twice.</Source>
      <Dest>当我舔靴子的时候，我专注于每一片泥土，甚至会舔两次。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I get your meaning.  If I pay attention to the details when I'm polishing boots, that means I'll do the same when I'm thwarting bandits.</Source>
      <Dest>不过我懂你的意思了。如果我在擦靴子的时候有点吹毛求疵了，当我面对强盗的时候也会犯这毛病的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>When I lick boots, I focus on every piece of dirt, and will even lick twice.</Source>
      <Dest>当我舔靴子的时候，我专注于每一片泥土，甚至会舔两次。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At least, I hope that's what you meant. </Source>
      <Dest>至少，我希望这是你的意思. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么心事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么想法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just contemplating my next opponent.  Or opponents, I should say.  Three Snow Elves, with snouts that hiss foul vapors.</Source>
      <Dest>想想我的下一个对手，或者是对手们，纠正一下。三个发出邪恶的嘶嘶鼻息声的雪精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么心事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么想法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thinking about my next battle.  I'm entering the fall forest, when a Spriggan emerges from the trees.  </Source>
      <Dest>想想我的下一仗吧。我走进一片落叶的树林，突然一只树精从树丛里蹦出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么心事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么想法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An epic, to be precise.  One that's coming to its climax.  There's a tower on the horizon, canvassed by a sky the color of blood.</Source>
      <Dest>准确的说，是史诗。由那里的天候造就的史诗。地平线上一座高塔，在血色的天空背景下傲然耸立。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Away with you, sycophant.</Source>
      <Dest>除掉你,奉承者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh you say that now, but just wait.  It'll rain and you'll get mud on your boots, and you'll think to yourself:</Source>
      <Dest>喔，你现在可以这么说，但等会下雨了而且你靴子沾满了烂泥的时候，这时你会想：</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Away with you, sycophant.</Source>
      <Dest>除掉你,奉承者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what might those pursuits be?</Source>
      <Dest>他们所追寻的应该是什么呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The most noble pursuits that any man can endeavor.  Vanquishing vampires, beheading warlocks, and saving damsels from the claws of despair.</Source>
      <Dest>这是每个人都可以有的最崇高的追求。打败吸血鬼，砍下巫师的头颅，还有从魔爪下拯救绝望的少女。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what might those pursuits be?</Source>
      <Dest>他们所追寻的应该是什么呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whenever I work the bench, I imagine I'm hammering my foes into submission.  </Source>
      <Dest>不论何时，只要我使用工作台，我脑子里都想象着把敌人揍得跪地求饶的情景。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what might those pursuits be?</Source>
      <Dest>他们所追寻的应该是什么呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whenever I deliver a letter, I imagine I'm charging the battlements of Fort Greymoor.</Source>
      <Dest>每当我送信的时候，我总会想象自己正在灰色荒原堡垒的战役中冲锋陷阵呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what might those pursuits be?</Source>
      <Dest>他们所追寻的应该是什么呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes when I'm in the middle of a job, I'll accidentally whisper under my breath, something like, "Die you dastardly bandit."</Source>
      <Dest>有时在我在工作中的间隙，我会无意识的喃喃自语，比如，“去死吧你个卑鄙的强盗。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And what might those pursuits be?</Source>
      <Dest>他们所追寻的应该是什么呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh you should see the look on my patrons' faces!  Although it's kind of like the face you're making now.</Source>
      <Dest>噢你真该看看我主顾脸上的表情！对，就是现在你脸上的表情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hey, don't insult maggots by comparing them to Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，将蛆与梭默比较这是在侮辱蛆好吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) The Thalmor are a despicable bunch.  That's the one thing my father and I agree on, if not on what makes one a Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑声）那帮梭默就是用卑鄙这两个字做成的。我和我父亲也就在这一点上有达成过共识。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hey, don't insult maggots by comparing them to Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，将蛆与梭默比较这是在侮辱蛆好吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He'll tell you it's anyone with pointy ears, bootskin, or fur.  I'll tell you anyone who says that is drunk on the liquor of hate.</Source>
      <Dest>他肯定是说尖耳朵、穿皮靴或者皮革服装的就是梭莫了。说这种话的人绝对已经被仇恨蒙蔽了双眼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No, no, and maybe.  Do you have a quill?</Source>
      <Dest>不，不是，也许，可能吧。你有毛笔吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh right, I knew I forgot something.  Is it a long missive?  Perhaps I can memorize it.</Source>
      <Dest>喔好吧，我就知道我又忘了什么。是一封很长的信吗？或许我可以回忆起内容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dearest love, I shall be at there at midnight's delight, when the twin moons...</Source>
      <Dest>我的挚爱，我会在午夜到达那里，当那对月亮...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whoa, whoa.  Can you slow down a second?  There's no way I can remember all that without some sort of potion.</Source>
      <Dest>哇，哇。你可以讲慢一点吗？没有某种药水的话，我可不能把它们全都记住。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're really bad at this.</Source>
      <Dest>你对这个真不在行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe. Or maybe I just need the right teacher.  You seem well traveled.  </Source>
      <Dest>也许吧。也可能只是我没遇到对的老师。你看起来经验还挺丰富的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're really bad at this.</Source>
      <Dest>你对这个真不在行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you in need of an apprentice?  I'll cook and clean, and can set traps to catch game.</Source>
      <Dest>你需要个侍从吗？ 我会煮饭、打扫，甚至还能做个陷阱捕猎呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Right.  A spouse would leave you over-encumbered.</Source>
      <Dest>Right.  A spouse would leave you over-encumbered.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell me about it.  That princess I saved from Numinex?  She turned out to be extremely possessive, and incredibly demanding.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲。那个我在纽莫纳斯救下的公主？原来她其实是个极具占有欲又极端苛刻的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sensing a pattern with your previous employers.</Source>
      <Dest>我感受到一种和你前任老板一样的风格。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know what you're getting at.  I hear the whispers.  But the only pattern I see is one of versatility.  </Source>
      <Dest>我知道你想说什么。我听到了些低语声。但我只能看见些模糊不清的画面。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sensing a pattern with your previous employers.</Source>
      <Dest>我感受到一种和你前任老板一样的风格。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean I'm no fool.  Yes, I can be clumsy.  And Mara knows I'm not the best cook.</Source>
      <Dest>我是说我不是白痴。是的，我是有点迟钝，而且玛拉知道我不是最棒的厨子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sensing a pattern with your previous employers.</Source>
      <Dest>我感受到一种和你前任老板一样的风格。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But that's only because I'm not really concentrating on what I'm doing.  And why should I? </Source>
      <Dest>但那只是因为我做事情不太专心。我为什么要专心呢？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sensing a pattern with your previous employers.</Source>
      <Dest>我感受到一种和你前任老板一样的风格。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's not as if the lumber chopping and dish washing is a mentally exhausting skill. </Source>
      <Dest>和砍柴洗碗的粗活不同，这活儿可费神了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sensing a pattern with your previous employers.</Source>
      <Dest>我感受到一种和你前任老板一样的风格。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I figure I can do that stuff while I fill my head with greater pursuits.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然我有鸿鹄之志，但我还是能做好燕雀的工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Pretty much.</Source>
      <Dest>非常漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, you're really wise stranger.  Can I be your apprentice?  I'll cook and clean, and craft potions to ail your wounds.</Source>
      <Dest>哇，你这个陌生人真是聪明。我可以当你的侍从吗？我会煮饭、打扫，还会在你受伤的时候制作一些药水。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And one not easily achieved.  Which is why I have to make good use of my time.</Source>
      <Dest>这事儿可不容易做到。所以我总是好好规划自己的时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You aim to become a true hero. It is a lofty goal.</Source>
      <Dest>你想成为真正的英雄。这是一个崇高的目标。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whenever I was tasked with doing something for the locals, I'd let my body do the work while my mind stayed focused on the art of battle.</Source>
      <Dest>当我为本地人做些杂活儿的时候，我的身体在工作，而我的内心则在战场上驰骋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You aim to become a true hero. It is a lofty goal.</Source>
      <Dest>你想成为真正的英雄。这是一个崇高的目标。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I am desperate.  It's mostly because people only offer a few septims for my services.</Source>
      <Dest>但我有些绝望了，主要是因为我的雇主们只付给我一丁点报酬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You shouldn't sell so hard boy, it makes you look desperate.</Source>
      <Dest>你不应该这么辛苦卖命的，它让你看起来有点积极过头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You shouldn't sell so hard boy, it makes you look desperate.</Source>
      <Dest>你不应该这么辛苦卖命的，它让你看起来有点积极过头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh...I get it.  You mean my desperation is why they offer me so little.</Source>
      <Dest>喔...我懂了。你的意思是过于积极就是他们付我那么少报酬的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A three-legged goat can dream he's a horse.  Doesn't make it true.</Source>
      <Dest>一只三条腿的山羊梦想竟然是变成一匹马。这不会是真的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, but I'm more like the horse who dreams he's the goat.  When I imagine myself in battle, I always put myself at a disadvantage.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，但我更像那些梦想自己其实是一头羊的马。当我在想象中战斗的时候，我总是将自己处于不利的位置。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Adventuring is no child's game, boy.</Source>
      <Dest>冒险不是儿戏，小子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha, you sound like my father.  Where were you eighteen years ago on the 14th of Frostfall?</Source>
      <Dest>哈，你说这话就像我的老爹。十八年前霜落月的14号那天你在哪？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Adventuring is no child's game, boy.</Source>
      <Dest>冒险不是儿戏，小子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll tell you what I told him.  I don't plan to go out into the wilderness unprepared.  I've been in countless fights already.</Source>
      <Dest>我会把告诉他的原封不动告诉你。我可不想不做任何准备就冲到茫茫野外去。我可是身经百战的老战士了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Adventuring is no child's game, boy.</Source>
      <Dest>冒险不是儿戏，小子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, I'm fighting right now, even as we speak.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，即使是我们说话的这会儿，我还在战斗呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Adventuring is no child's game, boy.</Source>
      <Dest>冒险不是儿戏，小子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha, you sound like my father.  I'd ask you where you were 18 years ago on the 14th of Frostfall, but I doubt you have the equipment to sire a child.</Source>
      <Dest>哈，你说这话就像我父亲，我想知道十八年前霜落月14日那天你在哪，但我怀疑你有没有生孩子的工具。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Adventuring is no child's game, boy.</Source>
      <Dest>冒险不是儿戏，小子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll tell you what I told him.  I don't plan to go out into the wilderness unprepared.  I've been in countless fights already.</Source>
      <Dest>我会把告诉他的原封不动告诉你。我可不想不做任何准备就冲到茫茫野外去。我可是身经百战的老战士了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, I'm fighting another lady warrior like yourself, right at this moment.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我正在跟另一个像你一样的女勇士决斗呢，此时此刻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Adventuring is no child's game, boy.</Source>
      <Dest>冒险不是儿戏，小子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, you can find time for both.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，你能为这两件事抽出空来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?  I don't think so.  I've played out the scenario in my head, and devoting half your time almost always makes you half a hero.</Source>
      <Dest>真的？我可不那么认为。我脑海里已经有计划了，但我必须全力以赴，三心两意只会让你变成半吊子英雄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll consider it.</Source>
      <Dest>我会考虑一下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>R-really?  I'll do everything you ask, just say the word!</Source>
      <Dest>真……真的？只要你开口，我什么都愿意做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like a volatile household.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来像个不稳定的家庭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, but at least when he's eating he keeps his mouth shut.  The worst part is afterward, when he starts spouting racist nonsense.</Source>
      <Dest>是，至少他在吃东西的时候能闭上他的臭嘴。糟糕的是，吃完以后他又会开始说那些种族主义的鬼话了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like a volatile household.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来像个不稳定的家庭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Elves poisoning our food. Elves stealing our children. And don't tell him there's a difference between the Elven races, let alone Altmer and Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>精灵向我们食物投毒。精灵偷了我们的孩子。千万别告诉他精灵种族之间是有区别的，更别提傲尔特默和梭默了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like a volatile household.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来像个不稳定的家庭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're all Thalmor maggots to him. Listening to the old man makes me ashamed to call myself a Nord.</Source>
      <Dest>对他来说所有的梭默都如蛆虫。听那个老头说的话真让我羞于称自己为诺德人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry. That must be difficult for you.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉。这对你来说肯定有点难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, but at least when he's eating he keeps his mouth shut.  The worst part is afterward, when he starts spouting racist nonsense.</Source>
      <Dest>是，至少他在吃东西的时候能闭上他的臭嘴。糟糕的是，吃完以后他又会开始说那些种族主义的鬼话了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry. That must be difficult for you.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉。这对你来说肯定有点难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Elves poisoning our food. Elves stealing our children. And don't tell him there's a difference between the Elven races, let alone Altmer and Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>精灵向我们食物投毒。精灵偷了我们的孩子。千万别告诉他精灵种族之间是有区别的，更别提傲尔特默和梭默了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're all Thalmor maggots to him.  Listening to the old man makes me ashamed to call myself a Nord.</Source>
      <Dest>对他来说所有的梭默都如蛆虫。听那个老头说的话真让我羞于称自己为诺德人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry. That must be difficult for you.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉。这对你来说肯定有点难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're fairly young for someone living out on his own.</Source>
      <Dest>就独自生活的人来说你确实年轻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm of age, and a man grown.  I can grow whiskers on my cheeks just like any old Nord.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经到了成熟男人的年纪了，我也会其他诺德爷们一样在脸上长胡子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're fairly young for someone living out on his own.</Source>
      <Dest>就独自生活的人来说你确实年轻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People treat me differently because of my station, but they still respect me as a man.  Which is more than I can say for my father.</Source>
      <Dest>人们因为我的地位而对我区别对待，但他们至少还把我当人看。至少比我老爹要好多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're fairly young for someone living out on his own.</Source>
      <Dest>就独自生活的人来说你确实年轻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The last time I saw the old toad all he did was bark orders and gripe.  He complained my pheasant roast was overcooked. </Source>
      <Dest>我最后一次看到老癞头时，他正在一边骂娘一边发号施令。他抱怨我的野鸡烤过头了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're fairly young for someone living out on his own.</Source>
      <Dest>就独自生活的人来说你确实年轻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He nearly slapped me when I poured his beer and left a less than frothy head, and then he berated me the entire time I cleared the table. </Source>
      <Dest>当他发现我弄洒了他的啤酒正不知所措的时候，差点给我一巴掌，然后我顶着他的责备擦完了桌子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You fight battles in your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在在天人交战？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Indeed I do.  Even now as we speak, I see my opponent dancing before me, a spear maiden, grains of light glinting off her lance.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，就算我们说话这会儿，我也仿佛能看见我的对手在我面前跳舞，一个持矛女子，她的长矛还闪着微光。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You fight battles in your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在在天人交战？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I lean to dodge her blow, the blade nearly shaving my chin.  But I can sense the irritation in her spear.</Source>
      <Dest>我试着躲避她的攻击，当时那把长矛离我的喉咙只有0.01公分。但我都能从矛尖上感受到她的怒火。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You fight battles in your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在在天人交战？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just as the trees rankle in the wind, her blows sway from their mark as her temper flares.  With each dodge, her heart grows more and more disquiet.</Source>
      <Dest>每当她发脾气时，她的攻击就像在风中摇曳的树枝一样偏离目标。而每次失误都让她的内心更加不安。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In time, I require neither agility or swiftness to dodge her blows.  For it's her spear that dodges my body.</Source>
      <Dest>这时候，我可不需要左右腾挪来躲避她的攻击。因为她的长矛在躲避我的身体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You fight battles in your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在在天人交战？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I bet your old man is equally as ashamed of you.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢打赌，你的父亲也会为你感到羞愧的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) You're probably right.  That's the only thing satisfying about the work I do.  That he has to tell people what became of his son.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)你很可能是对的。我对这份工作唯一满意的部分就是能让我老爹骄傲的告诉别人，他儿子是干什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I bet your old man is equally as ashamed of you.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢打赌，你的父亲也会为你感到羞愧的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Granted, he probably lies and tells people I joined the Stormcloaks.  Or that I died in some heroic battle, defending Skyrim from the Thalmor menace.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。他可能会造谣说我参加了风暴斗篷。或者说是我为了保卫天际免遭梭默的威胁而英勇牺牲了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I bet your old man is equally as ashamed of you.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢打赌，你的父亲也会为你感到羞愧的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The sad part is my ambition isn't that far off from his ideal.  Adventurers and soldiers both require courage.  Only the battlefield is different.</Source>
      <Dest>悲哀的是我的志向与他是理想相差不远。冒险家和士兵都需要勇气。只不过是战场不同而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Some people will complain about anything.</Source>
      <Dest>有的人就是什么事都抱怨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, that woman seems sweet on the outside, but beware, she has a real mean streak too.</Source>
      <Dest>对呀，那个女人表面上看起来人很好，但其实私底下脾气很差。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Some people will complain about anything.</Source>
      <Dest>有的人就是什么事都抱怨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gerdur though, she'll vouch for me.  And the blacksmith fellow, I forget his name.  He taught me how to strip leather down.</Source>
      <Dest>歌尔朵给我做了担保。还有铁匠铺那家伙……我忘了他的名字。他教了我制皮的技巧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Some people will complain about anything.</Source>
      <Dest>有的人就是什么事都抱怨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm guessing he would've hired me as his apprentice, but I think he knew I was destined for more.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜他本来想招我为学徒的，但我想他知道我命中注定另有大用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Three dishes does seem like a lot. Maybe you're being too hard on her.</Source>
      <Dest>三个盘子似乎有点多。或许你对她要求太多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha, that woman seems sweet on the outside, but beware, she has a real mean streak too.</Source>
      <Dest>哈，那女人看起来真可爱对不，但要小心了。她可也有真正卑劣的一面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Three dishes does seem like a lot. Maybe you're being too hard on her.</Source>
      <Dest>三个盘子似乎有点多。或许你对她要求太多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gerdur though, she'll vouch for me.  And the blacksmith fellow, I forget his name.  He taught me how to strip leather down.</Source>
      <Dest>歌尔朵给我做了担保。还有铁匠铺那家伙……我忘了他的名字。他教了我制皮的技巧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Three dishes does seem like a lot. Maybe you're being too hard on her.</Source>
      <Dest>三个盘子似乎有点多。或许你对她要求太多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm guessing he would've hired me as his apprentice, but I think he knew I was destined for more.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜他本来想招我为学徒的，但我想他知道我命中注定另有大用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I take it she treats you harshly.</Source>
      <Dest>所以,我认为她对你严厉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, that woman seems sweet on the outside, but beware, she has a real mean streak too.</Source>
      <Dest>对呀，那个女人表面上看起来人很好，但其实私底下脾气很差。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I take it she treats you harshly.</Source>
      <Dest>所以,我认为她对你严厉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gerdur though, she'll vouch for me. And the blacksmith fellow, I forget his name.  He taught me how to strip leather down.</Source>
      <Dest>歌尔朵给我做了担保。还有铁匠铺那家伙……我忘了他的名字。他教了我制皮的技巧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I take it she treats you harshly.</Source>
      <Dest>所以,我认为她对你严厉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm guessing he would've hired me as his apprentice, but I think he knew I was destined for more.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜他本来想招我为学徒的，但我想他知道我命中注定另有大用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have a job in town?</Source>
      <Dest>你在城镇里有工作吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you're asking if I specialize in something, I'd say I do just about everything.  For instance, I used to help Sven chop lumber.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你是问我有什么特别擅长的话，我可以告诉你，我什么都做过。比如，我曾经在胡德伐木厂工作过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have a job in town?</Source>
      <Dest>你在城镇里有工作吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is, until the day he almost lost his hand at the sawmill.  Wasn't my fault, he ran into me.  But he hasn't asked for my help since.</Source>
      <Dest>可是有一天，锯木厂的锯子差点砍掉他的双手，那明明不是我的错，他却责怪我。之后他就再也没有要我帮忙过了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have a job in town?</Source>
      <Dest>你在城镇里有工作吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Same with Delphine. She says I broke too many dishes. I broke maybe three at the most.</Source>
      <Dest>戴尔芬也一样。她说我打碎太多碗盘了。我最多也才打破三个而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You forget, I've been on thousands of adventures before.  This is nothing.</Source>
      <Dest>你忘了吗？我已经经历过无数次的生死考验了。这不算什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you faring?</Source>
      <Dest>你进展得怎么样?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you faring?</Source>
      <Dest>你进展得怎么样?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've defeated the most celebrated warriors in all of Skyrim, bested Daedric Princes against seemingly insurmountable odds.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经击败了整个天际省最着名的勇士，还打败了那看似无敌的迪德拉魔神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you faring?</Source>
      <Dest>你进展得怎么样?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not even my mother worries about my safety anymore.  Although she does manage to pester me in other ways.</Source>
      <Dest>甚至连我老娘都不担心我的安慰。虽然她总在别的事上来烦我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you faring?</Source>
      <Dest>你进展得怎么样?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She keeps sending me letters via courier, asking about my love life.  She doesn't realize we heroes are married to adventure.  Am I right?</Source>
      <Dest>她不断要信差给我送信，询问我的感情生活。她还没意识到我们这些英雄已经跟冒险结婚了。我说的对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you are referring to the pursuit of knowledge.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你是指追求知识。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You need to be more cognizant of the times, traveler.  And the place.  Skyrim cares naught for knowledge.  </Source>
      <Dest>你需要对时间有更多的认识，旅行者。还有地点。天际的无名小卒需要在知识上武装自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you are referring to the pursuit of knowledge.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你是指追求知识。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What good is becoming a scholar?  Only a handful of people will understand the things you say and they'll still disagree on the meaning.</Source>
      <Dest>话说，当个学者有什么好处？没几个人能听懂你在说什么，即使听懂的人也不一定赞同你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you are referring to the pursuit of knowledge.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你是指追求知识。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In Skyrim, people understand only one thing.  The cry of battle.  Blood and steel.  And songs to immortalize the heroes and the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>在天际，人们只懂得一类事。战场上的哀鸣，鲜血与钢铁，还有传颂不朽的英雄和逝者的歌谣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you are referring to the pursuit of knowledge.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你是指追求知识。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's what will get you the adulation of your peers.  Not reading some dusty old book.</Source>
      <Dest>这才是让你的同行会甘于奉承于你的东西，而不是因为你读了那些满是灰尘的旧书呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dear dragons, I'm coming for your souls.  Dragonborn, dictated, but not signed.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的巨龙，我为了你的灵魂而来。龙裔，口述但没签署。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, dear dragons, I'm going...or was it coming?  Can you repeat that?</Source>
      <Dest>好的，亲爱的巨龙，我将会……这家伙过来了？你可以再说一次吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dear dragon, I'm coming back for you.  &lt;Alias=Player&gt;, dictated but not signed.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的巨龙，我为了你而回来。&lt;Alias=Player&gt;，口述但没签署。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, Dear Dragon, I'm going...or was it coming?  Can you repeat that?</Source>
      <Dest>好的，亲爱的巨龙，我将……什么，它来了？你可以再说一次吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I ride fast and low, evading the sweep of his talons.  I enter the tower where my princess awaits, but my task is not yet complete.  </Source>
      <Dest>我把马骑得飞快，压下身子，躲避他魔爪的横扫。我得进那座塔。我的公主还在等待，我的任务还没完成。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I give her my steed and my love, and climb the winding steps to the top of the fort, where Numinex has a date with my steel.</Source>
      <Dest>我将我的爱与战马一起送给了她，然后顶着狂风攀上了堡垒顶端，努米内克斯与我的决战之地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Where the tender spot in his neck awaits my blade. </Source>
      <Dest>我的刀刃要砍进他后颈最柔软的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Her fears are confirmed when I pour it on my blade, as Spriggans fear only fire.</Source>
      <Dest>她因为我的刀刃而感到恐惧，就像树精遇见火一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A direct attack is foolish.  Numinex knows this. That's why I do it.  My aim is to shock him just long enough to run up his nose and behind his eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>莽撞的进攻是愚蠢的。努米内克斯知道这点。所以我才攻击他鼻子和眼睛后面让它晕眩了好一会儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He roars at the sight of me, and I answer him by raising the Sword of Dawn, shining like a beacon through the darkness.</Source>
      <Dest>他一看见我就大吼大叫，而我却举起黎明之剑，日光如同黑暗中的灯塔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Even Numinex cannot withstand its glare, as he winces and recoils behind the fort before taking flight.</Source>
      <Dest>即使努米内克斯也无法承受它的怒视，就在战斗发生之前它就张开双翼溜走了并躲在堡垒的城墙之后。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it has a weakness.  I reach for my wine bottle, and I can almost see her wooden mouth twist into a smile.</Source>
      <Dest>但它有一个弱点。我去拿我的酒瓶时，我几乎能看见她用她那如木头般的嘴巴拧出的一丝微笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then she realizes, as I tilt the bottle, the substance inside is viscous, moving with the consistency of oil. </Source>
      <Dest>当我倾斜瓶口的时候她终于明白过来了，那瓶子里装的物质极具粘性，依靠着油的润滑而缓慢移动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Three Falmer become two, and two become one.  The last is afforded only a second to make peace with the Divines, before all are gone.</Source>
      <Dest>三个伐莫变成了两个，两个又变成了一个。剩下的那个赶紧求饶，免得全军覆没。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But he fails to see that the twirl of my feet not only allows me to evade, but provides the torque for my blow.  </Source>
      <Dest>但他不知道我旋转脚踝不是为了躲闪，而是为我接下来的重击提供推力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As I ride my steed closer, I see that coiled around the tower like a serpent is the evil dragon Numinex resurrected by Alduin.  </Source>
      <Dest>我骑着马越走越近，终于看清盘绕在塔上的是被奥杜因唤醒的恶龙努米内克斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Her form is beautiful, and we stop to admire each other before I unsheathe my weapon.</Source>
      <Dest>她太美了，在我把剑收入鞘中之前我们都在互相赞美对方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Her body glows with bundles of light, as if a group of torchbugs danced inside her hollow chamber. </Source>
      <Dest>她的躯体微光闪烁，好似一群萤火虫在她的闺房里翩翩起舞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's a frame made of solid oak, flesh stronger than any shield.</Source>
      <Dest>骨骼由橡木组成，这副身躯比任何盾牌都更坚韧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Two of them try to flank me, while the mage attempts to slow me with a spray of frozen dust.</Source>
      <Dest>两个人想从侧面包抄我，而那个法师正试图用喷射的冰屑让我减慢速速度。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>His hope is that while I concentrate on evading him, his friends will offer the killing blow.</Source>
      <Dest>他希望当我集中注意应付他攻击的时候，他的朋友能在旁边给我致命一击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>哈啰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can I help you?</Source>
      <Dest>我能为你效劳吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What can I do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么可以效劳的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>你还有什么事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You sure look like you could use some help.</Source>
      <Dest>你看起来就是需要帮忙的样子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The name's Hjoromir, and I'm just the man for the job.</Source>
      <Dest>我的名字是肖罗密尔, 我是来找工作的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here.</Source>
      <Dest>在这里等着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here a moment.</Source>
      <Dest>在这等一会儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I won't move a muscle.</Source>
      <Dest>我绝对不会动的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sounds good.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Departs}</Source>
      <Dest>{离开 }</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you sure? You're going to regret it.  (Sigh) Alright.  If you need me, and you most certainly will, I'll be waiting in Riverwood.</Source>
      <Dest>你确定吗？你会后悔的。（叹气）如果你需要我，你肯定会需要的。我会在河木镇等你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's nothing. Never mind.</Source>
      <Dest>没什么事，不用担心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sounds good.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes. Let me show you.</Source>
      <Dest>不错，你看看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take your time.</Source>
      <Dest>抓紧时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take your time.</Source>
      <Dest>慢慢儿来。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need you to do something for me.</Source>
      <Dest>我需要你为我做件事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is it?  Need something cooked?  Polished?  Lectured?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？需要煮些什么？打扫哪？教训谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not a problem, like I said, just think of me as a two-legged pack mule, with a bit more charm.</Source>
      <Dest>不是问题，就像我说的, just think of me as a two-legged pack mule, 有一点魅力.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sounds good.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What can I do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么可以效劳的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Zzzzz...</Source>
      <Dest>Zzzzz……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So this is what an Orc Stronghold looks like.  Somehow I pictured it larger.  And meaner.</Source>
      <Dest>原来兽人要塞就长这样。我之前还以为它会大一些而且破一些呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow...the Blue Palace.  The site of one of my greatest duels.  This visit will give my training the additional details and color it needs.</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦……蓝宫。这将是我伟大生涯中的一个战场。这次参观让我的训练添上新的一笔浓墨重彩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The last three necromancers I fought were immune to poison.  It has to do with their connection to corpses, who have no blood.</Source>
      <Dest>最近我击败的几个亡灵术士都对毒药免疫。这肯定是因为他们总跟死去多时的尸体打交道的关系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By Arkay's blessing, is that a giant?  I-It's much bigger than the ones I've encountered.  Do you think it's friendly?</Source>
      <Dest>我的阿凯神啊，那是个巨人？它……它比我之前见到的所有巨人都大多了。你觉得它友善吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Kynesgrove is hallowed ground.  Just the sort a place a hero finds a legendary sword, gifted from the Divines.</Source>
      <Dest>基耐森林是个圣地。就像是故事里英雄找到圣灵赐予的神剑一样的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whiterun. Home of The Bannered Mare. I wonder which banner it flies?  I guess maybe all of them.  But someday mine will be the only one worth flying.</Source>
      <Dest>雪漫城。母马横幅的所在地。我想知道是哪位骑士的横幅在飘扬？我想也许都会。但总有一天我的横幅会是最引人注目的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you think the Orcs here would mind if I took a souvenir?  I really like the look of their daggers.</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得这些兽人会介意我留下一点小纪念品吗？我真挺很喜欢兽人匕首的模样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I tried applying for part-time work at one of the Battle-Born farms.  I figured they must pay well.  Still haven't heard back from Alfhild.</Source>
      <Dest>我想申请去战狂农场干份兼职。我估计那里的报酬一定很高。不过阿尔夫希德还没给我答复。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The key to defeating Draugr is to stay low and duck under their shout.  That or cover your ears.</Source>
      <Dest>击败尸鬼的关键在于低头前进和躲过他们的龙吼。捂上你的耳朵也可以。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I must confess, I haven't fought too many bandits in my lifetime.  But if every day you fight lions, it's not difficult to slay a house cat.</Source>
      <Dest>我得承认，这辈子我没有杀过多少强盗。但如果你每天都和狮子战斗的话，几只家猫当然不在话下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vampires.  They try to use their speed to flank you, and throw their fangs at your neck.  Keep your shield or weapon high.</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼，这些家伙会利用自己的速度来包抄你，然后将獠牙插进你的脖子。所以要保持警惕才行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The best part about caves is they provide all the tools for survival. I once survived a month long battle by eating mushrooms and drinking mud water.</Source>
      <Dest>洞穴最迷人的一点在于它能提供求生所需的所有东西。我曾经只靠吃蘑菇和饮泥水在长达一个月的战斗中幸存下来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's been my experience that as long as we don't threaten them, most beasts won't attack.  They're more scared of us then we are of them.</Source>
      <Dest>以我多年的经验来说，只要这些野兽感受不到威胁，是不会主动攻击的。与其说人怕动物，其实动物更怕人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Spriggans.  Beautiful but deadly.  I believe I've told you their weakness.</Source>
      <Dest>树精。美丽而致命。我想我告诉过你他们的弱点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I mine ore, I use the same form as I would with a two handed sword.  The miners thought I never got much done.  They have no idea.</Source>
      <Dest>当我采矿的时候，我用的是跟平时一样的装备，一把双手剑。矿工们认为这东西根本没法干活，那是因为他们不懂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say praying to the Divines cures your ailments.  What people don't tell you is, overcoming disease naturally will build your immunity to it.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说向圣灵祈祷可以治愈你的疾病。人们没有告诉你的是，等病自然好会增强你的免疫力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Small towns are a great place to find work.  The Jarls are stingy with their guardsmen, and the people really depend on adventurers like us.</Source>
      <Dest>小城镇是一个找工作的好地方。领主和他们的卫兵都很小气，那里的人们只能依赖你我一样的冒险者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've climbed the 7000 steps more times than I care to count.  At the top, you'll find the air is so crisp it rejuvenates the soul.</Source>
      <Dest>我爬过高吼峰7000阶梯的次数多的我懒得去数了。在山顶，你会发现清新的空气仿佛能洗净你的灵魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So this is High Hrothgar.  In my visions, the great hall was lined with the statues of old masters, but I suppose that would be too garish.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这就是高吼峰啦。我还以为大厅里得摆满大师的雕像呢，不过我猜这样会有点太花哨了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Love what you've done with the place.  And if by chance you're in the market for a new housecarl, I'm always available.</Source>
      <Dest>我真欣赏你把这个地方打理的这么井井有条。如果下次你想找个新管家的话，我随时待命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I heard a rumor that this place is a haven for thieves and derelicts. Saving this town could be the start of my legacy.</Source>
      <Dest>我听过一个传言，这地方是盗贼和流浪汉们的天堂。拯救这个城市会成为我传奇的第一页。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Windhelm.  My father talks about this place as if Tiber Septim were king, and the other 8 Divines were tending the bar.  </Source>
      <Dest>风舵城。每次我父亲讲到这个地方的时候，都好像泰伯‧赛普汀是这的国王，其他八圣灵都在这的酒吧里打工一样。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stendarr's mercy, I think I broke one of your items...no wait, false alarm, it was one of mine.  Don't worry, your things are safe with me.</Source>
      <Dest>慈悲的斯坦达尔啊，我想我弄破了你的一件东西……不，等等，搞错了。别担心，你的东西我好好保管着呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The way my father talked about Windhelm, the walls were made of gold, and the rivers flowed with mead.  Not quite, but it is impressive.</Source>
      <Dest>The way my father talked about Windhelm, the walls were made of gold, and the rivers flowed with mead.  Not quite, but it is impressive.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, I could've sworn you told me to hold on to some ore and metal we picked up on the road, but my sack is empty.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道，我知道你要我收集在路上捡的矿石和金属，但是我的包却空了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're not going to believe this, but I think I dropped my weapon back outside the city...Oh wait, no, here it is.</Source>
      <Dest>你是不会相信的，我想我把武器落在城外了……呃，等等，没有，它还在这。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How much gold did we have when we left that last city?  I'm trying to figure out where all of it went.</Source>
      <Dest>我们在离开上一个城市的时候还剩多少钱？我正试着弄清楚钱都跑哪儿去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It may be my imagination, but my coin purse feels a bit light.  Weird.</Source>
      <Dest>可能是我的幻觉，但我觉得我的钱包轻了些。真奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I fought the great warlock, Mannimarco, I used stealth to shatter his phylactery.  The battle was over before he knew it begun.</Source>
      <Dest>我打败了一个伟大的术士，曼尼马克，我通过潜行粉碎了他的护符。当他意识到发什么之前战斗就已经结束了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Elves, Redguard, Argonians...we're not in Riverwood anymore, are we.  Apologies to Faendal.</Source>
      <Dest>精灵，红卫人，亚龙人……我们可不是在河木镇。抱歉了，法恩达尔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The cities are bustling with so much life. I feel like the possibilities are endless.</Source>
      <Dest>这城市熙熙攘攘,三教九流，鱼龙混杂。我觉得这里发生什么都不奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's always good to pay your respects at the Bards College.  Without them, who would pass on our feats to the next generation of adventurers?</Source>
      <Dest>对吟游诗人学院保持尊重还是有好处的。要不然谁向以后的冒险者们传颂我们的歌谣？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The people here are ready to reclaim their city.  I can feel it.  All they need is a hero to lead them.</Source>
      <Dest>这里的人们准备夺回他们的城市。我能感觉到。他们所需的只是有一个英雄来领导他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've killed a dragon or two in my day. The secret is to stay in one of their blind spots, right around the neck.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾经在同一天里杀了大概两条龙。诀窍就是躲在它的盲点，就在脖子周围。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A Falmer hive.  Come on Hjoromir, you've done this a thousand times before.</Source>
      <Dest>一个伐莫窝。加油肖罗密尔。伐莫有什么可怕的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The innkeeper here in Rorikstead reminds me of my sister's boyfriend.  They both break wind like a thoroughbred.</Source>
      <Dest>洛利克镇的旅店老板让我想起了妹妹的男朋友。他们都像老学究一样满嘴废话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Trolls are strong and powerful, but terribly slow, and you can't damage what you can't hit.  I just tire them out and strike the killing blow.</Source>
      <Dest>巨魔是强壮有力的，但行动缓慢，再厉害打不着也白搭。我不仅让它们精疲力尽了，而且对他们做出了致命的打击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I laugh whenever I see someone sparring a straw man.  I'm sure all that training comes in real handy if your opponent decides not to fight back.</Source>
      <Dest>每次我看到人们对稻草人练习我就想笑。我确定如果对手能还击，这样的训练会更有效的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My mother's a sweet woman. She passes on my tales to the townsfolk as if they were true.  I don't mind, seeing as they someday will be.</Source>
      <Dest>我妈是一个挺逗的女人。她把我编的故事当成真事讲给镇子里的人听。我倒也不介意，因为反正总有一天会变成真的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I never realized how much day to day labor and, well, walking we adventurers do. I guess that's the sort of stuff they leave out of the tales.</Source>
      <Dest>我从没想过作为一个探险家每天要进行这么多的琐事以及，呃，步行。这就是他们在探险故事里没讲的部分吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some people asked me why I won't stick to one job and settle down. Yeah, because real men spend their lives tilling fields and working millstones.</Source>
      <Dest>有人问我为什么我不好好地干一份工作然后定居下来。是啊，因为真正的男人就应该用他的一生去种田。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I once told my father my plans to sail across Tamriel.  The old goat said  "A true Nord lives in Skyrim, works in Skyrim, and pays taxes to Skyrim."</Source>
      <Dest>我曾经告诉我老爹我计划环游整个泰姆瑞尔。这个老家伙说：“真正的诺德人住在天际，活在天际，税也应该交给天际。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, I've always imagined adventuring in my head, but because of you, I get to live out my dream in the flesh.  Thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道吗？我一直想去冒险，因为你，我得到了自己梦寐以求的生活。谢谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Didn't feel a thing!</Source>
      <Dest>就像挠痒痒！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh!</Source>
      <Dest>呃！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Agh!  Bastard!</Source>
      <Dest>啊！混蛋！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh, you fiend!</Source>
      <Dest>呃啊，你这恶魔！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like the bite of a flea!</Source>
      <Dest>就被跳蚤咬了一口！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ist that it? Is that your best?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？这就是你的极限吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eeeeyyargh!</Source>
      <Dest>耶呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hyagh!</Source>
      <Dest>哈啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Die, damn you!</Source>
      <Dest>去死吧，混蛋！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're nothing!</Source>
      <Dest>你这无名的蝼蚁之辈！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gyaaargh!</Source>
      <Dest>呀啊啊啊啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You need to do better than that!</Source>
      <Dest>你需要做得更好！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Easily blocked!</Source>
      <Dest>很容易堵住！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can take you!</Source>
      <Dest>你完了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't stand a chance!</Source>
      <Dest>你一点机会也没！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're going to look good mounted on my wall!</Source>
      <Dest>你的脑袋会成为我的收藏品！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You won't get away!</Source>
      <Dest>你跑不了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're outmatched!</Source>
      <Dest>你输了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But you don't have any stains on your chest plate.</Source>
      <Dest>但是你的胸甲上根本没有血迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings Gorr, that armor looks like it could use a polish.</Source>
      <Dest>向你问候戈尔,那套盔甲看上去要重新打磨一下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, it looked clean enough, and it was just going to get dusty again anyway and- (Sigh)  I'll get on it right away.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，看起来足够干净啦，反正早晚还是要弄脏（叹气），然后我马上再擦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes Delphine.  I-I believe I swept it this morning.  </Source>
      <Dest>是的，戴尔菲娜。 我……我相信我早上之前会打扫好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To Oblivion and back again.</Source>
      <Dest>进入湮灭走一遭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me. I need your help.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着我。我需要你的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your wish is my command.</Source>
      <Dest>如你所愿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right behind you.</Source>
      <Dest>我紧随在后。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We heading out?  I've got all your equipment cleaned and ready.</Source>
      <Dest>动身吗？我已经整装待发了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What can I do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么可以效劳的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The name's Hjoromir, and I'm just the man for the job.</Source>
      <Dest>我的名字是肖罗密尔, 我是来找工作的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You sure look like you could use some help.</Source>
      <Dest>你看起来就是需要帮忙的样子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>你还有什么事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We heading out?</Source>
      <Dest>我们启程吗？</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
