<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see. Back then, couriers needed to be on foot.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白。当时，信使还需要徒步送信。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nowadays though, I suspect it's more a matter of cost.  Bales of hay and sacks of oats cost a lot of coin.  </Source>
      <Dest>不过，在现在这个时代我觉得更多的是钱的问题。一包包干草和一袋袋燕麦可得花不少钱。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see. Back then, couriers needed to be on foot.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白。当时，信使还需要徒步送信。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stamina potions, on the other hand, are relatively cheap. I suspect the time saved isn't worth the maintenance.</Source>
      <Dest>耐力药水,另一方面,它相对比较便宜。我猜被节省的时间还值不回我的生活费呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see. Back then, couriers needed to be on foot.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白。当时，信使还需要徒步送信。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And if a horse were to die on the road, you'd lose a significant investment.  But if a courier were to die, you could easily replace him at no cost.</Source>
      <Dest>而且，如果一匹马倒在了路上，将会给你带来数目不菲的损失。但如果死的是个邮差，你可以毫不费力地找到替代者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see. Back then, couriers needed to be on foot.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白。当时，信使还需要徒步送信。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know when horses became more valuable than people, but such is the irony of freedom.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道什么时候马比人更有价值,或许这就是对自由的讽刺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't you couriers ever use horses?</Source>
      <Dest>你们做信使的为什么从不骑马呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Partly out of tradition. The first couriers were messengers for rebels and brigands for whom secrecy was paramount.</Source>
      <Dest>一方面出于传统，最初的情报员们都是为那些把保守秘密放在首要位置的人，例如叛徒和强盗来传递消息的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't you couriers ever use horses?</Source>
      <Dest>你们做信使的为什么从不骑马呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A horse tends to attract attention, especially those of the guard placed outside the stables.</Source>
      <Dest>马可以吸引注意力，尤其是对那些被派去盯着马厩的守卫来说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't you couriers ever use horses?</Source>
      <Dest>你们做信使的为什么从不骑马呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The couriers of old were master pickpockets. They could blend in with the crowd and slide the missive right into your tunic as you passed them.</Source>
      <Dest>那些老成的信使可是偷窃大师。他们混入人群之中，并在与你擦肩而过的时候把信件塞进你的长袍里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't you couriers ever use horses?</Source>
      <Dest>你们做信使的为什么从不骑马呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The recipient wouldn't even notice the folded note in their pocket until they were halfway undressed and readying for bed.</Source>
      <Dest>那些收到这个的人根本不会注意到他们口袋里折好的纸条，直至他们脱到一半准备上床睡觉的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Embarrassment?</Source>
      <Dest>Embarrassment?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These hunters, their bodies have such sheen and vigor, like a marble table burnished to a perfect polish.</Source>
      <Dest>这些猎人的尸体如此强健而光泽，就像是把大理石桌子擦干净后那么光滑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Embarrassment?</Source>
      <Dest>Embarrassment?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My skin, however is as piebald as a horse, and as wrinkled as an old tunic, stashed away at the bottom of a chest.</Source>
      <Dest>我的装备藏在柜子的最里面，虽然斑驳的和马皮差不多，皱巴巴的象古代花纹一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Embarrassment?</Source>
      <Dest>Embarrassment?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It may sound a bit odd for an old lady like myself to worry about such things, but while I may be old, I'm still a woman.</Source>
      <Dest>一个像我这样的老女人担心这样的事情听起来很奇怪，但就算是我太老了，我依然是个女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Embarrassment?</Source>
      <Dest>Embarrassment?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And a woman likes to feel beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>女人喜欢觉得自己很漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Isn't it dangerous for someone your age to bathe in the springs alone?</Source>
      <Dest>你这个年龄的人独自在小溪里洗澡不是很危险吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The hunters discourage most of the wildlife, as does the heat from the spring.  They also provide a few spirits to help pass the time.  </Source>
      <Dest>猎人们赶跑了大部分野生物，就像泉水赶跑热量一样。他们也花一些些精力来打发时间。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Isn't it dangerous for someone your age to bathe in the springs alone?</Source>
      <Dest>你这个年龄的人独自在小溪里洗澡不是很危险吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I need a bit of wine before I can get over the embarrassment you see.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我大概需要来点酒来让我忘却刚才在你面前的尴尬行为。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Seven months or so,  maybe eight if I'm lucky...</Source>
      <Dest>七个月左右，如果我幸运的话也许是八个月……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It must have been tough carrying all those stone tablets.</Source>
      <Dest>带走所有这些石桌实在是太困难了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yes, but they did come in handy when young people disrespected their elders, because we could use the tablets to smack them across the face.</Source>
      <Dest>哦是的，可当有年轻人不尊重长者的时候它们确实很好用，因为我可以用那些板子拍他们的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As long as you pay for the food and bed, you won't be a burden.</Source>
      <Dest>等你付得起食物和床了，你就不是个负担了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I do have gold to offer, although the courier's been late with this month's delivery.  They just don't make them like they used to.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我的确可以提供金子，但是这个月的货来得很慢。他们不像以前那样</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As long as you pay for the food and bed, you won't be a burden.</Source>
      <Dest>等你付得起食物和床了，你就不是个负担了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've had to borrow quite a bit of food as of late, but it helps that I don't have much of an appetite.</Source>
      <Dest>我不得不因为晚而借了一些食物 ，不过它让我没了胃口 。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You leech off the miners then.  Make yourself useful and get a pickaxe.</Source>
      <Dest>你占了矿工们的便宜。拿上你的镐好好干。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I'd pick one up, but just to teach an impertinent young fool a little manners.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我确实接到一个，但只是教一个粗鲁的年轻蠢货一些礼节。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You leech off the miners then.  Make yourself useful and get a pickaxe.</Source>
      <Dest>你占了矿工们的便宜。拿上你的镐好好干。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Folks always say that young ones have no respect for their elders.  </Source>
      <Dest>人们总是说年轻人不懂得尊重长辈.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You leech off the miners then.  Make yourself useful and get a pickaxe.</Source>
      <Dest>你占了矿工们的便宜。拿上你的镐好好干。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I used to think it was something old folks say out of some false sense of entitlement.</Source>
      <Dest>我过去认为这是老人说的一些虚假的福利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You leech off the miners then.  Make yourself useful and get a pickaxe.</Source>
      <Dest>你占了矿工们的便宜。拿上你的镐好好干。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it does seem like the older I get, and the younger my conversation partners, the more exercise my switch gets.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来我搞定了年纪大的那些。至于那些我年轻的谈话对象，我得多花点儿功夫了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to this part of Eastmarch?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来了东陲领?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to this part of Eastmarch?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹到东陲领这地上的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Not the mine, that's for sure.  I came to this part of Eastmarch for the hot springs.  I've heard they have the power to rejuvenate.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 不是我的，但我确信无疑。我来东陲领这旮旯就是为了这口温泉。我听说它能让人恢复活力 。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to this part of Eastmarch?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来了东陲领?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to this part of Eastmarch?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹到东陲领这地上的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm not searching for a miracle, or a cure for old age, just a little more time to enjoy it.</Source>
      <Dest>我并不是在奢求奇迹或是长生不老的秘法，仅仅是想有更多的时间，欣赏自己人生的闭幕式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Must've been some storm.</Source>
      <Dest>准有风暴要来了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was.  For a Nord to fear cold is like a fish fearing water.  But this wasn't just any cold, and it wasn't just any storm.</Source>
      <Dest>未必。对于诺德人来说害怕寒冷就像鱼会怕水一样荒谬。但这个可不仅仅是冷的的问题，也不仅仅是场暴风雪的问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I bet you could chip ore better than these louts.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢打赌在采矿这件事上你比这些蠢货们干得好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The miners here do good, honest work.  Even if there's no glamor in it, and no appreciation for their sacrifice.  </Source>
      <Dest>尽管挖矿既无聊又卑微，这里的工人依旧勤奋刻苦地工作着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I bet you could chip ore better than these louts.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢打赌在采矿这件事上你比这些蠢货们干得好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When your armor deflects an arrow, you thank the blacksmith who forged it.  When you rest easy in your home, you thank the builders who fashioned it.</Source>
      <Dest>当你的盔甲挡住箭时，你会感谢打造这盔甲的铁匠。当你在家中休息时，你会感谢替你造房子的工匠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I bet you could chip ore better than these louts.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢打赌在采矿这件事上你比这些蠢货们干得好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet it all starts with those steely men and women who descend bravely into the maw of the earth, picking ore from the walls of its throat.  </Source>
      <Dest>然而一切都是从那些钢铁一样的男人和女人勇敢的降落在地球的肚皮上开始，从它的咽喉壁上开采矿石。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where's the name come from?</Source>
      <Dest>你从那里知道的这个名字？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was once one of two Irises in the village where I grew up, long before I moved to Darkwater Crossing.</Source>
      <Dest>我是我长大的小村落里两朵鸢尾花之一，直到很久之后我搬到了黑水岔口.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where's the name come from?</Source>
      <Dest>你从那里知道的这个名字？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One was about a dozen years younger than I, just a babe when I was a girl.</Source>
      <Dest>有一个比我年轻12岁，在我是女孩的时候他还是个小宝宝呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where's the name come from?</Source>
      <Dest>你从那里知道的这个名字？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So she was Iris the Younger, and I was Iris the Elder, and the name stuck with me ever since.</Source>
      <Dest>所以她是青年艾瑞斯，而我是长老艾瑞斯。从那时起这个名字就跟随我了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Excuse me?</Source>
      <Dest>不好意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, just counting the months I have left to live.  I used to count by the years, and I suspect they'll come a time when I count by the days.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，只是在计算我还有多少个月可以活，这些年我一直在计算，我怀疑当我开始用天数来计算的时候他们就会来临。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Excuse me?</Source>
      <Dest>不好意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's a talent I have, sort of like reading palms.  But I do long for the days when I never bothered to count.</Source>
      <Dest>我的专长有点类似于看手相。但我从事这行的时间已经久得我懒得去计算了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Excuse me?</Source>
      <Dest>不好意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't do it for me, though.  My children just don't like surprises is all.  They want me to send a letter when the day gets close.</Source>
      <Dest>但我不是为了自己才做的，我的孩子们都不喜欢惊喜。那一天快到来的时候，他们想让我送一封信。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Excuse me?</Source>
      <Dest>不好意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry, I haven't properly introduced myself to you, child.</Source>
      <Dest>对不起，我还没有做正式的自我介绍，孩子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Excuse me?</Source>
      <Dest>不好意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My name is Iris the Elder, although it wasn't always meant to reflect my age.</Source>
      <Dest>我叫鸢尾长老，虽然这不是反映我年龄的意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Kynesgrove isn't far from Windhelm. Clearly this man wanted his wife to die.</Source>
      <Dest>基耐森林离风舵城不远，很明显这家伙想让他老婆去死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not so.  Had you lived through that winter, you would've known how fierce it was by the corpses that bloomed in the spring.</Source>
      <Dest>并非如此。如果你亲历过那个冬天。你就会知道它有多么可怕了。看看春天来临时融现出的堆堆白骨便一目了然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Kynesgrove isn't far from Windhelm. Clearly this man wanted his wife to die.</Source>
      <Dest>基耐森林离风舵城不远，很明显这家伙想让他老婆去死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That winter claimed many men of much greater constitution than he.  It was his love for his wife that brought him as far as he did.</Source>
      <Dest>那个冬天给了其他男人比他更多的东西，是他对他妻子的爱让他走到现在.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You Argonians have such brilliant scales.  And you're such good swimmers!</Source>
      <Dest>你们亚龙人的鳞片真是帅气。而且你们泅水的能力也很棒！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As a courier, just once I'd would have liked to put a letter in a bottle, stripped down to my bare skin and delivered it by sea.</Source>
      <Dest>作为一名信差，我有一次差点儿想把那封信装到瓶子里，然后脱得一丝不挂的跳进海里，扑腾着游过去把它送到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Imagine the faces on the recipients as I emerged from the ocean!</Source>
      <Dest>想像一下我从海中浮出来的时候收信人脸上的表情吧！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You Khajiit have such delicate fur, and it never seems to lose its luster the way skin does.</Source>
      <Dest>你们虎人有如此柔顺精美的皮毛，而且它似乎永远不会像皮肤那样失去光泽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>High Elves like yourself have such elegant complexions.  And such stature.</Source>
      <Dest>高精灵喜欢自己漂亮的肤色，和这样的身材。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I never get tired of the blood red eyes of a Dark Elf.  You are such a mysterious and beautiful people.</Source>
      <Dest>我从不会对黑暗精灵血红色的眼睛感到厌倦。你是那么神秘而美丽的种族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You Redguard have such smooth complexions.  Bronzed in the sun of the Alik'r, yet still as soft as a bulb of cotton.</Source>
      <Dest>你们红卫人有如此优雅的面庞，在阿利克尔的阳光下暴晒，却仍然柔软如一团棉花。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is something about you wood folk that is so adorable, it often makes me forget that you are Elves grown.</Source>
      <Dest>你们这些木头家伙有些地方真挺可爱的，我老是忘记你都长成一只精灵啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, an Imperial here in Skyrim!  Be careful, the very sight of you stirs the emotions of many who call this province home.</Source>
      <Dest>啊哈，天际省里的帝国人! 小心, 你的视野唤醒了很多视省为家的人的情绪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You Breton are such a cultured people, but I sense a weariness in you that knows too well the culture of war.</Source>
      <Dest>你是如此一个有教养的布莱顿人，但你这么清楚战争的文化，我都感觉有点儿烦你了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A fellow Nord!  A sight we see less and less these days it seems.  While I do enjoy new faces, I also like the sight of a familiar one.</Source>
      <Dest>一个诺德人老兄！最近好像越来越少看见诺德人啦。虽然我确实喜欢新来的种族，不过也喜欢看到熟悉的面孔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not everyday an Orc graces us with a visit.  I consider myself lucky.  Some may disagree, but I find your people have a raw beauty about you.</Source>
      <Dest>不是所有兽人都有如此优雅的见面。我认为我很幸运。虽然有人不信，但我发现你的人对你有一种原始的美感.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Olive skin, streams of ebony hair, and such prominent teeth!  What about that is displeasing to the eye?</Source>
      <Dest>橄榄色的皮肤，乌木般的秀发，还有突出的尖牙！怎么会不养眼呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I still think you're beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>我依旧认为你很漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you, and here I thought I would never hear such words from one so handsome and charming ever again.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你，而且我认为在这里我再也不会从一个如此英俊迷人的人那里听到这些话了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I still think you're beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>我依旧认为你很漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, when I was young I'd get the occasional suitor, some of them charming and a few that were handsome.  </Source>
      <Dest>当然，在我年轻的时候，偶尔会有一些求婚者。他们中的一些潇洒倜傥，还有一些英俊非凡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I still think you're beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>我依旧认为你很漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were those that were neither, and those were the ones that usually chased the hardest.</Source>
      <Dest>There were those that were neither, and those were the ones that usually chased the hardest.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I still think you're beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>我依旧认为你很漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I could outrun any man, always could, as I was the fastest courier in all of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>But I could outrun any man, always could, as I was the fastest courier in all of Skyrim.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I still think you're beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>我依旧认为你很漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I appreciate the compliment. They say females are the harshest critics when it comes to beauty, and thus your words are strong and my gratitude deep.</Source>
      <Dest>I appreciate the compliment. They say females are the harshest critics when it comes to beauty, and thus your words are strong and my gratitude deep.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I still think you're beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>我依旧认为你很漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, when I was young that criticism would take on a different form.  </Source>
      <Dest>Of course, when I was young that criticism would take on a different form.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I still think you're beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>我依旧认为你很漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It'd turn to jealousy and envy, and there were some women that wanted to chase me out of the village for the way I supposedly taunted their husbands.</Source>
      <Dest>它会变成嫉妒和羡慕，村里有些感觉我嘲笑了她们丈夫的妇女，想用这样的方式赶走我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I still think you're beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>我依旧认为你很漂亮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But they didn't need to.  I never stayed for long.  As a courier I was always running from one village to the next, gone as swiftly as I came.</Source>
      <Dest>但他们不需要这么做。我从不会呆的太久。作为一名信使，我总是会从一个村子跑去下一个村子，来去如风。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We spend so much time honoring some abstract notion of what a laborer is, what a warrior is, and we forget these are individual people.</Source>
      <Dest>我们花了这么多时间，尊重劳动者是一些抽象的概念，一个战士是什么，我们忘了这些人.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People with names and families.  Proud Nord men and women with hopes, desires and fears.</Source>
      <Dest>每个人都有名字和家庭。骄傲的诺德人有希望也有恐惧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you conflate them all, you forget they are many.</Source>
      <Dest>当你把他们全部合并，就会忘了他们有很多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So if you honor the miners here, honor them by name.  Tormir and Sondas, Derkeethus, Annekke and Verner. </Source>
      <Dest>因此如果你要称颂这些矿工，请提起他们的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We spend so much time honoring some abstract notion of what a laborer is, what a warrior is, and we forget these are individual people.</Source>
      <Dest>我们花了这么多时间，尊重劳动者是一些抽象的概念，一个战士是什么，我们忘了这些人.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People with names and families.  Proud Nord men and women with hopes, desires and fears.</Source>
      <Dest>每个人都有名字和家庭。骄傲的诺德人有希望也有恐惧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you conflate them all, you forget they are many.</Source>
      <Dest>当你把他们全部合并，就会忘了他们有很多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So if you wish to honor the miners, honor them by name.  Tormir and Sondas, Annekke and Verner.  And Derkeethus too, were he still here.</Source>
      <Dest>所以说如果你要对他们表达尊重，那就记住他们的名字。托蜜尔和松达斯，安尼克和维纳尔，还有德吉图斯——就假装他还在这儿吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The importance of miners should not be neglected.</Source>
      <Dest>矿工的重要性不容忽视。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, and it often isn't.  Not by Nords.  But I wonder sometimes...if when we raise a toast to the miners, we raise our cups to an idea.</Source>
      <Dest>真的，当通常不是如此。不过不是诺德人。但我怀疑有时候……如果当我们为矿工干杯，我们为一个想法而举杯的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The importance of miners should not be neglected.</Source>
      <Dest>矿工的重要性不容忽视。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The same is true for our warriors and our farmers.</Source>
      <Dest>这同样适用于我们的战士和农民。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do the hot springs work?  Do you feel rejuvenated?</Source>
      <Dest>这温泉起效了吗？你感觉恢复活力了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yes.  I've tried health potions and visited some of the most renowned healers in all of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。 我试过用生命药水也拜访过一些天际省最有名望的医师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do the hot springs work?  Do you feel rejuvenated?</Source>
      <Dest>这温泉起效了吗？你感觉恢复活力了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it's almost like everything is being forced back into place.  It feels so unnatural.</Source>
      <Dest>这几乎就像是所有东西都被迫回到了原来的位置上。这种感觉很不自然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do the hot springs work?  Do you feel rejuvenated?</Source>
      <Dest>这温泉起效了吗？你感觉恢复活力了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That may be fine for someone like yourself, but I much rather prefer a good soak.  All my aches and pains seem to float away.</Source>
      <Dest>这没问题有些人喜欢像你一样，但我更愿意舒舒服服的泡上个澡。身上所有的伤痛都好像漂走了一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I imagine couriers must be fleet of foot to escape the dangers of the road.</Source>
      <Dest>我想信使肯定快速逃走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fleet of foot and single-minded.  There's nothing you can't outrun if you just stick to the road and block your mind of anything outside it.</Source>
      <Dest>专心致志，健步如飞。如果你能坚持自己的道路并且把所有乱七八糟的念头都赶出脑袋的话你就可以超越一切，无所不能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I imagine couriers must be fleet of foot to escape the dangers of the road.</Source>
      <Dest>我想信使肯定快速逃走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The couriers who never make it are always the ones who stop for a breather, or just to admire the view.  </Source>
      <Dest>The couriers who never make it are always the ones who stop for a breather, or just to admire the view.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I imagine couriers must be fleet of foot to escape the dangers of the road.</Source>
      <Dest>我想信使肯定快速逃走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fear is never a good trait for a warrior, but for a courier it can be an excellent source of motivation.</Source>
      <Dest>对于一个战士来说，恐惧永远也不会是一件好事。但是对于信使，它可以说是个完美的动力来源。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I imagine couriers must be fleet of foot to escape the dangers of the road.</Source>
      <Dest>我想信使肯定快速逃走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not just from trolls and bears, but from one's own curiosity.  A mage with a secret can have sharper claws than any sabrecat.</Source>
      <Dest>动力并不仅仅来源于巨魔与巨熊，而是源于一个人的好奇心。一位拥有自己的秘密的法师可是能比一头剑齿虎还能打。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I mine sometimes.  It's a bit tedious, but the gems are valuable.</Source>
      <Dest>有些时候我也会去采矿，虽然是有点乏味，但是宝石可是挺值钱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, if you're lucky, mining can be quite profitable.  But the real reward is the work itself.</Source>
      <Dest>是的,如果你够幸运的话,挖矿是相当有利可图的。但真正的奖励是这项工作本身。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I mine sometimes.  It's a bit tedious, but the gems are valuable.</Source>
      <Dest>有些时候我也会去采矿，虽然是有点乏味，但是宝石可是挺值钱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That much I learned from my days as a courier.  Hard work means strength of body, and strength of mind.</Source>
      <Dest>That much I learned from my days as a courier.  Hard work means strength of body, and strength of mind.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I mine sometimes.  It's a bit tedious, but the gems are valuable.</Source>
      <Dest>有些时候我也会去采矿，虽然是有点乏味，但是宝石可是挺值钱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nobles scoff at such a notion.  They think wealth is spending your days bathing in pools of wine, sucking on grapes plumper than chaurus eggs.</Source>
      <Dest>贵族们嘲笑这种想法。他们认为财富意味着花整天时间把自己泡在酒池里，吮吸比查鲁斯卵还多汁的葡萄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I mine sometimes.  It's a bit tedious, but the gems are valuable.</Source>
      <Dest>有些时候我也会去采矿，虽然是有点乏味，但是宝石可是挺值钱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But they suffer from a poverty of spirit, and a dearth of vitality. </Source>
      <Dest>但是他们忍受精神上的缺乏，肉体上无能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of the people at Darkwater Crossing?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么看待那些在黑水岔路口的人们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good people, and an eclectic group.  I think Hrefna is quite blessed to be surrounded by such diversity.</Source>
      <Dest>大好人，和事佬。我觉得荷夫娜周围都是这样的人算是她的福气吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of the people at Darkwater Crossing?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么看待那些在黑水岔路口的人们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Derkeethus taught her how to swim, and Sondas is twice the man her father ever was.  </Source>
      <Dest>德吉图斯教她如何游泳，而松达斯则一如既往的第二次成为她的父亲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of the people at Darkwater Crossing?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么看待那些在黑水岔路口的人们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I find it rather adorable how she scurries around with that pickaxe too.</Source>
      <Dest>并且，我觉得她拿着斧头狂奔是那么可爱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of the people at Darkwater Crossing?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么看待那些在黑水岔路口的人们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's good to see young folk take an interest in such honest labor.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴看到年轻人热衷于诚实劳动啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure you were quite the catch back in the Merethic Era.</Source>
      <Dest>我确信是你把我们从米拉克时代带回来了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And you were quite the petulant baby two seconds ago, when you asked such a rude and disrespectful question.</Source>
      <Dest>刚刚你问起那个粗鲁又无礼的问题时，你看起来简直就是个不懂事的小孩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure you were quite the catch back in the Merethic Era.</Source>
      <Dest>我确信是你把我们从米拉克时代带回来了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your parents should be ashamed to have raised one with such little tact.</Source>
      <Dest>你的父母应该为养了你这么个只会耍小聪明的家伙而感到耻辱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure you were quite the catch back in the Merethic Era.</Source>
      <Dest>我确信是你把我们从米拉克时代带回来了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I may not look it, but in my youth I was also known as Iris the Swift, the fastest courier in all of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>或许我没亲眼见过，但从小我就知道斯威夫特家的艾瑞斯，天际省速度最快的信使。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Mining is fool's work.  You're a fool for praising them.</Source>
      <Dest>挖矿是愚蠢人干的，赞美他们你就是个蠢货。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such a sassy young lass.  It seems your mother never introduced you to the backside of her hand.  Perhaps I will introduce you to mine.</Source>
      <Dest>真是个无礼的小姑娘。看起来你妈妈从来没让你尝过她的巴掌。也许我应该让你尝尝我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Mining is fool's work.  You're a fool for praising them.</Source>
      <Dest>挖矿是愚蠢人干的，赞美他们你就是个蠢货。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such an impolite young lad.  It seems your mother never introduced you to the backside of her hand.  Perhaps I will introduce you to mine.</Source>
      <Dest>如此无礼的年轻人。看起来你的母亲把你宠坏了，也许我该教教你什么是礼节。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hunters can't protect you from a dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>猎人们无法从巨龙的魔爪下保护你.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True enough, but my legs can.  I may not look it, but in my youth I was also known as Iris the Swift, the fastest courier in all of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，不过我的腿可以。我可能确实没遇到过 ，但在我年轻的时候我被称作飞毛腿艾里斯，我是天际省内最快的信使 。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a story from your courier days.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲你送货时的那些故事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I remember my first job.  A courier fresher than the morning dew, asked to deliver a letter to an ornery and cantankerous Jarl.</Source>
      <Dest>我永远都忘不了我第一份工作。作为一个比晨露还新的信差新人，居然要去给一个暴戾肆恣的领主送信。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a story from your courier days.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲你送货时的那些故事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I recall how frightened I was entering that great hall, how the sound echoed through the chamber, and even the dust seemed to curtsy as it settled.</Source>
      <Dest>回想那时我走进那个大厅我是多么恐惧啊，还有那内庭中回响的声音，甚至就连灰尘都好像本来就是活的一样在行礼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a story from your courier days.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲你送货时的那些故事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The lords carried themselves with that air of nobility, postures straighter than a fence post.</Source>
      <Dest>The lords carried themselves with that air of nobility, postures straighter than a fence post.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a story from your courier days.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲你送货时的那些故事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet my eyes were drawn to an Argonian envoy, the first I had ever seen. I know it wasn't polite, but I couldn't help but stare.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，在我第一眼看见那个蜥蜴人特使时，我就被吸引住了。我知道这有点不太礼貌，但我就是忍不住盯着看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a story from your courier days.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲你送货时的那些故事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In the light his scales were a dazzle of colors, set off by majestic horns that were circled by rings of gold.</Source>
      <Dest>在阳光的照耀下，他的鳞片闪闪发光，其上装饰着由金制套环所包裹着的华丽号角。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a story from your courier days.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲你送货时的那些故事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How wondrous it must have been to be a Jarl, I thought, to meet such exotic people and see such fascinating things.</Source>
      <Dest>我想，成为领主以后的日子该有多么地刺激啊，能够遇上那么多异国之人，能见识到那么多奇妙之事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a story from your courier days.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲你送货时的那些故事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet as I waited to deliver my letter, the Jarl did nothing but complain, about the size of her Longhouse and the tediousness of her station.</Source>
      <Dest>而当我等着递信的时候，领主那二货就在那儿一个劲地抱怨，长屋不够大啦，做领主很单调乏味啦什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's your favorite courier story?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢的信使故事是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was Evening Star, two hours to midnight.  Me and the other couriers were at the inn, picking the snow off our boots, ready to call it a night.</Source>
      <Dest>那是星夜，还有两小时到半夜，我和其他快递员在酒馆里正把鞋里的雪抖出来，准备收工。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's your favorite courier story?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢的信使故事是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The snowstorm that night was the fiercest in years, and the inn was densely packed. Not a soul in Eastmarch was outside that night, or so we thought.</Source>
      <Dest>那夜的暴风雪是近年来最为激烈的一次，旅店密密麻麻的坐落着。那一夜东陲领没有一个灵魂在外漂泊，或者像我们想的那样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's your favorite courier story?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢的信使故事是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The door flung open to reveal a young Nord man, covered head to toe in thick furs, and thicker snow.</Source>
      <Dest>The door flung open to reveal a young Nord man, covered head to toe in thick furs, and thicker snow.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's your favorite courier story?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢的信使故事是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The innkeeper sat him down and gave him some hot tea.  The blood was only now beginning to thaw from his nose.</Source>
      <Dest>旅馆主人让他坐下，然后给了他些热茶。这时他全身的血液才逐渐暖和过来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's your favorite courier story?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢的信使故事是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He began to mumble, softly but desperately.  Trying to form the words.</Source>
      <Dest>他开始含含糊糊地叙说，竭尽全力使语气放得平缓一些。 努力试着说出连贯的话语。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's your favorite courier story?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢的信使故事是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>His wife, he said, had just given birth, but the bleeding would not stop.</Source>
      <Dest>他的妻子，他说是刚刚生产过，可是止不住血。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's your favorite courier story?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢的信使故事是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He needed a special health potion, but the alchemist in Windhelm was out on research, and the next closest lived in the old shack west of Ivarstead.</Source>
      <Dest>他需要一种特殊的治疗药水，但风舵城的炼金术士外出研究去了，另一个最靠近的炼金术师住在紫杉镇西的老木屋里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's your favorite courier story?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢的信使故事是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He wanted a horse, but the stablemaster had refused him. He tried to go on foot, but only made it as far as Kynesgrove.</Source>
      <Dest>他想要一匹马，但是马厩主人拒绝了他。他试着步行前往，但是也只到了基耐树林就作罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The innkeep, an old woman but one of conviction, took to pleading on his behalf. She went to warriors, to sellswords, but none would lend an ear.</Source>
      <Dest>作为旅店经营者，一个虽老却充满信念的女人，代表他去恳求别人，她走向那些战士，走向那些佣兵，但却没有一个人会倾听她的诉说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So she leapt on the table and scolded them. "This man's wife is in Candlehearth Hall fighting for her life, and he has naught the strength to go on."</Source>
      <Dest>所以她跳上桌子斥责他们。 "这个男人的老婆在烛炉堂旅店为她的生活奋斗,这个男人却没有能力继续"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who among his fellow Nords will lend a hand in his time of need? "Is there any man here willing to risk his life for a cause that is noble?"</Source>
      <Dest>Who among his fellow Nords will lend a hand in his time of need? "Is there any man here willing to risk his life for a cause that is noble?"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The others shied away.  But I stood.  "I am," I said, and without another word, I rushed out the door.</Source>
      <Dest>其他人都回避了，但我还站在那儿。”是我。”我说，然后不再多说什么话，就赶紧冲出门去。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I didn't know what pushed me more, my desire to prove myself, or my fury at the cowardice displayed by my fellow Nords.  Maybe a little of both.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道是什么让我这么干的，我希望能证明我自己，或者说是我对我的诺德同伴所显露的胆怯产生的愤怒。或者说两者兼有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Regardless, I braved the elements, the pounding snow and the unforgiving cold, to retrieve the potion and return to Windhelm.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我敢于面对元素之力，直击风雪，直面凛冬，只为取回药剂以及返回风舵城。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I lost a toe that night, and I still can't feel my all fingers.  And for all my efforts, I wasn't even paid.</Source>
      <Dest>在那一晚上，我失去了一根脚趾头，而我的手指至今都还未恢复知觉。我付出了那么多，却连一点回报都没有得到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it was payment enough to see the face on the man's wife as she held her newborn.</Source>
      <Dest>但在看到那个男人的妻子举起她的宝宝时候的面孔时，我感觉报酬已经足够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure your wisdom alone more than compensates the people of this village.</Source>
      <Dest>我确信单单以你的智慧就足以抵偿整个村子的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your words are kind, but a woman of my years is more of a nuisance than a helpful member of the community.</Source>
      <Dest>你的话是好意，可我那个年代的女人更多是讨厌的角色而不是有用的社会成员。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure your wisdom alone more than compensates the people of this village.</Source>
      <Dest>我确信单单以你的智慧就足以抵偿整个村子的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I try to do what I can, help cook or look after Hrefna, but as much as I hate to admit it, she's at an age where I can't keep pace.</Source>
      <Dest>我试着做力所能及的事，帮忙下厨或者照顾赫丽芙娜，可是我真不想说，她正处在我跟不上拍的年龄上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, child.</Source>
      <Dest>孩子，你好啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What brings you to this part of Eastmarch?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来了东陲领?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What brings you to this part of Eastmarch?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹到东陲领这地上的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How can I help you?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么我能效劳的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
