<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I forgot.  Something called "saving the world" took precedence.</Source>
      <Dest>我忘了 我要先去“拯救世界”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) I see Dragonborn.  As Master Meronin would say, it is my fault for leaving such task to one who had naught the time.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)我明白了，龙裔。因为马荣尼大师曾经说过，把这样的任务交托给一个浪费时间的人，是我的错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I forgot.  Something called "saving the world" took precedence.</Source>
      <Dest>我忘了 我要先去“拯救世界”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps she will forgive me for not having another option.</Source>
      <Dest>或许她会原谅我的别无选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I forgot.  Something called "saving the world" took precedence.</Source>
      <Dest>我忘了 我要先去“拯救世界”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can only hope that one day, Avassa and I will meet in death, and she will take pity on this worthless beggar once more.</Source>
      <Dest>我只希望终于有一天， Avassa 跟我在冥界相会，她还能给我这没用的乞丐再一次的怜悯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I forgot.  Something called "saving the world" took precedence.</Source>
      <Dest>我忘了 我要先去“拯救世界”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sugar and sands friend.  Tell my master I will be waiting for her on the other side.</Source>
      <Dest>愿月亮糖与沙与你同在,吾友。告诉我的主人，我会在另一边等她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No.  Something called "saving the world" took precedence.</Source>
      <Dest>不，还有一件事情叫做拯救世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) I see Dragonborn.  As Master Meronin would say, it is my fault for leaving such task to one who had naught the time.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)我明白了，龙裔。因为马荣尼大师曾经说过，把这样的任务交托给一个浪费时间的人，是我的错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No.  Something called "saving the world" took precedence.</Source>
      <Dest>不，还有一件事情叫做拯救世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps she will forgive me for not having another option.</Source>
      <Dest>或许她会原谅我的别无选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No.  Something called "saving the world" took precedence.</Source>
      <Dest>不，还有一件事情叫做拯救世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can only hope that one day, Avassa and I will meet in death, and she will take pity on this worthless beggar once more.</Source>
      <Dest>我只希望终于有一天， Avassa 跟我在冥界相会，她还能给我这没用的乞丐再一次的怜悯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No.  Something called "saving the world" took precedence.</Source>
      <Dest>不，还有一件事情叫做拯救世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sugar and sands friend.  Tell my master I will be waiting for her on the other side.</Source>
      <Dest>愿月亮糖与沙与你同在,吾友。告诉我的主人，我会在另一边等她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry.  I delivered your message as you asked.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心.  我已经照你的要求把消息送到了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I am forever in your debt.  By doing this deed, you have filled this cat's heart with joy.</Source>
      <Dest>Then I am forever in your debt.  By doing this deed, you have filled this cat's heart with joy.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry.  I delivered your message as you asked.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心.  我已经照你的要求把消息送到了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if she got the message!  Perhaps then, before I leave this mortal plane, I will find the twin moons once more, and look for her reply.  </Source>
      <Dest>我真想知道她是否得到了那消息！也许，在我离开这世界之前，我会再一次找到那双生之月，并且寻觅到她的回音。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry.  I delivered your message as you asked.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心.  我已经照你的要求把消息送到了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sugar and sands friend.  Tell my master I will be waiting for her on the other side.</Source>
      <Dest>愿月亮糖与沙与你同在,吾友。告诉我的主人，我会在另一边等她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Olivia has softened up a bit from when we first met.</Source>
      <Dest>自我们第一次见面後，奥莉薇雅已经有所软化了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is her way.  I have watched Master Meronin instruct many a young student.  She is harsh to begin with, if only to disarm them.</Source>
      <Dest>那就是她的风格。我见过马荣尼大师教导一个年轻的学生。She is harsh to begin with, if only to disarm them.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Olivia has softened up a bit from when we first met.</Source>
      <Dest>自我们第一次见面後，奥莉薇雅已经有所软化了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then she is kinder, just when it is needed. In this way, she can be comforting, without ever having to be gentle.</Source>
      <Dest>Then she is kinder, just when it is needed. In this way, she can be comforting, without ever having to be gentle.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Olivia has softened up a bit from when we first met.</Source>
      <Dest>自我们第一次见面後，奥莉薇雅已经有所软化了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But take heed.  If you think her sands warm, the old firebrand will rise once more to burn you.</Source>
      <Dest>但留心点。如果你认为她的【细沙】很温暖，这个【年老的放火者】将再次提升温度以此灼烧于你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not angry at all.  It's part of what makes me so charming.</Source>
      <Dest>我一点也不生气，因为那也成了让我更有魅力的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) That you are.  If I had half of your wit, perhaps I would have been a more successful beggar.  But then, I would not be a mage.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑声）就是这样。要是我有你一般聪明，我肯定能当一个更出色的乞丐。但就算这样，我也不会去当法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not angry at all.  It's part of what makes me so charming.</Source>
      <Dest>我一点也不生气，因为那也成了让我更有魅力的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So friend, let us be thankful for the things we are, and the things we are not.</Source>
      <Dest>所以嘛朋友，咱们要感激自己身为什么，同时也庆幸不是别的什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I can totally picture her saying that.</Source>
      <Dest>她所说的我完全了解。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She believes in discipline, but I imagine it is because one such as I was sorely in need of it.</Source>
      <Dest>她相信戒律,但我猜想那是因为像我这样的人需要约束.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I can totally picture her saying that.</Source>
      <Dest>她所说的我完全了解。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A house cat may need to be petted.  An alley cat needs to know that his master's claws are sharper.</Source>
      <Dest>家猫可能需要被宠爱。野猫只需要认识到它的主人锋利的爪子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should speak with Olivia.  She's in the next hall.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该和奥利维亚谈谈. 她在旁边的大厅里.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I should...but would you believe me if I said I am frightened she would scold me?</Source>
      <Dest>我真的应该…但是如果我说我害怕她责骂我，你会相信吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should speak with Olivia.  She's in the next hall.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该和奥利维亚谈谈. 她在旁边的大厅里.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your presence is distracting me! she'd say, "We can talk later!  There's still important work to be done!"</Source>
      <Dest>Your presence is distracting me! she'd say, "We can talk later!  There's still important work to be done!"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should speak with Olivia.  She's in the next hall.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该和奥利维亚谈谈. 她在旁边的大厅里.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And she would be right.  But I thought maybe, you would not be so angry to see a friendly face.</Source>
      <Dest>她也许是对的。但是我觉得，看到一张友善的脸，也许你就不会那么生气了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>About that last request...</Source>
      <Dest>关于最后一个请求……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right.  I know you told me you would not, but perhaps you changed your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>是的。我知道你告诉过我你不会那么做，但也许你改变了主意？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>About that last request...</Source>
      <Dest>关于最后一个请求……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yes, did you by chance deliver the message?</Source>
      <Dest>哦没错，那你正好是去带个信吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Laugh) Yes, the day we met you called me a liar.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑）是啊，我们第一次见面的时候，你说我是骗子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That I did.  Even worse, I called you green.  How foolish do I look now, to have been so wrong on both counts.</Source>
      <Dest>是我干的。甚至更糟，我曾叫你绿皮。鉴于我已经在这两件事上错的这么离谱，我现在看起来有多蠢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Laugh) Yes, the day we met you called me a liar.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑）是啊，我们第一次见面的时候，你说我是骗子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is the gap between myself and Master Meronin.  She saw in you what I could not, even when her vision was clouded by choices.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我和马荣尼师傅间的差距，她能在你身上看见我前所未见的那面。就算她的双眼出于选择已经模糊不清了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Agh!  Get away from me you hideous phantom!</Source>
      <Dest>啊～！滚开你这怪物离我远点！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, I apologize for frightening you. I often forget I have no fur.  Or anything else, for that matter.</Source>
      <Dest>啊哈，很抱歉袭击了你，我老忘了自己身上没长毛儿，或者是其他诸如此类的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Agh!  Get away from me you hideous phantom!</Source>
      <Dest>啊～！滚开你这怪物离我远点！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But given that I was once a beggar, you learn to make do with nothing.</Source>
      <Dest>但是想到我曾经是乞丐，你得学会凑合过活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Agh!  Get away from me you hideous phantom!</Source>
      <Dest>啊～！滚开你这怪物离我远点！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was the one you met at Shadowgreen Cavern.  You knew me as Master Meronin's assistant, Jadro'Ra.  </Source>
      <Dest>我是你在绿影洞穴遇见的那个人。你知道的，我是马荣尼的助手，贾卓’拉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you Jadro'Ra.</Source>
      <Dest>见到你真好，贾卓’拉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I am happy to say I am alive and well.  I mean, just well.  Old habits, you know.</Source>
      <Dest>对，我很高兴的告诉你我还健在。我的意思是说还不错。老毛病，你懂得。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you Jadro'Ra.</Source>
      <Dest>见到你真好，贾卓’拉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is a strange place...the other side, yet exciting.  Like when Master Meronin took me to the university all those years ago.</Source>
      <Dest>这是个奇怪的地方……另一面来说，也很令人兴奋。就像是马荣尼大师领我来到学院的那时候一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Better for you maybe.  I already have regrets.</Source>
      <Dest>或许对你来说更好，我已经开始后悔了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs)Regrets are something I know well, Dragonborn, but in this case, I think I would regret giving you any advice.  </Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)我对一些事感到很遗憾。 龙裔，但在这件事上，我想我无法给你任何建议。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Better for you maybe.  I already have regrets.</Source>
      <Dest>或许对你来说更好，我已经开始后悔了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have nothing to be ashamed of.  Nelos was evil.  His words may be sugar, but I am proof his actions are a bitter taste.</Source>
      <Dest>你没有什么好觉得羞耻的。纳洛斯是坏蛋。嘴里说的是甜言蜜语，但我保证他干的事都是心狠手辣的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, we meet again Dragonborn, but this time, under better circumstances.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，又见面了龙裔，不过这次的情况好得多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>.</Source>
      <Dest>。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>By the twin moons, I like moon sugar.</Source>
      <Dest>在两个月亮之间，我喜欢月糖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?  Only a simpleton would create such a foolish and derogatory passphrase.</Source>
      <Dest>什么？只有脑残才会想出这么一个傻逼而弱智的密码。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Relax.  I'm a friend of Olivia Meronin.</Source>
      <Dest>放轻松，我是奥莉薇雅·梅洛妮的朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Liar!  Master Meronin would not trust one so green.  </Source>
      <Dest>谎言！梅洛妮大师不会信任毫无经验的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Um...I forget.  Which moon is Masser?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯...我忘了。哪一个月亮是玛萨尔？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My apologies.  It is the larger moon, the one bathed in color of blood. The color of me, apparently.  (Laughs) (Coughs) In any case, I thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>我道歉。是那个血色的大月亮。显然也是我的颜色。（笑声）（咳嗽）不管怎么样我得谢谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Um...I forget.  Which moon is Masser?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯...我忘了。哪一个月亮是玛萨尔？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet there is still the matter of the notes, yes?</Source>
      <Dest>但笔记上还存在问题，对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Enough of your sob story, what about the notes?</Source>
      <Dest>别再提你那些悲惨故事了，说说那张字条如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fine.  Perhaps this Khajiit will see her in the next life.  The notes I have.</Source>
      <Dest>Fine.  Perhaps this Khajiit will see her in the next life.  The notes I have.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could find her and tell her how little you've changed.</Source>
      <Dest>我会找到她并告诉她你基本没什么变化。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Even then she would defend me, for that is the depth of her grace. This Khajiit would tell her himself, if he could see the open sky.</Source>
      <Dest>Even then she would defend me, for that is the depth of her grace. This Khajiit would tell her himself, if he could see the open sky.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could find her and tell her how little you've changed.</Source>
      <Dest>我会找到她并告诉她你基本没什么变化。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You see, on some nights, you could stare at the Twin Moons sitting in the heavens like a pair of mismatched eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>比如，有的夜晚，你可以盯着天上的两个月亮想象它们是一对大小不同的眼睛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could find her and tell her how little you've changed.</Source>
      <Dest>我会找到她并告诉她你基本没什么变化。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She told this foolish beggar that if one Khajiit prayed to Masser, and another prayed to Secunda, they could communicate through the stars.</Source>
      <Dest>她跟这个愚蠢的乞丐说，如果一个虎人向玛撒尔祈祷，而另一个跟塞康达祈祷，他们就可以和星辰沟通了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could find her and tell her how little you've changed.</Source>
      <Dest>我会找到她并告诉她你基本没什么变化。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Her moon was Secunda, and mine Masser.  So my final request is this.  The next time you look at the night sky and see the moons in flight, tell her.</Source>
      <Dest>她的月亮是塞康达，而我的则是玛撒尔。所以我最后的请求是，下次当你仰望夜空看见月亮悬在天空时，告诉她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could find her and tell her how little you've changed.</Source>
      <Dest>我会找到她并告诉她你基本没什么变化。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell her I am sorry, and that I never had a better friend.  Or a kinder one.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉她我很抱歉,我从来没有一个更好的朋友。或者说是一个善良的朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were young, and ambitious.  It was wrong, but you know better now.</Source>
      <Dest>那时你还很年轻，很自负，那样不好。现在可是成熟得多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You would not be so kind if I were not dying, I presume.  She was much the same.  She could have been angry with me, but instead she granted my wish.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我没死的话，你不会变成这个样子，我想。她也一样。她可一直在生我的气，而却还是满足了我的愿望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were young, and ambitious.  It was wrong, but you know better now.</Source>
      <Dest>那时你还很年轻，很自负，那样不好。现在可是成熟得多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Many times I would pass her on the street, and say nothing.  My eyes told her all she needed to know, and nothing she wanted to hear.</Source>
      <Dest>很多很多次，我在她面前默默走过,我的眼神足够告诉她我要说的一切，没有任何是她想听的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Suit yourself.  You can either take a chance on me, or die.  Your choice.</Source>
      <Dest>随你便。你可以选择我，或者选择死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You are right.  It is likely Master Meronin did not remember the passphrase.  </Source>
      <Dest>你说对了。看起来，似乎马荣尼大师没有记住那些通行口令。.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Suit yourself.  You can either take a chance on me, or die.  Your choice.</Source>
      <Dest>随你便。你可以选择我，或者选择死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When it comes to magic she is a brilliant mind, but with languages she stumbles about like blind man on a lake of ice.</Source>
      <Dest>魔法的话她很擅长，但是语言表达上就不行，总是结结巴巴，战战兢兢，如履薄冰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Suit yourself.  You can either take a chance on me, or die.  Your choice.</Source>
      <Dest>随你便。你可以选择我，或者选择死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Better to bury knowledge in the sand than provide an oasis to those who lack virtue.</Source>
      <Dest>宁愿把知识埋入荒漠也不要用来给无道之人撑起绿荫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A clever trick, but enough stories. We need to get you somewhere safe.</Source>
      <Dest>聪明的伎俩，不过到此为止了。看来我们得把你送到更“安全”的地方去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I am afraid this cat has exhausted all of its lives. </Source>
      <Dest>不，我恐怕这只小猫已经劳苦了一辈子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A clever trick, but enough stories. We need to get you somewhere safe.</Source>
      <Dest>聪明的伎俩，不过到此为止了。看来我们得把你送到更“安全”的地方去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, if you would be so kind, perhaps you would be willing to listen to a dying Khajiit's final request.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，如果你是个好心人的话，也许你会愿意聆听一个垂死虎人最后的请求。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you manage to keep the notes?</Source>
      <Dest>你如何保存那些笔记的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I brought many sets of clothes, in order to fashion a story. When I met the Dunmer at the inn, I was dressed as a farmer. </Source>
      <Dest>我带来了很多套衣服，为了让这看起来像一回事。当我在旅馆遇到一个黑暗精灵，我会把自己扮作一个农民。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you manage to keep the notes?</Source>
      <Dest>你如何保存那些笔记的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I shadowed him here, I came dressed as a thief.  The mage assumed the first was a disguise, and the second my true form.  </Source>
      <Dest>我跟踪他来到这里时，穿的就像个小偷。那名法师以为最先的那次不过是个伪装，第二次才是我的真实外貌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you manage to keep the notes?</Source>
      <Dest>你如何保存那些笔记的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Were I not a Khajiit, it is possible he would see past this disguise to the truth.  </Source>
      <Dest>Were I not a Khajiit, it is possible he would see past this disguise to the truth.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you manage to keep the notes?</Source>
      <Dest>你如何保存那些笔记的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, like most illusions, the spell works best on those who wish to believe.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，如同多数幻象一样，法术会在迷信的人身上得到最大的发挥。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vaba Thjizzrini.</Source>
      <Dest>Vaba Thjizzrini.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, that is the passphrase.  "It is a foolish concept."  Such was how she viewed all things Khajiit, and how Khajiit view all things Imperial.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，就是这个暗号：“【真是个愚蠢的想法】。”这就是她对所有虎人的看法，也是虎人对所有帝国人的看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vaba Thjizzrini.</Source>
      <Dest>Vaba Thjizzrini.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am surprised to discover she did not forget it.  Pleasantly, of course.</Source>
      <Dest>我很惊讶地发现她没有忘记它。真让人愉快，当然啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll take the notes to Meronin.</Source>
      <Dest>我将把这些笔记带给梅洛妮.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you friend.  With that this cat can rest easy.  Tell Olivia not to blame herself.  Her teachings did not fail me.  </Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你，我的朋友。这样我这只猫就能轻松地休息（安息？）了。告诉奥莉薇雅别内疚，[并不是她的教导让我失败的]。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll take the notes to Meronin.</Source>
      <Dest>我将把这些笔记带给梅洛妮.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They are what gave this poor beggar a reason to live, and honor in death.</Source>
      <Dest>他们给了这个贫穷的乞丐一个活着的理由，和死去的尊严。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could find her for you.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以帮你找到她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, that is not necessary.  You see, on some nights, you could stare at the Twin Moons sitting in the heavens like a pair of mismatched eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>不，那是不必要的。你瞧，在某些夜晚，你可以凝视着双生的月亮端坐在星空之上，就像是一对大小不一的眼睛。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could find her for you.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以帮你找到她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She told this foolish beggar that if one Khajiit prayed to Masser, and another prayed to Secunda, they could communicate through the stars.</Source>
      <Dest>她跟这个愚蠢的乞丐说，如果一个虎人向玛撒尔祈祷，而另一个跟塞康达祈祷，他们就可以和星辰沟通了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could find her for you.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以帮你找到她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Her moon was Secunda, and mine Masser.  So my final request is this.  The next time you look at the night sky and see the moons in flight, tell her.</Source>
      <Dest>她的月亮是塞康达，而我的则是玛撒尔。所以我最后的请求是，下次当你仰望夜空看见月亮悬在天空时，告诉她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could find her for you.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以帮你找到她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell her I am sorry, and that I never had a better friend.  Or a kinder one.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉她我很抱歉,我从来没有一个更好的朋友。或者说是一个善良的朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps it is the result of being a Khajiit.  But I followed.  And he noticed.  And so he led me here.</Source>
      <Dest>也许那就是做一只虎人的结果吧。不我跟上了。他也注意到了。于是就带我到了这儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is only by virtue of Master Meronin's teachings that I managed to hold on to the document.</Source>
      <Dest>It is only by virtue of Master Meronin's teachings that I managed to hold on to the document.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who was he?</Source>
      <Dest>他是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He was a Dunmer man, with a wisp of thick hair, eyes as hot as the sands of Elsweyr, and wings of crimson war paint gliding down his face.</Source>
      <Dest>他是一个暗精灵男人，浓密的头发被扎成发束，眼睛如艾斯维尔德沙子般炽热，深红的翼状战纹顺着脸颊展开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who was he?</Source>
      <Dest>他是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In his presence, this Khajiit did not move, could not move.  Yet all his fur stood on end.</Source>
      <Dest>有他在场，你面前的虎人就不敢移动，无法移动。然而他的寒毛却根根直竖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who was he?</Source>
      <Dest>他是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When he left, I should have run back to Master Meronin, but I have always been a bit of an overachiever.</Source>
      <Dest>当他走的时候，我本应该跑回去找梅洛妮大师的，但我做事总有那么一点做得好过头了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you get injured?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么受的伤？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is the fault of my own hubris.  Gulum-Ei charged a stiff price, but true to his word, what he possessed was worth every septim.</Source>
      <Dest>那是我自己的傲慢造成的苦果， Gulum-Ei说他的东西不二价，但是他确实信守诺言，他手里的东西值得我付出所有的钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you get injured?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么受的伤？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The notes he stole contained five prospective locations where the mages planned to conduct their separate research.  </Source>
      <Dest>他所偷走的那些笔记上记录了五个预期地点，这些地点都是那些法师们打算对他们各自的研究进行管理的地方。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you get injured?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么受的伤？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As per Master Meronin's instructions, I was to return to her with this information.  I was about to do so, when I saw the mage descend from his room.</Source>
      <Dest>遵照马荣尼大师的命令，我要带着这份消息回复他复她，正当我准备如此时，我看到那个法师从他的屋子里走了下来</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Krin, Renrij.</Source>
      <Dest>Krin, Renrij.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Smile, scum?  Is that some kind of joke?  This Khajiit does not find it funny as he sits on the brink of the void.</Source>
      <Dest>Smile, scum?  Is that some kind of joke?  This Khajiit does not find it funny as he sits on the brink of the void.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a horrible beast.</Source>
      <Dest>你是头可怕的野兽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This I know.  I desperately wanted respect, you see, and it was hard enough being a beggar, and a Khajiit.  I...I was ashamed to call her a friend.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道。我极度渴望得到尊重，你看，作为一个乞丐，一个虎人，举步维艰啊。我……我耻于与她为伍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a horrible beast.</Source>
      <Dest>你是头可怕的野兽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Many times I would pass her on the street, and say nothing.  My eyes told her all she needed to know, and nothing she wanted to hear.</Source>
      <Dest>很多很多次，我在她面前默默走过,我的眼神足够告诉她我要说的一切，没有任何是她想听的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine, furball. Die in this hollow cavern. I hope the bears chew off your face.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，毛球。你就死在这个洞穴里吧，祝你的脸被那些熊给撕碎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait!  Perhaps this Khajiit was hasty to judge.  Master Meronin would have entrusted you with a passphrase, to distinguish foe from friend.</Source>
      <Dest>等一下！也许对这个虎人判断的太草率了。马荣尼大师应该给你个暗号什么的来区分敌友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She said you looked unhappy, but your eyes were bright.</Source>
      <Dest>她说你看起来不高兴了，可我看你的眼睛很亮呀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is not the passphrase.  And while the first part sounds like the Master, the second seems a bit too...kind.  What else did she say?</Source>
      <Dest>那不是密码。况且相对而言第一部分听起来口气像主人，第二部分就有那么点太...和善了。她还说了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just be quick about it.</Source>
      <Dest>赶紧搞定算了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I was but a beggar, there was a Khajiit female who provided me with alms.  She was a poor farmer, but wealthy with kindness.</Source>
      <Dest>曾经我只是一个穷乞丐的时候，有个虎人女子给我酒喝。她是个贫穷的农民，可是富有的是善良。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just be quick about it.</Source>
      <Dest>赶紧搞定算了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such was her kindness that she considered my pride.  While others tossed their septims with disdain, she traded her alms for petty magic tricks.</Source>
      <Dest>肯定我的自尊就是她的善良所在。当别人都是带着鄙夷扔下金币时，她却要求用漂亮的魔法把戏交易捐款。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just be quick about it.</Source>
      <Dest>赶紧搞定算了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I still remember how her ears perked up ever so softly whenever I would conjure an orb of light into my palm.  </Source>
      <Dest>我依然记得当我召唤一个光球落入我的手掌中时她的耳朵会怎样柔和地竖起。   </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just be quick about it.</Source>
      <Dest>赶紧搞定算了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was during one of these tricks that Master Meronin recognized my talent.  Finally, I thought, this Khajiit will earn real respect.</Source>
      <Dest>我就是靠这些技巧赢得了梅罗尼大师的认可。我想道，我这亚龙人想来是终究能获得他人发自内心的尊重了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just be quick about it.</Source>
      <Dest>赶紧搞定算了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No one was more proud of me than the farmer.  Yet in the months that followed...I changed.  Suddenly it was I who could not associate with her.</Source>
      <Dest>没有比那个农场主更为我骄傲的人了。但在随后的几个月里……我改变了。突然之间，我就不能和她好好交往了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I was but a beggar, there was a Khajiit female who provided me with alms.  She was a poor farmer, but wealthy with kindness.</Source>
      <Dest>曾经我只是一个穷乞丐的时候，有个虎人女子给我酒喝。她是个贫穷的农民，可是富有的是善良。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such was her kindness that she considered my pride.  While others tossed their septims with disdain, she traded her alms for petty magic tricks.</Source>
      <Dest>肯定我的自尊就是她的善良所在。当别人都是带着鄙夷扔下金币时，她却要求用漂亮的魔法把戏交易捐款。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I still remember how her ears perked up ever so softly whenever I would conjure an orb of light into my palm.  </Source>
      <Dest>我依然记得当我召唤一个光球落入我的手掌中时她的耳朵会怎样柔和地竖起。   </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was during one of these tricks that Master Meronin recognized my talent.  Finally, I thought, this Khajiit will earn real respect.</Source>
      <Dest>我就是靠这些技巧赢得了梅罗尼大师的认可。我想道，我这亚龙人想来是终究能获得他人发自内心的尊重了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No one was more proud of me than the farmer.  Yet in the months that followed...I changed.  Suddenly it was I who could not associate with her.</Source>
      <Dest>没有比那个农场主更为我骄傲的人了。但在随后的几个月里……我改变了。突然之间，我就不能和她好好交往了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were lucky. Now get up fool, you aren't dead yet.</Source>
      <Dest>你真走运。现在起来把傻瓜，你还没死呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I am afraid this cat has exhausted all of its lives. </Source>
      <Dest>不，我恐怕这只小猫已经劳苦了一辈子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were lucky. Now get up fool, you aren't dead yet.</Source>
      <Dest>你真走运。现在起来把傻瓜，你还没死呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, if you would be so kind, perhaps you would be willing to listen to a dying Khajiit's final request.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，如果你是个好心人的话，也许你会愿意聆听一个垂死虎人最后的请求。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She told me you two had a passphrase.  A way to recognize a friend.</Source>
      <Dest>她告诉我，你们俩有个密码。以此来认出一个朋友。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmmm...that is true.  Do you know it?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯……那是真的。你知道吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She said you had whiskers like an Imperial.</Source>
      <Dest>她说你像帝国人那样留着大胡子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She forgot it again, didn't she.  It is not so hard a phrase, but rare enough to not be repeated.  "Vaba Thjizzrini."   "It is a foolish concept."</Source>
      <Dest>她又忘了是不是？这并不是一个很难的短语，但是却很少被提及。"Vaba Thjizzrini."   "这是个愚蠢的观念。"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She said you had whiskers like an Imperial.</Source>
      <Dest>她说你像帝国人那样留着大胡子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such was how she viewed all things Khajiit, and how Khajiit view all things Imperial.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是她怎样把所有事情都虎人化的，也是虎人如何把所有事情帝国化的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you're here to finish me, then do it.  Don't just stand there gaping.</Source>
      <Dest>If you're here to finish me, then do it.  Don't just stand there gaping.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you got there?</Source>
      <Dest>你到那儿后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The tavern owner there was...as the Master likes to say...garrulous.  They often are. </Source>
      <Dest>酒馆老板作为一个主人来说很...话唠，他们往往都是如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you got there?</Source>
      <Dest>你到那儿后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He pointed me in the direction of a room with a rather curious tenant.  He never left his quarters, but of guests...he had five in as many nights.</Source>
      <Dest>He pointed me in the direction of a room with a rather curious tenant.  He never left his quarters, but of guests...he had five in as many nights.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you got there?</Source>
      <Dest>你到那儿后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could not risk entering the room.  A cloaking spell is but a cheap jester trick to mages who can detect the essence of life. </Source>
      <Dest>我不能冒险进入这间屋子。对那些可以检测到生命本质的法师来说，隐形法术只不过是个廉价的小丑把戏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you got there?</Source>
      <Dest>你到那儿后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is by the luck of the Twin Moons that I found a friend in an Argonian named Gulum-Ei, whose swift hands found the pockets of his visitors.</Source>
      <Dest>上天眷顾，在双子月那天我遇见了一位朋友叫古鲁姆-埃，一位拥有一双能迅速摸到旅行者钱包的亚龙人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Right. There's only one place with that name. The Winking Skeever Inn.</Source>
      <Dest>对。只有一个地方叫这名字。眨眼雪鼠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The tavern owner there was...as the Master likes to say...garrulous.  They often are. </Source>
      <Dest>酒馆老板作为一个主人来说很...话唠，他们往往都是如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Right. There's only one place with that name. The Winking Skeever Inn.</Source>
      <Dest>对。只有一个地方叫这名字。眨眼雪鼠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He pointed me in the direction of a room with a rather curious tenant.  He never left his quarters, but of guests...he had five in as many nights.</Source>
      <Dest>He pointed me in the direction of a room with a rather curious tenant.  He never left his quarters, but of guests...he had five in as many nights.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Right. There's only one place with that name. The Winking Skeever Inn.</Source>
      <Dest>对。只有一个地方叫这名字。眨眼雪鼠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could not risk entering the room.  A cloaking spell is but a cheap jester trick to mages who can detect the essence of life. </Source>
      <Dest>我不能冒险进入这间屋子。对那些可以检测到生命本质的法师来说，隐形法术只不过是个廉价的小丑把戏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Right. There's only one place with that name. The Winking Skeever Inn.</Source>
      <Dest>对。只有一个地方叫这名字。眨眼雪鼠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is by the luck of the Twin Moons that I found a friend in an Argonian named Gulum-Ei, whose swift hands found the pockets of his visitors.</Source>
      <Dest>上天眷顾，在双子月那天我遇见了一位朋友叫古鲁姆-埃，一位拥有一双能迅速摸到旅行者钱包的亚龙人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Olivia said you were tracking a group of suspects.</Source>
      <Dest>奥莉薇雅说你在追踪一伙嫌犯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Correct.  We had interrogated witnesses in Winterhold.  Unlike those at the college, they are very sensitive to mages.  And these mages were three.</Source>
      <Dest>是的。我们询问了冬堡中的目击者。与学院的那些家伙不同，他们对法师非常敏感。那些法师有三个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Olivia said you were tracking a group of suspects.</Source>
      <Dest>奥莉薇雅说你在追踪一伙嫌犯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A child overheard them talking in private. It was but a single word, but it spoke volumes.  The word was "Winking."</Source>
      <Dest>一个孩子偷听到了他们的私密谈话。只听到了一个词，但这词出现频率很高，这个词便是“眨眼。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Olivia said you were tracking a group of suspects.</Source>
      <Dest>奥莉薇雅说你在追踪一伙嫌犯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Had the word been "Solitude" it could have meant any number of things. But "winking?"  The odds that such a word had any other context was slim.</Source>
      <Dest>"独孤"有着它独特的含义。但是“眨眼？“这样的一个词出现在其他上下文的几率都很渺茫。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What teachings are you referring to?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么样的指导？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Master Meronin once said that the greatest illusions require no spell.  I had once resented the fact that people assumed I was a simple thief.</Source>
      <Dest>梅洛妮大师曾经说过，究极的幻术是不必借助咒语的。人们觉得我只是一个简单的小毛贼，我曾经为此气得不行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What teachings are you referring to?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么样的指导？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My skills were such that I had earned an apprenticeship under a celebrated mage, yet still people clutched their coinpurses in my presence.</Source>
      <Dest>我的技能是我作为一个有名望的法师的学徒的时候学到的，但即便如此，人们在有我出席的场合还是会抓紧他们的钱包。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What teachings are you referring to?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么样的指导？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I addressed my concerns to Master Meronin, she called me a furry fool.  That I was, on both counts.</Source>
      <Dest>当我向梅洛妮导师发表我的顾虑时，她叫我做毛茸茸的傻瓜。我来说，她才是傻瓜。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What teachings are you referring to?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么样的指导？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She made me realize that their perception of me was an asset.  "Make them clutch their purse," she said, "instead of their shield."</Source>
      <Dest>她使我意识到他们对我的感觉是一笔财富.  "让他们放下钱包," 她说, "让他们放下戒备."</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd be honored to.</Source>
      <Dest>我很荣幸！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your words warm my heart. This Khajiit thanks you dearly, but we are not done yet.  There is still the business of the notes, yes?</Source>
      <Dest>你的话给我提了醒。那虎人深深地感谢了你，但我们还没谢过。笔记那事儿还有，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She said you were worth more as a rug, until you burned yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>她说你要比地毯稍微值钱一点，只要你不把自己烧掉的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha! (Coughs)  That is the fiery old mage I know.  You speak true.  Which must mean you are a college mage, and my eyes have deceived me once again.</Source>
      <Dest>哈！（咳嗽）这就是我认识的那个狂热的老法师。你说的是真的。也就是说你是一名学院法师，而我的眼睛再一次欺骗了我。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
