<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you declined the marriage.</Source>
      <Dest>我当做你拒绝这场婚姻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you declined the marriage.</Source>
      <Dest>我当做你拒绝这场婚姻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you declined the marriage.</Source>
      <Dest>我当做你拒绝这场婚姻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True enough.</Source>
      <Dest>绝对真。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True enough.</Source>
      <Dest>绝对真。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True enough.</Source>
      <Dest>绝对真。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, lots of things. Most of them involve violence.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，很多的东西。他们大多涉及暴力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We must let our loins do the thinking, for the mind knows naught of pleasure.</Source>
      <Dest>我们必须为我们的腰着想，已经感觉不到快感了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We must let our loins do the thinking, for the mind knows naught of pleasure.</Source>
      <Dest>我们必须为我们的腰着想，已经感觉不到快感了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We must let our loins do the thinking, for the mind knows naught of pleasure.</Source>
      <Dest>我们必须为我们的腰着想，已经感觉不到快感了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about Dibella.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲迪贝拉的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I dare not sully my good name by performing coitus with such a filthy trollop.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不会让那些下贱的婊子在被我操的时候玷污我美好的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I dare not sully my good name by performing coitus with such a filthy trollop.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不会让那些下贱的婊子在被我操的时候玷污我美好的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I dare not sully my good name by performing coitus with such a filthy trollop.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不会让那些下贱的婊子在被我操的时候玷污我美好的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Shouldn't you be communing with your God?</Source>
      <Dest>你不该正和你的上帝交流呢吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Shouldn't you be communing with your God?</Source>
      <Dest>你不该正和你的上帝交流呢吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Shouldn't you be communing with your God?</Source>
      <Dest>你不该正和你的上帝交流呢吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Shouldn't you be communing with your God?</Source>
      <Dest>你不该正和你的上帝交流呢吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Shouldn't you be communing with your God?</Source>
      <Dest>你不该正和你的上帝交流呢吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Shouldn't you be communing with your God?</Source>
      <Dest>你不该正和你的上帝交流呢吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Shouldn't you be communing with your God?</Source>
      <Dest>你不该正和你的上帝交流呢吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Shouldn't you be communing with your God?</Source>
      <Dest>你不该正和你的上帝交流呢吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought Mara is the Goddess of Love.</Source>
      <Dest>我以为玛拉才是爱情的女神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought Mara is the Goddess of Love.</Source>
      <Dest>我以为玛拉才是爱情的女神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought Mara is the Goddess of Love.</Source>
      <Dest>我以为玛拉才是爱情的女神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought Mara is the Goddess of Love.</Source>
      <Dest>我以为玛拉才是爱情的女神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do the priestess' opinions differ?</Source>
      <Dest>祭司们的意见有什么分歧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do the priestess' opinions differ?</Source>
      <Dest>祭司们的意见有什么分歧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do the priestess' opinions differ?</Source>
      <Dest>祭司们的意见有什么分歧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should listen to your mouth.  Mine's wet and possibly hungry.</Source>
      <Dest>看看你的下体吧。它和我一样早已饥渴难耐了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should listen to your mouth.  Mine's wet and possibly hungry.</Source>
      <Dest>看看你的下体吧。它和我一样早已饥渴难耐了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what was the problem?</Source>
      <Dest>那问题到底是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what was the problem?</Source>
      <Dest>那问题到底是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what was the problem?</Source>
      <Dest>那问题到底是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can guess for yourself which part I listen to the most.</Source>
      <Dest>来猜猜看我听到过的最多的那部分是什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can guess for yourself which part I listen to the most.</Source>
      <Dest>来猜猜看我听到过的最多的那部分是什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although not all here would share my opinion.  Some believe we should focus on art and beauty, and sever all ties with the concept of love.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然不是这儿的所有人都同意我的观点。有些人认为我们要专注于艺术与美丽，并在断绝与爱情相关的任何联系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They see a withering mountain flower and find it as beautiful as a lavender in full bloom.  </Source>
      <Dest>他们看到枯萎的花并发现它像薰衣草一样美丽盛开着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps you'd like to adjourn to your library, and read a thousand page tome on beans and corn. Or is that too graphic for you.</Source>
      <Dest>也许你想去你的图书馆，去读一千页厚的，有关于豆子和玉米的书。或许这对你而言太生动了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I still think he was the one who stole my first boyfriend, and not the neighbor girl with the skin like mammoth cheese.</Source>
      <Dest>我仍然认为他才是那个抢走我初恋男友的人，而不是隔壁那个皮肤像猛犸乳酪一样的姑娘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That disease was quite pernicious, and I was forced to find my own cure.  Thankfully, the local guards and miners were more than happy to oblige.</Source>
      <Dest>这种疾病非常严重，我被迫想办法治疗我自己，幸运的是，这里的卫兵和矿工都乐于协助我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, many of the sisters interpret love and beauty differently than I.  To some there is beauty to be found in all things.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，很多姐妹和我对爱与美的诠释是不同的。美来自于一切事物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The boy was not handsome.  Well, he might've been, if not for that elbow he called a nose.</Source>
      <Dest>这个男孩儿不怎么帅。好吧，他可能英俊过，如果他的鼻子没被手肘撞歪了的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father was not a traditional man, and while part of him wanted grandchildren, he shelved such desires because he understood my needs.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父亲不是一个老顽固。虽然他挺想要个孙子的，但由于他明白了我的需求，于是就搁置了这个念头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A nobleman's son, he said, one whom he befriended while tending to his horse.  </Source>
      <Dest>他说，那是一个把马当做朋友照看的贵族之子。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When couples marry, they seek the blessing of Mara so that familial love will blossom from the seed of their romance.</Source>
      <Dest>当一对爱人结婚，他们会寻求玛拉的祝福。这样他们爱情的种子便会开花结果</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How droll. So many handsome men and comely maidens in this city, and whenever they open their mouths it is such a disappointment.</Source>
      <Dest>多滑稽啊。这座城市有如此多的俊男美女，但不管何时，只要他们一张嘴，就那么地叫人失望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Before I was to journey to Markarth, he even made one last attempt to dissuade me, by offering the hand of a noble he had befriended as bait.</Source>
      <Dest>在我前往马卡斯城的旅程中，他最后一次试图劝阻我，以提供一个他结交的贵族的帮助为饵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or perhaps we can adjourn to a more private location, and suckle on oysters marinated in the potion of the stallion.</Source>
      <Dest>也许我们能换个更私人的地方，然后一起品尝这些泡在种马药水里的牡蛎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or perhaps we can adjourn to a more private location, and suckle on oysters marinated in the potion of the stallion.</Source>
      <Dest>也许我们能换个更私人的地方，然后一起品尝这些泡在种马药水里的牡蛎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mara is the Mother-Goddess.  It is a different thing to love one's mother than to love one's wife.</Source>
      <Dest>玛拉是慈母之神。爱某人的老妈与爱某人的妻子当然有很大区别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They point to how decay represents the impermanence of life, and how that is both artful and beautiful.  This logic is fundamentally backwards.</Source>
      <Dest>她们指出短暂的生命有多么易凋零，同时却又多么的艺术化和美丽。在逻辑上两者完全背道而驰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although it seems to me we need naught a Sybil to guide us along the path of passion.  We need only listen to our bodies.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管我不觉得我们需要先知把我们引向热情之道。我们只需听从肉体的渴望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And you will scream my name in the throes of passion, and mumble it in your sleep.  That name is Jolene, priestess of Dibella.</Source>
      <Dest>而你将会在撕心裂肺的剧痛中哭喊我的名，在睡梦中呢喃我的姓。我的名字是朱琳，迪贝拉的女祭司。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>After all, I bedded the neighbor girl myself, and she divulged all her secrets in her sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>终究，我还是御驾亲征把邻家小妹给睡了，而她在暖床的时候什么秘密都说了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And you are my kind of patron. Perhaps we should entwine our bodies here, and let the poor rubes watch.</Source>
      <Dest>而你则是我的顾客。也许我们就应在这里缠绵，然后让那些可怜的乡巴佬干看着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I once listened to my mind, it told me to read a book.  And I was never so bored.  If only you were there to rescue me from my folly.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾聆听我的心，它让我读一本书。我从来没有那么无聊。只要你在那从我的愚蠢中拯救我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, I've never held to the belief that the sisters need a Sybil to hear the commands of Dibella.  We need only listen to our bodies.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，我从没有过像姐妹们需要一个先知来倾听迪贝拉的圣谕这样的信仰，我们需要的只是聆听我们身体的呼唤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd love to hear Orla explain what exactly is so beautiful about him.</Source>
      <Dest>我真想听奥拉说说到底他哪里好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, but perhaps we should get to know each other first.  Unless you prefer we remain strangers. Some do.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，但我们最好先彼此了解一下。除非你希望我们就这样当陌生人。有些人的确这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is, until my father made the mistake of describing him.   Suddenly, the boy's reason for courting one such as myself was clear.</Source>
      <Dest>那是，直到我的父亲在自我介绍时犯了个错误。这个男孩寻找像我这样的人的原因瞬间就明了了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you should listen to our forums on the nature of Dibellan art.  There are heated words, things thrown, and sometimes the pulling of hair.</Source>
      <Dest>那么你应该听听我们关于迪贝拉的自然艺术的讲座。他们在那儿互相用语言攻击，向对方扔东西，还扯头发呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You will discover this truth when you lay your virgin down on the bed, and she lies there like a cold fish, complaining of the pain.</Source>
      <Dest>当你把处女摆在床上的时候你就会发现真相了。她就像条冻鱼似的挺在哪里，口中抱怨着疼痛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if they insist on finding ugly things beautiful, I suppose it will just mean more well built specimens will spend their nights in my chamber.</Source>
      <Dest>但如果他们坚持在丑陋的东西中寻找美丽，我想这只是意味着更多身体结实的标本将在我的小屋里度过他们的夜晚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some will tell you everything that's wonderful about what they are selling, except the one thing you want to know.</Source>
      <Dest>很多商人会告诉你关于他们售卖商品的一些有趣信息，除了你想要知道的之外.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Have you been speaking to the dead?  Unless you are referring to my father.  He certainly does act like a woman, the way he fawns over men.</Source>
      <Dest>你跟那个死人说过话了吗？除非你指的是我的父亲。他确实表现的像个娘们，那是他讨好别人的方式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems the boy had come to the stables to seek my hand, for he had fallen hopelessly in love with me.</Source>
      <Dest>看来那孩子跑来马厩寻求我的轻抚，因为他已经无可救药地爱上了我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not for this lesson, my eager disciple.  </Source>
      <Dest>不是为这堂课，我急急躁躁的学生呦。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mother Hamal and the other sisters are more than capable of finding the runt who will be our next Sybil.</Source>
      <Dest>要找到下一个能成为先知的小畜生，这任务对于哈玛尔嬷嬷和其他修女来说还是不难的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thankfully there was another option besides the iron bars of prison and the shackles of marriage. Although my father did try his best to have me wed.</Source>
      <Dest>幸好除了监狱的铁栅栏和婚姻的束缚之外还有另一种选择。虽然我父亲竭力想让我结婚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Goddess of beauty and love, and the best the Divines have to offer.  For what is more sacred and more honest than the love of beauty?</Source>
      <Dest>爱与美的女神。作为信仰对象来说这是最好的一位女神了。有什么能比美好的爱更神圣和忠贞呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For it's in the moistness of our mouths, the throbbing of our hearts, and the warmth of our loins that Dibella truly speaks to us.</Source>
      <Dest>迪贝拉对我们的轻声细语是在我们口中的湿润，我们心中的悸动，我们腰间的温暖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For it's in the moistness of our mouths, the throbbing of our hearts, and the warmth of our loins that Dibella truly speaks to us.</Source>
      <Dest>迪贝拉对我们的轻声细语是在我们口中的湿润，我们心中的悸动，我们腰间的温暖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's no different than Kerah boasting about the frame of her pendants, when the jewel set in the center is a worthless stone. </Source>
      <Dest>当一颗宝石被镶嵌在一个价值连城的石头上时，这和克拉自夸她打造的饰物是一样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not immediately.  It isn't every day someone is offered the hand of a wealthy noble.  It certainly piqued my interest.</Source>
      <Dest>不是马上。一个富人不用每天有人帮忙。这真激起我的兴趣了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A short life does not mean we should dwell on death.  Nor should the ephemeral nature of beauty mean we should focus on decay.</Source>
      <Dest>人生短暂并不意味着我们要等死。自然界瞬间的美好也不意味着我们硬要沉溺于腐烂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, but perhaps we should get to know each other first.  Unless you prefer we remain strangers.  Some do.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，但也许我们应该先互相了解。除非你想和某些人一样希望我们保持陌生人关系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mother Hamal and the other sisters are more than capable of training Fjotra.  </Source>
      <Dest>哈玛尔嬷嬷和其他姐妹都有能力训练弗洛嘉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, you'll have to earn it by starting with her boot.  Unless...by hungry you were referring to food.  Then I suggest you head to the market.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，你就必须通过她的引导来赚钱。除非...饥饿的你是指食物。那么我建议你前往市场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you are under my instruction, you will achieve a satisfaction that kindles fires greater than any addiction, and burns deeper than any regret.</Source>
      <Dest>来，按照我说的做，一步步，一步步来。你会飘飘欲仙，心中的激情如同干柴烈火一般瞬间释放，让你永生难忘。不要紧张，相信我，你不会后悔的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm willing to bet your bedroom is as dull and lifeless as your words.  </Source>
      <Dest>我敢打赌，你的房间一定和你的口才一般苍白且毫无生机。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet make no mistake, it is Dibella who brought them together, and Dibella who will make their family whole.</Source>
      <Dest>别搞错了，是迪贝拉让他们在一起，是迪贝拉让他们的家庭美满。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father told me the boy was smart, wealthy, and good with a sword.  He said he was well spoken, courteous, and refined.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父亲跟我说那个男孩很聪明, 有钱, 很会耍剑。他说他口才也不错，有礼貌，举止优雅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. I wasn't serious anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我不再那么认真了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you become a priestess?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么成为一名女祭司的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you become a priestess?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么成为一名女祭司的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you become a priestess?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么成为一名女祭司的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you become a priestess?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么成为一名女祭司的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you become a priestess?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么成为一名女祭司的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you become a priestess?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么成为一名女祭司的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do the quarrels with your sisters ever get...heated?</Source>
      <Dest>和你姐妹们的争吵...升级了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do the quarrels with your sisters ever get...heated?</Source>
      <Dest>和你姐妹们的争吵...升级了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do the quarrels with your sisters ever get...heated?</Source>
      <Dest>和你姐妹们的争吵...升级了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do the quarrels with your sisters ever get...heated?</Source>
      <Dest>和你姐妹们的争吵...升级了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do the quarrels with your sisters ever get...heated?</Source>
      <Dest>和你姐妹们的争吵...升级了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I find it hard to believe a hagraven like you attracts the eyes of anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>你这样的乌鸦鬼婆居然也能吸引别人的目光，这真是太难以置信了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I find it hard to believe a hagraven like you attracts the eyes of anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>你这样的乌鸦鬼婆居然也能吸引别人的目光，这真是太难以置信了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I find it hard to believe a hagraven like you attracts the eyes of anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>你这样的乌鸦鬼婆居然也能吸引别人的目光，这真是太难以置信了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While you devote yourself to pleasure, the mind atrophies and rots.</Source>
      <Dest>一味追寻快感，思想就会萎缩乃至腐烂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While you devote yourself to pleasure, the mind atrophies and rots.</Source>
      <Dest>一味追寻快感，思想就会萎缩乃至腐烂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, you're saying you didn't want to become a brothel worker.</Source>
      <Dest>换言之，你说你不想在妓院里工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, you're saying you didn't want to become a brothel worker.</Source>
      <Dest>换言之，你说你不想在妓院里工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, you're saying you didn't want to become a brothel worker.</Source>
      <Dest>换言之，你说你不想在妓院里工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, you're saying you didn't want to become a brothel worker.</Source>
      <Dest>换言之，你说你不想在妓院里工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm willing to share.</Source>
      <Dest>我很愿意分享。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, tell me your name.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，告诉我你叫什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, tell me your name.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，告诉我你叫什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't care who you are. You need to know my name, so you know what to scream.</Source>
      <Dest>无论你是什么身份，你只需知道我的名字，这样你尖叫的时候就有名字可喊了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't care who you are. You need to know my name, so you know what to scream.</Source>
      <Dest>无论你是什么身份，你只需知道我的名字，这样你尖叫的时候就有名字可喊了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Marry me.</Source>
      <Dest>嫁给我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a fairly vague description.</Source>
      <Dest>真是够没信息量的解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a fairly vague description.</Source>
      <Dest>真是够没信息量的解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should listen to your heart. Not when it throbs, but when it's stilled.</Source>
      <Dest>你要倾听你的心。并非在其搏动处，而是当它静止时。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should listen to your heart. Not when it throbs, but when it's stilled.</Source>
      <Dest>你要倾听你的心。并非在其搏动处，而是当它静止时。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean when you say, you wish your sisters were more honest?</Source>
      <Dest>你说希望你的姐妹们更诚实一点是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean when you say, you wish your sisters were more honest?</Source>
      <Dest>你说希望你的姐妹们更诚实一点是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean when you say, you wish your sisters were more honest?</Source>
      <Dest>你说希望你的姐妹们更诚实一点是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your parents must be so proud.</Source>
      <Dest>你的家人一定为此备感骄傲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your parents must be so proud.</Source>
      <Dest>你的家人一定为此备感骄傲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You are doing the Divines' work. Carry on.</Source>
      <Dest>你正在做诸神的工作。继续吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You are doing the Divines' work. Carry on.</Source>
      <Dest>你正在做诸神的工作。继续吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My coins are as good as any, and won't cost you your hand.</Source>
      <Dest>我的钱干净得很，而且也不用拿你的手来换。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The desire boiled within me even before I flowered.  But I was no fool.  Men do not respect those who tarnish their bodies for pleasure or coin.</Source>
      <Dest>早在发育之前，熊熊的欲望就在我体内燃烧。但我并不是傻瓜，我知道男人看不起那些只为愉悦和金币就玷污自己身体的女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until next time.</Source>
      <Dest>下回见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh my, it isn't often I get to lay my eyes upon such a handsome...specimen.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，天啊，我可很少看到这样漂亮的...标本。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For every lover that's preceded me, and every lover that follows will have to be measured by my standard. </Source>
      <Dest>对于每一个先于我的和每一个在我之后的情人都必须以我的标准来衡量。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Welcome.</Source>
      <Dest>欢迎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As am I. But then what's the point of marriage?</Source>
      <Dest>我也是。那结婚还有什么意义呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But my heart is never stilled, and my mouth is never dry, and my loins never cold.  </Source>
      <Dest>可我的心从未停止跳动，我的嘴也从未干涸，我的腰部也从未变冷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If all things are beautiful, than nothing is beautiful.  </Source>
      <Dest>如果什么东西都是美好的，那就没有美好的东西了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The ardor with which the miners pray to Dibella is quite amusing.  Men will pray to a Goblin if they thought it would earn my favor.</Source>
      <Dest>那些矿工对迪贝拉的狂热崇拜真是好笑啊。如果他们觉得会获得我的帮助的话，还不得向哥布林祈祷啦？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is more attractive to the thief, the coin purse on the table, or the one in the pocket of the armored guard?</Source>
      <Dest>对小偷而言，什么更具吸引力？是放在桌子上的钱包，还是一个全副武装的守卫的口袋？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well hello there.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, there are ladies more beautiful, but none as voracious.  There are women more voluptuous, but none who better advertise it.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，还有更漂亮的女人，但没有更贪婪的了。也有更性感的女人，但没有更放荡的了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Even here there are many divergent opinions as to what we should dedicate our lives to, particularly in the wake of the previous Sybil's death.</Source>
      <Dest>对于选择将我们的一生献给怎样的目标有着很多分歧，特别是在先知去世了之后。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thankfully, there was a woman in my town who practiced the Dibellan arts.  One who attached legitimacy to what I believed were primal instincts.</Source>
      <Dest>幸运的是，在我的城里有一个精通迪贝拉技巧的姑娘。一个给我所认为的原始本能附加上合理性的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And there will be those who seek my blessing.  Men and women both old and young.  Mother Hamal can attest to that.</Source>
      <Dest>来寻求我的赐福之人将大有人在。善男信女，黄发垂髫，哈玛尔嬷嬷可以为此作证。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But you hoped I was? Then you haven't been listening to a word I've said.</Source>
      <Dest>你希望我是谁啊？你有没有好好听我说的话啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've heard that in the heat of coitus, depriving your partner of air can increase sensation and pleasure.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说在交媾最激烈的时候，让你同伴短暂的窒息能增加快感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, and it's precisely the reason why Dibella is worshiped by so many disparate cults.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，而这也正是为何迪贝拉会被如此多不同的教派崇拜的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The same way a fighter becomes a soldier, or a plant lover becomes an alchemist.</Source>
      <Dest>一个战士成为一名士兵，跟一个植物爱好者成为一名炼金术师是一回事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have never been so bored in all my years.   It took me a dozen guards and miners before I was cured.</Source>
      <Dest>我这辈子就没有这么生气过。在我完事之前，这花了我几十个卫兵和矿工。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh my, it isn't often I get to gaze upon such a flawless beauty.</Source>
      <Dest>我了个...我可不是经常能看到这么完美无瑕的美人的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is Dibella's gift to me, that I may grant others satisfaction, while I myself am never satisfied.</Source>
      <Dest>那是迪贝拉给我的恩赐，我给别人带来愉悦，而我自己则一点也没。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I understand Bothela was quite the vixen in her day.  The zeal with which men pursued her was legendary.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白波塞拉年轻时是个彻彻底底的泼妇。这汉子追求她的热情堪称传奇啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some of them feel a moral obligation to find beauty in all things, but that is a contradiction.</Source>
      <Dest>他们中有些人觉得在万物中寻找美是一种道德上的义务，但这种思想是有矛盾的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if they insist, I will take my buxom wenches, melodic bards and chiseled warriors, and they can have the beggars like Degaine.</Source>
      <Dest>但如果他们坚持的话，我会带上我丰满的女侍，调子美妙的诗人以及棱角分明的战士，然后他们就能有个像德加因那样的乞丐了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, now, don't be selfish.  My body may belong to everyone, but my heart belongs to no one.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，现在，不要自私。我的身体可能属于每一个人，但我的心不属于任何人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've talked to the sisters about developing similar techniques based on the use of paralysis spells, but none of us are well versed in alteration.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经告诉我的姐妹们在瘫痪术的基础上研究一下类似的技巧，但是我们中没有人擅长变化系法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Aggressive and passionate.  I am intrigued by you. </Source>
      <Dest>积极又热情。我已对你着迷。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And while none of these things fell into my range of expertise, to simply wear the robe is to own those attributes by proxy.</Source>
      <Dest>这些东西却没有一个落入我擅长的范围内，简简单单地穿上长袍，作为代理人，就会得到这些属性。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The name is Jolene, priestess of Dibella.  A name that you may not remember now, but one that will haunt you forever.</Source>
      <Dest>名字是朱琳，迪贝拉的女祭司。这个名字你现在或许不记得，但未来将会永远萦绕在你心头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let's hope for your sake and mine, that you are a flame that burns both bright and long, for most can only be one of the two.</Source>
      <Dest>让我们为自己祈祷吧，你是团光明切长亮的火焰，我想你会成为我们两之间那幸运的一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It irks me how merchants of death are allowed to parade around town, their swords dripping with the blood of their last victim.</Source>
      <Dest>让我苦恼的是那些贩卖死亡的家伙们居然被允许在镇上耀武扬威，他们剑上所沾的那上一个受害者的鲜血都还没干呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At the moment they are sapped of their vitality, she enchants their tunic, fortifying their stamina.</Source>
      <Dest>那时他们的精力正逐渐被侵蚀，她给他们的外衣附了魔，提升了他们的耐力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While the Temple isn't taking on new students, perhaps you wish to rendezvous at the inn for a more...personal lesson.</Source>
      <Dest>神殿不再接受新的学生了，或许你会想在酒馆会合，来进行一些更...私人的课程。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mother Hamal, of course, saw through my ruse, but I was able to...persuade her that my talent in the erotic arts justified my entry into her service.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，哈玛尔嬷嬷看破了我的技俩。但是我成功地……成功地让她相信我在性爱方技巧方面有独特的天分，这让我能正当地为她工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>After all, Dibella is also the Goddess of artistry, beauty, and love.  </Source>
      <Dest>毕竟，迪贝拉仍是艺术，爱情与美貌的女神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Well, I can't speak for my mother, whom I barely knew and seldom met.  She left out of shame when my father revealed his appetite for men.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 好吧，我不会对老妈说的，我很少见她并几乎不了解她。在我父亲意识到自己对男人更感性趣后，她带着耻辱跑了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mother Hamal is a master enchanter.  In fact, there is a rumor that she prefers her men clothed and on the enchanting table for this very reason.</Source>
      <Dest>哈玛尔嬷嬷是附魔大师。因为这个原因，有传闻说她喜欢的是衣冠楚楚又在附魔学上有造诣的男人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If only more people in Skyrim shared your sentiments. </Source>
      <Dest>如果在天际省有更多的人能理解你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do find that a good argument does lead to nights of intense passion, but mostly behind closed doors.  Unfortunately.</Source>
      <Dest>我确实发现一场好的辩论能带来无数的激情，但大多数都藏的很深。真不幸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although the problems tend to still be there in the morning.  I do wish my sisters would be more honest with their interpretations of beauty.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管这些问题一直都在，但我还是希望我的姐妹们对美的理解更加诚实些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While the Temple isn't taking on new students, my lady, perhaps you wish to rendezvous at the inn for a more...personal lesson.</Source>
      <Dest>神庙已经不再接纳新的学徒了，我的女士，也许你想要在旅店里见见我来点……私人课程。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A young Dark Elf was in here the other day, but Senna turned him away.  Oh, the things I would've done to the boy.</Source>
      <Dest>一个年轻的黑暗精灵在某一天来过，但是辛纳把他赶走了。哦，我也想对那个男孩这么做来着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Antlers? Lichen? (Sigh) Why do you always have to ruin it.</Source>
      <Dest>灌木？苔藓？(叹气)你为什么总要破坏它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're looking quite handsome, Clario.  Perhaps you'll come over later and show me how you make that delectable cream sauce.</Source>
      <Dest>你可真帅啊，克拉里奥。或许哪天你可以顺便来我家逛逛，教我一下美味的甜果酱是怎么做成的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh my, whatever did you have in mind?</Source>
      <Dest>噢天哪，无论如何，你是怎么想的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
