<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why would there be Giant bones in the ocean?</Source>
      <Dest>海里怎么会有巨人的骨头？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know. Probably because they ran in fear of my axe when I killed their furry cows and slaughtered their young.</Source>
      <Dest>I don't know. Probably because they ran in fear of my axe when I killed their furry cows and slaughtered their young.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why would there be Giant bones in the ocean?</Source>
      <Dest>海里怎么会有巨人的骨头？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>From that day on they have painted the stones with my name. "Fear the one called Jonas, for he is the Giant's bane."</Source>
      <Dest>从那天起，它们把我的名字刻在了石头之上。“备受敬畏之人唤作乔纳斯，旨因其乃巨人之灾星。"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What makes you such a prolific Giant slayer?</Source>
      <Dest>什么让你成为了一个老道的巨人狩猎者？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One word. Fear. Two words. Fear not. They fear me, and I fear them not.  Their bones quiver, and my footsteps quake, for I am their bane.</Source>
      <Dest>一个字。怕。两个字。不怕。他们怕我，而我不怕他们。他们的骨头因恐惧颤栗着，而我的脚步让整个大地震颤，因为我是他们的克星。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That axe doesn't look like it can cut warm butter.</Source>
      <Dest>这把斧子看起来连块儿被加热的黄油都切不开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is not the sharpness of the axe, but the force of the cut. There is a reason the Giants mark my name on the stones.</Source>
      <Dest>不在于斧头的锋利，而是劈砍的力量！我的名字被巨人们写在石头上是有原因的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That axe doesn't look like it can cut warm butter.</Source>
      <Dest>这把斧子看起来连块儿被加热的黄油都切不开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say, "Fear the one called Jonas, for he is the Giant's bane."</Source>
      <Dest>他们说，“备受敬畏之人唤作乔纳斯，旨因其乃巨人之灾星。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That is precisely what we need. You're hired.</Source>
      <Dest>这正是我们所需要的。你被录用了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You will not be disappointed. The Giants fear me. They mark their stones with my name in their ancient tongue.</Source>
      <Dest>你不会失望的，巨人们怕我，它们用它们的远古文字在石头上刻着我的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We need your assistance with a Giant.</Source>
      <Dest>我们需要你帮忙对付一个巨人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, so you seek the axe of the one they call Giant-Bane. </Source>
      <Dest>啊，所以你要找那把被人称为“巨人灾星”的斧头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We need your assistance with a Giant.</Source>
      <Dest>我们需要你帮忙对付一个巨人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My legend is as vast as the Sea of Ghosts, and yet I could fill it to the brim with the bones of Giants I have slain.</Source>
      <Dest>我的传说如同幽灵海一样辽阔，而且我能用我杀死的巨人骨头将其填满。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They are not lies, wench! I am the Giant's Bane!</Source>
      <Dest>They are not lies, wench! I am the Giant's Bane!</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
