<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where can we find Deneris?</Source>
      <Dest>我们在哪儿能找到丹尼勒斯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where can we find Deneris?</Source>
      <Dest>我们在哪儿能找到丹尼勒斯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you join this brotherhood?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎样加入这个兄弟会的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you join this brotherhood?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎样加入这个兄弟会的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>At which point you surrendered and begged for mercy.</Source>
      <Dest>你看时机适合就投降求饶.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you chosen any brothers?</Source>
      <Dest>你选过别的弟兄没？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to go back to my earlier questions.</Source>
      <Dest>让我们回到先前的问题上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's absurd. The assassin is more than just a tool.</Source>
      <Dest>真荒唐。刺客不过是工具。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's absurd. The assassin is more than just a tool.</Source>
      <Dest>真荒唐。刺客不过是工具。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's absurd. The assassin is more than just a tool.</Source>
      <Dest>真荒唐。刺客不过是工具。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then you fought her and held your own. Or else you wouldn't be here now.</Source>
      <Dest>然后你跟她打了一架并取得了胜利。否则的话你现在就不会在这里了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That would have probably been a good time to escape.</Source>
      <Dest>那将会是个逃跑的好时机。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We split up. I had to make sure she didn't come back for you.</Source>
      <Dest>我们分手了。我必须确保她不是为了你才回来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You know about the killings then?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你知道这些谋杀对吧?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You know about the killings then?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你知道这些谋杀对吧?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes. The only question now is, what do we do with it?</Source>
      <Dest>是的，唯一的问题就是，我们要拿它做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes. The only question now is, what do we do with it?</Source>
      <Dest>是的，唯一的问题就是，我们要拿它做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes. The only question now is, what do we do with it?</Source>
      <Dest>是的，唯一的问题就是，我们要拿它做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One of the assassins escaped. Tikrid's searching the ruins for her.</Source>
      <Dest>其中一个刺客跑了。提克瑞德正在遗迹里搜索她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, you want to put an end to these black market contracts.</Source>
      <Dest>换句话说，你想给黑市交易画个句号。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, you want to put an end to these black market contracts.</Source>
      <Dest>换句话说，你想给黑市交易画个句号。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happens to Clan Darksteel now?</Source>
      <Dest>黑铁氏族现在怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happens to Clan Darksteel now?</Source>
      <Dest>黑铁氏族现在怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happens to Clan Darksteel now?</Source>
      <Dest>黑铁氏族现在怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happens to Clan Darksteel now?</Source>
      <Dest>黑铁氏族现在怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm no hero. I just did what any person would have in my position.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是英雄，我只是做了别人在这种情境下也会做的事情罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm no hero. I just did what any person would have in my position.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是英雄，我只是做了别人在这种情境下也会做的事情罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm no hero. I just did what any person would have in my position.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是英雄，我只是做了别人在这种情境下也会做的事情罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your brotherhood can be restored. Only a milk-drinker gives up so easily.</Source>
      <Dest>你的兄弟会是可以复兴的。只有吃奶的废物才会如此轻易放弃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your brotherhood can be restored. Only a milk-drinker gives up so easily.</Source>
      <Dest>你的兄弟会是可以复兴的。只有吃奶的废物才会如此轻易放弃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not an assassin, but someone is trying to eliminate your brotherhood.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是刺客，但有人正想要消灭你们兄弟会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not an assassin, but someone is trying to eliminate your brotherhood.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是刺客，但有人正想要消灭你们兄弟会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I heard what happened to your temple. I'm trying to rectify things.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说了在你圣殿里发生的事情，我正试图收拾残局。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I heard what happened to your temple. I'm trying to rectify things.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说了在你圣殿里发生的事情，我正试图收拾残局。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could come with us.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以跟我们一起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could come with us.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以跟我们一起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not bad for a couple of corsairs, smugglers and thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>这对一群海盗、走私贩和盗贼来说也不坏嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not bad for a couple of corsairs, smugglers and thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>这对一群海盗、走私贩和盗贼来说也不坏嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not bad for a couple of corsairs, smugglers and thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>这对一群海盗、走私贩和盗贼来说也不坏嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thanks to me. I believe I'm entitled to some sort of reward.</Source>
      <Dest>多亏我。我相信我该被授予一些奖赏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thanks to me. I believe I'm entitled to some sort of reward.</Source>
      <Dest>多亏我。我相信我该被授予一些奖赏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Very well.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where is your wife now?</Source>
      <Dest>你的妻子现在在哪儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where is your wife now?</Source>
      <Dest>你的妻子现在在哪儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what now? The assassin's still out there.</Source>
      <Dest>那现在怎么办？外面的刺客还在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what now? The assassin's still out there.</Source>
      <Dest>那现在怎么办？外面的刺客还在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It must have been difficult to watch her kill your companions.</Source>
      <Dest>眼看着她杀死你的伙伴们一定很难过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It must have been difficult to watch her kill your companions.</Source>
      <Dest>眼看着她杀死你的伙伴们一定很难过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The brothers have always been chosen for their ability to work alone. They'll continue to work and thrive.</Source>
      <Dest>兄弟们一直是选择依靠自己的双手，他们会继续如此并成长起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're probably right, but what do I give to a person who has everything? The only practical item I have is practically worthless, but here.</Source>
      <Dest>也许你是对的，可对一个拥有一切的人我能给他什么呢？我这儿唯一能算是件东西的也没什么价值，拿去吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That girl has an obsessive streak about her. Obsession can be your best friend and your worst enemy, depending on how you use it.</Source>
      <Dest>那个姑娘挺执着的。执念是最好的朋友，也是最可怕的敌人。看你怎么利用它了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I actually enjoy playing this game. But the Elf who came to warn me, a Dunmer named Erevan, he was quite serious about putting a stop to it.</Source>
      <Dest>不，事实上我很喜欢这游戏。但是那个来警告我的叫埃里温的矮人就中止这游戏的问题上非常严肃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe you're right, but only a fool tries to walk up a mountain made of ice. Some things can't be avoided, regardless of how bravely you face them.</Source>
      <Dest>也许你是对的，但只有蠢蛋才会去爬一座冰山。这与勇气无关，该来的终归要来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The real problem was the Gods had blessed me with a bit of luck, and I was too foolish to accept their gift. I actually tried to avenge my brothers.</Source>
      <Dest>真正的问题在于诸神赐予我的一点儿运气，而我太过愚蠢以至于接受了他们的馈赠。我其实是想为我的兄弟们报仇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then they've already succeeded. Outside of their chosen, most of the brothers don't know each other in life. It's in death that we meet.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说他们已经成功了。大部分兄弟活着的时候没有互相了解，只有在死后才认知彼此，他们没有别的选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know there's a contract on my head, and I know there's little I can do about it.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道我脑袋里有个契约，我还知道我拿它没什么办法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I was told to expect someone else. A Redguard woman with the eyes of a feline.</Source>
      <Dest>然而一个有着如猫般的眼眸的红卫女人让我去指望别人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, with Clan Darksteel going the way of the Dwemer, we have to find other ways to survive in death. I wonder if Sovngarde is still taking souls.</Source>
      <Dest>因此，随着黑铁氏族踏上与矮人相同的道路，我们必须找到另一种在死后永生的办法。我不确定松加德是否仍在吸纳灵魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nothing will do short of praying to Azura to bring the temple back. To think I made the pilgrimage for the first time to find it in ruin.</Source>
      <Dest>除了向阿祖拉祈祷以外，没什么可以恢复这座神殿。 To think I made the pilgrimage for the first time to find it in ruin.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>His name was Erevan, I believe. He said he wanted to put an end to the black market contracts.</Source>
      <Dest>他叫艾里温。他曾说过他想让所有黑市交易销声匿迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, having the tools to defend yourself is every bit as important. Maybe you can make use of this one, just as I have.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，有合适的工具来保护自己的安全同样重要。也许你可以用这个，就像我那样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I suppose we have society to thank, for teaching us how to behave in the face of danger.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我认为我们应该感谢这个团体，因为它教会了我如何面对危险。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I went outside to piss and have a drink, and I returned just in time to see her snatch our leader's heart right out of his chest.</Source>
      <Dest>当我出去小解喝了一杯然后回去时，恰好看见她直接掏去了我们老大的心脏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You see, I used to be a member of the Forsworn.</Source>
      <Dest>你瞧，我过去是个弃誓者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's not uncommon for the chosen to run in darker circles. Our skills, after all, are valued by those who work in secret.</Source>
      <Dest>这种隐入黑暗的选择并不罕见。毕竟，我们技能的价值就是被那些工作在密处的人所体现出来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thought I'd find you here. I was tracking an assassin, and found a corpse. You two wouldn't have anything to do with that, would you?</Source>
      <Dest>我就知道我会在这里找到你。我正在跟踪一个刺客，然后发现了一具尸体。你俩不会跟这事有关连的，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so our heroes live to see another day.</Source>
      <Dest>所以，英雄长存。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The remaining Darksteel have rallied behind a new leader, one of the pilgrims who escaped Wanderer's Rest.</Source>
      <Dest>剩下的黑铁成员已经聚集在了一名新的领袖麾下，一个从流浪者之家逃出来的朝圣者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was, but losing them was no different than any other day in the wild.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊。但失去他们跟在野外的任何一天相比没什么不同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They all headed over to Shadow's Gulch, east of Snow Veil Sanctum. That's where Deneris' spirit rises.</Source>
      <Dest>他们都去了暗影峡谷，就在白雪面纱安息所的东边。那里是丹尼勒斯的灵魂崛起之所。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They all headed over to Shadow's Gulch, east of Snow Veil Sanctum. That's where Deneris' spirit rises.</Source>
      <Dest>他们都去了暗影峡谷，就在白雪面纱安息所的东边。那里是丹尼勒斯的灵魂崛起之所。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now I can only hope that wherever our spirits end up, we'll be in the same place.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我只能希望我们在黄泉之下可以团聚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, don't answer that. The sword you're carrying says enough. And if your aim is to kill Deneris, I need only point you the way.</Source>
      <Dest>不，不用回答。你戴着的这把剑已经能说明一切了。如果你想杀丹尼勒斯，我只需要为你指路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A real paragon of virtue, that one. As uptight as he was brave. I would meet him in Windhelm, and follow the trail from there.</Source>
      <Dest>那个人是真理的象征，如同他的勇气一样严肃。我会在风盔城和他见面，然后从那里追寻他的足迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A real paragon of virtue, that one. As uptight as he was brave. I would meet him in Windhelm, and follow the trail from there.</Source>
      <Dest>那个人是真理的象征，如同他的勇气一样严肃。我会在风盔城和他见面，然后从那里追寻他的足迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, not bad at all, although our training helped in this situation. My love would have never forgiven me if I let some greenthumb sneak up on me.</Source>
      <Dest>不，一点也不，即使在这种情况下我们的训练有所帮助也是如此。如果我让一群淫贼潜行到我身边的话我的爱人是不会原谅我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, how did everything go in there? I notice we seem to be one short.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，现在如何？我觉着我们好像稍微变矮了一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, how did everything go in there? I notice we seem to be one short.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，现在如何？我觉着我们好像稍微变矮了一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, how did everything go in there? I notice we seem to be one short.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，现在如何？我觉着我们好像稍微变矮了一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, how did everything go in there? I notice we seem to be one short.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，现在如何？我觉着我们好像稍微变矮了一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Believe it or not, it was my wife who chose me. But that's not as strange as the story of how we met.</Source>
      <Dest>信不信由你，是我老婆选的我。可还是比不上我们相遇时的故事那样离奇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, if the old Gods had blessed me with humility, or at the very least, fear. I was not so wise. I tried to kill her.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，如果那些古老的神明能够赐予我谦逊，或者至少，赐予我恐惧的话。但我没有那么明智，我试图与她拼命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I returned, I learned of the contract on my head. Imagine that. A man losing both his life and his afterlife in a single fortnight.</Source>
      <Dest>当我回去了之后，我终于想明白了这所谓的契约。想象一下，一个人在短短两星期内就把他这辈子和下辈子都给丢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you ever find yourself acting as bait, knowing a little alteration comes in handy too. Here. Take this spell tome.</Source>
      <Dest>如果有朝一日你发现你自己不得不扮作一只饵，那懂一点变形法术是很有用处的。给你，拿着这本法术书吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe you can spend it reading this tome. It's a bit of alteration magic we nightblades are fond of using.</Source>
      <Dest>也许你可以花点时间读读这本书。里面有些我们夜莺喜欢用的变幻系魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I appreciate the concern, but I wouldn't worry too much about me. Anyone who interrupt my walks gets to see my cranky side.</Source>
      <Dest>我感谢你的关心，但是我不会太担心自己。任何人打扰我散步的人都会看到我狂暴的一面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well.</Source>
      <Dest>非常好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Either way, it seems I'm quite the catch. But with our temple gone, I have more of a stake in staying alive.</Source>
      <Dest>总之，看起来我是最合适的那个啊。但既然我们的神殿已经没了，我就必须得肩负起责任来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, some say the Dark Brotherhood has never killed a soul. The same goes for our assassin.</Source>
      <Dest>喔，有人说黑暗兄弟会从没有抹除过灵魂。我们刺客也是如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it'll be for nostalgia's sake. There won't be any oaths to swear, or any afterlife waiting for us.</Source>
      <Dest>但这就是为什么会怀旧。不需要宣誓，也没有什么来世等待着我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's the problem isn't it? We always want more time, and we finally get it, we haven't the slightest clue about how to spend it.</Source>
      <Dest>这是个问题，不是吗？我们总想多要些时间，而当我们最终有了时间的时候，却对如何利用这些时间毫无头绪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No. I had an apprentice once. Younger than the hair on my chin and greener than a sailor's teeth.</Source>
      <Dest>不。我曾经有个徒弟。比我下巴上的胡茬更年轻，比水手的牙齿更生嫩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I guess the ending isn't much of surprise, but to this day I still don't know what I was thinking, trying to sneak up on a professional.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜结局也没什么悬念了。只不过直到现在我都不知道我是怎么想的，居然去试图隐匿接近一个潜行的专家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There you are. You're a bold assassin, to confront me in public.</Source>
      <Dest>你在这儿啊。你这个胆大包天的刺客，给我站出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She's gone. Passed away not long ago. She always talked about how we'd spend eternity at Wanderer's Rest.</Source>
      <Dest>她死了。不久前去世的。她生前经常说起我们怎样在流浪者庇护所度过一生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Because the real killer is the one who puts out the contract.</Source>
      <Dest>因为凶手就是那个提出契约的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some may even choose disciples and dress their fingers in shadow, like my wife did with me.</Source>
      <Dest>有人甚至会选择私下里教训他们一下，就像是我老婆对我做的一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you chosen any brothers?</Source>
      <Dest>你选过任何弟兄没？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you chosen any brothers?</Source>
      <Dest>你选过任何弟兄没？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would you classify yourselves as criminals?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为自己是罪犯吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would you classify yourselves as criminals?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为自己是罪犯吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would you classify yourselves as criminals?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为自己是罪犯吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of work did you and your brothers do?</Source>
      <Dest>你和你的兄弟们做的是什么样的工作？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of work did you and your brothers do?</Source>
      <Dest>你和你的兄弟们做的是什么样的工作？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of work did you and your brothers do?</Source>
      <Dest>你和你的兄弟们做的是什么样的工作？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What if someone dies? Doesn't the link get broken?</Source>
      <Dest>如果有人死了呢？关系链不会断裂吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have any of your brothers attempted to contact you?</Source>
      <Dest>你的兄弟们有哪个试着联系过你吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have any of your brothers attempted to contact you?</Source>
      <Dest>你的兄弟们有哪个试着联系过你吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Thieves Guild uses shadowmarks to know friend from foe. We use the blackened finger, and the chain of the chosen.</Source>
      <Dest>盜賊公会使用暗影印記來分辨敌我，而我们则使用黝黑之手与选择之链。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He tried to warn me, just as you did. And I gave him a similar reply.</Source>
      <Dest>他试图警告我，就像你一样。我给了他一个类似的答复。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you make your choice of successor, these are the kinds of things you have to consider.</Source>
      <Dest>当你指定继承人的时候，通常有很多需要考虑的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That would defeat the purpose of being outside, my lady. I'm going for a nice, leisurely walk.</Source>
      <Dest>这会打消你出去的念头，夫人。我要出去悠闲地散一会步了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's right. An ice spell just to slow me down. Or maybe it was a fear spell. Whatever it was, it was enough.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。一个冰系魔法会让我慢下来。或者恐惧术也行。不管哪个，都够我受了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You two go on ahead! She can't escape that way!</Source>
      <Dest>你们两个追上去！绝不能让她就这么跑了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Needless to say, he never amounted to much. At the time, I was worried I wouldn't have anyone to bear my corpse.</Source>
      <Dest> 他什么事也办不成。现在我都怀疑如果我死了他能不能把我的尸体带回去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True. They raise all the pillagers to fight that way, but I was so right hand dominant, I never even bothered to use my left.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，他们派出了全部掠夺者像那样战斗，不过我只用右手就解决了，左手一点都没用到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, if you'll excuse me, I'd like to get some fresh air.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，如果你不介意的话，我想呼吸点儿新鲜空气。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, I'd be dead if I hadn't gone outside that night. I used to have trouble sleeping, and this night was no exception.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，如果那天晚上我没出去，我就死定了。但是我一直以来都被失眠困扰，那天晚上也不例外。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't speak for all of us, but Varyan built this brotherhood on the idea that whoever we cheat, rob, or kill, is someone that deserves it.</Source>
      <Dest>不能说是我们所有人，但瓦里安是以“无论谁被我们欺骗，抢劫，乃至被杀，都是他们的命”为理念，创建的兄弟会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We dueled for about five minutes, blade to blade. I actually might've bested her, but we were both fighting with one hand behind our backs.</Source>
      <Dest>我们实刀实枪鏖战了五分钟。实际上我已经击败了她，但是我们都是用一只手战斗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If we're unsure about a job we can appeal to the ones who chose us, and they can appeal to a higher rank, all the way up to Varyan Darksteel himself.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我们对某一个任务没有把握，我们可以向选择我们的人请示，而他们又可以请示上级，最高可以一直请示到黑铁瓦里安本人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Theft, assassinations, and smuggling. We work independently for the most part, but it's forbidden to act against the interests of a brother.</Source>
      <Dest>偷窃，暗杀，还有抢劫。我们独立地为大多数人的利益服务，但不能够因之损害自己弟兄的利益。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But then she lifted that finger, the one dressed in black, and bade me to follow.</Source>
      <Dest>随后她举起手指，那个穿黑衣服的人就叫我跟着走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Before we had Wanderer's Rest. All those who have delivered the dead can return to the temple. Now, who knows.</Source>
      <Dest>我们到流浪者歇脚点之前，那些所有运死人的家伙都回神殿了。现在，谁知道呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when a lot of tourists who come up here to drink, they soon find it's a long way down.</Source>
      <Dest>当大量的游客想到这喝一杯时，他们很快会发现这是个漫长的旅程。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, when it came to our off hands, only one of us knew how to use it.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，当意外到来之时，我们之中仅有一人懂得使用它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was contracted to kill a Briar-heart. I was sworn to defend him. Not that I did a good job of it.</Source>
      <Dest>她一心要干掉一个荆棘之心。我发誓保护他。然而我失败了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I like to stand up on the banister there and watch the people go to and from the market.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢站在栏杆边上，看着人们在市场里出出入入。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know what you're talking about my lady. I'm just out here for a walk. The same walk I take every day at 10 in the morning.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道你在说什么，我的小姐。我来这儿只是散步，每天早上十点也会来这儿走来走去的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, most people say to truly appreciate this city, you need get a better view. And to get a better view, you first have to climb a few stairs.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，很多人都说如果你想要真正的见见这个城市的风景，你就需要找个好视角。而要找到好视角，你就得爬些楼梯了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I told her I taught myself. And she said, "No wonder you're so bad at it."</Source>
      <Dest>我跟她说我是自学的。然后她说：“难怪你学的那么差劲。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I got about ten paces behind her when she swiveled around and came at me. </Source>
      <Dest>当我离她的背影只有十步之遥的时候她突然转过身冲着我过来了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Huh, it's a decoy! Where's the real assassin?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，这是个诱饵！真正的刺客在哪里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She chose me, she taught me, and she loved me. And from that day forward, my eyes have always been open, but I have no trouble falling asleep.</Source>
      <Dest>她选择了我，她教导我，然后她爱上了我。从那一天起，我的双眼再未合上，但仍能安然入睡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh relax. We can't stop living just because a handful of people want us dead!</Source>
      <Dest>哦放轻松。我们不能因为几个人想让我去死就遂了他们的愿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Criminals, brigands, corsairs...we did things that violated the laws of mortals, but men have always been a poor judge of character.</Source>
      <Dest>罪犯，强盗，海盗……我们做的事都违反凡人的法律，但是人们对角色的定义能力却相当可怜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, the way Markarth is constructed, there's only one way out of the city.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，马卡斯城的路已经被修好了，只有一条出城的道儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She disarmed me and put the blade to my neck. I closed my eyes. But she didn't kill me. She asked where I learned to sneak.</Source>
      <Dest>她缴了我的械，把刀放在我的脖子上。我闭上眼睛准备迎接死亡。但她没有杀死我，只是问我是在哪儿学的潜行、</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not in the slightest.</Source>
      <Dest>一点也不。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's good news. An old fool like myself welcomes whatever help he can get.</Source>
      <Dest>那还真是好消息，像我这样的老蠢货欢迎任何能得到的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
