<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They had a deal with the Jarl.  If I didn't kill Sevaris, you, me, we'd all be hunting for them.  </Source>
      <Dest>他们和领主有一笔交易。如果我没有杀赛伯斯的话，你，还有我，如今就会在寻找他们了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What reason do I have to lie?  He sold our right to hunt on our own land. </Source>
      <Dest>我有什么理由撒谎？我们在自己的土地上狩猎，他却把这项权利给卖了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sevaris was working for the East Empire Company, and some southern Baron named Gabania. </Source>
      <Dest>赛伯斯为东帝国贸易公司服务，也为南面的某个名叫卡贝尼亚的贵族服务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You still don't get it, do you?  Sevaris sold us out.</Source>
      <Dest>你还是不明白，对吗？赛伯斯把我们全都出卖了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bastard!  How much is he paying you?</Source>
      <Dest>混蛋！他付了你多少钱？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Brakh. You're the same old lap dog.</Source>
      <Dest>布拉可。你同样是一只老哈巴狗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What reason do I have to lie, idiot?  He sold our right to hunt on our own land. </Source>
      <Dest>我有什么理由撒谎，白痴？我们在自己的土地上狩猎，他却把这项权利给卖了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sevaris was working for the East Empire Company, and some southern Baron named Gabania. </Source>
      <Dest>赛伯斯为东帝国贸易公司服务，也为南面的某个名叫卡贝尼亚的贵族服务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They had a deal with the Jarl.  If I didn't kill Sevaris, you, me, we'd all be hunting for them.</Source>
      <Dest>他们和领主有一笔交易。如果我没有杀赛伯斯的话，你，还有我，如今就会在寻找他们了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You still don't get it, do you, boulder brain?  Sevaris sold us out.</Source>
      <Dest>你还是不明白，对吗，石头脑袋？赛伯斯把我们全都出卖了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
