<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The smell of death is intoxicating. You should be proud to call this place home.</Source>
      <Dest>死亡的气息令人陶醉。你应该自豪地称这个地方为家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The smell of death is intoxicating. You should be proud to call this place home.</Source>
      <Dest>死亡的气息令人陶醉。你应该自豪地称这个地方为家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Seems to me this hut belongs to a "Lund."  Are you him?</Source>
      <Dest>在我看来这间小屋属于"伦德"。你是"伦德"吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Seems to me this hut belongs to a "Lund."  Are you him?</Source>
      <Dest>在我看来这间小屋属于"伦德"。你是"伦德"吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Seems to me this hut belongs to a "Lund."  Are you him?</Source>
      <Dest>在我看来这间小屋属于"伦德"。你是"伦德"吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Seems to me this hut belongs to a "Lund."  Are you him?</Source>
      <Dest>在我看来这间小屋属于"伦德"。你是"伦德"吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Seems to me this hut belongs to a "Lund."  Are you him?</Source>
      <Dest>在我看来这间小屋属于"伦德"。你是"伦德"吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I was going to suggest we bury him, not add another body.</Source>
      <Dest>我建议我们埋了他，而不是再添一具尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I was going to suggest we bury him, not add another body.</Source>
      <Dest>我建议我们埋了他，而不是再添一具尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I apologize for intruding good sir, I'll be on my way.</Source>
      <Dest>我为冒犯好人道歉，我会以自己的方式处理。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I apologize for intruding good sir, I'll be on my way.</Source>
      <Dest>我为冒犯好人道歉，我会以自己的方式处理。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I apologize for intruding good sir, I'll be on my way.</Source>
      <Dest>我为冒犯好人道歉，我会以自己的方式处理。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Forget it.  I don't know how you live in this sty.</Source>
      <Dest>算了，我不知道你在这个猪圈里是怎么生活的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Forget it.  I don't know how you live in this sty.</Source>
      <Dest>算了，我不知道你在这个猪圈里是怎么生活的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Forget it.  I don't know how you live in this sty.</Source>
      <Dest>算了，我不知道你在这个猪圈里是怎么生活的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't mind.  Lund stays.</Source>
      <Dest>我不介意。伦德永存。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't mind.  Lund stays.</Source>
      <Dest>我不介意。伦德永存。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't mind.  Lund stays.</Source>
      <Dest>我不介意。伦德永存。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, Lund's already a pile of ash.  I fried him when you weren't looking.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，伦德已经化为一堆灰了。你没注意时我就烧了他了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why lie about it?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么在这事情上撒谎？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why lie about it?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么在这事情上撒谎？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why lie about it?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么在这事情上撒谎？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why lie about it?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么在这事情上撒谎？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why lie about it?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么在这事情上撒谎？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why lie about it?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么在这事情上撒谎？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Too bad, scum-bucket.  I go where I please.</Source>
      <Dest>那可真不幸，杂种。我要去别的地方了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Too bad, scum-bucket.  I go where I please.</Source>
      <Dest>那可真不幸，杂种。我要去别的地方了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Too bad, scum-bucket.  I go where I please.</Source>
      <Dest>那可真不幸，杂种。我要去别的地方了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Too bad, scum-bucket.  I go where I please.</Source>
      <Dest>那可真不幸，杂种。我要去别的地方了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Too bad, scum-bucket.  I go where I please.</Source>
      <Dest>那可真不幸，杂种。我要去别的地方了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, so it's your property now?  This man is barely cold.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，那么现在这是你的财产咯？这人竟冷酷得如此露骨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, so it's your property now?  This man is barely cold.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，那么现在这是你的财产咯？这人竟冷酷得如此露骨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something about you seems off.  Tell me, what does cabbage smell like?</Source>
      <Dest>你好像不在状态。告诉我，卷心菜闻起来是什么味道？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My mistake.  I presumed you had some dignity left.</Source>
      <Dest>都是我的错。我希望你还留有一点自尊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My mistake.  I presumed you had some dignity left.</Source>
      <Dest>都是我的错。我希望你还留有一点自尊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you considered living elsewhere?</Source>
      <Dest>你想过搬去别处住吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥的新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Housecarls don't do that, do they?</Source>
      <Dest>做侍卫的应该不会干这个吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Housecarls don't do that, do they?</Source>
      <Dest>做侍卫的应该不会干这个吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Housecarls don't do that, do they?</Source>
      <Dest>做侍卫的应该不会干这个吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Those clothes don't seem to fit you.</Source>
      <Dest>你那身衣服好像不太合身啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't I raise Lund and ask him about this arrangement?</Source>
      <Dest>我为什么不让伦德复生，然后问问他这项协议的事情呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't I raise Lund and ask him about this arrangement?</Source>
      <Dest>我为什么不让伦德复生，然后问问他这项协议的事情呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Barely cold, ash, or bones, dead is dead.  And unless them skeevers is his kin, I believe the law is quite clear what happens next.</Source>
      <Dest>略有点冰冷，灰或者骨头，尸体就是尸体。除非那帮雪鼠是他的亲戚，否则接下来按照法律来处理就可以了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, no, not kind, humble, Ulfric!  Ugly, yes.  Dead, most certainly.  But arrogant?  How dare anyone suggest such a thing!</Source>
      <Dest>不，不。不善良，也不谦逊。乌佛瑞克! 假恶丑，没错！真恶心。死，一定得死。但是说——傲慢？别歪曲事实行么！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Because I'm a man, and a man has his pride.  Don't want people feeling sorry for me every time they pass around a bottle.</Source>
      <Dest>因为我是一个男人，而一个男人有他的骄傲。每当人们传着喝一瓶酒的时候，我都不想让他们为我感到难过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Because I'm a man, and a man has his pride.  Don't want people feeling sorry for me every time they pass around a bottle.</Source>
      <Dest>因为我是一个男人，而一个男人有他的骄傲。每当人们传着喝一瓶酒的时候，我都不想让他们为我感到难过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Red as a snowberry, and mad as a bull.  Someone had the stones to call Ulfric arrogant.</Source>
      <Dest>红如浆果，疯如狂牛。一些人将这块儿石头称为乌佛瑞克的傲慢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Red as a snowberry, and mad as a bull.  Someone had the stones to call Ulfric arrogant.</Source>
      <Dest>红如浆果，疯如狂牛。一些人将这块儿石头称为乌佛瑞克的傲慢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bury him?  You mean, dispose the corpse?  Why don't you just invite the bandits into my home, and serve them tea?</Source>
      <Dest>把他埋了？你的意思是，你就想这么处理这具尸体？你为什么不干脆邀请强盗到我家做客，然后给他们敬茶呢？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You ever met that girl Sissel?  Cute girl, and smart too.  Must've gotten it all from the mother's side.</Source>
      <Dest>你见过那个叫希塞尔的女孩吗？漂亮妞儿一个，而且聪明着呢。肯定是她妈妈那边的遗传。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not much for bathing, that one.  Not much for anything I suppose, given he's dead.</Source>
      <Dest>这都不够用来洗澡。如果他死了，我猜干什么都不够用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eh, but I reckon she likes her men with all their teeth and a functioning hip.  It's all in the hips, you see.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，但我估计她喜欢她的那些有着一口漂亮的牙齿和不错的臀部的人。屁股决定一切，你瞧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you really need a bed for the night, then be my guest.  You can have his bed, he ain't got no use for it.</Source>
      <Dest>而要是你真需要一张床来过夜，那就请便啦。你可以用他的床，他反正是用不上了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I believe it's something to the effect of "Finders Keepers."  But you can check with the nearest Jarl if you want to confirm that.</Source>
      <Dest>我相信法律上有对"谁发现谁拥有"这条做出规定。但你如果想弄明白的话，可以去找离这最近的领主确认。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The other half just wants to sit here and get drunk.  Guess which half I listen to.</Source>
      <Dest>他们中另一半却只想坐在原地喝个痛快。猜猜我最终听了哪些人的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why yes, let me just summon my carriage and housecarl, and have one escort me to my home in Solitude while the other tends to my nipples.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，是的，让我传唤我的马车和侍卫吧，他们其中一个能送我回独孤城的家，而另一个只对我的乳头感兴趣。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I knew it.  You're one of them conjurers.  I heard about your type.  Raising the dead...sleeping with them.  Just try not to make a mess.</Source>
      <Dest>我就知道，你是一个巫师。你们这种人我很清楚的。唤醒死者...然后睡了它们，只是别搞出什么乱子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've been sleeping on the floor myself.  Was too lazy to bury the poor bastard, hoped maybe the skeevers would eat him.</Source>
      <Dest>我自己都睡在地上，当然懒得去埋了那个可怜虫了。也许雪鼠吃掉他最好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's like when you can't make fun of ugly people because there's an Orc in the room.  It just makes things awkward.</Source>
      <Dest>这就像是当有兽人在房间里时你不能开那些丑人的玩笑。这只是把事情弄尴尬罢了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What in Stendarr's Mercy?  Are those...manners?  You must've been raised by a noble or something, polite as you are.</Source>
      <Dest>斯丹纳尔的怜悯在上？这些是……礼貌？你肯定是受贵族或别的教导，才会如此彬彬有礼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Cabbage?  Smells like dirt and rivers and uh, sunsets.  You know, vegetable smells.</Source>
      <Dest>卷心菜？闻起来像泥土和河流和呃，日落。你知道，蔬菜的味道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I wouldn't be in a hurry to bury him.  The odor helps keep the deviants off my property.  You know, bandits, thieves, children.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管我不会这么快埋葬他。这个气味会让不速之客远离我的地盘。你知道，强盗，小偷，孩子之类的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't get me wrong, half of me wants to head down to Rorikstead and ask old Jouane for a job.</Source>
      <Dest>别误会了，我也有点想去洛利克镇问老乔安找个工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, no, not kind, humble Ulfric!  Ugly, yes.  Stupid, most certainly.  But arrogant?  How dare anyone suggest such a thing!</Source>
      <Dest>不，不，乌佛瑞克既不善良也不谦逊！（他）丑陋，没错，愚蠢，这是当然的啦。但要说他傲慢？怎么有人胆敢这样说！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What does that even mean, "Hm?"  How do you respond to that?  It's not a question, and it's not a statement.  It's not even a word.</Source>
      <Dest>那到底意味着什么，“嗯”？你是怎么理解的？这并不是一个问题，也不是一个说明。这甚至连一个字都算不上！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, all part of the circle of life.  Rats eat man, man eats rats, then man moves into dead man's home.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道的，所有这一切都是生命的轮回。鼠吃人，人吃鼠，然后活人搬进死人家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unless...unless he's already lost his smell...Stendarr's Mercy, I thought these things take months to rot!</Source>
      <Dest>除非……除非他已经失去嗅觉了……斯丹纳尔怜悯我们，我以为这些东西得过几个月才能腐烂呢！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, Lund is that fellow lying on the bed over there.  That thing you smell?  Like rotten meat stuffed into a warm armpit?  That's Lund.</Source>
      <Dest>不，伦德是躺在那边床上的家伙。你闻到那个味儿了吗？像是把烂肉塞进一个温暖腋下的味道？那就是伦德的味儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ulfric?  Arrogant?  No...No...Not a chance!  Sure he thinks he's a dragon and treats his own soldiers like fungus, but what man wouldn't?</Source>
      <Dest>乌佛瑞克？傲慢？不…不…不可能！当然他认为他是一条巨龙而且对自己的士兵如同草芥，但哪个男人又不那样呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well in that case, you're welcome to ask my imaginary housecarl to tend to yours as well.  </Source>
      <Dest>好吧这么说起来，也欢迎你要求你虚构的侍卫来帮你忙。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ulfric?  Arrogant?  No...No...Not a chance!  Sure he thought he was a dragon and treated his own soldiers like fungus, but what man wouldn't?</Source>
      <Dest>乌佛瑞克?傲慢？不…不…不可能！当然他认为他是一条巨龙而且对自己的士兵如同草芥，但哪个男人又不那样呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for their worst enemy, well, I'd say that was a tie between common sense and common decency.</Source>
      <Dest>至于他们最大的敌人，好吧，我得说那是常识与社会风化之间不相伯仲的较量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So it ain't my roof.  Big deal.  That don't make me a thief.  Don't see how it's a crime to take from a dead man with no kin.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这不是我的屋子。问题大发了。这可不能让我去做贼。你不知道从一个无子嗣的私人手里拿东西有多大罪过啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, but I was thinking.  Ever notice how some folks don't even greet you properly?  They just smack their lips together and go "Hm?"</Source>
      <Dest>不，但我在想。是不是有些人没有用合适的方式欢迎你。他们闭着嘴巴然后离开了“嗯?"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then we'll go outside and watch her milk Ennis' goat.  Won't that be a fun time to be a complete moron.</Source>
      <Dest>那么我们就出去看看她找埃尼斯的山羊挤奶。对一个彻头彻尾的蠢货来说还真是段美好时光。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What, you're asking me?  Does the concept of sarcasm mean nothing to you?</Source>
      <Dest>什么，你在问我吗？? 难道那些讽刺的想法对你来说一文不值吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, "Hm" to you too friend.  I'll just be over at your place tonight, "Hm'ing" your sister, unless you got something you wanna say to that.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧哥们儿，也‘哼’你一个。今晚我就去你那儿，跟你妹妹也‘哼’一个，除非你有什么话想说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're, uh, hand me downs.  From my brother.  Lun-dius.  </Source>
      <Dest>那些是，呃……捡人家用过的。是我哥哥伦迪斯的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't want to be the one who ruins everyone's good time.</Source>
      <Dest>我不想因为我扫了大家的兴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't want to be the one who ruins everyone's good time.</Source>
      <Dest>我不想因为我扫了大家的兴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>On the other hand, the worse he smells, the less I have to worry about.</Source>
      <Dest>不过换个角度想想，他的气味越难闻，我就越没什么好担心的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's like when you can't make fun of short people because there's a Breton in the room.</Source>
      <Dest>打个比方说，如果屋子里有布莱顿人的话，那你就不能开矮个子的玩笑啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What are you, some kind of conjurer or something?  I've always said a corpse's best friend was a mage.</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么人，巫师还是什么别的？我就说和尸体最亲的人就是法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I knew it.  You're one of them conjurers.  I heard about your type.  Raising the dead...sleeping with them.  Just as long as I, uh, get to watch.</Source>
      <Dest>我就知道，你是一个巫师。你们这种人我很清楚的。唤醒死者...然后睡了它们。每次我看到的时候，嗯，都是那样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It ain't all bad.  I got a roof over my head, mead in my hand, and all the skeevers I can eat.</Source>
      <Dest>还不是很坏。我头上还有屋顶能遮风挡雨，我手头还有瓶蜜酒，而这堆雪鼠我可以随便吃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait!  There's room enough for the both of us.  You can have the bed, if you're willing to do something about Lund.</Source>
      <Dest>等等！这间房够我们俩住的了。如果你愿意帮伦德做点事，那你可以睡床。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I feel the same way about that Sonja woman over at the inn.  The set of gourds on that one!  </Source>
      <Dest>我对那个酒店女索尼娅有类似的感觉。就是胸口长着对“葫芦”的那个！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I went down to the inn the other day, and the topic was about Ulfric, and you should've seen the look on Sonja's breasts, I mean face.</Source>
      <Dest>某天我去了旅馆，那里在谈论着的话题是关于乌弗瑞克的，而你应该已经见过索尼娅胸上，我是说脸上的样子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I went down to the inn the other day, and the topic was about Ulfric, and you should've seen the look on Sonja's breasts, I mean face.</Source>
      <Dest>某天我去了旅馆，那里在谈论着的话题是关于乌弗瑞克的，而你应该已经见过索尼娅胸上，我是说脸上的样子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, my liege, worry not, because there's room in this old hut for two.  In fact, bed's all yours, if you're willing to do something about Lund.  </Source>
      <Dest> 好吧，大人您不用担心。这个小屋够两个人住。实际上床也归你，你想跟床上那位伦德做点啥那也请便。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although granted, it does help to keep the bandits and wolves from uh, trespassing on my property.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管得到允许了，它确实能让强盗和狼不在侵犯我的，额，我的财产。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ash?  You...you fool!  We have to leave.  Good home with a good roof, just off the main road, it'll attract all sorts of criminals and fiends.</Source>
      <Dest>啊？你……你个蠢货！我们得马上离开。这么完整的一幢好房子，还就在大路边上，这下各种各样的朋友和罪犯都会来光顾啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What?  Corpses all have the same odor.  The terrible kind.</Source>
      <Dest>什么？尸体都有相同的气味。那种气味很可怕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What?  Corpses all have the same odor.  The terrible kind.</Source>
      <Dest>什么？尸体都有相同的气味。那种气味很可怕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Smell is also linked to sight.  Memory in particular.</Source>
      <Dest>所见和所闻经常是不可分割的，特别是在记忆里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Smell is also linked to sight.  Memory in particular.</Source>
      <Dest>所见和所闻经常是不可分割的，特别是在记忆里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Smell is also linked to sight.  Memory in particular.</Source>
      <Dest>所见和所闻经常是不可分割的，特别是在记忆里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Smell is also linked to sight.  Memory in particular.</Source>
      <Dest>所见和所闻经常是不可分割的，特别是在记忆里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You have no sense of smell, do you?</Source>
      <Dest>你没有嗅觉对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You have no sense of smell, do you?</Source>
      <Dest>你没有嗅觉对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You have no sense of smell, do you?</Source>
      <Dest>你没有嗅觉对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You have no sense of smell, do you?</Source>
      <Dest>你没有嗅觉对吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Even beggars have standards.</Source>
      <Dest>甚至乞丐们都有标准。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Even beggars have standards.</Source>
      <Dest>甚至乞丐们都有标准。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Even beggars have standards.</Source>
      <Dest>甚至乞丐们都有标准。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Smells influencing taste?  That's the craziest sodding thing I've ever heard.</Source>
      <Dest>嗅觉影响着味觉？这是迄今我所听到的最疯狂的事儿了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Smells influencing taste?  That's the craziest sodding thing I've ever heard.</Source>
      <Dest>嗅觉影响着味觉？这是迄今我所听到的最疯狂的事儿了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Smells influencing taste?  That's the craziest sodding thing I've ever heard.</Source>
      <Dest>嗅觉影响着味觉？这是迄今我所听到的最疯狂的事儿了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I lied earlier, the stench is gone.  And I saw some drifters outside.</Source>
      <Dest>早先是我在撒谎说恶臭已经没有了。而且我看到一些流浪者在外边。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, I was just wondering if you might move and leave this fantastic home vacant.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我只想知道你能不能离开这儿然后搬往那个闲置而美好的新家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, I was just wondering if you might move and leave this fantastic home vacant.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我只想知道你能不能离开这儿然后搬往那个闲置而美好的新家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, I was just wondering if you might move and leave this fantastic home vacant.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我只想知道你能不能离开这儿然后搬往那个闲置而美好的新家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>At some point something will have to be done about Lund.</Source>
      <Dest>待到某个时候，伦德会被安置好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting rumors or news?</Source>
      <Dest>有啥新鲜事儿说说吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like the way people get so passionate about their mead, or how certain foods that have no business tasting the same, always do.</Source>
      <Dest>就像人们钟情于他们的蜜酒，或者别的一些没时间尝试的食物那样，一向如此.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was a Nord I knew who was born in Falkreath, who loved this one tavern because he said the tables and counters smelled like fresh pines.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道一个出生在佛克瑞斯的诺德人很喜欢这家酒馆儿。他说是因为这儿的桌子和柜台闻起来的味道像是新鲜的松树。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose that makes sense.  I've heard people talk about how cities all have their own smell.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这是很有意义的。人们嘴里所说的，对于这座城市的气味的印象各不相同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it was all beautiful to him, because the smell reminded him of home.</Source>
      <Dest>但这一切对他而言都是那么美好，因为那股气息让他想起了家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Next time you eat something, hold your nose.  Same thing.</Source>
      <Dest>下次你吃东西时，记得把鼻子堵上。这是一码事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Huh?</Source>
      <Dest>哈？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He told me smell ain't just about odor.  Turns out when you taste something, you gotta smell it too, or it ends up not having any taste.</Source>
      <Dest>他告诉我闻并不只跟香味有关。而是当你在品尝东西时，你也要闻，要不然你是尝不出什么结果的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey!  What are you doing here?   You can't stay here, I found this place first!</Source>
      <Dest>嘿！你在这里干什么？你不能呆在这里，是我先发现这个地方的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well there's more than just the smell you gotta deal with.  You got skeevers nipping at you day and night.  Spiders big as a human hand.</Source>
      <Dest>你要处理的可不只是身上的臭味儿。你可日夜被雪鼠追着咬呢。还有人手那么大的蜘蛛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you talk to him, it's like time stops, and he has to walk from his mouth to his mind like it's in another room.</Source>
      <Dest>跟他对话的时候，你会觉得时间像是静止了一样，他的回答总是慢慢地从他的脑子里走到他的嘴里，而且他的脑子和他的嘴隔得还挺远。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Divines only know what you'd find in there.  Probably the void.</Source>
      <Dest>鬼才知道你能在那儿找到什么，大概只能找到虚空。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Salty, sour, sweet, bitter and savory.  That's it.</Source>
      <Dest>酸甜苦辣咸，五味俱全。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Make it quick.</Source>
      <Dest>有话快说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, I reckon you're right.  But where am I going to get another corpse?  Skeevers don't have the same smell.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，或许你是对的，但是我从哪儿搞到另一具尸体？雪鼠可没有闻起来气味相同的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gone?  Then...then my worst fears have been realized.  There's no telling how many of them are out there.</Source>
      <Dest>不见了？那......那就意味着我最害怕的事情已经发生了。天知道外面还有多少个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, I ain't explaining it very well.  Basically what he said was, when I eat something, ain't got but five flavors.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我刚刚没有解释清楚。他所说的大体意思是：当我吃东西时，我只能尝到五种味道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thought it was about the plainest tavern in all Tamriel, and home to the frumpiest wenches in all of Nirn.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这就是整个泰姆瑞尔大陆里最简朴的酒馆儿了，还有整个奈恩最邋遢的酒馆女。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?   I mean, of course they do, I can smell them just as good as you can.  Smells like, uh, old coins.</Source>
      <Dest>真的？我的意思是，他们当然做了, 我可以像你一样闻到他们. 闻起来像，呃, 古老的钱币.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Way people talk about how everything stinks, used to think it was a blessing.  But then I met this soldier who lost his sense of smell in the war.</Source>
      <Dest>人们说到某样东西有什么气味时，一般把它当成一种祝福。可我后来就遇见了这个在战场上失去了嗅觉的士兵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But Lund ain't just a smelly corpse.  He, uh, haunts this place too, so don't get any ideas.</Source>
      <Dest>可是伦德不只是一具腐臭的尸体。他，呃，他的灵魂还萦绕在这间屋子，所以不要有什么想法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was an unbeliever once.  Then I started noticing things.  Things I probably should've noticed, but was just too thick to pick up on.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾经是个异教徒。后来我逐渐开始注意到了一些我本不该注意到的事，它们太过于沉重，以至于让人难以去正视。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is it?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why when folks get sick, they complain about losing their sense of taste.  What they really lost is their sense of smell.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是为什么当人们生病的时候，会抱怨自己的舌头不灵光。他们真正失去的其实是他们的嗅觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That Lemkil is about two bees short of a hive.</Source>
      <Dest>莱姆吉尔那儿可是两个蜜蜂共享一个蜂房。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I...I guess it's no use lying about it.  You're right.  Never had a sense of smell.  Although I've always done my best to fake it.</Source>
      <Dest>我……我猜在这上面撒谎也没用。你说的没错。我没有嗅觉。即便我一直都在掩饰这点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He was out fighting Thalmor and got kissed by an ice spike.  Said the last thing he ever smelled was the cold blood crawling down his nose. </Source>
      <Dest>他去和梭默打架然后被一个冰刺刺穿了嘴，说的最后的话是他闻到了冰血流过他鼻子的味道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Figured one of these days someone else was gonna come around and not be bothered by the smell.</Source>
      <Dest>想想吧，有一天有人醒过来时发现自己并不再被这些味道所烦扰了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>About time.</Source>
      <Dest>是时候了。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
