<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry, but you heard her.  Zora is hungry for a goat roast.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉，不过你也听到了。佐拉现在饿得能够吞下一只烤全羊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, that was the signal for me to kill you.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，那是给我的信号，让我杀掉你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here. Take it and get out of here.  I never want to see you again.</Source>
      <Dest>这个...拿着它然后离开这里，我再也不想见到你。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A deal's a deal.  Here you go.</Source>
      <Dest>成交。就这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now don't give me that look girl, I don't care if your sister lives or dies.</Source>
      <Dest>别用那种眼神看我，小姑娘。我不在乎你姐妹是死是活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Better you stay that way. A girl your size could stand to lose a few pounds.</Source>
      <Dest>你还是保持原样的好。你这么瘦弱的女孩再减去几磅重就没法活了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for what you'll find inside, it's anyone's guess. Young people are idiots. Children even more so.</Source>
      <Dest>至于你将会在里面发现的那些，仅仅是某人的猜测。年轻人没脑子，小孩子更甚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, the only way to revive the crystal's power is to remove the soul inside it.  Thus, our goals are one and the same.</Source>
      <Dest>总之，获取水晶之力的唯一方法是把其中的灵魂去掉。因此我们的目标是一致的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Girl, this is hardly the place to talk of such things.   Come, to the graveyard. At least the dead share no secrets.</Source>
      <Dest>好姑娘，这可不是谈论这类东西的地方。来吧，去墓地。至少死者不会分享我们的秘密。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You took the words right out of my mouth, barbarian.  I'll gladly take my leave of the lot of you.</Source>
      <Dest>你正好说出了我要说的话，野蛮人。我很乐意离你远远的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Evidently the snowstorm brought her back, and with it, my property.</Source>
      <Dest>显然，暴风雪带着她和我的财产一起回了家。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course it's the crystal. I didn't come all this way to watch you fools tangle with bloodsuckers.</Source>
      <Dest>这当然是那块水晶。我从没想过要看着你像个傻瓜似的和一个吸血鬼起冲突。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goat roast? What are you talking about?</Source>
      <Dest>烤全羊？你在说些什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for you, my foolish apprentice, be thankful you are alive.  But if I ever see you again, you won't be.</Source>
      <Dest>至于你，我的傻徒弟，谢天谢地你还活着。但如果我再见到你，你就得死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gods know I warned the stupid girl.  But young people just do not listen.</Source>
      <Dest>天晓得，我已经警告过那个笨女孩。可年轻人就是听不进去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goat roast?  It seems like the crystal has warped your companion's mind.  But that's not my concern.  Give me the crystal.</Source>
      <Dest>烤全羊？看来那块水晶把你那伙伴的脑子给烤坏了啊。不过这跟我没有任何关系，把那块宝石给我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?  None of you are making any sense!  You give me my crystal now!</Source>
      <Dest>什么？你们真是一点用处都没有！把我的水晶还给我！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, it was only a matter of time before I caught the traitor, which is why she escaped into the very crystal she stole.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，要抓住那个叛徒只是时间问题，这也是为什么她会逃入她所偷的那块水晶里的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That would not be wise, if you wish to see your dear sister again.  I am the only one who can open the portal.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你还想再见到你那亲爱的妹妹的话，这可不怎么明智。我是那个唯一可以打开这个入口的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What are you two idiots babbling on about?  Let's get going.</Source>
      <Dest>你们两个白痴在嘀咕什么呢？我们走吧。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're back!  Wait...why are there only two of you!  We had a deal you ugly scar-covered whetstone!</Source>
      <Dest>你回来啦！等等...为啥只回来了两个！我们说好了不是吗你这个难看的布满伤痕的磨刀石！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The devil is in the wording, of course.  Eternal youth indeed.  It's a curse.</Source>
      <Dest>这语句里可是装着魔鬼呢，当然了。的确是能永葆青春，但这也是个诅咒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you sure, girl? Are you sure you aren't better off crawling around like a newborn babe? Isn't that the life you prefer?</Source>
      <Dest>你确定，女孩？整天爬来爬去得像个婴儿岂不是更好吗？这不是你的理想生活吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I would do it myself, but why risk my life when you can risk yours. In exchange, the girl is allowed to live.  I trust we have a deal?</Source>
      <Dest>我会亲自动手的。但为什么你在拿你自己的命来冒险的时候，我却要用我的生命冒险？作为交换，那个姑娘得活着。这下我们可以成交了吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you think I've come all this way to let that girl escape with my crystal?  Now give it here before I kill all three of you idiots!</Source>
      <Dest>你以为我大老远来会让那个女孩逃脱我的水晶？现在在我干掉你们三个白痴之前把它放在这儿！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've changed my mind, target dummies don't talk as much as you do.  And your face is carved up like a bloody whetstone.  That's it.  Whetstone.</Source>
      <Dest>我改主意了，活靶子可不像你那么话多。而且你的脸被整的雕塑一样。没错，雕塑。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Those are some hefty scars, girl.  I've got a new name for you.  Target Dummy.</Source>
      <Dest>那些是严重的伤疤，姑娘，我可以给你起个新名字，就叫你，“活靶子”好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How gracious.  That fat little whetstone could learn a few things from you.</Source>
      <Dest>多么仁慈啊，那个油嘴滑舌的胖家伙肯定能从您身上学到很多东西！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As in "Joselyn Fair-Child.  The mother of all fools."</Source>
      <Dest>和"约瑟林 菲欧巧儿。 众愚之母。"里一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The legends say it would transport you to a paradise of eternal youth.  Naturally, for someone of my years, this seemed like an attractive prospect.</Source>
      <Dest>传说它会把你传送到一个可以永葆青春的天堂里。自然的，对于像我这么大年纪的人来说，这似乎还挺有吸引力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes I wonder if your sister is no ordinary fool, but the kind of fool so foolish that her name should be carved on the tree of all creation.</Source>
      <Dest>有些时候我觉得你姐姐并不是一个一般的蠢货，而是蠢得能上蠢人纪念碑的那种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't worry, my foolish apprentice, your whetstone of a sister hasn't betrayed you.  You're the only traitor here.  All I want is what's mine.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，我愚蠢的徒弟，你姐妹并没有背叛你。你才是这里唯一的叛徒。我想要的就是我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What did you say?</Source>
      <Dest>你说啥？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which was good.  I tire of young people and the endless flapping of their tongues.  She made for the perfect apprentice.</Source>
      <Dest>我厌倦了年轻人还有他们喋喋不休的婆婆嘴，她作为学徒在这点上表现的令人满意，很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For your information, your sister joined our coven and was otherwise happy, until her greed got the best of her.</Source>
      <Dest>至于你的信息，你的姐妹加入了我们的集会，而且非常高兴——直到贪婪占据了她的内心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You two want to say any last words to each other before we do this? Well, too bad! In you go!</Source>
      <Dest>在我们动手之前，你们互相之间还有什么遗言要说么？好吧，那真是太糟糕了！去死吧！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, you both stand still. I'll use the old magic to send you both inside the crystal.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，你俩都站稳了。我要用那招古老魔法送你们进入水晶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Somehow I doubt that.  My girls were waiting for her there for quite some time.  </Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说我都不相信。我的女孩们在这里等她很久了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anyone who enters the plane turns into a child.  A child of body, and a child of mind.</Source>
      <Dest>任何进入那个世界的人都像孩童一样。拥有孩童的身体，以及孩童的心态。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're right.  You know what is my business? Getting my crystal back.  If you can't do that, I'll add another stripe to your collection.</Source>
      <Dest>你说得很对。你知道我是做什么的？把水晶交出来。否则，你的这些藏品可就说不准了...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you think she can actually hear you?  Of course you must.  You're a fool.</Source>
      <Dest>你该不会真的以为她会听你的吧？哦你当然会那样认为。因为你是蠢货嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And they say witches have no sense of honor!  To the void with all of you!</Source>
      <Dest>他们都说巫师是没有恐怖感的！你们这帮混蛋都给我下地狱去吧！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My girls tracked her to Bloodlet Throne.  Which means she ran from my coven right into a castle full of vampires.</Source>
      <Dest>我的姑娘跟着她到了释血王座。也就是说她前脚踏出我的女巫大聚会，后脚就迈进了一座充满了吸血鬼的城堡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you're Joselyn's sister.  She never talked much about you, but the girl never talked much at all.  I thought she was a sodding mute!</Source>
      <Dest>那么你肯定就是约瑟林的妹妹了。 她从未提起过你，不过她平时也就是不怎么开口。我还以为她是个哑巴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Meaning, I'm more than willing to let her live, if it saves me the trouble of dealing with you.  I simply want what is rightfully mine. </Source>
      <Dest>意思是, 如果跟你的这单交易能解决我的麻烦的话, 我更情愿让她活着.  我仅仅是想要合法的矿产而已. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Where did you get all those scars anyway?</Source>
      <Dest>你这些伤疤都是哪来的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's another thing about you young people.  You think you know everything.  So arrogant.</Source>
      <Dest>这另一件事是关于你，年轻人。你总是认为你自己知道所有的事情。太傲慢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Young people, so impatient.  The crystal is a key.  A portal to another plane of existence.</Source>
      <Dest>年轻人，太重要了。这水晶可是关键。这可是另一个平行世界的入口。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
