<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You put a lot of faith in Gods that are about to orphan your daughter.</Source>
      <Dest>你太忠于那些想让你的女儿失去父母的神灵了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You put a lot of faith in Gods that are about to orphan your daughter.</Source>
      <Dest>你太忠于那些想让你的女儿失去父母的神灵了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Stay right there. I can mix a poultice that can fix you right up.</Source>
      <Dest>待在这。我能够马上合成一个药膏来给你疗伤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Stay right there. I can mix a poultice that can fix you right up.</Source>
      <Dest>待在这。我能够马上合成一个药膏来给你疗伤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Stay right there. I can mix a poultice that can fix you right up.</Source>
      <Dest>待在这。我能够马上合成一个药膏来给你疗伤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's better this way.  You don't want to confuse the poor child.</Source>
      <Dest>这样更好。你不想扰乱那可怜的孩子吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He died trying to save you.</Source>
      <Dest>他为了救你而死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He died trying to save you.</Source>
      <Dest>他为了救你而死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The priestess in Whiterun can take care of you.  I can vouch for her skill.</Source>
      <Dest>白漫城的女祭司会照顾你的，我可以为她的能力担保。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The priestess in Whiterun can take care of you.  I can vouch for her skill.</Source>
      <Dest>白漫城的女祭司会照顾你的，我可以为她的能力担保。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The priestess in Whiterun can take care of you.  I can vouch for her skill.</Source>
      <Dest>白漫城的女祭司会照顾你的，我可以为她的能力担保。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Brace yourself. I'm about to hit you with a healing spell.</Source>
      <Dest>振作起来。我会对你施展一个治疗法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your husband.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我说说妳丈夫的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your husband.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我说说妳丈夫的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your husband.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我说说妳丈夫的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your husband.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我说说妳丈夫的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your husband.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我说说妳丈夫的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why, what's wrong?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么？出了什么问题吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you staying in Falkreath?</Source>
      <Dest>你会在佛克瑞斯逗留吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you staying in Falkreath?</Source>
      <Dest>你会在佛克瑞斯逗留吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you staying in Falkreath?</Source>
      <Dest>你会在佛克瑞斯逗留吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you staying in Falkreath?</Source>
      <Dest>你会在佛克瑞斯逗留吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you staying in Falkreath?</Source>
      <Dest>你会在佛克瑞斯逗留吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened to her father?</Source>
      <Dest>她的父亲出什么事了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened to her father?</Source>
      <Dest>她的父亲出什么事了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did he die?</Source>
      <Dest>他是怎么死的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did he die?</Source>
      <Dest>他是怎么死的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did he die?</Source>
      <Dest>他是怎么死的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An incurable illness? By Akatosh I hope you're not contagious!</Source>
      <Dest>不治之症？阿卡托什之上！我希望你的病不会传染！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An incurable illness? By Akatosh I hope you're not contagious!</Source>
      <Dest>不治之症？阿卡托什之上！我希望你的病不会传染！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She must get that from her mother.</Source>
      <Dest>她大概是从她母亲那边得到那个的吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you tried praying at a shrine?  That usually works for me when I'm sick.</Source>
      <Dest>你有去神庙祈祷过吗？通常我生病的时候都会这么做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you tried praying at a shrine?  That usually works for me when I'm sick.</Source>
      <Dest>你有去神庙祈祷过吗？通常我生病的时候都会这么做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you tried praying at a shrine?  That usually works for me when I'm sick.</Source>
      <Dest>你有去神庙祈祷过吗？通常我生病的时候都会这么做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your husband's belief in Arkay was strong.  He knew the child would find a home.</Source>
      <Dest>你的丈夫深信着阿尔凯的力量。他相信它会带领孩子找到一个家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there anything you can do to help her remember?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么办法能帮她回忆起来吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there anything you can do to help her remember?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么办法能帮她回忆起来吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there anything you can do to help her remember?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么办法能帮她回忆起来吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there anything you can do to help her remember?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么办法能帮她回忆起来吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Like what?</Source>
      <Dest>就像怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Like what?</Source>
      <Dest>就像怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Like what?</Source>
      <Dest>就像怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The bright and talented part.</Source>
      <Dest>聪明伶俐的那部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She's being adopted?</Source>
      <Dest>她就要被领养了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She's being adopted?</Source>
      <Dest>她就要被领养了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't have time for that.</Source>
      <Dest>我没那个闲时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That fiend.</Source>
      <Dest>恶毒的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That fiend.</Source>
      <Dest>恶毒的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That fiend.</Source>
      <Dest>恶毒的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That fiend.</Source>
      <Dest>恶毒的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That fiend.</Source>
      <Dest>恶毒的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That fiend.</Source>
      <Dest>恶毒的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which part?</Source>
      <Dest>关于哪部分的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When the Great War began, he was one of the first in our town to enlist in the Imperial Army.  He despised the Thalmor, and so did I.</Source>
      <Dest>当世界大战开打时，他是我们镇上第一批加入帝国军队的人。他鄙视梭默，我也是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sweetheart, you'll know when you're older.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的，等你老了，你就会能明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I traveled with my young daughter from Bruma, braving the trek across the mountains that fringed the border.</Source>
      <Dest>我与我的女儿从冬至城翻山越岭，越过边界而来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've already arranged for a plot of land, away from the trees, where the stone is warmed by the dawn light coming from the east.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经找到了一块土地，在森林的另一端，东方冉升的曦阳照暖了那里的岩石。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When that failed, I considered taking her to the orphanage in Riften, but their cemetery is full, and the divines blessed us by guiding us here.  </Source>
      <Dest>当希望破灭，我考虑把女儿带去裂谷城的孤儿院，但那里的公墓没有空位，谢天谢地，圣灵们最后还是引领着我们来到了这儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was a foolish thing.  A romantic thing, but the two are often one in the same.</Source>
      <Dest>这样或许死得很盲目，又或者死得很浪漫，但这两者又有什么区别呢，反正都是死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I've tried.  I prayed at the chapel in Bruma, at the Temple of Kynareth and every shrine and altar along the way.  </Source>
      <Dest>唉，我试过了。我在冬至城的教堂，在凯娜瑞斯的神庙，还有一路上每个神殿与祭坛都祈祷过了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're right.  Only through faith can we achieve the impossible, and should our efforts fail, the Divines will reward us for our belief.</Source>
      <Dest>你说的对。唯有信念能让我们成就不可能。即便最后铩羽而归，圣灵们仍会回报我们坚定的信仰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I plan to stay here with my daughter until Arkay bid me leave.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，我打算跟女儿长住在这里，直到阿尔凯来接我离去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's funny, when they told me about the grand cemetery at Falkreath, I was so worried it might be too large.  </Source>
      <Dest>这说来也真好笑，当初人们跟我说佛克瑞斯有个大墓园时，我还担心太大太热闹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know when she's older she'll remember Indara as her real mother.  It's wrong to think so, but it almost makes me jealous.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道，当她再大点后，她会记起她真正的母亲因达拉。我知道这样想是错的，但我竟然感到嫉妒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Things finally began to slow down.   It took some time to patch our relationship back together, but we made it work for twenty years.</Source>
      <Dest>状况终于平缓了下来。我们花了不少时间让我们的关系恢复成以前那样，但那样的关系整整维持了二十年。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And here I thought you were going to say the "complaining" part.  Not that you'd be wrong, but it'd be sort of mean to say.</Source>
      <Dest>我刚想你可能正要说到“抱怨”的部分。不是说你错，只是这样说话有点无礼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I believe she will.  I have yet to broach the subject with them, because their loss is so fresh.</Source>
      <Dest>我相信她会的。我要赶快去跟他们提这件事，现在正是新伤未愈的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These last few days I've tried to tell her all the little things, the stuff she won't understand until she's older.</Source>
      <Dest>这几天我一直想告诉她那些事，那些在她长大前她都不会明白的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As the base ingredient in an alchemy potion, they said it could cure almost any disease.</Source>
      <Dest>它是种炼金药剂的基底，人们说这种药剂能医治百病。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's where he met a girl, in a small town by the southern peninsula. </Source>
      <Dest>在半岛南部的一个小村庄他遇见了一个姑娘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He was a gallant man, and my best friend.  We met on the coast of Rihad as children, and married as young adults.</Source>
      <Dest>他是个讲义气的男子汉，是我的至亲挚友。我们儿时在瑞雅德的海岸遇见彼此，青春年华时就互许终身。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know it sounds selfish, but she is my daughter.  I want to be part of her life, even in death.  But thank you anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道这听起来很自私，但她是我的女儿。我想成为她生命中的一部份，即使我死后也是。但无论如何，谢谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I supported him in his decision.  I told him to go to Gilane where the army needed soldiers most.  </Source>
      <Dest>我支持他的决定。我叫他去缺兵最严重的吉廉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My husband passed away not too long ago.  She reminds me so much of him.</Source>
      <Dest>我丈夫才过世不久。看着她总让我不由自主地又想起了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm worried she'll forget me. She's just a child, and the memories she has now will soon be replaced.</Source>
      <Dest>我担心她会忘记我。她只是个孩子，现在发生的事她也会很快忘掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How to brush her hair. How to tell when a man lies.  The perfect recipe for apple cabbage soup.</Source>
      <Dest>如何梳头？如何识破男人的谎言？外加完美的苹果卷心菜汤菜谱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In Riften, she would grow up in an orphanage.  Here, she will have two parents, an Imperial mother, and the support of the village.</Source>
      <Dest>在裂谷城，她会在孤儿院中长大。而在这里，她有两对父母，一个帝国人母亲，和一班村民的支持。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not unless you're going to Valenwood. My husband heard there's a rare mushroom that grows on the trees there.</Source>
      <Dest>不然除非你打算去威木省。我丈夫曾听说那里树上生长着一种罕见的磨菇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If she ever asks me what he was like, I'd just tell her to look in the mirror.</Source>
      <Dest>当女儿问起我爸爸是甚么样子，我都说，你看着镜子就会明白的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Divines blessed us by bringing us here.  In Bruma, my daughter would have grown up without a father.   </Source>
      <Dest>圣灵庇佑了我们，指点我们来到这儿。在冬至城，我的女儿会在没有父亲的情况下成长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't worry, if the disease was the kind that spread, I couldn't hold my child, or be out here talking to you.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，如果这病是那种会传染给人的，我也不能抱着我的孩子，或是走出家门外在这里跟你谈话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When the White Gold Concordant was signed, he defected from the Legion to join the Redguard forces as they pushed the Elves back to Summerset Isle.</Source>
      <Dest>当白金协定签订后，他脱离了军团，转而投效红卫人，帮他们把精灵赶回夏暮岛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She wouldn't have to wonder how much I loved her. Yet when I talk her to now, all my words float by her like...like dandelion clocks in the wind. </Source>
      <Dest>她不会质疑我有多爱她。至今每当我和她谈话时, 我的词藻自然浮现就像...像蒲公英在风中飘扬。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What did he think would happen to Henrietta if he never came back?  If not for the guidance of the Divines, I shudder to think of the consequences.</Source>
      <Dest>他有没想过若不回来，亨丽埃塔会怎样啊？倘若没有圣灵们的庇佑，光是想像后果我就吓得发抖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say it's as colorful as a flower, rose pink with a head shaped like a chalice.</Source>
      <Dest>人们说它多彩如繁花，缀着玫瑰的粉嫩，菌伞形如一只圣餐杯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I couldn't look at the desert sands without thinking about the war, and I couldn't think about the war without thinking about that girl.</Source>
      <Dest>我无法直视荒漠的沙而不想起那残酷的战争，当想起那残酷战争时，我也无法不去想那个姑娘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As a base agent, it could make a potion strong enough to cure any disease. </Source>
      <Dest>它是一种药剂的主要药材，那种强效药剂不管什么病都能治好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An alchemist told him about a magical plant that grows only in the damp forests of Valenwood.  </Source>
      <Dest>一个炼金药剂师告诉我们一种生长在威木省沼泽森林里具有神奇魔力的植物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But Mara forgive me, I still loved him.  That was the problem.  But I also knew I couldn't bear to stay in Hammerfell any longer.  </Source>
      <Dest>愿玛拉宽恕我，我当时仍深爱着他。这很让我困扰，我知道自己无法继续待在落锤省。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's alright.  You've already done so much.</Source>
      <Dest>没关系。你已经做了很多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He said it meant nothing, but it changed everything.  He betrayed my trust and the vow he made before Mara.  </Source>
      <Dest>他说他们之间只是友谊。但那超出了纯友谊关系。他背叛了我的信任，背叛了我们曾在玛拉面前许下的诺言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I just want to be part of her life, even when I'm gone.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是想成为她生命中的一部份，即使我死后也是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And in the meantime I had Henrietta.</Source>
      <Dest>也是这时候我生下了亨丽埃塔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I feared Henrietta wouldn't be able to find my headstone.</Source>
      <Dest>我怕亨丽埃塔会找不到我的墓碑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's by the grace of the Divines that I'm granted this small measure of happiness.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵们恩典予我这微薄的小幸福。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But when we got here, I was relieved.  The graveyard is so cozy, and the priest is a kind man.</Source>
      <Dest>但当我来到这里时，我松了一口气。墓园非常舒适，而且祭司是个慈祥的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've prayed standing, kneeling, and prostrating, to any Divine that would hear me.</Source>
      <Dest>我站着祈祷，跪着祈祷，甚至伏地而拜，我拜着任何一位肯听我诉说的圣灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If only it were so.  I'd heard that Danica Pure-Spring is the most powerful healer in all of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>但愿如此。我听说丹妮卡·纯洁之春是整个天际省最厉害的治疗师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes prayers aren't enough.  Some things are just meant to be.  I thank Arkay for bringing us to Falkreath, and restoring my faith.</Source>
      <Dest>有时光是祈祷不够。有些事情冥冥中自有定数。我感激阿尔凯带领我们来到佛克瑞斯，让我重拾信念。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So we moved back to Cyrodiil, to Bruma, a place without sands or oceans.  </Source>
      <Dest>于是我们迁回赛瑞迪尔，然后搬到冬至城，一个没有沙没有海的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Henrietta dear, I don't want you talking to the High Elf lady.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的亨丽埃塔，我不想让你同高精灵小姐聊天。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's kind of you, but there isn't a spell in the school of restoration that's been able to cure me of my affliction.</Source>
      <Dest>你人真好，但没有任何的治疗法术有办法治愈那折磨我的苦难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was quite fortuitous. The Riften Orphanage is a terrible place.</Source>
      <Dest>这真的是意外，裂谷城孤儿院那个地方真是糟透了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Glad to help.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴能帮到你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Glad to help.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴能帮到你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Glad to help.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴能帮到你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The complaining part.</Source>
      <Dest>抱怨的那部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you feeling?</Source>
      <Dest>感觉如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you feeling?</Source>
      <Dest>感觉如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you feeling?</Source>
      <Dest>感觉如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you feeling?</Source>
      <Dest>感觉如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you feeling?</Source>
      <Dest>感觉如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you feeling?</Source>
      <Dest>感觉如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could write her a letter.  To her future self.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以写封信，写给长大后的她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you alright?</Source>
      <Dest>你没事吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You sound ready.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来你已经准备好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You sound ready.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来你已经准备好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You sound ready.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来你已经准备好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Divines often work in ways beyond our comprehension. But they are working.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵帮助我们的方式是我们无法理解的。但他们确实有在提供协助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Divines often work in ways beyond our comprehension. But they are working.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵帮助我们的方式是我们无法理解的。但他们确实有在提供协助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it the young girl always with you is your daughter?</Source>
      <Dest>我想那个一直跟在你旁边的小女孩是你女儿吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it the young girl always with you is your daughter?</Source>
      <Dest>我想那个一直跟在你旁边的小女孩是你女儿吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did that renew your faith?</Source>
      <Dest>那是如何让你重拾信心的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did that renew your faith?</Source>
      <Dest>那是如何让你重拾信心的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The mountains to south are filled with Ogres.  No place for a small child.</Source>
      <Dest>山的南半部都被食人魔占领了。没地方可以让小孩去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He left you. Wives are like swords, tossed away at the first sign of rust.</Source>
      <Dest>他弃你而去了。妻子就像剑，出现锈迹的第一时间就会被扔掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are the bad days like?</Source>
      <Dest>最糟的时候是怎样的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are the bad days like?</Source>
      <Dest>最糟的时候是怎样的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are the bad days like?</Source>
      <Dest>最最糟的时候是怎样的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are the bad days like?</Source>
      <Dest>最糟的时候是怎样的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You doubted the existence of the Divines?</Source>
      <Dest>你质疑过圣灵的存在吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You doubted the existence of the Divines?</Source>
      <Dest>你质疑过圣灵的存在吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You doubted the existence of the Divines?</Source>
      <Dest>你质疑过圣灵的存在吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You doubted the existence of the Divines?</Source>
      <Dest>你质疑过圣灵的存在吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like you've given up.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来你好像已经放弃了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like you've given up.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来你好像已经放弃了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like you've given up.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来你好像已经放弃了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not a problem.</Source>
      <Dest>没问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is why religion is dumb. How are you blessed?</Source>
      <Dest>信仰根本就没有用。你又是如何被圣灵救赎了的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is why religion is dumb. How are you blessed?</Source>
      <Dest>信仰根本就没有用。你又是如何被圣灵救赎了的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tired.  I asked Bolund if he could build a bench by the cemetary, but he wouldn't even talk to me.</Source>
      <Dest>很累。我问过布伦德可不可以在墓地附近加张长凳，但他甚至连话也不跟我谈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's funny how the same hardship that makes us pray to the Divines also makes us doubt them.</Source>
      <Dest>吊诡的是，遭逢困境让我们对圣灵们祈祷，却也让我们怀疑圣灵们的安排。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I was sure Henrietta was fast asleep, I'd crawl out into the forest and just let it all out. </Source>
      <Dest>当我确定亨丽埃塔很快入睡后，我逃进了森林并远离了那一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How can that be a coincidence? How is that not the work of the Divines?</Source>
      <Dest>这怎么会是巧合呢？这难道不是经圣灵们之手而产生的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I'm sure it's still nothing compared to an arrow in the thigh or losing a limb.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，我很确定跟膝盖中箭或瘸了只腿相比，这没啥大不了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now my heart is filled with more trivial concerns, and I often forget how lucky I am to have them.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我都只顾些鸡毛蒜皮的问题，而忘记我是有多么的幸运。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thankfully, his brother Solaf was kind enough to do it.</Source>
      <Dest>值得庆幸的是，他兄弟索拉夫就仁慈多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not at all.  I took my daughter and journeyed to Skyrim in hopes of finding a cure.  Yet not even a priestess of Kynareth can heal what ails me.  </Source>
      <Dest>不尽如此。我带着我的女儿怀着能找到解药的希望，长途跋涉来到天际省。但即使是凯娜瑞斯的女祭司也对我的病束手无策。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Better.  Zaria gave me a potion that eased some of the pain.  Added a little pick me up too, but don't tell Henrietta.</Source>
      <Dest>好点了。萨莉亚给了我一瓶药水来减轻些痛楚，让我打起精神了，但不要告诉给亨丽埃塔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello...(coughs)...Oh, don't worry, I'm not contagious.  (coughs)</Source>
      <Dest>你好啊……咳，咳咳……哦，别担心，咳咳……我这病……咳……是不会传染的。咳咳咳咳……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you alright?</Source>
      <Dest>你还好吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here I was lamenting my own predicament, yet my daughter is still alive.  </Source>
      <Dest>这时，我为自己的处境而悲伤，但我的女儿还活着。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Henrietta.   My baby girl.  Bright, talented, and just enough of her father's courage to be brave without being fearless.</Source>
      <Dest>亨丽埃塔，我的宝贝女孩。开朗聪颖，而且就像她父亲一样勇敢却不莽勇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm afraid now that we've come to Falkreath, I won't live much longer.  </Source>
      <Dest>我既然已经来到佛克瑞斯，怕是命不久矣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You take care.</Source>
      <Dest>请多加小心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Coughs) Oh, I'm sorry.  How can I help you?</Source>
      <Dest>（咳嗽）哦，我很抱歉。我能帮你吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I talked to Indara, I found out the girl they lost was about Henrietta's age. An Imperial girl like her mother.</Source>
      <Dest>当我跟英达菈谈过后，我发现那个走丢的女孩儿，跟亨丽埃塔—— 一个和走丢女孩儿母亲很像的帝国姑娘——差不多大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think Runil has a quill and paper he keeps for his journal.  I'm going to get started right away.</Source>
      <Dest>我想鲁尼尔为了写他的日记总会有笔和纸吧，我马上就开始了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're wrong. I believe this story will have a happy ending.</Source>
      <Dest>你错了。我相信事情会有圆满的结局。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know, it was stupid.   But I couldn't bear the thought of being apart.  Her and the Divnes are the reason I managed to stay alive this long.  </Source>
      <Dest>我明白，这话很不理智。但我没办法承受要跟女儿别离。她与圣灵们是我还能苟延残喘的动力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can only thank the Divines for guiding us this far, and showing me my faith was not in vain.</Source>
      <Dest>我能做的只有感谢圣灵们带领我们走到这么远，证明我的信念不是徒劳。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Coughing)</Source>
      <Dest>(咳)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Coughing)</Source>
      <Dest>(咳)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Coughing)</Source>
      <Dest>(咳)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She complains a lot too, but I forgive her.  </Source>
      <Dest>她也很爱抱怨，但我原谅她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Valga's a nice woman, but her constant gossiping is a bad influence on Henrietta.</Source>
      <Dest>瓦尔加是个不错的女人，但她不停嘴的八卦会教坏亨丽埃塔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thought she would end up lost and alone, a child few people noticed and nobody wanted.</Source>
      <Dest>我以为她会死在迷惘和孤独中，她是个不怎么被人重视和需要的孩子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not a chance. At least, not this time.  My husband had his frailties, but he was young then, and I was strong.  And he would never abandon Henrietta.</Source>
      <Dest>不可能，就算是，也不能会是现在。我丈夫有他的弱点，也曾年少轻狂过，而我当时也很坚强。他绝不会离弃亨丽埃塔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May the Gods be with you.</Source>
      <Dest>愿众神与你同在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am.  I was afraid to die before, not knowing what would become of my daughter.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我怕我去世之后，我女儿的命运就会如枯叶一般漂浮不定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can feel my bones whittling away, as if the slightest touch could turn them to ash.</Source>
      <Dest>我感觉的到骨头正支离碎裂着，彷彿轻轻一碰就会散成灰烬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>On bad days it hurts to be alive.  The air feels like solid ice, and even the light from a candle will burn your eyes.  </Source>
      <Dest>严重的时候，连活着都是种痛。呼吸像是吸进冰山，就连烛光也像火一般的灼着双眼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the Divines, why didn't I think of that!  That's a wonderful idea! </Source>
      <Dest>众灵在上，为什么我没想到！这真是个妙极了的点子！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think I've earned the right.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为我有权抱怨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's an important lesson. One I didn't always heed.</Source>
      <Dest>这能学到很重要的一课。我以前总是没静下心留意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, then I believe it's not just Arkay's hand, but Mara too who blesses me and my daughter.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，那我相信这不仅是阿尔凯的安排，玛拉也庇祐着我和我的女儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wanted to blame them, curse them, but in the end...all I could do was weep.</Source>
      <Dest>我想去责骂他们，诅咒他们，但是到最后...我能做的就只有流泪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you could look in on her from time to time, make sure everything's alright, I'd appreciate it.</Source>
      <Dest>但如果你可以顺路探访一下她，确定一切是否正常，我会对此很感激。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not a problem.</Source>
      <Dest>没问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Truly, the divines must have sent you to answer my prayers.  Thank you again, so much.</Source>
      <Dest>真的，一定是圣灵派你来回应我的祈祷的。再次感谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I suppose it's fine as long as Henrietta knows which one is Mommy.  I'd hate for some old Nord Jarl to have to listen to her problems.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，我想只要亨丽埃塔知道谁才是她的母亲就好了，我讨厌一些老诺德贵族去听她的问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But knowing my pain isn't the worst this world has to offer, well, let's say that doesn't provide any comfort.  Not when my daughter is so young.</Source>
      <Dest>但我知道我的疼痛不是世上最沉重的担子，这么说吧，死亡对我来说不是慰藉。我的女儿还这么年幼。</Dest>
    </String>
	    <String List="2">
      <Source>Worried.  I talked to Kust the other day, and he said my burial spot was different from the one Runil showed me.</Source>
      <Dest>很着急。某天我与卡斯特聊了一下，关于我的埋葬地点，他所告诉我的与鲁尼尔当时指给我的并不是同一处。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
