<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey Hadring, tell your tavern wench to fetch some more ale.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，哈德灵，让你酒馆儿的小丫头去取些啤酒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like what?  A dress?  Yeah, that's right, you wood-hugger, I can see your jokes coming from an ocean away.</Source>
      <Dest>Like what?  A dress?  Yeah, that's right, you wood-hugger, I can see your jokes coming from an ocean away.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sad thing is, a dress would look better on me than on that troll carcass you call a body.</Source>
      <Dest>悲哀的是，一件衣服穿在我身上明显要比穿在你称为“身体”的巨魔遗骸上更好看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A flagon of mead, wench. On my table. Now.</Source>
      <Dest>姑娘，一壶蜂蜜酒。放到我桌上来，麻利点儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I want a beer. Do you have any beer? If not, then get me the usual.</Source>
      <Dest>我想喝啤酒。你这儿有啤酒的吗？没有的话，还是按老样子来吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And then what, sell the ale to horkers?  You're out of your mind, Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>然后要干嘛，把麦芽酒卖给海象吗？你脑子出问题了吗，蠢精灵？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Have you seen Fultheim's sword?  It's one of them Akaviri things.  You don't think...</Source>
      <Dest>看到弗瑟姆的剑了吗？这他们那帮人里阿卡维尔的东西。你不感觉...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My ribs hurt so bad they had to carry me here to Nightgate Inn.  All the while this Legionnaire has a grin on his face like an open wound.</Source>
      <Dest>我的肋骨伤得很重，于是他们只好把我抬到了夜扉旅店。从始至终那个军团军官都在笑，好像一道伤口挂在他脸上一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not a week later and there isn't a bard in Skyrim who isn't telling the tale of Moris the Draugr and the bear who pitied him.</Source>
      <Dest>在不到一周之后，就没有任何吟游诗人再提起尸鬼和熊关爱莫里斯的传奇了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That explains things.</Source>
      <Dest>这就让一切说得通了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My ribs hurt so bad they had to carry me here to Nightgate Inn.  All the while this Legionnaire has a grin on his face like an open wound.</Source>
      <Dest>我的肋骨伤得很重，于是他们只好把我抬到了夜扉旅店。从始至终那个军团军官都在笑，好像一道伤口挂在他脸上一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That explains things.</Source>
      <Dest>这就让一切说得通了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not a week later and there isn't a bard in Skyrim who isn't telling the tale of Moris the Draugr and the bear who pitied him.</Source>
      <Dest>在不到一周之后，就没有任何吟游诗人再提起尸鬼和熊关爱莫里斯的传奇了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Uh-oh. Those things are relentless.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯喔。这事情发生的真可怕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Uh-oh is right.  Instead of trying to show me up, this Legionnaire coward gives way, forcing me to take the lead.  </Source>
      <Dest>嗯啊，对啦。这位胆小的军团将官没试着在我面前炫耀，反倒把机会让给我，逼我带头处理它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Uh-oh. Those things are relentless.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯喔。这事情发生的真可怕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I swear this bear came at me like I killed its sister, and I couldn't even lift Ebony over my head.  The weight and the pain dropped me to ground.</Source>
      <Dest>我发誓那熊冲着我来，彷佛我宰了它老妹一样。而我连把埃博妮挥过头顶的力气都没。迎面的重量与疼痛把我扑倒在地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Uh-oh. Those things are relentless.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯喔。这事情发生的真可怕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now I ain't no lily-liver, but sometimes a man has to swallow his pride and ask for help.  If only I asked.  Instead I look backed and screamed.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是什么胆小鬼，但有时候男人应该要吞下自尊请求帮助。但愿我当时有开口问。可我却只是回头尖叫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Uh-oh. Those things are relentless.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯喔。这事情发生的真可怕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Funny thing is, the officer, even the recruits, they were all laughing. I was so hysterical I didn't even notice the stupid bear was licking my face.</Source>
      <Dest>有趣的事情发生了。那个军官，甚至是那些新兵全都笑成一团。我当时太歇斯底里而没发现那只愚蠢的熊正舔着我的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No thanks, I'm trying to cut down.</Source>
      <Dest>不，谢了。小心我把你那里剪了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha, that's a good one. You're alright stranger. Sit down, have a drink. On second thought, you better not.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)哈，你的笑话真有趣呢。没关系，陌生人。坐下，喝点什么吧。仔细想想呢，你最好还是别喝了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No thanks, I'm trying to cut down.</Source>
      <Dest>不，谢了。小心我把你那里剪了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hadring's swill isn't all that different going in as it is coming out, if you get my meaning.</Source>
      <Dest>哈德灵的馊水吃进去跟拉出来时都差不多啦，如果你懂我的意思的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why didn't you just tell him you were injured?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么不告诉他你受伤了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A warrior doesn't go advertising his injuries.  Let's the bad guys know where to stick it.</Source>
      <Dest>战士不会张扬他的伤处，让坏蛋知道该往哪里捅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>But you were committed to staying with this Nord.</Source>
      <Dest>但是你被安排与这个诺德人呆在一起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I stuck by my old lady. Reckon'd half the time I deserved it, and the other half she needed to let it out just to keep her head straight.</Source>
      <Dest>我被老女士绊住了，我估摸着一半时间是我应该花的，而另一半时间则完全是浪费在等她理清思路上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>But you were committed to staying with this Nord.</Source>
      <Dest>但是你被安排与这个诺德人呆在一起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ain't easy giving up a bow and arrow for a kettle and broom. </Source>
      <Dest>不要轻易为了安逸的生活放弃自己的冒险之魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As opposed to your marriage, which was bitter and loveless.</Source>
      <Dest>与你的婚姻截然相反，这是苦涩而无情的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I stuck by my old lady. Reckon'd half the time I deserved it, and the other half she needed to let it out just to keep her head straight.</Source>
      <Dest>我被老女士绊住了，我估摸着一半时间是我应该花的，而另一半时间则完全是浪费在等她理清思路上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As opposed to your marriage, which was bitter and loveless.</Source>
      <Dest>与你的婚姻截然相反，这是苦涩而无情的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ain't easy giving up a bow and arrow for a kettle and broom. </Source>
      <Dest>不要轻易为了安逸的生活放弃自己的冒险之魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And you lived unhappily ever after?</Source>
      <Dest>然后你从此过着不幸的生活？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not quite. The old lady got on me, like any big Nord cow, but it wasn't all scars and prison bars. Not like some of these fur huggers make it seem.</Source>
      <Dest>不尽然。虽然黄脸婆像只硕大的诺德奶牛一般扑上我，但生活不是只有抓痕与牢笼。不像那些真正批着毛皮的东西给人看起来的感觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And you lived unhappily ever after?</Source>
      <Dest>然后你从此过着不幸的生活？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know about you, but I find a lot of these Talos lovers like to boast about the strength of their women as much as the power of their god.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然我不了解你，但我发现许多塔洛斯的信徒喜欢吹嘘自家女人跟他们的神明一样强。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And you lived unhappily ever after?</Source>
      <Dest>然后你从此过着不幸的生活？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then first chance they get, they go out and marry some Breton girl they can fit in their palm.</Source>
      <Dest>而他们一有机会，就跑去娶手掌能合他们大小的布莱顿姑娘为妻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Look on the bright side. You still have Ebony.</Source>
      <Dest>往好处想。至少你还有玄曜石。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I reckon I'll be the one to leave her first. Just as well. I can't bear the thought of some filthy grave robber putting his hands on her waist.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我在想若没发生这些事，也许先离开她的人是我。光是想像那些肮脏的盗墓贼用手碰她的腰我就无法忍受。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Look on the bright side. You still have Ebony.</Source>
      <Dest>往好处想。至少你还有玄曜石。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Enough of this somber talk. It's a big world, and there are still plenty of ladies to bed and caves to raid.</Source>
      <Dest>说够了这些郁闷的话了。世界很大呢，还有好几打的女人等着睡，好几打的洞穴要去闯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I crawled back to Windhelm. Lay in bed at Candlehearth Hall for two straight days. Couldn't even breathe without pain.  </Source>
      <Dest>我爬回风舵城，在烛心堂的床上疼入心扉地躺了整整两天。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I get this message from an urchin.  Said Orthus Endario wanted to see me about a job.  I told him to go screw.</Source>
      <Dest>之后有个小鬼给我这封信。说奥休斯有件委托要和我谈谈。我跟他说：“玩蛋去”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then the next day Orthus himself graces me with his presence.  I tell him again to go screw.  Said I'm too tired to be running his errands.</Source>
      <Dest>第二天奥休斯就亲自来找我。我让他滚蛋。我再也没力气给他卖命了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something must have given people reason to doubt you.</Source>
      <Dest>一定有什么事情让人们有理由怀疑你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not something, someone.</Source>
      <Dest>不是什么东西，是个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something must have given people reason to doubt you.</Source>
      <Dest>一定有什么事情让人们有理由怀疑你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It all started when I was exploring the Forsaken Cave in Eastmarch. I was being chased by Draugr and like a dumb mule I stepped on a pressure plate.</Source>
      <Dest>一切要从我在东陲的遗忘洞穴探险时说起。当时我被尸鬼追着屁股，像只莽驴一脚踩进地上的机关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something must have given people reason to doubt you.</Source>
      <Dest>一定有什么事情让人们有理由怀疑你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Next thing I know I'm taking a battering ram to the gut. Shattered just about every rib I own, and other parts I didn't know I had.</Source>
      <Dest>接着我感觉到一阵拳打脚踢朝着我的肚子打来。我每根肋骨都被打碎了，还有一些我不知道的其他地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned your old lady. There's a...Mrs. Draugr?</Source>
      <Dest>你提到了你的老妻子。这是...尸鬼女士？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like I said, used to be. I reckon I wouldn't be here in this Sload belly of an inn if she still was.</Source>
      <Dest>就我刚说的，曾经是。我猜要是她要是还在的话，我大概不会再光顾这像藏在蛤蟆人肚里的旅店。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned your old lady. There's a...Mrs. Draugr?</Source>
      <Dest>你提到了你的老妻子。这是...尸鬼女士？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We met in one of them forts.  I was feeding Ebony a nice plate of bandit breakfast, when I found one of them still in her bedroll.</Source>
      <Dest>我们是在某座堡垒相遇的。当时我喂我家埃博妮吃一盘鲜嫩的土匪肉早餐时，我发现还有个人蜷在床卷里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned your old lady. There's a...Mrs. Draugr?</Source>
      <Dest>你提到了你的老妻子。这是...尸鬼女士？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now I ain't no softy, I'll kill a man in his sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我不再软弱了，我要趁他熟睡时宰了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned your old lady. There's a...Mrs. Draugr?</Source>
      <Dest>你提到了你的老妻子。这是...尸鬼女士？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This one though, she rolls over and looks at me with those big doe eyes just as I was about to take her head.</Source>
      <Dest>可这个呢，转过身来用一双水汪汪的大眼盯着我看，好像我要砍她的脑袋一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned your old lady. There's a...Mrs. Draugr?</Source>
      <Dest>你提到了你的老妻子。这是...尸鬼女士？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I took her maidenhead instead.</Source>
      <Dest>于是我索性夺走了她的处女膜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How about we step outside and I turn you into a real Draugr?</Source>
      <Dest>不如我们到外面去然后我把你变成一只真正的尸鬼？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Go bark at Fultheim, mutt. You ain't worth the time it'll take to clean Ebony.</Source>
      <Dest>去对弗瑟姆吠吧，蠢货。你不值得我浪费清洗埃博妮的时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you and your wife split up?</Source>
      <Dest>你和妻子为什么分开了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In a word, it was her father.</Source>
      <Dest>简单来说，就是她的父亲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Ebony?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是玄曜石？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You blind, or just slow?  Ebony's my sword.  My girl.  She always has my back, and I mean that literally.</Source>
      <Dest>你是瞎子，还是反应迟钝啊？埃博妮是我的配剑。我的小姑娘。她总是在背后守护着我，我是指照字面上的解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What else did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他还做了什么别的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He started hiring mercenaries to accompany me.  Which ain't my thing.  Moris the Living Draugr doesn't work with hired thugs.</Source>
      <Dest>他开始雇佣一些雇佣兵与我同行。事实上不太适合我。尸鬼莫里斯不和那群被雇佣的恶棍们共事。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What else did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他还做了什么别的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not to mention sellswords ain't exactly brimming with honor.  But I didn't have the heart to tell the old man "No."</Source>
      <Dest>更不用说佣兵这职业的确不怎么光彩。但我真的不忍心跟这个老人说：“不。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's an understandable fear.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一个可以理解的恐惧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only now the poor old fool wet his pants if I so much left the house, scared his little girl will go back to being a bandit again.</Source>
      <Dest>只不过现在我要是离开家那老混球就会吓得尿裤子，害怕他的宝贝女儿又跑回去做强盗了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's an understandable fear.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一个可以理解的恐惧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>'Course,that meant I was dragging around two ball and chains instead of one. But one of 'em ain't exactly my type, and the other one's a man.</Source>
      <Dest>'当然，那意味着我正在两人之间摇摆不定。但其中一个不是我所好，而另一个是男人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He was grateful to you.</Source>
      <Dest>他非常感激你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only now the poor old fool wet his pants if I so much left the house, scared his little girl will go back to being a bandit again.</Source>
      <Dest>只不过现在我要是离开家那老混球就会吓得尿裤子，害怕他的宝贝女儿又跑回去做强盗了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He was grateful to you.</Source>
      <Dest>他非常感激你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>'Course,that meant I was dragging around two ball and chains instead of one. But one of 'em ain't exactly my type, and the other one's a man.</Source>
      <Dest>'当然，那意味着我正在两人之间摇摆不定。但其中一个不是我所好，而另一个是男人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it he didn't approve?</Source>
      <Dest>我可以理解成他不打算接受么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know that's how it usually is, but approval was one thing this bootlicker didn't lack.  Nah, if anything, he approved too much.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白这事经常发生，但赞同从不是这些马屁精缺少的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it he didn't approve?</Source>
      <Dest>我可以理解成他不打算接受么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thing is, before I came riding in on my white horse, him and the old lady weren't exactly on speaking terms.  Us tying the knot changed that.</Source>
      <Dest>是这样的，在我骑着白马翩然来到之前，他跟那黄脸婆正在闹冷战。但我们的结合改变了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it he didn't approve?</Source>
      <Dest>我可以理解成他不打算接受么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As far as he was concerned, I was some dashing milk-drinker who came and rescued his princess like in them stories.</Source>
      <Dest>对他而言，我就是他们传说中潇洒倜傥的喝奶者，跑来拯救了他的小公主。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nothing good can ever come from marriage.</Source>
      <Dest>婚姻可一点好处都没有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, I'll drink to that. I should probably thank the bloody sellswords for saving me the trouble.</Source>
      <Dest>对阿，我这就继续喝。也许我该感谢那些嗜血的佣兵帮我省了不少麻烦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nothing good can ever come from marriage.</Source>
      <Dest>婚姻可一点好处都没有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now let's get some more ale, before Fultheim hogs it all to himself.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，在弗瑟姆一个人嗑完全部之前，我们来去喝点麦酒吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait. Isn't Colovia populated with people of Nordic descent?</Source>
      <Dest>等等。不是克罗维亚人溶入诺德血统吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So what.  You saying I can't call a Nord a bloody snow bard because we're family?  Seems like that gives me all the more right.</Source>
      <Dest>那又怎样啊。你是说我不能管一个诺德人叫血腥雪诗人，只因为我们都是一家人？这样我不就更有权力这么叫了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything new at the inn?</Source>
      <Dest>酒馆里有什么新鲜事没？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I never see this Orc everyone keeps muttering on about.  Maybe he opened his trap once too often and got himself killed.  Or worse...he's sober.</Source>
      <Dest>我不断跟哈德灵说，他鼻孔里没有矿石啦，但他还是不停采着矿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything new at the inn?</Source>
      <Dest>酒馆里有什么新鲜事没？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still no comely women, if that's what you're talking about.  I don't know why Fultheim doesn't find some other tavern.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你想说的就是，仍然没有什么标致姑娘啊这句话。那别问我，天晓得为什么弗瑟姆不去别的酒馆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything new at the inn?</Source>
      <Dest>酒馆里有什么新鲜事没？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unless he's one of "those" people.</Source>
      <Dest>至少他是"那些"人中的一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything new at the inn?</Source>
      <Dest>酒馆里有什么新鲜事没？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I keep telling Hadring there ain't no ore in his nose, but that don't stop him from mining it.</Source>
      <Dest>我不断跟哈德灵说，他鼻孔里没有矿石，但他还是不停的挖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything new at the inn?</Source>
      <Dest>酒馆里有什么新鲜事没？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They call the area west of here the White Shore. I call it the place with trees and snow.</Source>
      <Dest>人们称这里西边的地方叫白色海岸，因为它围绕着一片像海的草原向南延伸。我叫它有着树与雪的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything new at the inn?</Source>
      <Dest>酒馆里有什么新鲜事没？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not unless you brought some real ale with you.</Source>
      <Dest>除非你帮我弄点真正的麦酒来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then what happened?</Source>
      <Dest>那么发生了什么事情？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Next day we went to the chapel in Riften and got Mara's blessing.</Source>
      <Dest>隔天我们直奔裂谷城的神庙以获得玛拉的祝福。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then what happened?</Source>
      <Dest>那么发生了什么事情？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The priest asked me if I'd love her "Now and Forever," and I was too much of a coward to run.</Source>
      <Dest>The priest asked me if I'd love her "Now and Forever," and I was too much of a coward to run.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm done with questions.</Source>
      <Dest>我的问题没有了。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>About time.</Source>
      <Dest>是时候了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's Penitus Oculatus, mammoth brain.</Source>
      <Dest>是锐眼鹰，笨蛋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey, my ancestors were Colovian.  We founded the Legion.  It's the Nibenese that made up all these weird titles and rituals.</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，我的祖先可是克罗维亚人哩。我们奠立了军团。就是尼本人创造了这些奇怪的名称与仪式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Interrupt) Are you sure it isn't because of your armor?</Source>
      <Dest>（打断）你确定不是因为你的护甲？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that came after.  I figured if these sodding ice blondies were going to start calling me a Draugr, I might as well look the part.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，那是后来发生的事啦。我猜要是那些该死的冰原金发开始叫我尸鬼的话，我会真的看起来像是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Interrupt) Are you sure it isn't because of your armor?</Source>
      <Dest>（打断）你确定不是因为你的护甲？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now where was I?</Source>
      <Dest>我刚说到哪里了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You haven't met him though?</Source>
      <Dest>你还没见过他？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's a cellar door that leads to the back of the inn. And if he passed through here, I was probably too drunk to notice.</Source>
      <Dest>这里有个地窖门可以直达旅馆的后方。而且如果他真正经过过这里，我可能因为喝醉了而没留意到他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened with the sellswords?</Source>
      <Dest>我不喜欢事情的发展。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source> It didn't take them long to figure out it was easier to kill the man with the gold than take on a nest of angry Draugrs.</Source>
      <Dest>我也不喜欢事情变成这样。他们不用多久就意识到，拿钱杀人比看照一窝愤怒的尸鬼还简单多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened with the sellswords?</Source>
      <Dest>我不喜欢事情的发展。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When we got inside the barrow, I charged on ahead like a dumb beast.</Source>
      <Dest>当我们进入坟塚时，我像只鲁莽的野兽一股脑往前冲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened with the sellswords?</Source>
      <Dest>我不喜欢事情的发展。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wasn't until I was halfway through the dungeon that I realized the yellow bellies had locked the door behind me.</Source>
      <Dest>直到闯了那地宫的一半我才发现，那群胆小鬼把我进来的门锁上了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened with the sellswords?</Source>
      <Dest>我不喜欢事情的发展。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I ain't no good with locks, so it took me all night to get out the back way.  By the time I got home, both the old lady and her father were dead.</Source>
      <Dest>我对开锁不太行，所以原路回来竟花了我一整个晚上。当我一回到家，黄脸婆跟她爸都死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was fast.</Source>
      <Dest>够快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, in truth she probably was no maiden. Finding a real maiden in Skyrim is like finding a chicken that craps diamonds.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，事实上她应该不是处女。在天际省要找一个真正的处女比找一只会生钻石的鸡还难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was fast.</Source>
      <Dest>够快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These Nord women, I tell you, they're hungry as sabrecats, and strong as 'em too. Sometimes they even bite like them, so watch where you stick it.</Source>
      <Dest>这些诺德女人啊，我告诉你，她们饿如剑齿虎，且也壮如剑齿虎。有时这些女人还跟它们一样用嘴咬，奉劝你别插错洞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was fast.</Source>
      <Dest>够快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, in truth she probably was no maiden.  Finding a real maiden in Skyrim is like finding a chicken that craps diamonds.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，事实上她应该不是处女。在天际省要找一个真正的处女比找一只会生钻石的鸡还难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was fast.</Source>
      <Dest>够快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These Nord women, I tell you, they're hungry as sabrecats, and strong as 'em too.   Sometimes they even bite like them.</Source>
      <Dest>这些诺德女人啊，我告诉你，她们饿如剑齿虎，且也壮如剑齿虎。有时这些女人还跟它们一样用嘴咬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's awful.</Source>
      <Dest>真要命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, but it gets worse. I can't even get my revenge on that sellsword trash. I never even bothered to look at their faces. Or get their names.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，但状况更糟了，我甚至无法对那群佣兵杂碎复仇。我从没正脸瞧过他们的长相，或知道他们的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's awful.</Source>
      <Dest>真要命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, it's probably for the best. I hope the fiends live until they're old and gray. There's nothing more pathetic than a warrior who dies in bed.</Source>
      <Dest>Ah, it's probably for the best. I hope the fiends live until they're old and gray. There's nothing more pathetic than a warrior who dies in bed.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you already sampled the goods, there's no need to buy.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你已经达到你的目的，你可以不用负责。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well put. Truth be told the second we get to the temple in Riften, my feet were colder than a necromancer's girlfriend.  </Source>
      <Dest>说的好。当我们一抵达裂谷城的教堂，有人说出了这个事实，那时我的双腿冻得比亡灵术士他女友还冰冷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you already sampled the goods, there's no need to buy.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你已经达到你的目的，你可以不用负责。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was just about to turn my ass around and run straight for Cheydinhal, but then I met the priest.  Real skeptic, that one.</Source>
      <Dest>我正打算拔腿就跑直奔去找香丁赫尔，但不巧刚好撞见了祭司。他啊，疑神疑鬼的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you already sampled the goods, there's no need to buy.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你已经达到你的目的，你可以不用负责。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When he said the line "Now and Forever," I could hear the doubt in his voice.</Source>
      <Dest>当他说出"从现在直到永远"时，我能听出他声音里的动摇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you already sampled the goods, there's no need to buy.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你已经达到你的目的，你可以不用负责。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now me being the stubborn type, I decided to Oblivion with this priest.  So I said the words.  Now and Forever.</Source>
      <Dest>我又是挺顽固的人，我下定决心，反正要下湮灭地狱也要拉着祭司陪，所以我说了"从现在直到永远"。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you already sampled the goods, there's no need to buy.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你已经达到你的目的，你可以不用负责。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I figured, hey, we already had the "Now" part down.  How hard was "forever?"</Source>
      <Dest>我心想，嘿，反正我们"现在"这个目标已经达成了，"永远"会有多难？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were saying they called you "The Living Draugr."</Source>
      <Dest>你刚说他们叫你“活着的尸鬼。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right, on account I ain't dead. Only now I've gotten to that age where they don't bother to make a distinction.</Source>
      <Dest>好啦，跟你说实话我不是死人啦。只不过我到了这把年纪，人们也分不出有啥差别了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were saying they called you "The Living Draugr."</Source>
      <Dest>你刚说他们叫你“活着的尸鬼。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean I get it.  Maybe I can't swing Ebony the way she likes it.</Source>
      <Dest>我说我懂了。也许我无法用埃博妮照她希望的方式来挥舞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were saying they called you "The Living Draugr."</Source>
      <Dest>你刚说他们叫你“活着的尸鬼。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe some days I wake up and my knees burn, or my back starts barking like my old lady used to when I forgot to burn the trash.</Source>
      <Dest>有些人说我比20个男人的剑还有用处。我也这样讲好多年了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were saying they called you "The Living Draugr."</Source>
      <Dest>你刚说他们叫你“活着的尸鬼。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I'm hardly an old man, even for a warrior.</Source>
      <Dest>但作为战士，我可一点都不老呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were saying they called you "The Living Draugr."</Source>
      <Dest>你刚说他们叫你“活着的尸鬼。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some say I'm still worth the swords of twenty men. I've been saying it for years!</Source>
      <Dest>有人说我仍能和20个持剑者匹敌。我已经这么说过好多年啦！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm just saying something could've happened to him. Something sharp and pointy.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是在说一些可能发生在他身上的事情，赤果果血淋淋的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What's that mean, one less Orc in the world?   Excuse me if I don't go to my room and sob to death.</Source>
      <Dest>什么意思？世界上又少了一个兽人？要是我没有跑回我的房间哭死的话请原谅。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm just saying something could've happened to him. Something sharp and pointy.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是在说一些可能发生在他身上的事情，赤果果血淋淋的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sure he's down in the cellar just like Hadring says, or out on the pier. And if he ain't, well, nobody's gonna miss him.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢肯定他就像哈德灵所说的一样，除非在地窖或是码头。不然不会有人想念他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They mock your age, when it represents the level of your strength.</Source>
      <Dest>根据你的强壮程度，他们在估算你的年龄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suspect you're right. None of these bed-wetters would dare mock Moris the Living Draugr to his face.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜你说对了。没有尿床鬼胆敢当面嘲弄活尸鬼莫里斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Nords used to call me Moris the Living Draugr, because of my prowess on the battlefield and the fear I struck in my enemies.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人封我为活尸鬼莫里斯，因为在战场上敌人都被我巧妙的伪装吓的屁滚尿流。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Orthus want?</Source>
      <Dest>奥苏斯想要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Orthus says it's a milk run.  A training exercise for new Legion recruits.  They were escorting a minimum security shipment to Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>奥苏斯说这没甚么危险。只是军团的新兵训练，他们正准备护送最低限度武装的船运去独孤城。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Orthus want?</Source>
      <Dest>奥苏斯想要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All I had to do was show the little cave rats what to look out for.  There'd even be another senior soldier from the...what do you call it?</Source>
      <Dest>我要做的只有提醒那些小穴鼠们该留意些什么。同行还会有另一个老鸟军官，来自那...你们都怎么称呼它来着？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did Orthus want?</Source>
      <Dest>奥苏斯想要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Pennius Ocularium?</Source>
      <Dest>锐眼鹰？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Let him continue)</Source>
      <Dest>(让他继续)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now they just call me Moris the Draugr on account I should be dead.</Source>
      <Dest>现在人们简单地叫我莫里斯尸鬼，这样讲我好像该死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Let him continue)</Source>
      <Dest>(让他继续)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean I get it. Maybe I ain't what you call prime venison.</Source>
      <Dest>也许我称不上是你说的顶级鹿肉，但说我是老芋头还早得很咧，即使是对个战士而言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Let him continue)</Source>
      <Dest>(让他继续)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe some days I wake up and my knees burn, or my back starts barking like my old lady used to when I forgot to burn the trash.</Source>
      <Dest>有些人说我比20个男人的剑还有用处。我也这样讲好多年了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Let him continue)</Source>
      <Dest>(让他继续)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I'm hardly an old man, even for a warrior.</Source>
      <Dest>但作为战士，我可一点都不老呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Let him continue)</Source>
      <Dest>(让他继续)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some say I'm still worth the swords of twenty men.  I've been saying it for years. </Source>
      <Dest>有人说我仍能跟20个人的刀剑相匹敌。我已经说这件事很多年了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He tried to put me in my place, said stuff that'd make the Daedra cover their ears.  But I can give it as good as I can take it.</Source>
      <Dest>他想挫挫我的锐气，他说的话蠢得让魔族忍不住捂上耳朵。但我可以做出让步，如同我经受得住它一样。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not that it was hard, what with that stupid Legion skirt he was wearing.</Source>
      <Dest>并不是说回击他很难，尤其是在他还穿着一件愚蠢的军团裙子的情况下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Problem is, my insults worked too well.  See, we were just up the road from here when we got ambushed by a snow bear.</Source>
      <Dest>问题是，我的辱骂声太有效率。你看，我们刚刚从这儿上路，就遭到了雪熊的伏击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I take it you went?</Source>
      <Dest>所以我猜你去了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You bet your sweet roll I did. A man in my position doesn't pass up easy coin, even if it means dealing with Nibenese worms.</Source>
      <Dest>赌上你的甜甜圈，我真的这么做了。换作谁都不会放过这种简单好赚的机会。即便这意味着要跟尼本人的虫子们打交道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I take it you went?</Source>
      <Dest>所以我猜你去了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The trouble was this senior Legion officer took exception to my reputation.  Didn't like that the recruits looked up to an outsider.</Source>
      <Dest>麻烦的是那个军团军官对我的名声很有意见。他不希望其他新兵把外人当成榜样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I take it you went?</Source>
      <Dest>所以我猜你去了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Especially a Colovian Imperial dressed in the armor of a frost-hugger.</Source>
      <Dest>特别是那个穿着寒霜盔甲的克罗维亚帝国人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Close enough.</Source>
      <Dest>好像是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, my ancestors were Colovian. We founded the Empire. It's the Nibenese who made up all these weird names and rituals.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，就是那个尼本人创造了这些奇怪的衔称与仪式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Draugr! A Draugr in the inn!</Source>
      <Dest>尸鬼！有一个尸鬼闯入旅店！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hold on skeever bait. I ain't no Draugr. Not a real one anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>你这只雪鼠别冲动啊。我不是尸鬼啦。不是一只真的就是了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Only the cowardly and the strong grow old. I think we know which one you are.</Source>
      <Dest>只有懦弱的和强大的，我想我们知道你是哪个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Listen you horker's uncle, at some point tonight, I'm going to walk outside, find "The Lover" constellation, and pray a Dremora beds your mother.</Source>
      <Dest>你这只海狮大叔听着，今晚我要找时间在外头转转，找到"恋人"星座，然后祈祷魔人睡了你老母。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Only the cowardly and the strong grow old. I think we know which one you are.</Source>
      <Dest>只有懦弱的和强大的，我想我们知道你是哪个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I'm going to come back and knock your teeth in.  But first I need another drink.</Source>
      <Dest>那我会回来一拳把你的门牙打掉。不过现在我还想再来一杯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not convinced. How about I cut you, and see if you bleed?</Source>
      <Dest>我不想信。不然我砍看看，看看会不会流血？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How about I piss in your flagon and you tell me it's honey?</Source>
      <Dest>How about I piss in your flagon and you tell me it's honey?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could reclaim your name fighting alongside me.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我混，就能让你重振威名！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And live in your shadow? Not a chance.</Source>
      <Dest>然后活在你的阴影下？想得美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, good luck with that then.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，祝你马到成功吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm Moris the Living Draugr. I don't need luck.</Source>
      <Dest>我是活死人莫里斯。我不需要运气。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yeah, about that. This place has undergone a change in management.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，的确那样。这儿在管理上有了一些变化。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So who's running things now? You? Don't make me laugh. You're a fighter, not a barkeep.</Source>
      <Dest>那这儿是谁负责经营的？你？扯蛋。你是个打手，不是掌柜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yeah, about that. This place has undergone a change in management.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，的确那样。这儿在管理上有了一些变化。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll bet this place still has its fair share of crooks. Just need to figure out who to let Ebony taste first. Been a long time since she last ate.</Source>
      <Dest>我打赌这个地方仍然有着那么几个骗子。只需要找出谁先让埃博妮用餐的，自她上次用餐已经有段时间了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, go ahead. Kill all the bandits in here.</Source>
      <Dest>来吧上吧，把这里所有的强盗杀光光！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm about to. I just...didn't expect there to be so many of them.</Source>
      <Dest>我正要开打呢。我只是...没有想到那里强盗那么多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If I knew you were coming, I would have saved you a few thugs.</Source>
      <Dest>要知道你要来，我就留几个歹徒给你玩啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah hell. So you cleaned this place up already? Figures. But I bet there's still some rotten apples in this bunch.</Source>
      <Dest>Ah hell. So you cleaned this place up already? Figures. But I bet there's still some rotten apples in this bunch.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If I knew you were coming, I would have saved you a few thugs.</Source>
      <Dest>要知道你要来，我就留几个歹徒给你玩啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll just bide my time until Ebony tells me she's hungry.</Source>
      <Dest>我刚刚在等待时机，直到埃博妮跟我说她饿了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're too late, and too slow. Just retire already.</Source>
      <Dest>你太晚、太慢了。刚刚已经撤退了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I ain't late for nothing. I'm sure there's still plenty of killers and thieves here. </Source>
      <Dest>我可没有来晚。我敢保证这儿还有蛮多杀手和小偷呢。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're too late, and too slow. Just retire already.</Source>
      <Dest>你太晚、太慢了。刚刚已经撤退了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just have to figure out which ones are which. Don't want Ebony's first meal to be a some skooma addict.</Source>
      <Dest>必须搞明白哪个是哪个，别想让一些斯库玛瘾君子成为埃博妮初餐的主菜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you finally left that inn.</Source>
      <Dest>那最终你离开了那个旅馆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Damn straight. You think I like those people? I was just waiting for my injuries to heal.</Source>
      <Dest>没错！你以为我喜欢这帮人？我只是在这儿等待治疗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you finally left that inn.</Source>
      <Dest>那最终你离开了那个旅馆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I got better, the first thing I did was wring Hadring's neck until all the bounties fell out of his pockets.</Source>
      <Dest>我要是感觉好点了，我肯定要拧着哈德灵的脖子找这个混蛋要钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you finally left that inn.</Source>
      <Dest>那最终你离开了那个旅馆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I had one of the other idiots find me the most expensive and dangerous one. Robber's Refuge.</Source>
      <Dest>我让另一个傻瓜觉得我是个危险而富有的家伙。劫匪庇护所。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hadring says there's an Orc living in the cellar.</Source>
      <Dest>哈德灵说有一个兽人住在这里的地窖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And there's a pine tree living in my trousers, but you don't see me bothering you about it.</Source>
      <Dest>在我的裤子内还有一棵大松树，但我猜你不会想看的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>About time.</Source>
      <Dest>是时候了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>About time.</Source>
      <Dest>是时候了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Make it quick, huh.</Source>
      <Dest>有话快说，哼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Need something?</Source>
      <Dest>有事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Speak up already.</Source>
      <Dest>已经大声说出来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is it now?</Source>
      <Dest>又怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah?</Source>
      <Dest>啊?</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
