<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, Arch-Mage.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会，首席法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was thinking a hamster.</Source>
      <Dest>I was thinking a hamster.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I think I have precisely the right person.  </Source>
      <Dest>Then I think I have precisely the right person.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I teach you some magic. You let me replace your brain with Dwemer gears and wheels powered by rodents.</Source>
      <Dest>我教你些魔法。你让我拿啮齿力量注入的锻莫齿轮机械替换掉你的大脑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, you must be the new assistant I've been asking for! I take it you've agreed to the terms?</Source>
      <Dest>哦，你一定是我一直强烈要求要换的新助理！我想你已经同意的那些条件了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Carve the markings into the wooden coins. Then enchant them with gold.</Source>
      <Dest>把制成品雕刻成木质硬币，然后用它们去交换金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh! That would work, although engraving them would be too difficult. You can't just use an imprint like with metal.</Source>
      <Dest>哦！那样可行， 尽管雕刻他们会很麻烦. 你不能只用一个金属工具。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Carve the markings into the wooden coins. Then enchant them with gold.</Source>
      <Dest>把制成品雕刻成木质硬币，然后用它们去交换金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But...I've heard there are these beetles in Black Marsh, mirror beetles they're called, that learn to chew tough bark by watching their mothers.</Source>
      <Dest>但是...我曾听说这些是黑沼省的甲虫，那里的人叫它镜虫，他们能观察他们的妈妈，从而学到如何咀嚼硬树皮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Carve the markings into the wooden coins. Then enchant them with gold.</Source>
      <Dest>把制成品雕刻成木质硬币，然后用它们去交换金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If we could train these beetles to chew in a pattern that matches a Septim...Oh, it's brilliant!</Source>
      <Dest>要是我们能训练这些甲虫啃出一枚金币上的纹样……哦，真是天才！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I meant like a regular hobby. You know, like killing bandits.</Source>
      <Dest>我是指类似一个周期性习惯。你知道的，就像杀土匪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I sometimes do that too.  Yes, this is an institution of learning, but we are in Skyrim, after all.  And when in Skyrim, do like the Nords.</Source>
      <Dest>哦,我倒也有那么干的时候.  嗯，这倒是一种学习的方法.不过我们毕竟在天际这鬼地方.到头来,我们还是入乡随诺德俗好一点……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I meant like a regular hobby. You know, like killing bandits.</Source>
      <Dest>我是指类似一个周期性习惯。你知道的，就像杀土匪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, using destruction magic would be too dull.  Even the illusion spells get boring.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，毁灭系法术用起来很单调。就算是幻术系用多了也会无聊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I meant like a regular hobby. You know, like killing bandits.</Source>
      <Dest>我是指类似一个周期性习惯。你知道的，就像杀土匪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I did get this idea after casting a Fear spell.  What if there was an illusion spell that made all your movements backwards?</Source>
      <Dest>Although I did get this idea after casting a Fear spell.  What if there was an illusion spell that made all your movements backwards?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I meant like a regular hobby. You know, like killing bandits.</Source>
      <Dest>我是指类似一个周期性习惯。你知道的，就像杀土匪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You try to take a step forward, you take a step back.  You try to look up, you end up looking down.</Source>
      <Dest>你想要奋勇向前，但最后却不进反退。你试图昂首向天，但最后却只会俯首对地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I meant like a regular hobby. You know, like killing bandits.</Source>
      <Dest>我是指类似一个周期性习惯。你知道的，就像杀土匪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the time you get things straightened out, the spell wears off and now your mind is a total ball of yarn.</Source>
      <Dest>慢慢地当你终于理顺的时候，法术的效果消退，你的脑子里也成了一团浆糊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I meant like a regular hobby. You know, like killing bandits.</Source>
      <Dest>我是指类似一个周期性习惯。你知道的，就像杀土匪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I can just figure out how the muscles and the mind are connected, it's a simple matter of using illusion to cross those signals.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我能知道人体的组织肌肉是怎么和心灵是相通的，那么通过幻术来阻止这种信号就会是很简单的事了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Or a Giant riding a flying mammoth, powered by cheese.</Source>
      <Dest>或者一个骑着以奶酪为动力的猛犸的巨人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course!  That had to be it!  It couldn't possibly be anything else!</Source>
      <Dest>那当然！必须是这样！绝对没有别的可能！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Or a Giant riding a flying mammoth, powered by cheese.</Source>
      <Dest>或者一个骑着以奶酪为动力的猛犸的巨人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although...I don't know if it would be powered by cheese.  That part makes no sense.  Carried by moth spiders, more likely.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然……我不知道它是由奶酪驱动的。这部分绝对行不通。用蛾子蜘蛛的可能性还大点儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Or a Giant riding a flying mammoth, powered by cheese.</Source>
      <Dest>或者一个骑着以奶酪为动力的猛犸的巨人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They shoot the mammoths with their webbing and then float off together into the sky.  It takes a thousand, no a million moths to lift it!</Source>
      <Dest>他们用他们的带子射中猛犸象然后一齐飘到了半空中。为了把它举起来用了一千只，不对一百万只月蛾！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That sounds absolutely amazing, but can plants really use magic?</Source>
      <Dest>这听起来太惊人了，但植物真的能使用魔法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course! I bet in places like Valenwood, there are all sorts of carnivorous plants that use magic to capture their prey.</Source>
      <Dest>那当然！我敢打赌在 威木省 那样的地方，到处都是会用魔法捕猎的食肉植物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That sounds absolutely amazing, but can plants really use magic?</Source>
      <Dest>这听起来太惊人了，但植物真的能使用魔法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like a plant with invisible fangs on its fronds, trapping birds and insects who stop to rest their weary wings.</Source>
      <Dest>就像植物在它的叶子上拥有无形之牙，俘获那些停下来歇息它们疲惫的翅膀的鸟类还有昆虫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That sounds absolutely amazing, but can plants really use magic?</Source>
      <Dest>这听起来太惊人了，但植物真的能使用魔法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or how about a talking plant who uses magic to mimic speech?  A stamen is almost like a tongue. Then you get real close, and the fangs chomp you!</Source>
      <Dest>或者一株用魔法模仿演讲的会说话的植物怎么样？花蕊就像舌头，当你靠的足够近时，毒牙就咬过去！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That sounds absolutely amazing, but can plants really use magic?</Source>
      <Dest>这听起来太惊人了，但植物真的能使用魔法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is, if the mud monsters don't get you first.  Plants must have some version of the undead.  Raised from the ground by magical spores and such.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，如果泥怪没先找到你. 魔法的种族会在土地里生长， 植物会变成一些不死怪物.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Plants using magic. Right.</Source>
      <Dest>会使用魔法的植物。好吧。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course! I bet in places like Valenwood, there are all sorts of carnivorous plants that use magic to capture their prey.</Source>
      <Dest>那当然！我敢打赌在 威木省 那样的地方，到处都是会用魔法捕猎的食肉植物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Plants using magic. Right.</Source>
      <Dest>会使用魔法的植物。好吧。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like a plant with invisible fangs on its fronds, trapping birds and insects who stop to rest their weary wings.</Source>
      <Dest>就像植物在它的叶子上拥有无形之牙，俘获那些停下来歇息它们疲惫的翅膀的鸟类还有昆虫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Plants using magic. Right.</Source>
      <Dest>会使用魔法的植物。好吧。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or how about a talking plant who uses magic to mimic speech?  A stamen is almost like a tongue. Then you get real close, and the fangs chomp you!</Source>
      <Dest>或者一株用魔法模仿演讲的会说话的植物怎么样？花蕊就像舌头，当你靠的足够近时，毒牙就咬过去！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Plants using magic. Right.</Source>
      <Dest>会使用魔法的植物。好吧。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is, if the mud monsters don't get you first.  Plants must have some version of the undead.  Raised from the ground by magical spores and such.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，如果泥怪没先找到你. 魔法的种族会在土地里生长， 植物会变成一些不死怪物.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you ever actually witnessed any such strange phenomena?</Source>
      <Dest>实际上你是否见过这种奇怪的现象？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, all the time.  Especially at the College where the magical energy is strong. Floating objects like books, soul gems, and silverware for one.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，一直都是。特别是在学院魔法能量强壮的地方。物体漂浮如书本啊，灵魂宝石啊，有一次甚至是银具。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you ever actually witnessed any such strange phenomena?</Source>
      <Dest>实际上你是否见过这种奇怪的现象？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You really have to watch where you're going or you might run your eye into a fork.</Source>
      <Dest>你真的需要看看自己会去哪里或者会遇到什么样的情况。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you ever actually witnessed any such strange phenomena?</Source>
      <Dest>实际上你是否见过这种奇怪的现象？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then there's the multiplying fruit.  Master Drevis thinks the several hundred apples he found in his pillow was a prank. </Source>
      <Dest>然后是许多的水果。德莱维斯大人认为他在他枕头里发现这几百个苹果发现是一场恶作剧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you ever actually witnessed any such strange phenomena?</Source>
      <Dest>实际上你是否见过这种奇怪的现象？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think it was a rare form of spontaneous cloning.  Clearly some type of plant based magic, like an evolved form of alchemy.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这是种罕见的自发性克隆。它显然是一些植物基于魔法而产生的, 就像一种炼金术的进化形式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not a floating island inhabited by Giants?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么不说一个悬浮的岛上住着巨人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh!  I've heard of that!  Ever been to the Sleeping Tree Camp!  A floating island crashed to the ground there, powered by a magical tree.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，我听说过这个！我也去过沉睡之树营地！一个由魔力之树驱动的浮空的岛屿正坠落于此处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not a floating island inhabited by Giants?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么不说一个悬浮的岛上住着巨人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When it crashed, the tree left its seed in the ground, and its progeny will grow and lift the island into the sky once more.</Source>
      <Dest>在它倒下的时候，这树就把它的种子留在土地里。它的子孙后代便在此繁衍生息，把这个岛再一次举到天空中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not a floating island inhabited by Giants?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么不说一个悬浮的岛上住着巨人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At least, that's what supposed to happen.  It might go underground instead, if the skies are too crowded.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，这大概就是最后的结果。但如果天空中太拥挤的话，那也有可能是往地下发展。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see no harm in it. Proceed.</Source>
      <Dest>我看里面没什么危险,动手吧.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wish Nirya would be more encouraging.  She calls my research nonsense, and goes out of her way to do so.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望尼尔雅会令人振奋。她不用她的方式这样做，也使我的研究无地自容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see no harm in it. Proceed.</Source>
      <Dest>我看里面没什么危险,动手吧.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She said Master Gestor would reject my proposal on conjured ink.  Said only the most talent devoid novice would need to make notes in spell tomes.</Source>
      <Dest>她说盖斯特大师一定会拒绝我关于魔法墨水的提议。她还说只有最有天赋的新人才能在魔法书上圈重点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see no harm in it. Proceed.</Source>
      <Dest>我看里面没什么危险,动手吧.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose an alternative would be to enchant the tomes themselves, so the readers could gain an intelligence boost.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜还有个办法是在那些书卷上面附魔，来让阅读者获得智力提升。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Personally, I think 5 schools are too many. Alteration and Illusion, same thing.</Source>
      <Dest>个人觉得，五个魔法学校太多了。变换和幻术其实是一样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?  They aren't even in the same realm!</Source>
      <Dest>什么？他们根本不在一个次元啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Personally, I think 5 schools are too many. Alteration and Illusion, same thing.</Source>
      <Dest>个人觉得，五个魔法学校太多了。变换和幻术其实是一样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd say Alteration is more like Dwarven magic, because they both transform things into things they aren't, like machines into people.</Source>
      <Dest>要我说的话，变换更像是矮人魔法，因为这两者都将此物变成彼物，比如说把机器变成人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Personally, I think 5 schools are too many. Alteration and Illusion, same thing.</Source>
      <Dest>个人觉得，五个魔法学校太多了。变换和幻术其实是一样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although some think Dwarven spiders are powered by a combination of Alteration and Destruction magic, particularly lightning energy.</Source>
      <Dest>然而有些人认为矮人蜘蛛是由变化系和毁灭系魔法支撑的，尤其是闪电能量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Personally, I think 5 schools are too many. Alteration and Illusion, same thing.</Source>
      <Dest>个人觉得，五个魔法学校太多了。变换和幻术其实是一样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>See, it just gets more and more complicated if you try and limit yourself to 5 schools.  It's obvious Dwarven magic is its own property.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道如果你同时投身于五所不同学校的话，什么事都会越来越复杂的。很显然，矮人的魔法存在于另外的体系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Personally, I think 5 schools are too many. Alteration and Illusion, same thing.</Source>
      <Dest>个人觉得，五个魔法学校太多了。变换和幻术其实是一样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unlike the other schools, my theory is Dwarven magic relies on sound. That's why spiders, spheres, and Centurions are all drawn to your footsteps.</Source>
      <Dest>不同于其他学校所教授的那样，我的理论认为矮人的魔法依赖于声音。所以那些矮人蜘蛛，机械球和百夫长都是循着你的脚步声而来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Personally, I think 5 schools are too many. Alteration and Illusion, same thing.</Source>
      <Dest>个人觉得，五个魔法学校太多了。变换和幻术其实是一样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I bet that's also why Dwarven ruins are so noisy.  It's like they're funneling in air for them to breathe.</Source>
      <Dest>我打赌这也是矮人遗迹如此吵闹的原因。听上去就像整座遗迹都在呼吸一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Could have been a dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>可能曾经有一只龙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, but that is far too ordinary.  Maybe not yesterday, but now, very much so.  Unless it was a water dragon!  A dragon fish whose breath was steam!</Source>
      <Dest>是的，但动静也太小了一点吧。或许那条龙并不是昨天来的，而是马上就要来。除非那是一条水龙！一条会喷蒸汽的龙鱼！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Could have been a dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>可能曾经有一只龙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, it's more fish than dragon, and more bug than fish.  It feasts on wood, and its diet consists solely of mortal-made ships.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，比起龙来它更像鱼，比起鱼来又更像虫子。它喜食木材，以人造船只为食。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You have quite the imagination.</Source>
      <Dest>你的想象力真不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Strange.  Master Drevis and Tolfdir also use that word.  I don't like to think I'm imagining anything.  I like to think it's all undiscovered.</Source>
      <Dest>奇怪，德莱维斯和托夫迪尔两位大师也用那个字眼。我不喜欢思考我正在设想的东西，我喜欢思考完全未知的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Exactly. Why dumb things down for the novices? The more schools, the better.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。为什么要对初学者们有所隐瞒？学校是越多越好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes! For instance, can you imagine being able to take courses here on Nord battlecries?  Metamorphosis?  Hist sap? </Source>
      <Dest>是啊！比方说，你能想象给诺德人开设战斗咆哮课的情景吗？ 或者变形术?  希思特汁树？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Exactly. Why dumb things down for the novices? The more schools, the better.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。为什么要对初学者们有所隐瞒？学校是越多越好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An institution like this should welcome all forms of magical study, as well as the occult.  It's one of my dreams to dissect a werebear.</Source>
      <Dest>像这样的学术机构应该欢迎一切形式的魔法和神秘学研究。能够解剖一头熊人是我们的梦想之一。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Exactly. Why dumb things down for the novices? The more schools, the better.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。为什么要对初学者们有所隐瞒？学校是越多越好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right now I'm studying how Bosmer can manipulate beasts of the wild.  Can you imagine commanding a horde of angry bees?</Source>
      <Dest>现在我正在研究木精灵如何控制野生动物。你能想象掌控一整个愤怒的蜂群的情景吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Exactly. Why dumb things down for the novices? The more schools, the better.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。为什么要对初学者们有所隐瞒？学校是越多越好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could fly them in to Nirya's mouth, and have them grow a hive in her throat.  Then all her words would be honey.</Source>
      <Dest>我打算让蜜蜂都飞进尼尔雅的嘴，让他们在她喉咙里筑窝。那样她说出的话都应该像密一样甜了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Exactly. Why dumb things down for the novices? The more schools, the better.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。为什么要对初学者们有所隐瞒？学校是越多越好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or even better, control the elements.  Why use magicka making an ice spike if you can freeze the rain into shards?</Source>
      <Dest>或者更好的，能够控制元素。如果能冻雨成矛又何必耗费魔法自制冰锥呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Exactly. Why dumb things down for the novices? The more schools, the better.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。为什么要对初学者们有所隐瞒？学校是越多越好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I feel like these things should be addressed.  Promptly.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得这些东西应该被整理一下。立刻马上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What's happening out there?  What's going on?  Is it the thing from Saarthal?  Did they crack it open?  Were there...were there Dwarves inside?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么回事？什么声音啊？是 萨瑟尔城遗迹里面发出的吗？他们把哪里劈开了？里面……里面有矮人吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, there was a great rumble outside this morning, did you feel it?  Surely it must have been a Giant riding a carriage, or a flying ship!</Source>
      <Dest>哦，今天早上外面有很大的隆隆声，你感觉到了吗？那一定是一个巨人驾着一辆马车，或者是飞船！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's a much better defense against thieves than a lock or a bear trap.</Source>
      <Dest>这玩意用来防贼可比锁头或者捕熊夹强多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yes. Which gives me another idea.  Hanging bear traps!  Would work much better than bone chimes.  You'd need an invisibility spell to cloak them.</Source>
      <Dest>哦是的。这让我想到了另一个主意。[用那些捕熊的陷阱]！如果与骨制编钟配合的话效果更佳。你只需要一个隐形法术来让它们“消失”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's a much better defense against thieves than a lock or a bear trap.</Source>
      <Dest>这玩意用来防贼可比锁头或者捕熊夹强多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The problem is the weight.  Spells are transient, and the Steed Stone won't work on a thread.  Frosbite spider webbing maybe</Source>
      <Dest>最大的问题是负重，咒语效果难以长久，战马之石不能即刻生效。 没准霜啮蜘蛛的网会有用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's a much better defense against thieves than a lock or a bear trap.</Source>
      <Dest>这玩意用来防贼可比锁头或者捕熊夹强多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Probably too difficult to harvest...hm...What if we abandoned using gossamer altogether, but instead gave the traps wings?</Source>
      <Dest>这很难有效……嗯……如果我们不用整个网，而是用一小块陷阱代替呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's a much better defense against thieves than a lock or a bear trap.</Source>
      <Dest>这玩意用来防贼可比锁头或者捕熊夹强多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is Arniel still around?  He's the expert on Dwarven magic.</Source>
      <Dest>阿内尔还在附近吗？他很擅长矮人们的法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Kill a coin purse? Are you sure you these theories won't get you hanged?</Source>
      <Dest>杀死一只钱包？你确定这些理论不会误你的事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yes. Which gives me another idea.  Hanging bear traps!  Would work much better than bone chimes.  You'd need an invisibility spell to cloak them.</Source>
      <Dest>哦是的。这让我想到了另一个主意。[用那些捕熊的陷阱]！如果与骨制编钟配合的话效果更佳。你只需要一个隐形法术来让它们“消失”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Kill a coin purse? Are you sure you these theories won't get you hanged?</Source>
      <Dest>杀死一只钱包？你确定这些理论不会误你的事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The problem is the weight.  Spells are transient, and the Steed Stone won't work on a thread.  Frostbite spider webbing maybe...</Source>
      <Dest>但问题在于重量。魔法持续时间很短暂，而驮马之石不可能作用于一根细绳。或许霜噬蜘蛛的丝可以做到...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Kill a coin purse? Are you sure you these theories won't get you hanged?</Source>
      <Dest>杀死一只钱包？你确定这些理论不会误你的事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Probably too difficult to harvest...hm...What if we abandoned using gossamer altogether, but instead gave the traps wings?</Source>
      <Dest>这很难有效……嗯……如果我们不用整个网，而是用一小块陷阱代替呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Kill a coin purse? Are you sure you these theories won't get you hanged?</Source>
      <Dest>杀死一只钱包？你确定这些理论不会误你的事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is Arniel still around?  He's the expert on Dwarven magic.</Source>
      <Dest>阿内尔还在附近吗？他很擅长矮人们的法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Soul traps trigger when the shell is killed.  How do you kill a coin?</Source>
      <Dest>当躯体被杀死，灵魂陷阱就会触发。你要怎么杀死一枚硬币呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't kill the coin, but the purse, and that's already dead. The coins inside are what mimic the properties of a soul.</Source>
      <Dest>You don't kill the coin, but the purse, and that's already dead. The coins inside are what mimic the properties of a soul.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Soul traps trigger when the shell is killed.  How do you kill a coin?</Source>
      <Dest>当躯体被杀死，灵魂陷阱就会触发。你要怎么杀死一枚硬币呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As long as the harmonic resonance is stable while they take flight, the trap will secure the coins into a soul gem.</Source>
      <Dest>只要和声的共鸣在灵魂妄图逃走的时候依旧稳定，陷阱就能稳稳当当的把“金币”塞进灵魂石里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Soul traps trigger when the shell is killed.  How do you kill a coin?</Source>
      <Dest>当躯体被杀死，灵魂陷阱就会触发。你要怎么杀死一枚硬币呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The trapping part's all rather elementary once you get the hang of it.</Source>
      <Dest>一旦你掌握的轻松自如就发现在设置陷阱部分是相当基础的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't feel anything.</Source>
      <Dest>我什么也感觉不到了。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must have been deep asleep.  It's possible the luna moth fairies sprinkled their slumber-dust on you.</Source>
      <Dest>你一定是睡着了，有可能仙女蛾的睡梦粉尘洒落到你身上了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't feel anything.</Source>
      <Dest>我什么也感觉不到了。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I heard an old Nord once slept for a 1000 years in a patch of tundra cotton after inhaling a cloud of the stuff.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说有个诺德人曾因为吸了它一口就在一片棉花上睡了1000年。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have any other interests besides magic?</Source>
      <Dest>除了魔法你还对什么感兴趣？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, plenty!  Although they all sort of relate to magic in one way or another.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，多的是呢！虽然他们都或多或少和魔法有点关系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have any other interests besides magic?</Source>
      <Dest>除了魔法你还对什么感兴趣？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For instance, I was trying to build a more secure coin purse, by trapping your gold inside a soul gem.</Source>
      <Dest>For instance, I was trying to build a more secure coin purse, by trapping your gold inside a soul gem.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have any other interests besides magic?</Source>
      <Dest>除了魔法你还对什么感兴趣？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was a bit tricky getting the conjuration trap to recognize inanimate objects as souls, but a dash of blood and harmonizing the resonance did it.</Source>
      <Dest>让魔法陷阱能识别出像灵魂那样的无生命的物体有点儿难，但丁一点儿血或是协调共振就能很轻易的被陷阱识别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have any other interests besides magic?</Source>
      <Dest>除了魔法你还对什么感兴趣？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The problem was getting the gold out.  I tried enchanting a couple of wooden coins using the gem, but they lost the Imperial markings.</Source>
      <Dest>The problem was getting the gold out.  I tried enchanting a couple of wooden coins using the gem, but they lost the Imperial markings.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like you've been drinking that Sleeping Tree Sap the lunatics rave about.</Source>
      <Dest>看来你已经喝了那个能让疯子赞不绝口的沉睡之树的液汁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I would never try anything like that!  Won't even drink a bottle of ale.  I need my mind absolutely clear so I know what I see is real.</Source>
      <Dest>Oh, I would never try anything like that!  Won't even drink a bottle of ale.  I need my mind absolutely clear so I know what I see is real.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Intriguing. Tell me more about this "repulsion" system.</Source>
      <Dest>有意思，多讲讲这个“排斥”系统的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It works like this.  Imagine smearing a bit of ground Draugr paste on a table.  Then, place a dinner plate above it, enchanted to repel the undead.</Source>
      <Dest>It works like this.  Imagine smearing a bit of ground Draugr paste on a table.  Then, place a dinner plate above it, enchanted to repel the undead.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Intriguing. Tell me more about this "repulsion" system.</Source>
      <Dest>有意思，多讲讲这个“排斥”系统的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The floating hall would work on the same principle.  Although I'm not sure how they would get down.</Source>
      <Dest>这和浮动大厅的工作原理应该是一样的。虽然我不知道他们怎么下来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh boy, here we go again...</Source>
      <Dest>哦天哪，我们再去一次……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh boy, here we go again...</Source>
      <Dest>哦天哪，我们再去一次……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It works like this.  Imagine smearing a bit of ground Draugr paste on a table.  Then, place a dinner plate above it, enchanted to repel the undead.</Source>
      <Dest>It works like this.  Imagine smearing a bit of ground Draugr paste on a table.  Then, place a dinner plate above it, enchanted to repel the undead.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh boy, here we go again...</Source>
      <Dest>哦天哪，我们再去一次……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh boy, here we go again...</Source>
      <Dest>哦天哪，我们再去一次……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The floating hall would work on the same principle.  Although I'm not sure how they would get down.</Source>
      <Dest>这和浮动大厅的工作原理应该是一样的。虽然我不知道他们怎么下来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting.  Any other experiments you're working on?</Source>
      <Dest>有意思。你还在搞哪些方面的实验？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yes. Telekinesis interests me greatly.  If we could just reduce the magicka cost by concentrating the propulsion energy, it could replace bows.</Source>
      <Dest>Oh yes. Telekinesis interests me greatly.  If we could just reduce the magicka cost by concentrating the propulsion energy, it could replace bows.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting.  Any other experiments you're working on?</Source>
      <Dest>有意思。你还在搞哪些方面的实验？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can just keep a pouch of bear claws in your pocket, and fire them at your enemies.  Very effective against mages with strong wards.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以把一捆熊爪放在你的口袋里，然后冲着你的敌人点燃它们。这样干的话，对抗拥有强力结界的法师非常有效果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting.  Any other experiments you're working on?</Source>
      <Dest>有意思。你还在搞哪些方面的实验？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The same principle applies to my other project, the floating hall.  A hall without a floor, or a ceiling.  Everything just floats.</Source>
      <Dest>这我另一个项目漂浮大厅是一个原理。  大厅里没有地板，没有天花板。里面的一切都是悬浮的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting.  Any other experiments you're working on?</Source>
      <Dest>有意思。你还在搞哪些方面的实验？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So instead of having to walk up a lengthy flight of stairs, you're pushed upward.  Or rather, repelled.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你并不需要走上那条漫长的台阶，你是被推上去的。或者说，是被挤上去的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While the results are similar, things like shouts aren't technically magic.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然看起来差不多，不过龙吼那种东西还是跟魔法有本质不同的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But Magnus' imprint is everywhere. Some say it was he, not Lorkhan, who made the world.</Source>
      <Dest>但马格努斯的痕迹到处都是。有些人说是他创造了这个世界，而非洛克汗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While the results are similar, things like shouts aren't technically magic.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然看起来差不多，不过龙吼那种东西还是跟魔法有本质不同的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>His departure made the sun, and when plants use it to grow, they use magic.  All the energy on Mundus is related to Magnus is some form.</Source>
      <Dest>他的离去造就了太阳，当植物因此生长之时，他们使用了魔法。梦达思的所有能量与梦达思的某种形式息息相关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While the results are similar, things like shouts aren't technically magic.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然看起来差不多，不过龙吼那种东西还是跟魔法有本质不同的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes if you look at the sun, I bet you could see Magnus himself, poking his head back in to see how we're doing.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢打赌，当你看着太阳的时候，你会看见马格努斯那家伙正在把他的脑袋伸出来注视着我们的行动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While the results are similar, things like shouts aren't technically magic.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然看起来差不多，不过龙吼那种东西还是跟魔法有本质不同的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not that I'd ever try it.  Looking at the sun. You'll go blind.  Of course, I've been talking with Master Colette about a ward spell to do just that.</Source>
      <Dest>我试过了，才不是那样。直盯着太阳你的眼睛只会瞎掉，当然，我在那样做之前有向蔻莱特大师讨教过防护法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While the results are similar, things like shouts aren't technically magic.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然看起来差不多，不过龙吼那种东西还是跟魔法有本质不同的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know if it's possible.  You would need a powerful ward spell to fend off the glare of a god.  Maybe if you used his staff...</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道是否可行。你需要一个强力的魔杖以挡住神刺眼的光芒。也许你可以用他的...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of magic do you study?</Source>
      <Dest>你研究的是那个类型的魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The field of unknown and undiscovered magic.  It seems odd that there are only five schools.  There should be at least five hundred!</Source>
      <Dest>对于那些未知和未被探索到的魔法领域。只有五个学派，听起来很奇怪吧，其实至少有五百个！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of magic do you study?</Source>
      <Dest>你研究的是那个类型的魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How else can you explain all the magical phenomena in this world?  Doomstones, alchemy, and dragon shouts for instance...</Source>
      <Dest>还有什么魔法现象是你能解释的？灵魂石，炼金术，或者龙吼什么的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of magic do you study?</Source>
      <Dest>你研究的是那个类型的魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Those can't be categorized by any of the five schools.  And I still don't understand why the council chose to conflate conjuration and mysticism.</Source>
      <Dest>它们无法归类到五种学派中的任何一个。 而且我还是想不明白为什么评议会将咒语魔法和神秘主义混为一谈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of magic do you study?</Source>
      <Dest>你研究的是那个类型的魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Master Colette said even Restoration might be stripped of its status!  Can you believe such a travesty?</Source>
      <Dest>蔻莱特大师说甚至恢复系法术也许会被剥夺它应有的地位！你相信这种笑话吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of magic do you study?</Source>
      <Dest>你研究的是那个类型的魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If anything, we need an additional school to account for the differences in classical Restoration and Aedric shrine magic.</Source>
      <Dest>总之，我们需要另外找个学院去说明传统回复法术和神族圣祠魔法的区别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until next time.</Source>
      <Dest>下回见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Looks like they brought something back from Saarthal.  A giant egg filled with Dwarves.  Or taffy.  I can't decide which.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来他们从萨瑟尔城带了什么东西回来了。一个装满矮人的巨蛋。或者太妃糖。我拿不准到底是哪个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Where did the egg go?  What was inside?</Source>
      <Dest>那枚蛋后来弄到那儿去了？里面有什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Horses are dull.  The Nords should use different animals to pull their carriages.  Wolves, no...spiders!  The driver can use ice spikes to slow down.</Source>
      <Dest>马太迟钝了。诺德人应该用些不同的动物来拉货车。狼什么的，不妥......蜘蛛！驾车的可以用冰锥来控制它减速。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think earwax is there to keep out Will o' Whispers. Creatures whose body is a spoken word that slithers into your brain and causes nightmares.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为耳垢是把那些惑人之物挡在外边的。不是常说那些动物的尸体会溜进你的脑子里让你做噩梦吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One time I was out in the field, and I thought I met a Snow Elf!  But turns out he was just a regular Elf, covered in snow.</Source>
      <Dest>曾有一次，我走在路上，还以为自己撞见了一个雪精灵。不过后来发现他是个普通精灵，只是一身白罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I admit, I was suffering from apprentice level boredom. Then came the dragons.  What's next, tree gnomes?  By the Gods I hope so.</Source>
      <Dest>我承认，我受够了学徒水平的无趣了。接下来是一条龙，然后呢，树精吗？众神在上，但愿如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I heard that the Shrine of Azura used to be a giant tower made of mammoth skulls, and cliff racers nested atop it.  Implausible, but not impossible.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说阿祖拉祭坛以前是一个用猛犸头骨做成的高塔，崖壁鸟在上面做巢。简直不可思议，但又并不是不可能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Faralda and Nirya like Sergius, but I think he fancies the new mage, who probably likes someone else.  That's right, an old fashioned love trapezoid.</Source>
      <Dest>法萝达和尼尔雅 喜欢瑟吉尔斯，不过我想他痴迷于新来的那个法师，那法师大概也喜欢着某个人。没错，喜闻乐见的四角恋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I met an Orc once who called me a "milk-drinking snowberry."  It gave me an excellent idea for a fruit cheese platter.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾经遇到了个兽人，他叫我"吃奶的雪浆果"这给了我一个绝佳的创意——水果奶酪拼盘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>More things should have wheels on them.  More animals should have wings.  There isn't enough of either.</Source>
      <Dest>带轮子的东西应该多一点。带翅膀的动物也是。可惜都不够多啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mysticism is a perfectly valid school of magic, and I won't forget it.</Source>
      <Dest>秘法是个正规且完美的魔法学校，我不会忘了这点的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can nirnroot be played like a musical instrument?  I think it's possible, with the right magical fields.</Source>
      <Dest>奈恩根可以当乐器弹奏吗？我觉得有可能，只要配上合适的魔法力场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One of these days, I'm going to catch a Nirnroot saying something in Dwarven, and that'll solve two mysteries at once.</Source>
      <Dest>总有一天，我会找到一颗会说矮人语的奈恩之根，这就能一次性解决两个谜团。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The disappearance of the moons only confirms my theory.  The moons are floating islands in the sky, only sideways.</Source>
      <Dest>The disappearance of the moons only confirms my theory.  The moons are floating islands in the sky, only sideways.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fire and ice are clearly separate disciplines.  I think wards are more like alteration too, but Colette's heart would stop if I said it.</Source>
      <Dest>冰与火有明确的界限，我觉得防护术其实也是这样。但是我估计如果我公开地这样说的话蔻莱特会疯掉的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That Olivia woman in The Arcanaeum scares me.  Her words are sweet enough, but that voice is so mean.</Source>
      <Dest>那个在秘藏馆的奥莉薇雅女人吓到我了。她的语言很甜美，但是那个声音实在是太尖刻了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Master Drevis can disappear a lot of things, and I'm sure he has.  He's like a pack rat.</Source>
      <Dest>德莱维斯大师能让很多东西消失，我确定他能办到，他就像一只袋鼠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think every species has a language.  I think a chaurus tried to say "Greetings" to me once.  I probably shouldn't have lit it on fire.</Source>
      <Dest>我想每种动物都有他们独有的语言。我想那条蜈蚣尝试向我打招呼。或许我不该把它扔到火里烧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We need a garden.  Wouldn't it be better if there were more bugs?  Alchemical magic is so interesting.</Source>
      <Dest>我们需要一个花园，如果这儿有更多的虫子不是会更好一些吗？炼金术太有意思了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm pretty sure dragons are the new Silt Strider.  I'm still holding out hope for an airship lifted into the sky by butterflies.</Source>
      <Dest>我十分确信龙是新型的跳蚤大巴。还有，我依旧坚持有朝一日会出现由蝴蝶驱动的飞艇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had a dream last night that it rained rocks.  First thing tomorrow, I'm buying a helmet.  Maybe second thing tomorrow, after my morning sweet roll.</Source>
      <Dest>我昨晚梦见天上下了石头雨。所以今早第一件事就是买个头盔戴。或者是第二件事吧，在我吃完早点之后。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What if you could conjure a disease, and its cure?  I'm sure it's possible.  I really hope to see it in my lifetime.</Source>
      <Dest>要是你能召唤一种疾病，那么能召唤它的治愈魔法又有什么呢？我相信这是可能的。我真希望能在有生之年看到它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Giants are huge, but I bet there are ones so big that entire cities live on their backs. How else do you explain the moving castles of Valenwood?</Source>
      <Dest>巨人是挺大的，但我打赌有肯定有什么家伙能巨大到背负起整座城市。不然你怎么解释威木省的移动城堡？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever wonder how cave tunnels were made?  Digging probably, but not by mortals.  Giant sand armadillos, or dragon worms, or wyrms, as it were.</Source>
      <Dest>Ever wonder how cave tunnels were made?  Digging probably, but not by mortals.  Giant sand armadillos, or dragon worms, or wyrms, as it were.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I left a piece of meat out the other day in a jar.  Next day, flies were in it.  Do you think flies can be born out of meat?</Source>
      <Dest>有一次，我把一片碎肉留在罐子里。隔天呢，苍蝇就跑进去了。你觉得苍蝇可以不靠肉维生吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if the emergence of dragons is affecting weather patterns as well as Skyrim's ecosystem. Their shouts disperse clouds, which increases heat.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道龙的出现是否会影响天气模式和天际省的生态系统。他们的叫喊声驱散乌云，使温度骤增。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever heard of Dwarven tonal locks?  I bet they only open if you sing the correct sequence of notes.</Source>
      <Dest>听说过矮人声控储藏室么?我打赌只有你发出正确顺序的声音他们才会打开.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell me, would you rather have flutes for thumbs or a drum for a foot?  I can't decide.  Maybe if I was still a thumbsucker.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我，你是要一支指笛呢还是想要一面脚鼓？我不好决定。兴许我是太过斤斤计较了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People say I don't walk around enough. They say I need the exercise. But I'm in the best shape of a horker's life.  That has to count for something.</Source>
      <Dest>他们都说我宅，缺乏锻炼 但我觉得这是最好的生活方式了.这已算是死得其所。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was asked to collect greenspore samples for Wylandriah, but the letter clearly says greenmote.  I wonder what that is?</Source>
      <Dest>受维兰瑞亚之托我来收集绿色孢子的样本，但是信里清清楚楚的写着绿色颗粒。我在想到底是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe greenmote means "green moat."  Can you imagine, a moat made of tiny green ticks that infect your lungs when inhaled.  Or was that greenspore?</Source>
      <Dest>也许绿色尘埃意味着“绿色城壕”。你能想象吗，一条完完全全由微小的绿色虱子构成的城壕，会在你吸入的时候会感染你的肺部。或许叫它绿色孢子更形象点儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if there's another world out there where people wear pies on their feet because that's the prevailing fashion.</Source>
      <Dest>我很好奇是不是有存在着这样一个世界，那里的人们喜欢在脚上穿着派，因为那是时尚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I heard there are poultices that allow Khajiit to regrow lost fur!  I wonder if it'd work on a Nord scalp. Sergius' head is brighter than the sun.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说过虎人有一种膏药可以使脱落的皮毛重新长出来！我在想那膏药对诺德人的头皮有没有用。瑟吉尔斯的脑袋比太阳还亮眼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you think it's true what they say about Orc tusks?  That if you plant them in the garden, they'll grow into a skeleton?  I want to try it.</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得兽人虎牙的那种说法可信吗？说你要是把它们种进土里，就能长出一副完整骨架来？我打算试试看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say there's a book about Barenziah that talks about her Khajiit lover and...well...is it true?  Is it lumpy?</Source>
      <Dest>They say there's a book about Barenziah that talks about her Khajiit lover and...well...is it true?  Is it lumpy?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say gold doesn't grow on trees but...how do we know that's true?  Have you seen every tree in Tamriel?</Source>
      <Dest>他们说金子不可能长在树上但是……我们怎么能确定他们说的就是真的呢？你亲眼见过泰姆瑞尔大陆的每一棵树吗</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe you have to sing off-key to open a tonal lock.  Dwarves aren't musical people, are they?  It would only make sense.</Source>
      <Dest>也许你不得不唱得一点调也不走才能打开一把音调锁。矮人不是爱好音乐的人对吧？这应该能奏效。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say if you look in a mirror and say "Sithis" 5 times, he'll reach through the glass and suck you into the void. I never make it past 3. </Source>
      <Dest>They say if you look in a mirror and say "Sithis" 5 times, he'll reach through the glass and suck you into the void. I never make it past 3. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've been trying to stay awake at night, in case tiny fairies are stealing sugar from the dining area.  Or it could just be Drevis.</Source>
      <Dest>我试着整晚不睡，看看是不是有小精灵在用餐区偷糖吃。或者就是多雷米斯那魂淡干的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mountain air is so thin.  I wonder if it's possible to conjure more of it.  What am I saying, of course it's possible. I just have to figure out how.</Source>
      <Dest>山上空气真稀薄啊。我琢磨着是不是能召唤点出来。呃我说想什么呢，当然有可能。只要我想出办法来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever tried counting the 7,000 steps?  I have.  I got to about 414 when I got attacked by a frost troll.  But I think I was more than halfway up.</Source>
      <Dest>试过数数那七千级台阶吗？我试过，数到第414阶的时候我遭遇了霜巨魔。可是我觉得那时候已经爬了过半的路了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What happens if you don't trim your fingernails?  Do they just keep going on forever?  Do you think I could maybe touch the sun?</Source>
      <Dest>如果我一直不剪指甲会怎么样？指甲会不停地变长吗？是不是能很长很长，长到可以碰到太阳？</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
