<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm telling you, I'm Lorne. Watch me drink this ale or mead.</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉你，我洛恩。只喝麦芽酒或蜂蜜酒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This sounds very much like the mouse named Lorne. You care not for safety when your mouth is dry.</Source>
      <Dest>这声音和那只叫洛恩的大老鼠发出的声音很像。不过当你渴得嘴里发干的时候你可能也就顾不上危险了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm telling you, I'm Lorne. Watch me drink this ale or mead.</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉你，我洛恩。只喝麦芽酒或蜂蜜酒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I am not sure. I would rather not risk my life for a liar who only pretends to be Lorne. For coins are too round to square this debt.</Source>
      <Dest>可我不能肯定。我实在不愿意把自己的小命赌在一个假装成洛恩的骗子身上。这生意不划算。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are you looking for? I can help you find them.</Source>
      <Dest>你在找谁？我可以帮你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is a good plan. You can do the hunting, while I sleep in. But what if your name is on the list? That would complicate things.</Source>
      <Dest>那真是不错的计划，你去打猎，而我安心睡觉。但如果你的名字在名单上怎么办？那事情可就棘手了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are you looking for? I can help you find them.</Source>
      <Dest>你在找谁？我可以帮你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Prices must be paid, and coins are far too round to square this debt.</Source>
      <Dest>有债必偿，而且这不是靠金币能解决的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You better pray to the Divines that my name isn't on that list.</Source>
      <Dest>你最好向圣灵祈祷我的名字不在名单上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is good advice. I detest a challenge. I would rather they pay a different price, but coins are far too round to square this debt.</Source>
      <Dest>这个建议不错，我讨厌挑战。我宁愿他们以另外的方式支付报酬，用钱来支付账单可远远不够啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What list are you talking about?</Source>
      <Dest>你说的名单是指什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not your concern. There are names, and they must be scratched off. For a gold coin is too round to square this debt.</Source>
      <Dest>这不关你的事。这就是一份名单，写着需要被做掉的那些人的名字。有些债用钱偿还不了，只能拿命来还。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I'm Lorne. You got any ale or what?</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我是洛恩。你带了酒来还是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Funny. You look too strong and smell too sweet to be the one called Lorne. But you do look like a liar.</Source>
      <Dest>有意思。你看起来这么强壮，而且香味这么浓，根本不像是那个叫做洛恩的家伙。但是，你真的很像是一个骗子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I'm Lorne. You got any ale or what?</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我是洛恩。你带了酒来还是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am beginning to suspect the real Lorne no longer lives. I am happy to cross him off the list.</Source>
      <Dest>我开始怀疑：真正的洛恩或许已经死了。我很乐意把他从名单上叉掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lorne is in Sovngarde. Try looking for him there.</Source>
      <Dest>洛恩在松加德。试着在那儿找到他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lorne will never see Sovngarde so long as he is unable to pay her debts. This is clear to even the most dishonest of mice.</Source>
      <Dest>只要他不付清她的债务，他就永远到不了松加德。即使是最狡猾的老鼠也知道的清清楚楚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lorne is in Sovngarde. Try looking for him there.</Source>
      <Dest>洛恩在松加德。试着在那儿找到他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if he paid the blood price willingly, then perhaps there is a loophole. In any case, he is no longer on the list.</Source>
      <Dest>但是如果他乐意用血来偿还，那他身上那个洞一定是我敲出来的。无论如何，名单上已经没有他了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You shouldn't speak ill of the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>你不该诽谤死人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And why not? The dead don't fight back. Far better to speak ill of them than someone strong and living.</Source>
      <Dest>凭什么不行？死人可不会回嘴。总比说那些活着的强人们的坏话强吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You shouldn't speak ill of the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>你不该诽谤死人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Besides, if Lorne is dead, this is good news. I can scratch his name off the list.</Source>
      <Dest>再说了，如果洛恩死了，那就是好消息。我可以把他的名字从表里给划了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You've got the wrong person. I'm not Lorne.</Source>
      <Dest>你认错人了，我不是洛恩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I see. I am inclined to believe you. I was promised a mouse who smells of liquor. You are one who smells of blood.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了。我更倾向于相信你。我还以为我能逮到一只沾满酒精味的耗子，可你却是全身沾满鲜血味。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You've got the wrong person. I'm not Lorne.</Source>
      <Dest>你认错人了，我不是洛恩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If it is Lorne's blood, this is a good thing. It is one more name off the list.</Source>
      <Dest>如果这真是洛恩的血，那这就是件好事儿了。名单上又少一个人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lorne's a dead little mouse, actually.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，洛恩已经是一只死耗子了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This may be true. I was told Lorne was a timid, weak little thing, that would squeak when stepped on. You are not.</Source>
      <Dest>这可能是真的。我听说洛恩是个胆小如鼠，脆弱无力的家伙，被踩到脚都会大声尖叫。但你没有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lorne's a dead little mouse, actually.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，洛恩已经是一只死耗子了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If Lorne is dead, it is simply one more name off the list. This is a good thing.</Source>
      <Dest>如果洛恩死了，那么名单上就又少一个名字了。这可是件好事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You've been a naughty little mouse, Lorne. You've made a lot of noise, and a lot of debts.</Source>
      <Dest>你这个淘气的小老鼠，洛恩。你制造了很多噪音，欠了一屁股债。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He leaves the mice scratched and bitten, and returns to bed a less hungry kitten.</Source>
      <Dest>He leaves the mice scratched and bitten, and returns to bed a less hungry kitten.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For now, this cat will take a nap. He does not like long hours. He prefers to wake up as the sun goes down. But I am sure we will meet again.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，小猫要去睡个觉。他不愿意连续奋战，而是更喜欢一觉睡到太阳下山。不过我相信咱们会再见面的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Kitten, kitten, wearing ribbons, hides his claws beneath his mittens;</Source>
      <Dest>小猫，小猫，戴上丝巾，藏住小爪；</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's enough about the girl.</Source>
      <Dest>关于那个女孩已经说的够多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then perhaps it is time you hear my proposal.</Source>
      <Dest>那么也许该是你听听我建议的时候了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you provide a more detailed description of this assassin?</Source>
      <Dest>你能提供有关于这个刺客的更多细节吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It won't help. She will likely be dressed in the robes of the Dark Brotherhood, so all you will see is her eyes. That is how you will know her.</Source>
      <Dest>这帮不了忙。她多半会穿着黑暗兄弟会的长袍，所以你能看到的只是她的眼睛。你得以此认出她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The two of you have a history it seems.</Source>
      <Dest>你们两个似乎有相同的境遇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I make no secret of it. I despise the girl. She has always bested me, always made the hardest jobs look so easy.</Source>
      <Dest>我不想藏着掖着的，我讨厌那个女的。她总是在我之上，总是让最困难的工作变得那么容易。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The two of you have a history it seems.</Source>
      <Dest>你们两个似乎有相同的境遇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only it's her personality that truly pins my tail. She never takes credit for anything.</Source>
      <Dest>只是她的个性实在让我头疼。她向来不会信守诺言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The two of you have a history it seems.</Source>
      <Dest>你们两个似乎有相同的境遇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have dealt with braggarts. But this...false humility? It is the worst kind of arrogance.</Source>
      <Dest>我能应付吹嘘。但这……故作谦虚？这是最恶劣的一种傲慢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You called her a half-cat.</Source>
      <Dest>你管她叫半猫女。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She prowls like a cat, has claws like a cat, and has eyes like a cat. Thus, she is a cat, even when she is not.</Source>
      <Dest>她踱起步来像猫一样，有猫一样的爪子，猫一样的眼睛。所以，她就是一只猫，不是也得是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly are you proposing?</Source>
      <Dest>你究竟建议做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An alliance. I will give you the names, and you will save their lives, so that I can kill them myself at a later time.</Source>
      <Dest>那就合作吧。我把名单给你，也授予你拯救他们生命的权利, 这样我便可以在此之后亲自杀掉他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly are you proposing?</Source>
      <Dest>你究竟建议做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can see you are much stronger than I am, and more importantly, not as attached to your pillow.</Source>
      <Dest>我看得出你比我强壮得多，更重要的是，精力充沛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly are you proposing?</Source>
      <Dest>你究竟建议做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Normally, I can take my time, but that yellow-eyed bitch is too much. She never takes a break.</Source>
      <Dest>通常情况下，我忍声受气，但是那黄眼婊子太过分了。她死不松口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who contracted you to kill these Darksteel Agents?</Source>
      <Dest>是谁雇佣你们去杀那些黑铁间谍的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is not my business to know. We are provided a list of names, bounties written by everyday citizens, and beside each name is a price in gold.</Source>
      <Dest>这就不是我该知道的内容了。提供给我们的是一份名单，每天都有市民在上面写名字，在每个名字的旁边还会写有赏金数额。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who contracted you to kill these Darksteel Agents?</Source>
      <Dest>是谁雇佣你们去杀那些黑铁间谍的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That list tripled in size in the past month. As did the rewards.</Source>
      <Dest>名单的长度在上个月里增加了双倍。薪酬也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is the yellow-eyed girl?</Source>
      <Dest>那个黄眼睛的姑娘是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No one knows. She came to Falkreath wearing the armor and answered the door. She took the contracts that should've been mine.</Source>
      <Dest>没人知道. 她全副武装来到佛克瑞斯叫门. 她带着的那份契约应该不是我的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is the yellow-eyed girl?</Source>
      <Dest>那个黄眼睛的姑娘是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thought I was rid of her when I left the Dark Brotherhood. But still, she steals my mice.</Source>
      <Dest>我还以为离开了黑暗兄弟会就能摆脱她了。可她还是偷走了我的猎物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were with the Dark Brotherhood?</Source>
      <Dest>你和黑暗兄弟会一伙的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Many moons ago. You see, once we were many. When the Listener died, it was Astrid who realized the Night Mother is not the only one who speaks.</Source>
      <Dest>很长时间之前。我们曾经人数众多。聆听者死后，阿斯垂德觉得夜母并不是唯一一个能发号施令的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were with the Dark Brotherhood?</Source>
      <Dest>你和黑暗兄弟会一伙的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When word of mouth reached us, we lent it our ears. It wasn't long before the guild was thriving once more.</Source>
      <Dest>当口言之趋近，吾等侧耳倾听。距公会那复兴时代也没过去多久。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were with the Dark Brotherhood?</Source>
      <Dest>你和黑暗兄弟会一伙的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if anyone can be a listener, then there is no need for a guild. We can all go into business for ourselves.</Source>
      <Dest>But if anyone can be a listener, then there is no need for a guild. We can all go into business for ourselves.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For you see, while we may have left the guild, we are still assassins by trade.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你看，虽然我们可能已经离开了公会，但我们仍然在通过等价交换来进行刺杀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And the cat cannot eat without killing the mouse.</Source>
      <Dest>猫儿不吃没有被玩死的老鼠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Forget it. She's already gone, now that she got what she came for.</Source>
      <Dest>忘却这一切吧。她已然去了，她已经得到她想要的东西了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stupid Nord...Don't ask questions when you...already know the answer.</Source>
      <Dest>愚蠢的诺德人..别明...明知故问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No...the half-cat, she must have used him to draw me out.</Source>
      <Dest>不……那条半猫，她肯定利用他来把我钓出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Once I saw it wasn't her, I realized my mistake and ran for cover, and walked right into her trap.</Source>
      <Dest>一旦我看到这不是她，我才意识到我的错误并试图寻找掩体，然后却径直走进了她的陷阱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vaba Renrij...I had thought at the very least....I could kill the two of you...but it seems I am the one to lose...this game of cat and mouse.</Source>
      <Dest>Vaba Renrij...I had thought at the very least....I could kill the two of you...but it seems I am the one to lose...this game of cat and mouse.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A Breton man in Markarth named Krillo. 1000 gold for this one. The girl is working from the bottom up.</Source>
      <Dest>一个来自马卡斯城的名叫奎依罗的布莱顿人。1000金币，解决掉他。这女孩儿得从头学学该怎么工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She is no fool. She knows the others will go for the highest contract first, even though it is clearly the hardest.</Source>
      <Dest>她不是傻子。她知道别人首先会对最高等级的合同感兴趣，尽管它明显是最难的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, but the list has many names. If you kill me after a divulge one, you will still be responsible for the others.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，但这清单有很多名字。就算你在泄露清单之后杀了我，你也得干掉剩下的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, we are wasting time talking. The half-cat is already on the prowl.</Source>
      <Dest>In any case, we are wasting time talking. The half-cat is already on the prowl.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am not asking you to help an assassin. I am asking you to save a life. At least, temporarily.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是请你帮助一个刺客。我是在求你救一条性命。至少，是暂时救一下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, but it's true. She has taken every name on the list so far. It is just like the days in the Brotherhood. That is why I am in need of your help.</Source>
      <Dest>Oh, but it's true. She has taken every name on the list so far. It is just like the days in the Brotherhood. That is why I am in need of your help.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just a kitten who has had his toys taken away for the second time. This mouse was my kill, but again, the half-cat beat me to it.</Source>
      <Dest>就像一只眼睁睁地看着到手的玩具又一次被抢走的可怜猫咪一样。这只老鼠是我的猎物，但再一次，这只小猫又抢先了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The girl with the yellow eyes is a selfish one. She does not share the yarn with the rest of the litter.</Source>
      <Dest>那个黄眼睛的女孩儿挺自私的。她甚至连个故事都不愿跟别的孩子共享。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Winking Skeever has drunken men, but the cat and mouse are in another den.</Source>
      <Dest>眨眼雪鼠醉汉说，猫与老鼠不同窝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Go on. I will be here. I would come with you, but she will recognize me and blow your cover. Also, my back is sore.</Source>
      <Dest>向前走吧。我稍后到。我将会与你同行, 但是她会认出我而识破你的伪装。我感觉背后很痛.</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
