<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You'll pay for what you've done, boy.  Whatever that is.</Source>
      <Dest>无论你做了什么，你都将为你所作所为付出代价，少年。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You mean...you aren't with Jaree-Ra? (Gasps) By the Divines, when you said I'd pay...my heart almost stopped.</Source>
      <Dest>你是说……你没和加雷-拉在一起？（喘气）圣灵在上，你说要我付出代价的时候……我的心跳都快停了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's what made you do it. You didn't want a circlet. You wanted a friend.</Source>
      <Dest>那就是你这样做的原因。你不是想要一个戒指。你就是想要一个朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ma'zaka said the same thing.  Looking back, you're both right.  I hated stealing.</Source>
      <Dest>马扎卡也这么说。回想起来，你都是对的。我讨厌偷东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's what made you do it. You didn't want a circlet. You wanted a friend.</Source>
      <Dest>那就是你这样做的原因。你不是想要一个戒指。你就是想要一个朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But when Jaree-Ra gave his toast, everyone would smile and salute me.  It was the camaraderie that I wanted.  The feeling that I belonged.</Source>
      <Dest>而当加雷-拉举杯祝酒时，每个人都朝我微笑致意。我需要的就是这样的同志感情，这种有所归属的感觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who was Deeja again?</Source>
      <Dest>谁又是蒂亚?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>His sister.  No...if she's still alive...you can't tell anyone you saw me here, please!</Source>
      <Dest>他姐姐.  不……如果她还活着……你别告诉人你见过我, 求你了!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're pathetic. I would kill you now, but you aren't worth staining my boots.</Source>
      <Dest>可怜虫，我真想现在杀了你，又不值得弄脏我的靴子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Please, I know I'm a terrible person.  Worse than dirt.  I never meant to lead a wicked life.</Source>
      <Dest>拜托了！我知道我是一个烂人，连烂泥都不如。但我从没想过要做恶人啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're pathetic. I would kill you now, but you aren't worth staining my boots.</Source>
      <Dest>可怜虫，我真想现在杀了你，又不值得弄脏我的靴子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you'll spare me, I promise, I'm doing my best to change.  Just ask Ma'zaka.</Source>
      <Dest>但是如果你能饶了我，我保证，我会尽我所能来有所改变。不信去问马扎卡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're pathetic. I would kill you now, but you aren't worth staining my boots.</Source>
      <Dest>可怜虫，我真想现在杀了你，又不值得弄脏我的靴子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Please, I know I'm a terrible person. Worse than dirt.  I never meant to lead a wicked life.</Source>
      <Dest>拜托了！我知道我是一个烂人，连烂泥都不如。但我从没想过要做恶人啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're pathetic. I would kill you now, but you aren't worth staining my boots.</Source>
      <Dest>可怜虫，我真想现在杀了你，又不值得弄脏我的靴子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you'll spare me, I promise, I'm doing my best to change. Before he died, Ma'zaka showed me how to tend the lighthouse. </Source>
      <Dest>但如果你放了我，我发誓，我会尽我全力变得更好。在马扎卡死前，他曾教过我该如何照管灯塔。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're pathetic. I would kill you now, but you aren't worth staining my boots.</Source>
      <Dest>可怜虫，我真想现在杀了你，又不值得弄脏我的靴子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I live an honest life now, I swear on the Divines!</Source>
      <Dest>我以圣灵的名义起誓，现在我已经不做伤天害理的事了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You'll make a fine keeper.  Just remember who your friends are.</Source>
      <Dest>你会成为一个好店主的，要记得你的朋友们啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you for your kind words.  May the Divines keep the flame of righteousness alive in both our hearts.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你的吉言。愿圣灵保佑我们心中永燃正义之火。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ever feel guilty for your crimes?</Source>
      <Dest>曾经为你的罪行感到内疚吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do.  I'm not proud of the things I did.  But it's Jaree-Ra's fault.  He used me.  I would've never been in that situation if it weren't for him.</Source>
      <Dest>我承认。我并不为我所做的一切令人自豪，但是这是加雷-拉的错，他利用了我。要不是因为他我本打算再也不要卷入这浑水之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Except most crowds are too busy talking about me to stare at you.</Source>
      <Dest>除大部分人都忙着讨论我盯着你看的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you some sort of hero?  Wow.  I never would have thought someone like you would take an interest in me.</Source>
      <Dest>你是个英雄人物吗？哇噻，想不到我能有幸受到您的关注。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I understand. Occasionally I forget there are people who shouldn't be killed.</Source>
      <Dest>我理解。有时候我会忘记有些人不该杀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hope I'm not one of them.  I may not be a hero, or a priest, by I don't want to die.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望我不是他们中的一员。我可能不会成为什么英雄好汉，因为我才不想英年早逝呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, I don't think you should feel guilty.  Stealing is fun.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得你不必怀有任何罪恶感，偷窃可是件好玩的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It wasn't for me.  I didn't do it for the rush, or for the coin.  I did it because I thought Jaree-Ra was my friend.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是为了我自己。我不是一时冲动，也不是为了钱。我这么做是因为我觉得加雷-拉是我的朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, I don't think you should feel guilty.  Stealing is fun.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得你不必怀有任何罪恶感，偷窃可是件好玩的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He manipulated me.  Fooled me.  If there's a reason I shouldn't feel guilty, it's because I'm the victim.</Source>
      <Dest>他操纵我，愚弄我。我觉得问心无愧是因为我才是受害者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我发生什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Jaree-Ra sent me here.  He wanted me to extinguish the fire in the lighthouse.  I don't know why I said yes.</Source>
      <Dest>加雷-拉让我到这儿来，要我把灯塔的火给灭掉。我稀里糊涂地就答应了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我发生什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We used to be friends.  At least I thought so.  Then he started having me do things.  Things I regretted later.</Source>
      <Dest>我们曾是朋友，至少我自以为我们是朋友。但后来他开始要我做些事，要我做那些不久之后就让我后悔不已的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我发生什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of things did Jaree-Ra have you do?</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉让你做什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It started out with just stealing.  I would walk into store and Jaree-Ra would distract the shopkeep, and I'd stuff anything I could into my tunic.  </Source>
      <Dest>最开始只是偷窃。我走进商店，加雷-拉分散店主的注意力，然后我把所有偷到的东西都塞进外套里。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我发生什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of things did Jaree-Ra have you do?</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉让你做什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I still remember that first time.  I was so scared.  We were in Radiant Raiment, and Jaree-Ra was trying on clothes a Jarl couldn't afford.</Source>
      <Dest>我仍记得那一次。我们在锦衣，然后加雷-拉想要去试一件连领主都买不起的衣服。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我发生什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of things did Jaree-Ra have you do?</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉让你做什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was a circlet on the counter. Gold and emerald. Endarie never even noticed when I switched it with the copper one I was wearing.</Source>
      <Dest>柜台上摆放着一个绿宝石金饰头环。我把它换成我自己戴的铜制山寨货，而恩达蕊根本没注意到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我发生什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of things did Jaree-Ra have you do?</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉让你做什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I felt horrible afterward. But Jaree-Ra always found a way to make it seem okay. Those haughty knife-ears got what they deserved, he said.</Source>
      <Dest>我有些后怕，但加雷-拉总能找到办法让一切看上去毫无问题。他说，那些傲慢的尖耳朵（精灵）完全是自作自受。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what happened.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我发生什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of things did Jaree-Ra have you do?</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉让你做什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when we went drinking at the inn to celebrate, Jaree-Ra would pat me on the back and give a toast in my honor.</Source>
      <Dest>And when we went drinking at the inn to celebrate, Jaree-Ra would pat me on the back and give a toast in my honor.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Jaree-Ra was right.  Stealing's not a crime when the target deserves it.</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉是对的。偷该偷之人的钱财不算犯罪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ma'zaka said that wasn't the point.  He said it doesn't matter if Jaree-Ra was right, because his intent was wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>马扎卡说那无所谓。他说就算加雷-拉那套理论是对的也无所谓，因为他的出发点是错的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Jaree-Ra was right.  Stealing's not a crime when the target deserves it.</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉是对的。偷该偷之人的钱财不算犯罪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thought he wanted to comfort me.  But all he really wanted was to deceive me.</Source>
      <Dest>我以为他想安慰我。但其实他是想骗我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You'll get the hang of it.  You're talking to me right now.</Source>
      <Dest>你会得到窍门的。你正在和我说话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, and Ma'zaka is here too, although with him mostly I just listen.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，而且马扎卡也在这里，尽管和他在一起的时候我大多只是听他说话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You'll get the hang of it.  You're talking to me right now.</Source>
      <Dest>你会得到窍门的。你正在和我说话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you.  With Ma'zaka gone, it's so lonely here.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你。马扎卡走了，稍微有点寂寞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the significance of the Shadow sign?</Source>
      <Dest>What was the significance of the Shadow sign?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He said as a Khajiit born under the shadow, many told him his destiny was to be a brigand, or a thief.</Source>
      <Dest>他说作为生于阴影中的虎人，很多人都说他命中注定会成为一个夜匪，或是窃贼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the significance of the Shadow sign?</Source>
      <Dest>What was the significance of the Shadow sign?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He told me how he spent his life as a pirate, and still misses the clash of sabres, and the ocean smell tickling his whiskers.</Source>
      <Dest>他告诉了我他的海盗生涯，而且依然怀念短剑的摩擦声，海洋的味道依然挑逗着他的胡须。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the significance of the Shadow sign?</Source>
      <Dest>What was the significance of the Shadow sign?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But in the end, he preferred the quiet life. And it wasn't until he reached an old age that he learned we make our own destiny.</Source>
      <Dest>但是最后，他还是选择回归平静的生活。当他步入暮年，他才终于意识到，自己的命运还是由自己来左右的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the significance of the Shadow sign?</Source>
      <Dest>What was the significance of the Shadow sign?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then he invited me downstairs for tea. And I've been with him ever since.</Source>
      <Dest>然后他邀请我去楼下喝茶。从那以后我一直跟他在一起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why didn't you extinguish the lighthouse flame? What changed?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么不把灯塔的火灭掉？发生什么事了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was standing before the fire, holding a tankard of water when Ma'zaka came up behind me.  When I saw him, my face flushed with blood, and I froze.</Source>
      <Dest>当马扎卡出现在我身后时，我正端着一杯水，站在壁炉前。当我看到他时，就止不住的血气上涌，浑身冰凉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why didn't you extinguish the lighthouse flame? What changed?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么不把灯塔的火灭掉？发生什么事了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thought he was going to attack me, or have me arrested.  But you know what he said?  "The weather is nice today, is it not?"</Source>
      <Dest>我以为他得攻击我，或有我要被捕了。但你知道他说什么了吗？”今天天气真好，不是吗？”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why didn't you extinguish the lighthouse flame? What changed?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么不把灯塔的火灭掉？发生什么事了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are the keepers assigned?</Source>
      <Dest>那些守卫是怎么分派的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Usually one of the Jarl's Thanes has one of his attendants get a recommendation.  Naturally, the previous keeper's input carries a lot of weight.</Source>
      <Dest>一般做法是，领主的男爵通过举荐的形式来任命他的随从。因而，来自于前一任雇主的评价就非常重要了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are the keepers assigned?</Source>
      <Dest>那些守卫是怎么分派的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Once the names are recommended, the captain of the guard checks the candidates for potential criminal history.</Source>
      <Dest>一旦被推荐，守卫队长就会检查候选人是否有潜在的犯罪史。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are the keepers assigned?</Source>
      <Dest>那些守卫是怎么分派的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's what worries me most.  I've never been officially accused of a crime, but Jaree-Ra's reputation could come back to haunt me.</Source>
      <Dest>这是让我最担心的。我从来没有被正式指控犯罪过，但加雷-拉的名声非得让我不得安生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I myself like to blame others for my crimes.  It's rather convenient.</Source>
      <Dest>我个人习惯于将自己罪行怪罪到他人身上，这样省事多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't mean it that way.  I'm the victim here. Jaree-Ra is the one who took advantage of me.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是那个意思，我就是个受害者。加雷-拉才是利用我的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've been asked to do the same, but I don't exactly trust Jaree-Ra's intentions.</Source>
      <Dest>我也被告知要我做同样的事。但我其实并不确信扎里拉的意图。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Please, I implore you, reconsider!  I should know, I almost made the same mistake. </Source>
      <Dest>拜托！求求你，再考虑考虑啊！我应该知道的，我曾经差点犯下一模一样的错误。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I was duped by Jaree-Ra as well.  But I'm the sort who does something about it.</Source>
      <Dest>我也被加雷·拉忽悠了，但不同的是：我不会善罢甘休。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then the Divines have blessed you with courage.  Not all of us are so lucky.  But I'm glad they've given me their mercy instead.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵会赐予你勇气。不是所有人都如此幸运。但我很高兴他们最终用仁慈包容了我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The more you talk about Jaree-Ra, the more I want to befriend him.</Source>
      <Dest>你说扎里拉的事越多，我就越想和他交朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You may like him now, but he'll use you and then toss you away like an old boot.  There are better to people to befriend.  People like Ma'Zaka.</Source>
      <Dest>你也许现在喜欢他，但他会狠狠利用完你再把你像个旧鞋子一般的丢掉。想交朋友的话这里有更好的人选。马扎卡的为人就不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Easy, young man. What's the problem?</Source>
      <Dest>放松点，年轻人。出了什么事?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait...so you aren't here to kill me?  Oh thank the Divines!</Source>
      <Dest>等等...那你不是来杀我的？哦谢天谢地！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Someone like you doesn't deserve to be the keeper of the flame.</Source>
      <Dest>你这样的人不配做火焰的看守者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's fine...I don't have to be the keeper.  Just please, don't tell the guard I'm staying here.  I don't want Ma'zaka to get into trouble.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧……我并不是非要成为看守者……求求你，别去告诉守卫我还在这儿。我可不想给马扎卡惹麻烦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Jaree-Ra used you.  Some people do that.</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉利用了你，其他人也是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know that now. I was such a fool.  He never wanted my friendship. I was just some tool he used to steal coin. Never even gave me a proper cut.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我知道了。我真是个傻瓜。他从来没有把我当朋友，我只是他用来偷盗钱财的工具而已。他甚至从来没有让我穿过一件体面的衣服。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Jaree-Ra used you.  Some people do that.</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉利用了你，其他人也是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He knew I wouldn't care.  Toward the end, he didn't even bother with reasons.  All he'd do is raise another toast.</Source>
      <Dest>He knew I wouldn't care.  Toward the end, he didn't even bother with reasons.  All he'd do is raise another toast.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who...who are you?  By the Divines, you're here for me, aren't you.  I swear I tried, I was going to do it!  Please, don't hurt me!</Source>
      <Dest>你……你是谁？圣灵在上，你在这儿等着我，是不是。我发誓我试过了，我会去做的！别伤害我，拜托了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>那个计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The plan was to extinguish the flame at the lighthouse, so that the ships would lose sight of the docks and crash.</Source>
      <Dest>这个计划是熄灭灯塔上的火焰，使船寻觅不到码头所在，继而撞毁沉没。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>那个计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I didn't want to do it.  Stealing is one thing, but killing a man...but Jaree-Ra assured me no one would die.</Source>
      <Dest>我不想那么做。偷抢尸一回事，而杀人却……但是加雷-拉向我保证过没人会丧命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>那个计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He said they'd thank us for rescuing them. And I believed him. </Source>
      <Dest>他说他们会感谢我们的救命之恩。而我相信了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did Jaree-Ra recruit you?</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉是怎么招募你的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was at the Skeever, when Jaree-Ra came by with his Marauder friends.  The ones that make me nervous.  </Source>
      <Dest>当加雷-拉 和他的掠夺者朋友来的时候，我在雪鼠那里。那些家伙搞得我有点儿紧张。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did Jaree-Ra recruit you?</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉是怎么招募你的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But Jaree-Ra put his arm around my shoulder and mussed my hair with those coarse fingers of his.  That always put me at ease.</Source>
      <Dest>但加雷-拉搂住了我，用他粗糙的手指拨乱了我的头发，这样让我很舒服。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did Jaree-Ra recruit you?</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉是怎么招募你的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then he tells me about this new plan of his.  He says he needs me.  That nobody can do it but me. </Source>
      <Dest>然后他向我讲述了他的这个新计划。他说他需要我，因为只有我才能完成它。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did Jaree-Ra recruit you?</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉是怎么招募你的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think one of his gang snickered.  But Jaree-Ra told him to shut his mouth, and that made me feel good.</Source>
      <Dest>我想他的一个同伙在窃笑。但加雷-拉要他闭嘴，这让我感觉不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're obviously guilty of something.</Source>
      <Dest>很明显你不是无辜的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Please, just here me out, it's not what you think.  I haven't done anything wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>哦拜托了，听我把话说完，不是你想的那样。我没做错什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree.  It was a heinous thing to take advantage of your weakness.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。抓住你的软肋这种做法真是太卑鄙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I appreciate you seeing the whole picture.  Some would not absolve me of my crimes, even after knowing how I was manipulated.</Source>
      <Dest>我很感激你看到了整个过程。有些人不能免除我的罪行, 即使知道我是如何任人摆布的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree.  It was a heinous thing to take advantage of your weakness.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。抓住你的软肋这种做法真是太卑鄙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The truth is, I never had many friends growing up.  People who genuinely cared about me.  </Source>
      <Dest>事实是，我从小就没什么朋友。没有人真正关心我。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree.  It was a heinous thing to take advantage of your weakness.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。抓住你的软肋这种做法真是太卑鄙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you go to a tavern, they have stools and tables.  I always opted for the stool.  It's hard sometimes, drinking alone.</Source>
      <Dest>你进到一个酒馆儿的时候，他们有板凳和桌子。我老是挑板凳。独酌有时候真的是很艰难的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree.  It was a heinous thing to take advantage of your weakness.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。抓住你的软肋这种做法真是太卑鄙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Especially when so many are in the company of friends.  I used to hate the way they laughed. Jaree-Ra noticed too.  Said they barked like hounds.</Source>
      <Dest>特别是当看到大部分人都有朋友陪伴的时候。我曾经挺讨厌他们大笑时的样子的。加雷-拉也注意到了这点，他说他们吠起来就像猎犬一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree.  It was a heinous thing to take advantage of your weakness.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。抓住你的软肋这种做法真是太卑鄙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's how we met.  Suddenly I was the one sitting at the tables.  Drinking in a good cheer.  Laughing. </Source>
      <Dest>我们就是这么认识的。出乎意料地，我坐在桌子边上，喝酒吃菜，大笑起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree.  It was a heinous thing to take advantage of your weakness.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。抓住你的软肋这种做法真是太卑鄙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It turns out I laugh like a mammoth grunts.  It's funny, but even now I look back on those times fondly.</Source>
      <Dest>事实证明我笑起来像一个长毛象打呼噜。这很有趣，但即使是现在，我也喜欢回顾那段日子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree.  It was a heinous thing to take advantage of your weakness.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。抓住你的软肋这种做法真是太卑鄙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I might've been a fool, but I don't see how I had any other choice.  Not in a tavern.  I needed to come here, but how could I have known that?</Source>
      <Dest>我可能显得很傻，但是我只能这么做。不是在酒馆里。也许我应该到这来，但是我不知道！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree.  It was a heinous thing to take advantage of your weakness.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。抓住你的软肋这种做法真是太卑鄙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I would have never guessed that an old Khajiit lighthouse keeper would become my best friend.</Source>
      <Dest>我从没有想到一个看守灯塔的老虎人会成为我最好的朋友.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ever the coward, still blaming others instead of owning up to your part.</Source>
      <Dest>这个胆小鬼，不承认自己的错误，还去指责别人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's not cowardice.  I told you, Jaree-Ra manipulated me.  Ma'zaka said I'm a good man.  And I never wanted to hurt anyone.  </Source>
      <Dest>这不是懦弱。我跟你说，是加雷-拉控制了我。马扎卡说我是个好人。我从来没想过要伤害任何人。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The manipulated aren't necessarily victims.  At some point you have to be smart.</Source>
      <Dest>就算被操纵也未必都是牺牲品。在某些关键时候你还是得有脑子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's not that simple.  I never had many friends growing up.  People who genuinely cared about me.  </Source>
      <Dest>这种事不是那么简单。我从小就没什么朋友。没有人真正关心我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The manipulated aren't necessarily victims.  At some point you have to be smart.</Source>
      <Dest>就算被操纵也未必都是牺牲品。在某些关键时候你还是得有脑子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you go to a tavern, they have stools and tables.  I always opted for the stool.  It's hard sometimes, drinking alone.</Source>
      <Dest>你进到一个酒馆儿的时候，他们有板凳和桌子。我老是挑板凳。独酌有时候真的是很艰难的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The manipulated aren't necessarily victims.  At some point you have to be smart.</Source>
      <Dest>就算被操纵也未必都是牺牲品。在某些关键时候你还是得有脑子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Especially when so many are in the company of friends.  I used to hate the way they laughed. Jaree-Ra noticed too.  Said they barked like hounds.</Source>
      <Dest>特别是当看到大部分人都有朋友陪伴的时候。我曾经挺讨厌他们大笑时的样子的。加雷-拉也注意到了这点，他说他们吠起来就像猎犬一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The manipulated aren't necessarily victims.  At some point you have to be smart.</Source>
      <Dest>就算被操纵也未必都是牺牲品。在某些关键时候你还是得有脑子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's how we met.  Suddenly I was the one sitting at the tables.  Drinking in good cheer.  Laughing.</Source>
      <Dest>我们就是这么认识的。出乎意料地，我坐在桌子边上，喝酒吃菜，大笑起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The manipulated aren't necessarily victims.  At some point you have to be smart.</Source>
      <Dest>就算被操纵也未必都是牺牲品。在某些关键时候你还是得有脑子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It turns out I laugh like a mammoth grunts.  It's funny, but even now I look back on those times fondly.</Source>
      <Dest>事实证明我笑起来像一个长毛象打呼噜。这很有趣，但即使是现在，我也喜欢回顾那段日子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The manipulated aren't necessarily victims.  At some point you have to be smart.</Source>
      <Dest>就算被操纵也未必都是牺牲品。在某些关键时候你还是得有脑子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I might've been a fool, but I don't see how I had any other choice.  Not in a tavern.  I needed to come here, but how could I have known that?</Source>
      <Dest>我可能显得很傻，但是我只能这么做。不是在酒馆里。也许我应该到这来，但是我不知道！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The manipulated aren't necessarily victims.  At some point you have to be smart.</Source>
      <Dest>就算被操纵也未必都是牺牲品。在某些关键时候你还是得有脑子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I would have never guessed that an old Khajiit lighthouse keeper would become my best friend.</Source>
      <Dest>我从没有想到一个看守灯塔的老虎人会成为我最好的朋友.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They say mortals are slaves to habit.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说人类已经习惯成为奴隶了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know that all too well.  And part of me worries that I'll go back to my old ones.  But Ma'zaka keeps me strong.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道得太清楚了。我担心我会变回原来的我。但马扎卡使我坚强。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then what are you waiting for?  Do whatever it is you're supposed to do.</Source>
      <Dest>那你还等什么呢？干你该干的事儿去！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait...so...you don't know who I am?  Oh by the Nine Divines, what a relief!</Source>
      <Dest>等等……所以……你不知道我是谁？哦九圣灵在上，真让我松了口气儿！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's life at the lighthouse?</Source>
      <Dest>灯塔里的生活怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It' s peaceful.  I don't yearn for company like I used to, nor am I afraid of being alone.</Source>
      <Dest>It' s peaceful.  I don't yearn for company like I used to, nor am I afraid of being alone.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's life at the lighthouse?</Source>
      <Dest>灯塔里的生活怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although sometimes when I head up to the docks for supplies, I get a little anxious.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然有时去码头买补给品时，我会有点紧张。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's life at the lighthouse?</Source>
      <Dest>灯塔里的生活怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's like learning to ride a horse again.  Pretty much every young boy is taught how to ride a horse and nock an arrow.</Source>
      <Dest>就跟再学一次骑马一个样儿。几乎每个年轻男孩儿都会被教导如何骑马射箭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's life at the lighthouse?</Source>
      <Dest>灯塔里的生活怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But not all of us can be soldiers.  Or rich enough to buy a horse.  So you kind of forget how.</Source>
      <Dest>但不是我们每个人都能成为一名士兵，或是有钱买一匹马的。所以你尽管忘了该怎么来吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's life at the lighthouse?</Source>
      <Dest>灯塔里的生活怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's what it feels like being around crowds.  Like everyone's staring at me.  </Source>
      <Dest>这感觉就像置身于人群当中，就像每个人都盯着我一样。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's life at the lighthouse?</Source>
      <Dest>灯塔里的生活怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when people say hello, I sometimes lose the words.  Can you imagine? Forgetting something so simple as a greeting.</Source>
      <Dest>当有人向我打招呼，有时我会突然忘记怎么回答他，你能想象吗？忘记一件简单的就像问候的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The more you talk about Jaree-Ra, the more I wish I hadn't killed him.</Source>
      <Dest>越是听你说加雷·拉的事，我就越后悔杀了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes I don't know whether you're joking, trying to raise my spirits, or just mean.  Maybe all three.  </Source>
      <Dest>有时候我不知道你到底是在跟我开玩笑，还是在激励我，或仅仅是个低劣的恶作剧。也有可能三种兼备。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The more you talk about Jaree-Ra, the more I wish I hadn't killed him.</Source>
      <Dest>越是听你说加雷·拉的事，我就越后悔杀了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If he's truly dead, then maybe I won't have to live in fear anymore.  But either way, I have Ma'zaka to thank for saving my life.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他真的死了，那么也许我再也不会生活在恐惧之中了。但是不管怎么说，我必须谢谢马扎卡救了我的命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you help tend to the Lighthouse now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在帮忙注意哪里有灯塔吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not officially, but I assist Ma'zaka any way I can, in exchange for room and board.</Source>
      <Dest>还没正式决定，但我尽我所能的协助马扎卡，以此换取食宿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you help tend to the Lighthouse now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在帮忙注意哪里有灯塔吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If he were to pass on, perhaps he might recommend me for the job.  Or maybe I could tend to the lighthouse in Dawnstar.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他去世了，也许他会推荐我去做这份工作的。或许我更偏重于去晨星城灯塔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you help tend to the Lighthouse now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在帮忙注意哪里有灯塔吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know if I've earned the right to be the keeper here.  There's still so much I need to atone for.</Source>
      <Dest>不知我是否已然得到了成为这里看守者的权利，我所要偿还的还是太多太多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Jaree-Ra?  He's dead.  I killed him.</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉?他死了。我杀了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You...what?  And Deeja?</Source>
      <Dest>你....什么？迪彻呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Also worm food.</Source>
      <Dest>也是温暖的食物。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then...then it's over.  I'm free!</Source>
      <Dest>然后……然后就结束了。我自由了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't be so hard on yourself.  I fell for the same trick.</Source>
      <Dest>别太苛责自己啦，我也栽在这上头过</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?  That makes me feel a little better.  I hope you didn't go through with it.</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗？这让我好过些。我真希望你没有经历过这些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't be so hard on yourself.  I fell for the same trick.</Source>
      <Dest>别太苛责自己啦，我也栽在这上头过</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But...but if you did I won't say a word.  I swear.  After all, I almost did the same.</Source>
      <Dest>但是...如果你真的这么做了，我发誓什么都不会说。不管怎样，我也几乎做了同样的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry, Jaree-Ra found someone else.  Someone who isn't a total coward.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，加雷·拉找到另一个人了。一个大概不会那么没用的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you're that determined, I can't stop you.  But please, I implore you, to think on what you're about to do.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你下定了决心，那我就无法阻止你了。但是，算我求你了，请再考虑一下你做了以后的后果吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry, Jaree-Ra found someone else.  Someone who isn't a total coward.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，加雷·拉找到另一个人了。一个大概不会那么没用的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know, I was about to make the same mistake. </Source>
      <Dest>我知道，我差点就犯了同样的错误。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Jaree-Ra sounds like bad news.</Source>
      <Dest>加雷·拉听起来像坏消息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then my suggestion is to stay away from him. After I failed him, someone fearless like you may be exactly who he's looking for.</Source>
      <Dest>我的建议是离他远点。我失败之后，像你这么无畏的人可能正对他的胃口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么心事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么想法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
