<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right, yeah. This is all useful stuff. I'll be stealin' from the Jarl in no time.</Source>
      <Dest>对啊，没错。这些都是派得上用场的东西。我马上就从领主那儿偷过来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmm. Maybe you're right. I'm better at fighting than half the guards and smarter'n most.</Source>
      <Dest>唔。也许你是对的。和守卫们中的半数人以及那些靠聪明脑子的大部分人比起来，我更擅长战斗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, I'm good at stabbing. If you're goin' off on some bandit whacking mission, you'd be smart to take me with you.</Source>
      <Dest>知道吗？我特擅长刺杀。要是你正好有什么剿匪的业务，带上我就对了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, my arm is achy after practice.</Source>
      <Dest>练完之后我的胳膊又酸又疼的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I been practicing my forms, like you showed me. I think I'm getting better.</Source>
      <Dest>我正在逐渐形成我自己的风格，就像你告诉我的那样。我想我比以前更好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah....Twas nothin'.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯……那不算什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I been down to the market today and they had some Horker meat. I made it into a stew. So you can have some, if you want.</Source>
      <Dest>今天我去了集市，买了些三牙海象肉，如果你想吃，就去锅里拿点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's good advice. I'll punch him right in his kisser.</Source>
      <Dest>那真是一个不错的建议. 我将会混在他要去亲的人当中猛击他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That older boy was giving me trouble again. I'm tryin' to be all civilized and solve things with words, but I want to punch him in his fat face.</Source>
      <Dest>那孩子又在给我惹麻烦了，我是想君子动口不动手的，但是今天我非得糊他一熊脸才行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't be daft. I was just wondering when I'd next be getting' some more sword training. ....You are careful, though, int you?</Source>
      <Dest>Don't be daft. I was just wondering when I'd next be getting' some more sword training. ....You are careful, though, int you?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You was gone a long time last time you went off heroin'.</Source>
      <Dest>离你上一次当英雄已经过去很久了吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like the boy got what he deserved.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来似乎是那个男孩遭到了报应。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Pretty much, cap'n.  If you're dumb enough to get caught, you deserve whatever comes next.</Source>
      <Dest>差不多的意思，头儿。要是你笨到能被抓住，那接下来不管发生什么都是你活该。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Like it never happened. Now get out of here before I change my mind.</Source>
      <Dest>好像什么都没发生过。趁我改变主意之前离开这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okey-dokey Cap'n.  I ain't even here.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，好啦头儿。就当我从没来过这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That poor boy.  It should've been you.</Source>
      <Dest>可怜的孩子。那不应该是你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That ain't very nice cap'n, but you're half right, it shoulda been me with the gem.  I would've gotten away with it.</Source>
      <Dest>头儿你猜的并不全对，但你对了一半，本该让我和那些宝石在一起的。这样我就可以带它们一起出来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Get away from me, kid. I don't have time for this.</Source>
      <Dest>离我远点，小孩，我现在没功夫玩这些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fine.  Stupid skeever brain.</Source>
      <Dest>行吧你。跟雪耗子一样智商堪忧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Get away from me, kid. I don't have time for this.</Source>
      <Dest>离我远点，小孩，我现在没功夫玩这些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fine.  Stupid skeever brain.</Source>
      <Dest>行吧你。跟雪耗子一样智商堪忧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not join the Thieves Guild?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么不加入盗贼公会呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So they can take a big chunk of my spoils? I do just fine on my own.</Source>
      <Dest>所以他们想从我的战利品里分走一大块儿？我一个人处理得来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, these things happen.  Usually to bad people like you.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧这些事情都发生了。 通常这些也是来自于像你这样的坏人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Shut up, shut up, shut up!  Leave me alone you big mean toe licker!</Source>
      <Dest>闭嘴！闭嘴！闭嘴！离我远点你这又大又贱的马屁精！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eh, not right now.  Ask me later.</Source>
      <Dest>现在不行。晚点再问我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eh, not right now.  Ask me later.</Source>
      <Dest>现在不行。晚点再问我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll have whatever you're havin'.</Source>
      <Dest>你所有的东西都会是我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nope.  I got everything I need right here.</Source>
      <Dest>不。这儿有我所需要的一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nothin' Cap'n.  Just some time to myself will do.</Source>
      <Dest>没什么，头儿。我只需要一个人待会就行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thanks Cap'n, but I'm fine.</Source>
      <Dest>船长，谢谢你，但我很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll have whatever you're havin'.</Source>
      <Dest>你所有的东西都会是我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nope.  I got everything I need right here.</Source>
      <Dest>不。这儿有我所需要的一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nothin' Cap'n.  Just some time to myself will do.</Source>
      <Dest>没什么，头儿。我只需要一个人待会就行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thanks Cap'n, but I'm fine.</Source>
      <Dest>船长，谢谢你，但我很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, I been thinking. I'm good with a dagger. Great, even.</Source>
      <Dest>对，我想过了，我会耍匕首。而且，对此很在行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could hit a dartwing with a throwing knife from twenty paces and I can skin a Skeever in seconds flat. </Source>
      <Dest>我可以在二十步开外用飞刀击中飞鸟，也可以干干脆脆地在一秒内剥下雪鼠的皮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But that int gonna do much against a Dragon, or an ogre, or a giant, or them Centaurs they got in High Rock. </Source>
      <Dest>但要对付一头龙，或者一头食人魔，或者一头巨人，或者在高岩省那儿发现的半人马，这点小伎俩是不够的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>While I'm here, is there anything you need?</Source>
      <Dest>反正我已经在这了，你需要什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I want you to show me how to use a sword and shield, so I can grow up to be like a hero...the Champion of Tamriel!</Source>
      <Dest>我希望你能教我使用剑和盾的技巧，那样我长大以后就能成为英雄……成为泰姆瑞尔的守护者!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't you get lonely?</Source>
      <Dest>你难道不寂寞吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you're one of them bleedin' hearts I pinch septims from all the time, then? </Source>
      <Dest>所以你也是那些“大善人”之一？我经常从他们那儿榨钱。所以呢？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't you get lonely?</Source>
      <Dest>你难道不寂寞吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I got my stabber, my wits and all my fingers. I don't get lonesome.</Source>
      <Dest>我有我的匕首，聪慧和手艺。我从不孤单。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, do you know how to play? I could teach you, if you'd like?</Source>
      <Dest>喔，你知道怎么玩吗？我可以教你，有兴趣吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's ok. I know a bit already and I'll pick up the rest quick enough.</Source>
      <Dest>就这样。我已经了解了这个计划，我很快会付诸实施的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry for your loss. I'll leave you alone for a while.</Source>
      <Dest>对你的损失我深感抱歉。我会让你独自呆会儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait.  I din't wanna ask but... I was gonna go down to the docks by the fishery.</Source>
      <Dest>等等。我不是有意要问的但是……我也差点要去渔场旁边的船坞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry for your loss. I'll leave you alone for a while.</Source>
      <Dest>对你的损失我深感抱歉。我会让你独自呆会儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ma always used to like sitting down there with her feet in the water.  Maybe you can join me, if...if you feel like it.</Source>
      <Dest>Ma always used to like sitting down there with her feet in the water.  Maybe you can join me, if...if you feel like it.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well from the sound of it she was a useless Skooma fiend anyway. Good riddance.</Source>
      <Dest>那么从它的声音，她是一个毫无用处的斯库玛恶魔。太好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, shut up, you dung slinging mudcrab lover. What do you know? </Source>
      <Dest>噢，闭嘴，你这个抛粪泥蟹爱好者。你懂什么？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That sounds fair.  But do you know how to play?</Source>
      <Dest>那听起来很公平，但你知道如何加入吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A bit. Ma used to play, sometimes and I pick up stuff quick. And hey, maybe one day I'll sing tales o' your heroic adventures.</Source>
      <Dest>会一点儿。以前都是妈妈弹琴的，有些时候也会换我来弹，我学得很快的。嘿，也许有一天我会把你的英雄事迹当歌来唱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not live at the Orphanage?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么不住在孤儿院呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I heard the lady that runs it is a Hagraven who gobbles up stupid children.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说那个跑掉的女人是个乌鸦鬼婆，她专门吃那些愚蠢的小孩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not live at the Orphanage?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么不住在孤儿院呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>'Sides, no-one would want to adopt a dirty guttersnipe with broken teeth and blood under her nails. Not with the likes of cute, sweet Runa around.</Source>
      <Dest>想要领养一个满口破牙，指甲里带血的脏兮兮的流浪儿，反倒不喜欢身边甜蜜可爱的卢娜？这种人根本不存在吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Calm down, girl. Tell me, what does your father look like?</Source>
      <Dest>镇定，姑娘，告诉我你父亲长什么样?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, he's got red hair, like me. And a big bushy beard!  Oh, won't you help me find him?</Source>
      <Dest>呃，他有一头红发，跟我一样。还有浓密的大胡子！哦，你能帮我找到他吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I own a Dwarven style house in Markarth called Vlindrel Hall.</Source>
      <Dest>我在马卡斯城有一套矮人风格的豪宅，名叫林德尔会堂.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I never seen Markarth before.  I hope they got skeevers there.</Source>
      <Dest>我以前从未见过马卡斯城。我希望这儿也有雪鼠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have a house in Whiterun.  The carriage driver can take you.</Source>
      <Dest>我在白漫城有个房子。马车夫可以载你去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I been to Whiterun a few times before Ma passed. I know my way around.</Source>
      <Dest>I been to Whiterun a few times before Ma passed. I know my way around.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you manage to keep fed?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么想办法填饱肚子的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You jokin'? There'll always be that stinker of a fool ready to pat my head and lose their purse.</Source>
      <Dest>你在开玩笑？每天总会有那么一两个臭气熏天的傻瓜拍拍我的头然后弄丢他们的钱包的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you manage to keep fed?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么想办法填饱肚子的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or a fellow sneaky type wantin' the freshest news that's trickled down inta the gutter. </Source>
      <Dest>或者一个鬼鬼祟祟的家伙想打听点贫民区流传的最新小道消息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you manage to keep fed?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么想办法填饱肚子的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when fools is short, there's always skeevers to eat. Cook up nice with a touch of pilfered garlic or a dab of lifted lavender.</Source>
      <Dest>食物短缺的时候总会有雪鼠可以吃。做的时候加一些偷来的大蒜和一小捏薰衣草那就完美了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you manage to keep fed?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么想办法填饱肚子的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lotsa skeevers in the Warrens. I don't like it down there, though. Full of crazies and some mage type who sets my spine a-tingling.</Source>
      <Dest>贫民窟里有很多雪鼠。虽然我并不喜欢那鬼地方。那里装满了能让我脊背发凉的疯子和法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hold on a second. I'm not going to rat you out. I just want to talk.</Source>
      <Dest>等一下。我不会出卖你，我只是想谈一谈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sounds like you're stallin' till a guard walks past and nabs me. Why risk it? What's in it fer me?</Source>
      <Dest>听起来就像你犯了罪但我这个路人却被当了替罪羊。为啥要冒这个险？这么做对我有啥好处呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yeah, you'd think at least the nobles would know better than to live here.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，你会觉得比起住在这儿，至少贵族更明白事理。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, and I mostly steal from the richies. Stupid merchants or lovers swaggerin' by with fat purses ripe for the picking. </Source>
      <Dest>是啊，我大多数时候只偷富人。从那些愚蠢的商人和穿着时髦的恋人们身上总能捞出很多油水来。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a matter of fact, I have a home right here in Riften. Honeyside.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，我在裂谷城有一个叫甜蜜湾的家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, I know the place!  I stole some enchanted pants from there once. Not to worry, though, I'll leave your riches alone.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我知道地方了！我曾在那儿偷了几条附过魔的裤子。不过别担心，我不会动你的东西的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not skilled in melee combat.  But I could bring you some books on it.</Source>
      <Dest>我不擅长肉搏，不过我可以给你带来一些相关书籍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I int much for reading. But thanks for the thought. Maybe you're not such a daedra-toucher, after all.</Source>
      <Dest>不啦，我不太识字。谢谢你的好意。看来你也不一定就是个信仰魔族的家伙.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Lie) I'm not skilled in melee combat.  Go read a book on it.</Source>
      <Dest>（撒谎）我不擅长近战。还需要多加学习。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I int much for reading. But thanks for the thought. Maybe you're not such a daedra-toucher, after all.</Source>
      <Dest>不啦，我不太识字。谢谢你的好意。看来你也不一定就是个信仰魔族的家伙.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like to help, but I need you to be more specific.</Source>
      <Dest>我愿意帮忙，但是我需要你更具体一些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Um, he's got a scar on his chin shaped like a star...and a big fat belly!</Source>
      <Dest>嗯, 他下巴有道伤痕，形状如同星星...对了,还有个啤酒肚！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Olette, I'm so sorry.</Source>
      <Dest>欧列特,我很抱歉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I already knew, in a way. It's just strange to...really know it, no question.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经了解了，某种程度上。只是还有点奇怪……呃，真的懂了！没有问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where are your parents?</Source>
      <Dest>你的父母呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Pa was a sailor with a kid in every port from Seyda Neen to Stros M'Kai.  One of them ports is Windhelm, and one of them kids is me.</Source>
      <Dest>我的爸爸是名水手，他跟一个孩子一起，从西达尼恩那边每一个港口往斯图尔斯·迈凯来回穿梭。其中的一个港口在风舵城，而那个孩子就是我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where are your parents?</Source>
      <Dest>你的父母呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ma's a skooma fiend.  She likes to go where the skooma is. One day she went off into the Ratways to get her some more and never came back. </Source>
      <Dest>妈妈是个瘾君子。哪里有斯库玛哪里就有她。自从她某天去鼠道想给自己找些斯库玛后，我就再也没见过她了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where are your parents?</Source>
      <Dest>你的父母呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Probably murdered for the clink she had on her.  Or maybe it was the skooma that done her in.  Don't matter all that much to me.</Source>
      <Dest>或许是她身上那些叮当作响的东西让她被害，又或者是那些斯库玛葬送了她。对我来说这没什么区别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where are your parents?</Source>
      <Dest>你的父母呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If she showed up here tomorrow right as rain I'd spit right in her face and tell her to go kiss a deadroth. I take care of myself.</Source>
      <Dest>如果她明天毫发无伤地出现在这里，我会直接啐在她脸上然后叫她去亲吻尸鬼。我会照顾好自己的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, I think I saw him over by the Pawned Prawn. Yeah, that's it. Good day.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，我想我看到他经过典当小虾。对，就这些。再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?  Do you mind heading on over there to see?  Pa can be really scary sometimes, and I don't want to go in alone.</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗？你能替我去那边看看吗？爸爸有时候很可怕，我不想自己去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, I think I saw him over by the Pawned Prawn. Yeah, that's it. Good day.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，我想我看到他经过典当小虾。对，就这些。再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just head on over there, I'll be right behind you.</Source>
      <Dest>Just head on over there, I'll be right behind you.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, I think I saw him over by the Pawned Prawn. Yeah, that's it. Good day.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，我想我看到他经过典当小虾。对，就这些。再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?  Do you mind heading on over there to see?  Pa can be really scary sometimes, and I don't want to go in alone.</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗？你能替我去那边看看吗？爸爸有时候很可怕，我不想自己去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, I think I saw him over by the Pawned Prawn. Yeah, that's it. Good day.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，我想我看到他经过典当小虾。对，就这些。再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just head on over there, I'll be right behind you.</Source>
      <Dest>Just head on over there, I'll be right behind you.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't think I didn't notice that.  If you needed money you had only to ask.</Source>
      <Dest>不要认为我没有注意到。如果你需要钱，你只有去请求。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Notice what?  I don't need money.  I told you Pa has a big belly and he keeps me fed.  You need to get your eyes checked Cap'n.</Source>
      <Dest>注意到了吗？我不需要钱。我告诉过你老爹有的是资产，他来养我。头儿，我觉得你得检查检查眼睛去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't think I didn't notice that.  If you needed money you had only to ask.</Source>
      <Dest>不要认为我没有注意到。如果你需要钱，你只有去请求。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Seems to me you're just a big bully harassing some poor kid.  Maybe you tried to kidnap me and I stuck you where the sun don't shine.</Source>
      <Dest>在我看来你只是个敲诈可怜孩子的混蛋。你也许可以试试来勒索我然后我会把你钉死在永无天日的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't think I didn't notice that.  If you needed money you had only to ask.</Source>
      <Dest>不要认为我没有注意到。如果你需要钱，你只有去请求。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or you can let me slip off without a fuss and we'll be as merry as a Midyear mornin'.</Source>
      <Dest>或者你可以毫无抱怨地让我离开，然后我们俩都能非常愉快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Excuse me sera, have you seen my pa? We was trading at the market stalls and then he was gone and I can't find him!</Source>
      <Dest>先生，打扰了，请问你看见过我的父亲吗？我们本来是在商亭那边做生意的，但他突然离开了然后我就找不到他了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?  What is it now?  Talk ain't cheap, Cap'n.</Source>
      <Dest>什么？那么现在呢？要从我嘴里套出话来可没那么简单哦，头儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So. Ma. I....don't really know what to say. Most of the time you was gobbling up Skooma or getting drunk at the Bee and Barb or pining over papa. </Source>
      <Dest>所以，妈妈，我……真的不知道该说什么。大部分时间你都在嗑斯库玛，或是在蜂与钩买醉，要么就是在想着爸爸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But...there was other times too. So I guess I should talk about them. I remember how you used to read me stories about the Champion of Cyrodiil...</Source>
      <Dest>可……还有其他时间。所以我想我应该聊聊别的。我记得你是怎么给我读赛瑞迪尔守护者的故事的……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And how you'd make me dance with you at the Bee and Barb when the bard started chirping about some hero or another. I was so embarrassed. </Source>
      <Dest>那当时在蜂与钩旅馆有吟游诗人唱那个英雄之歌的时候你怎么让我跟你跳舞来着？我当时真是好尴尬啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it was fun, really....And I remember you used to call me Little Dartwing. That was nice. So thanks...for all that stuff. Rest easy, Ma.</Source>
      <Dest>但这挺有趣的，真的……而且我想起你过去老叫我小鸟呢，挺不错的。谢谢……你所做的一切。安息吧，妈妈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait a second...Hey! Did you swipe a gold piece from me?</Source>
      <Dest>等一下…嘿！你是不是从我这里偷了块黄金碎片？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't know what you're blabbering about, Cap'n. But if I was you, I'd keep my lips shut.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道你在说啥，头儿。但我要是你，我就闭嘴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait a second...Hey! Did you swipe a gold piece from me?</Source>
      <Dest>等一下…嘿！你是不是从我这里偷了块黄金碎片？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Noisy people get stuck before sound passes their lips.  And the thing that sticks ya?  It slips right back inta the gutter unseen.</Source>
      <Dest>Noisy people get stuck before sound passes their lips.  And the thing that sticks ya?  It slips right back inta the gutter unseen.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait a second...Hey! Did you swipe a gold piece from me?</Source>
      <Dest>等一下…嘿！你是不是从我这里偷了块黄金碎片？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or you can let me slip off without a fuss and we'll be merry as a Midyear mornin'.</Source>
      <Dest>或者你可以让我不慌不忙地离开，那么我们将会像年中的清晨一样轻松愉快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right, that was my plan.  And it worked.  Guards! Guards!  A thief!</Source>
      <Dest>你说的都对，这就是我的主意，现在成功了。卫兵！卫兵！这里有贼！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Guards!  Guards!  A kidnapper!  See?  You don't want to play that game Cap'n. </Source>
      <Dest>守卫！守卫！有绑架犯！看见了吗头儿？你不会想加入这游戏的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right, that was my plan.  And it worked.  Guards! Guards!  A thief!</Source>
      <Dest>你说的都对，这就是我的主意，现在成功了。卫兵！卫兵！这里有贼！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How about we make a deal?  I help you in exchange for the clink.  A few hushed words from a little bird.</Source>
      <Dest>作笔交易如何？给我点金币，我就闭嘴不说话了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What kind of father fills his belly and leaves his malnourished child at home?</Source>
      <Dest>什么样的父亲才会将面黄肌瘦的孩子留在家里而只填饱自己？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, pa's always drinking and coming home late.  Maybe he's over at the inn.  But urchin's like me in't allowed inside.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，爸爸总是喝酒然后很晚才回家。也许他在旅馆里。但是像我这样的淘气鬼却进不了那里。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What kind of father fills his belly and leaves his malnourished child at home?</Source>
      <Dest>什么样的父亲才会将面黄肌瘦的孩子留在家里而只填饱自己？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just head on over there, I'll be right behind you.</Source>
      <Dest>Just head on over there, I'll be right behind you.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What kind of father fills his belly and leaves his malnourished child at home?</Source>
      <Dest>什么样的父亲才会将面黄肌瘦的孩子留在家里而只填饱自己？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, pa's always drinking and coming home late.  Maybe he's over at the inn.  But urchin's like me ain't allowed inside.</Source>
      <Dest>恩啊，爸爸总是在外面鬼混，喝酒喝到很晚还不回家。也许他就在那家酒馆里。但像我这样的孩子却进不去那里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What kind of father fills his belly and leaves his malnourished child at home?</Source>
      <Dest>什么样的父亲才会将面黄肌瘦的孩子留在家里而只填饱自己？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just head on over there, I'll be right behind you.</Source>
      <Dest>Just head on over there, I'll be right behind you.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What will you do now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在有什么打算？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I dunno.  Ma's in a better place, but I ain't.  Beggar's Row ain't exactly the best of it.  </Source>
      <Dest>我不知道。妈妈在一个更棒的地方，但我不是。乞丐的平房并不完全是最好的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you sleep in the same hovel as the rest of the gutter trash.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你和其他贫民渣滓睡在同一个茅屋里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right as rain, cap'n.  I got me a bedroll right by the fire in Beggars Row.  Would be aces if Edda didn't snore.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，头儿。我在乞丐的平房的火堆边找到了个铺位，只要无视艾达的鼾声那地方就简直完美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem at peace.</Source>
      <Dest>你看起来很平静。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah. I...I just...I just needed to say goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>是的我……我就……就想说句再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you sure it was her? There are a lot of people down in the Ratways.</Source>
      <Dest>你确定那是她？ 在鼠道死了好多人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sure, alright.  She always wore a ring that papa gave her to charm her into bed.  It was on the corpse.</Source>
      <Dest>我很确定，没错。她总是戴着一个戒指，那个戒指是爸爸为了把她骗上床而送给她的。戒指还在尸体上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you sure it was her? There are a lot of people down in the Ratways.</Source>
      <Dest>你确定那是她？ 在鼠道死了好多人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Always thought he'd come back and we'd be a proper family. Stupid.</Source>
      <Dest>我还指望着能见到她回来，一家人团聚呢。我可真够傻的啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't have time for this. Just don't let me catch your hand on my purse again.</Source>
      <Dest>我时间紧迫。只要别在扒窃的时候再让我抓到你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okey-dokey cap'n.  Next time you won't catch me.  Thief's honor.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，头儿。下次你就抓不住我了。赌上盗贼的荣誉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't you come and live with me?  I could take care of you.</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你不来跟我住一块儿呢？我可以照顾你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But...I barely know you.  That would just be weird.  Thanks but no thanks, cap'n.  I'll take my chances in the gutter.</Source>
      <Dest>但……我跟你完全不熟。这可有点儿奇怪。谢啦，但还是免了，老大。我还是在小河沟里碰碰运气吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't want to rush this decision. Let me think about it.</Source>
      <Dest>我不想武断决定。让我好好想想。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright cap'n.  Beggar's Row it is then.</Source>
      <Dest>没问题，头儿。那就乞丐的平房吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sorry, I haven't seen him.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉，我没有见过他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fine.  Stupid skeever brain.</Source>
      <Dest>行吧你。跟雪耗子一样智商堪忧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sorry, I haven't seen him.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉，我没有见过他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fine.  Stupid skeever brain.</Source>
      <Dest>行吧你。跟雪耗子一样智商堪忧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, I'm a rogue with a large estate and I wouldn't mind having an understudy.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我是个富有的泼皮，我并不介意找个替身。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You mean it, Cap'n?  I always wanted to train under an adventurer! Well, a master thief first, but an adventurer second!</Source>
      <Dest>你是认真的吗，头儿？ 我一直想在冒险家门下受训呢，呃，应该是先是大师级盗贼，然后才是冒险家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, I'm a rogue with a large estate and I wouldn't mind having an understudy.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我是个富有的泼皮，我并不介意找个替身。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I got one condition.  My pa was a sailor, and we always moved from place to place.  I hated it.  So wherever it is, I'm there to stay.</Source>
      <Dest>但是我有个麻烦。我爸爸是一个水手，我们总是在不同的地方搬来搬去，我很讨厌这一点。所以说不管是哪个地方，能够让我定居下来就好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Windstad Manor, my home in Hjaalmarch.</Source>
      <Dest>风临馆，我在希雅陲领的家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A manor? Oh, well how fancy. Not to worry though, I'll leave your riches alone.</Source>
      <Dest>一处庄园？噢，好棒。不要担心，我会离你的财产远远儿的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lakeview Manor in Falkreath.</Source>
      <Dest> 福瑞克斯的观湖山庄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A manor? Oh, well how fancy. Not to worry though, I'll leave your riches alone.</Source>
      <Dest>一处庄园？噢，好棒。不要担心，我会离你的财产远远儿的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I own a manor in the Pale called Heljarchen Hall.</Source>
      <Dest>我在苍原领有座庄园，叫勇士堑山庄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A manor? Oh, well how fancy. Not to worry though, I'll leave your riches alone.</Source>
      <Dest>一处庄园？噢，好棒。不要担心，我会离你的财产远远儿的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could adopt you. I always have need of a squire with an ear for gossip.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以收养你。我一直需要一个收集情报的侍从。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That makes sense. You want the word around town while you're off heroing.  In that case, I'm your mole.</Source>
      <Dest>That makes sense. You want the word around town while you're off heroing.  In that case, I'm your mole.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could adopt you. I always have need of a squire with an ear for gossip.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以收养你。我一直需要一个收集情报的侍从。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I got one condition.  My pa was a sailor, and we always moved from place to place.  I hated it.  So wherever it is, I'm there to stay.</Source>
      <Dest>但是我有个麻烦。我爸爸是一个水手，我们总是在不同的地方搬来搬去，我很讨厌这一点。所以说不管是哪个地方，能够让我定居下来就好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about Riften.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于裂谷城的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Riften is a stinkhole full to burstin' with suckers of all kinds. </Source>
      <Dest>裂谷城是一个被各式各样的杂种塞爆的臭泥坑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about Riften.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于裂谷城的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You got the lovers comin' in all trussed up to get 'trothed at the Temple giggling like maids.</Source>
      <Dest>在这里本应被捆进神庙宣誓忠贞的娼妇笑得就像纯洁的少女。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about Riften.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于裂谷城的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You got the guards who don't know a dog from a dragon, and the city folk who seem to want to get robbed blind.</Source>
      <Dest>你会见识到从狗到龙啥事儿都不知道的守卫，和排着队赶着被打劫的市民</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't you want more from your life than that?</Source>
      <Dest>你不想要比这更好的生活吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whatcha want to hear?  That I wanna be a big famous adventurer or some wailin' bard crooning for the Jarl of Solitude?  Those are stupid kid dreams.</Source>
      <Dest>你想听到什么？我想成为着名的冒险家或者那种为了独孤城领主而哭泣低吟的吟游诗人？那些都是蠢孩子们的梦想。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where's a good place to spend the night?</Source>
      <Dest>哪儿能找到个好地方过夜啊？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Haelga's had half the town 'neath her sheets, from what I hear. So head to her Bunkhouse if that's what you're after.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说城里一半的人都住过哈尔嘉那里。如果你在找地方的话就去她的工坊吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me something about the townsfolk.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲那些村民的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That Mara priestess, Jade? Well, she in't as behaved as a priestess oughta be. Picked more than a few pockets in her time.</Source>
      <Dest>那个玛拉的女祭司，玉洁？好吧，她看起来真不像是一个女祭司。她在当职的时候可“捡了”不少东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me something about the townsfolk.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲那些村民的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mjoll caught me pinching her pockets once.</Source>
      <Dest>我有次在掏穆月尔的口袋时被她发现了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me something about the townsfolk.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲那些村民的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thought I were in fer it, but she give me a gold piece and told me to get some food. Just like that. Talk to her if yer needin' a strong arm.</Source>
      <Dest>我还以为我要完蛋了，但她给我一个金币让我去买些吃的。就像那样. 如果你需要好帮手就和她说说吧.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Care to give a traveler some advice?</Source>
      <Dest>对给一个旅行者一些建议这点很介意？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't die all lonesome! Buy flowers from Yushari! And tell her I sent you.</Source>
      <Dest>不要孤独终老！从攸雪瑞那儿买点花！然后告诉她是我叫你过去的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Care to give a traveler some advice?</Source>
      <Dest>对给一个旅行者一些建议这点很介意？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The market stalls are an easy target, if you're itching for sumthin' to pinch.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你急于偷些什么的话，可以去市场的摊位下手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Care to give a traveler some advice?</Source>
      <Dest>对给一个旅行者一些建议这点很介意？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Thieves Guild have Shadowmarks all over the city. Gnives told me all about them.</Source>
      <Dest>整座城里到处都是盗贼公会的暗影标记，奈福斯跟我说起过他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me something about the townsfolk.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲那些村民的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hear Runa Fair-Shield has ataxia.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说卢娜·平盾患了运动失调症。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me something about the townsfolk.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲那些村民的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you want a laugh, go see Dirassi at Mistveil Keep and tell her you got Brain Rot.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你想笑一笑，就去雾隐塔楼找迪菈希，然后告诉她你得了脑残病。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hear Sadrin's got a problem with his man bits.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说萨汀和她的男人之间稍微有点儿矛盾？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me something about the townsfolk.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲那些村民的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you need a hand there's usually a smug Breton mage for hire hanging about in The Bee and Barb.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你需要帮手的话，有一个自命不凡的布莱顿法师经常在“蜂与钩”里闲逛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where can I find a strong companion?</Source>
      <Dest>我去哪儿找个强壮的跟班呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sapphire don't talk much about her past, but I know all about it and it's not for me to tell.</Source>
      <Dest>蓝宝石很少谈及她的过去，但我全都知道，不过那并不是我该谈论的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me something about the townsfolk.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲那些村民的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The beggars say that Wylandriah is a strange one.</Source>
      <Dest>The beggars say that Wylandriah is a strange one.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the word around town?</Source>
      <Dest>城里有什么传闻吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I heard a few whispers about some Skooma dealers in a warehouse on the outskirts of the city. Feel free to go kill 'em.</Source>
      <Dest>我在城外郊区的一座仓库里听到过一些斯库玛贩子的谈话。如果要杀了他们，那请随意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the word around town?</Source>
      <Dest>城里有什么传闻吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's some mad Khajiit running about the place called Maiq. He wanted to know if I had any calipers. What's calipers?</Source>
      <Dest>一个叫麦奎的脑子不大正常的虎人在经营那个地方。他想知道我有没有带卡钳。卡钳是啥？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any new rumors or gossip?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么新的流言或消息么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's my Ma.  I found her body down in the Warrens.</Source>
      <Dest>是我母亲。我在贫民窟找到了她的遗体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You look a little down, is all.</Source>
      <Dest>你看起来有点不高兴,是吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okey-dokey, Cap'n.</Source>
      <Dest>没问题，老大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've decided on where you should live.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经决定了你应该呆在哪里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What kind of freak are you?  No thanks, cap'n.  I'm not gonna end up being gobbled up by some daedra toucher. </Source>
      <Dest>你是什么怪胎吗？不，还是算了，头儿。我才不想被某些魔族接触者活活吞掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You ought to live with me, little girl.  We can be best friends.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该跟我在一起, 小女孩.  我们能够成为最好的朋友.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, you're new here, right?  How about some clink in exchange for the news?  A few hushed words from a little bird.</Source>
      <Dest>等等，你是新来的，对吗？付点小钱交换点小道消息怎么样？听听可怜的小鸟的小请求吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nothing, you filthy urchin. Get out of here before I call the guards.</Source>
      <Dest>你这个肮脏的家伙！在我叫守卫之前从这里滚出去！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha. Keep that to yerself or fine upstandin' citizens will start checking you for wolfy bits.</Source>
      <Dest>哈。你自己最好保守好自己的小秘密，否则让正直的公民发现到你的小狼牙的话，看你怎么办。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I prefer my Skeevers raw and bloody, personally.</Source>
      <Dest>就个人而言，我更喜欢宰掉我的雪鼠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, well, neither can I. I do what I have to to get by. </Source>
      <Dest>是的，呃，我也不行。但我会尽我所能的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They're trying to build a life.  People can't just up and leave.</Source>
      <Dest>他们正尝试着生活下去，人不能总是置身事外。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not everyone gets to snuggle up in their warm beds with Mama and Papa reading them some foolish story 'bout heroes and maidens and loincloths.</Source>
      <Dest>不是每个人都能在温暖的床上依偎着爸爸妈妈读一些愚蠢的英雄和少女的故事的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They're trying to build a life.  People can't just up and leave.</Source>
      <Dest>他们正尝试着生活下去，人不能总是置身事外。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you want fer it?</Source>
      <Dest>你想要啥？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here.  Have a gold piece.</Source>
      <Dest>拿着，一个金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fair trade Cap'n.  Fer a few clink I'll sing like a sparrow. So whaddaya want?</Source>
      <Dest>公平的交易，头儿。只要一点小钱让我去学麻雀唱歌我也能接受。所以你想要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A septim or two, to get you a few meals, if I like what you say.</Source>
      <Dest>一两个金币，拿去买点吃的，如果你说话我爱听的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Course. A good bit of information nets me a nice deal more than some old stolen plates or a pair of pilfered pants.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。对我来说有用的消息比一堆偷来的盘子或者旧裤子来的更好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A lot of people come to you for rumors, then?</Source>
      <Dest>很多人因为这谣言来找你，然后呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh....Alright then.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，那好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maybe another time.</Source>
      <Dest>也许下次吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, why are you talkin' to me then, Cap'n?  There's hero stuff that needs doin', like saving a defenseless salmon from a dragon or summat. </Source>
      <Dest>呃，你为什么要跟我说呢，头儿？这些都是英雄才该做的事业，像是从龙口拯救一条无法自保的大马哈鱼啥的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This city needs a hero.  I'm going to clean this place up.</Source>
      <Dest>这个城市需要一个英雄，我准备清理一下这地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I've been looking after your bits and chasing off the Skeevers and things.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会帮你看管你的马嚼子并且帮你赶跑那些雪鼠或者其他别的什么东西的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you adjusting to life here?</Source>
      <Dest>你在这过的怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I was thinkin' maybe it'd be fair if you got me a lute for a job well done. </Source>
      <Dest>但我觉得，作为工作完美结束的奖赏，你给我把鲁特琴还比较公平。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you adjusting to life here?</Source>
      <Dest>你在这过的怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean....I'd just steal one, but they're too big to secret out of someone's house under my skirts.</Source>
      <Dest>我的意思是…我刚刚偷了一个，但是那东西太大了，以至于我不能把它藏在我的裙子底下，悄悄带出屋子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are you adjusting to life here?</Source>
      <Dest>你在这过的怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thanks. And if I can't get the hang of it, I can always use it to bash bandits with.</Source>
      <Dest>谢了。如果我玩不明白这东西，我也可以用它来揍揍土匪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here.  Have this lute.</Source>
      <Dest>给你，拿着这把鲁特琴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, what are you 'tending to do about it, hmm? Holler fer the guards? </Source>
      <Dest>所以,，你准备怎么 “照顾”它，哼？ 叫上一堆守卫吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you're going to try to steal from me, you'd better improve your technique.</Source>
      <Dest>想从我这儿偷东西？回家再练两年吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll stick you before sound passes lips and slip right back inta the gutter unseen. </Source>
      <Dest>那我就紧贴着你等你话一出口的瞬间就溜进旁边的水沟踪影皆无。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you're going to try to steal from me, you'd better improve your technique.</Source>
      <Dest>想从我这儿偷东西？回家再练两年吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or you can let me slip off without a fuss and we'll be merry as a Midyear mornin'.</Source>
      <Dest>或者你可以让我不慌不忙地离开，那么我们将会像年中的清晨一样轻松愉快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you're going to try to steal from me, you'd better improve your technique.</Source>
      <Dest>想从我这儿偷东西？回家再练两年吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ain't that right. All I need is my stabber and a mind to tell me when ta use it. </Source>
      <Dest>难道不对吗。我所需要的只是我的匕首还有一个声音告诉我该怎样使用它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We can only rely on ourselves. Some fools take decades to learn that.</Source>
      <Dest>我们所能依靠的只有自己，有些白痴花了几十年才明白这一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I got me a bedroll right by the fire in Beggars Row.  Would be aces if Edda didn't snore.</Source>
      <Dest>我在乞丐的平房的火堆边找到了个铺位，只要无视艾达的鼾声那地方就简直完美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where do you sleep?</Source>
      <Dest>你在哪睡觉的来着？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I asked them sera, but the guards are mean and won't help.</Source>
      <Dest>I asked them sera, but the guards are mean and won't help.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm very busy, but you could ask one of the guards to assist you?</Source>
      <Dest>我很忙，你能找个卫兵帮你吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah?  He's creepy like that guy.  I ain't never seen his face though.  Then again, I can't see your friend's either.</Source>
      <Dest>是吗？他像那家伙一样让人毛骨悚然。虽然我没看到他的脸。话说回来，我也看不见你朋友的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My friend here is a mage type.</Source>
      <Dest>我这位朋友是法师类型的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Says you.  I mean, have ya seen his face?  'Cause you'd be the first.  I'm beginning to think he don't have one.</Source>
      <Dest>说你呢。我的意思是，你见过这个人吗？因为你是第一个。我开始在想他是不是真的没有脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dagri'lon?  He's harmless when you get to know him.</Source>
      <Dest>迪格隆？如果你深入了解他的话，你就会发现他人畜无害。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah. Dagri-sumthin. All the sneaks are 'fraid o him and I don't much like him either.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，就是那个瘦佬迪格。不管是哪种蛇看了他都绕道走，我也不怎么喜欢他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Some mage type?</Source>
      <Dest>一些法师式的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really? Brilliant! I'll be collectin' Daedroth teeth in no time.</Source>
      <Dest>真的？太棒了！我马上去收集恶魔的牙齿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright. It will do you good to be able to defend yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。能够自保对你来说还是有好处的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We came by boat to Windhelm, but I were too young to remember. I hear if you tug Ulfrics beard he lets out a Thu'um. </Source>
      <Dest>我们是乘船来到风舵城的，但我那时年纪太小，已经记不得啦。我听说如果你去拽乌佛瑞克的胡子的话，他就会发出吐目。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Windhelm's cold, but the homes are rather cozy.  We could live there.</Source>
      <Dest>风舵城是很冷，可家里很暖和的。我们可以住那儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You did that?  For me?  Um...thanks.</Source>
      <Dest>你做的？为了我而做的？呃...谢谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Raid) Rest in peace.  Know that I've avenged you, mother of Olette.</Source>
      <Dest>(突袭) 大仇已报，安息吧，欧列特的母亲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry cap'n.  I didn't come here for that.  I just came here to say goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉头儿，我不是出于这原因来而这的，我只是来这说声再见的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is no time for tears, girl.  Now is the time for vengeance.</Source>
      <Dest>没时间流泪，女孩。现在是时候复仇了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A manor? Oh, well how fancy. I always wanted to go to Solitude. Lots of pockets to pick. And that Bard's college!</Source>
      <Dest>一座庄园？哦，真棒。我一直想去独孤城。那儿有很多鼓鼓的腰包可以掏。还有吟游诗人学院！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ever been to Solitude?  I own a place there called Proudspire Manor.</Source>
      <Dest>去过独孤城吗？我在那儿有座房子叫豪塔别墅</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, stuff you, then. Who are you to tell me what I should be doing, anyway?</Source>
      <Dest>噢，快闭嘴吧。你以为你是谁，我需要你来告诉我该做什么么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The life of an adventurer is dangerous. You should focus on your studies.</Source>
      <Dest>冒险者的生活充满了危险，你还是专注于你的学业吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, alright. Thanks, I s'pose.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，好吧。我想……谢谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nothing. Just take it.</Source>
      <Dest>没什么，拿着就是了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know about that Cap'n, the thieving scum would be gone, but the regular scum would still be there.</Source>
      <Dest>那我可不知道，老大。偷东西的人渣可能会消失，不过普通的人渣还是会有的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If it weren't for thieving scum like you Riften would be a beautiful city.</Source>
      <Dest>如果没有你们这些小偷渣滓的话，裂谷城会是一个美好的城市.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I din't wanna ask. But I was gonna go down to the docks by the fishery. Ma always used to like sitting down there with her feet in the water.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有什么想问的。不过我会去趟渔场码头。妈妈过去经常坐在那儿并把她的双脚侵入水中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wish there was something I could do.  Do you need anything?</Source>
      <Dest>我希望我能做点什么。你需要什么吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source> You can join me, I guess. If you feel like it. </Source>
      <Dest> You can join me, I guess. If you feel like it. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wish there was something I could do.  Do you need anything?</Source>
      <Dest>我希望我能做点什么。你需要什么吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He beat me bloody and stole my riches. And then, then he was stupid enough to get caught! I wouldn'ta got caught.</Source>
      <Dest>他使我浑身浴血，他偷盗我的家资。这还不够，他竟然愚蠢到被抓住了！我本不想他被抓住的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You didn't feel bad for the boy?</Source>
      <Dest>你不为那男孩感到心疼吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't much do big jobs. I take what I need and most people here don't have much o value 'cept to themselves, anyway. </Source>
      <Dest>I don't much do big jobs. I take what I need and most people here don't have much o value 'cept to themselves, anyway. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the most expensive thing you've ever stolen?</Source>
      <Dest>你偷过最值钱的东西是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But this one time...some big time merchant came marchin' into the city, fat as anything, and behind him was a caravan full of all sorts of treasures.</Source>
      <Dest>But this one time...some big time merchant came marchin' into the city, fat as anything, and behind him was a caravan full of all sorts of treasures.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the most expensive thing you've ever stolen?</Source>
      <Dest>你偷过最值钱的东西是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I managed to pinch the biggest ruby you've ever seen from him while he was slobberin' all over the meats in the market and on Haelga's backside.</Source>
      <Dest>我试过向他勒索他那块大红宝石，就是你看到过的那块，就在他对着满市场的肉类包括哈尔嘉那对肥臀垂涎三尺的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the most expensive thing you've ever stolen?</Source>
      <Dest>你偷过最值钱的东西是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Woulda been made for life but one of the bigger boys knocked me into next Middas and took the gem.</Source>
      <Dest>本来是可以养家糊口的，但大个子中的一个把我敲进了旁边的密达斯中并且拿走了宝石。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the most expensive thing you've ever stolen?</Source>
      <Dest>你偷过最值钱的东西是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Big as a scrib it were, too... Still, the guards lopped off his head on the way out of the city so I don't feel too sore about it.</Source>
      <Dest>那东西就跟个巨蚁幼虫一边儿大……不过，守卫在出城的路上砍掉了他的脑袋，所以我对此没感觉多伤心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the most expensive thing you've ever stolen?</Source>
      <Dest>你偷过最值钱的东西是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Um, he's got a scar on his chin shaped like a star...and a big fat belly!</Source>
      <Dest>嗯, 他下巴有道伤痕，形状如同星星...对了,还有个啤酒肚！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright, girl.  What does he look like?</Source>
      <Dest>好的小姑娘。他长的什么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>G'bye then.</Source>
      <Dest>那么再见了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>See you later Cap'n.</Source>
      <Dest>一会见，老大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright then.</Source>
      <Dest>那好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't forget to bring home some more stuff.  We ain't never got enough.</Source>
      <Dest>别忘了给家里带点东西回来。我们还不怎么够用呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Need something?</Source>
      <Dest>有事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whatcha want?</Source>
      <Dest>Whatcha want?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah?</Source>
      <Dest>啊?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A skeever followed me home, so I made it into a stew. It's in the pot.</Source>
      <Dest>A skeever followed me home, so I made it into a stew. It's in the pot.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some slinkin' Khajiit snuck in to steal your spoils, so I chomped his finger off. He ran off, caterwaulin' like a humping horker.</Source>
      <Dest>Some slinkin' Khajiit snuck in to steal your spoils, so I chomped his finger off. He ran off, caterwaulin' like a humping horker.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A dragon was circling over the city today. I ran out the house with my stabber and it flew off.</Source>
      <Dest>今天早些时候，一条龙在城市上空盘旋。我抄了家伙跑出屋子，结果它就飞走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're back! Did you slay any dragons? Did you fight off a horde of naked Nords? What spoils did you bring back?</Source>
      <Dest>你回来了！你杀了龙没有？有没有干翻一群诺德裸男？有没有搞到点什么战利品？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I been practicing and practicing with my stabber. I think I'll be ready to come on an adventure soon.</Source>
      <Dest>我一直在练习使用我的匕首，我想不久之后我就可以准备好一次冒险了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you have a lute? I always wanted a lute. That int stupid, is it?</Source>
      <Dest>你有鲁特琴吗？我一直想要把鲁特琴。这很愚蠢，是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, I was thinking. What if them dragons has you fer dinner? Gods forbid, o course. But maybe I should be training to fight 'em. Just in case.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，我刚刚还想着……要是你被那些龙叼去当晚餐了怎么办？哎呀不是冒犯你。不过也许我确实得学学怎么跟它们周旋。大概有必要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If the guards come round askin' about me, tell 'em I was with you last Fredas. Far from the market stalls.</Source>
      <Dest>If the guards come round askin' about me, tell 'em I was with you last Fredas. Far from the market stalls.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Someone came by with this for you. Probably for some heroing you did.</Source>
      <Dest>有人送来这个给你。大概是因为你的什么英雄事迹吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A skeever followed me home, so I made it into a stew. It's in the pot.</Source>
      <Dest>A skeever followed me home, so I made it into a stew. It's in the pot.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was a vampire attack in the city while you was...away. I barred the door and stuffed garlic up the chimney.</Source>
      <Dest>当你……不在的时候，有一个吸血鬼攻击了城市。我挡住了门，将大蒜塞进了烟囱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I put some simple traps on the locks while you were away. Anyone pickin' at em will get a nasty surprise.</Source>
      <Dest>在你离开期间，我会在锁上设一些简单的陷阱。给任何想要打开它的人来个可怕的惊喜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A courier came by with a letter.  It was from Mjoll.  She wants to know if I was keeping out of trouble.</Source>
      <Dest>信使带来了一封穆月尔写的信。她想知道我是不是一直在惹麻烦呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A courier came by with a letter fer you. I threw it away.  It wasn't important.</Source>
      <Dest>一个信使给你带来信件，而我扔了它，因为显然那玩意没啥重要的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can you get some easier books? I been trying to learn how to read better. I found this one called 'The Lusty Argonian Maid' but it's too hard for me.</Source>
      <Dest>你能给我找些简单点的书吗？我一直学着怎么能好好读书。我发现这本书叫作“元气满满的亚龙人女仆”但对我来说它实在是太难了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One of the older boys told me that if I kissed a mudcrab it'd turn into a handsome knight, so I shoved his stupid lying face in the mud.</Source>
      <Dest>一个比我大的男孩儿告诉我，如果亲吻一只泥沼蟹的话，它就会变回一名英俊的骑士，所以我就把他的蠢脸按进了泥沼里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Beware, Beware, the Skeeverborn comes. With a dung wielding power of the ancient rat farts! Believe, Believe, the Skeeverborn comes...</Source>
      <Dest>当心啊当心啊，鼠裔归来。鼠粪力量附体，还有着远古的鼠屁之力！相信吧相信吧鼠裔已经归来……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I been practicing my curtsies and manners and speaking proper. All the easier to get closer to thee noble ladies and steal their jewels</Source>
      <Dest>我一直在练习我的屈膝礼，礼貌态度以及适当的言辞。这一切都是为了接近你这样高贵的女士，然后偷走她们的珠宝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Them housecarls sure complain a lot. I am swoooorn to carry your buuurdens!</Source>
      <Dest>那些侍卫肯定会抱怨满满。我已经宣～誓替你分～担一切。!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some shifty folk came round dressed as Stendarr priests. They said the house was haunted and it needs 'cleansin', but I know a thief when I see 'em.</Source>
      <Dest>一些狡猾的家伙装扮成斯丹纳尔祭司。他们说这房子闹鬼，需要“净化”，但我一看就知道他们是贼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One of them Thalmor types came knockin' on your door while you was away. I told em we was fine upstandin' citizens and we hate them Talos lovers.</Source>
      <Dest>当你不在的时候有一个梭默大使馆的人来敲你的门。我告诉他们我们是良好正直的公民而且我们讨厌那些塔洛斯崇拜者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I found this weird plant down by the river. Here.</Source>
      <Dest>我在河流下游找到这种怪植物。这儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ain't Imperials supposed to be good at chatter? I prefer to bash stuff, anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>帝国人不是只会耍嘴皮子吗？总之我更喜欢用拳头说话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't wait for the next burning of King Olaf.</Source>
      <Dest>我等不及要看下一次的火烧奥拉夫了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I heard that the Empire was full of wimpy bum kissers. What you doing with them?</Source>
      <Dest>我听说帝国人都是一群阿谀奸佞之人。你和他们在一起做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I snuck in to the bards college today. They make such pretty music.</Source>
      <Dest>我今天偷偷去了吟游诗人学院。他们演奏的音乐是如此动听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I like it in the Gray Quarter. Nobody there expects me to curtsy and say my pleases and thank you's and they let me sit in the New Gnisis Cornerclub.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢呆在灰色居住区，在那里没有人会希望我行屈膝礼然后说“我的荣幸”或“谢谢你”接着非得邀请我到新吉西斯角吧坐一坐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I went and pinched an arrow from Jorrvaskr today, just to see if I could.</Source>
      <Dest>我今天去月瓦斯卡顺了一支箭，就为了看看我能不能办到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This city is confusing. Perfect for losing guards.</Source>
      <Dest>This city is confusing. Perfect for losing guards.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Same old Riften. 'Cept now people notice I'm here. When I want them to.</Source>
      <Dest>Same old Riften. 'Cept now people notice I'm here. When I want them to.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm glad you joined them Stormcloaks. It seems like them Empire types all want to bow and scrape to some haughty elves. </Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴你加入了风暴斗篷。那些帝国的家伙可老在对那些傲慢的精灵点头哈腰啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think my stabber needs a new name. What about 'Skeeverbane!?!'</Source>
      <Dest>我想我的匕首需要一个新名字。“雪鼠之祸”怎么样！？！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One of the local girls showed me her doll.  I want one...to hide my stabber in.</Source>
      <Dest>一个当地的女孩儿给我看了她的布娃娃。我也想要一个玩偶……用来藏起我的匕首。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't use the cooking pot for a while. Gorr drank too much mead and peed in it.</Source>
      <Dest>暂时不要用这个锅. 戈尔喝太多蜜酒，然后尿在了里面.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gorr is teaching me how to burp like a warrior!</Source>
      <Dest>戈尔教我如何像战士一样的打饱嗝！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Raynes is nice. He kills the bad guys.</Source>
      <Dest>瑞纳斯棒极了。他杀了那些坏人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Zora showed me how to braid my hair. That should keep it out of my face when I'm slaying vampires.</Source>
      <Dest>佐拉给我演示了怎么扎头发。这样我在杀吸血鬼的时候它们就不会挡着我的脸了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Valgus says he'll help me with my reading.</Source>
      <Dest>威尔格斯说他会教导我读书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Have you seen Morndas in action? I'd challenge her to a lockpicking contest, but there aren't enough locks in the city.</Source>
      <Dest>你们看到过摩恩达丝行动过？我想向她发起一场开锁比赛，但是这城市连足够的锁都没有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I asked Isobel to forge me a new stabber.  She said daggers ain't toys.  You'll talk to her, won't you?</Source>
      <Dest>我让伊莎贝尔给我打造一把新锐器，她却说匕首不是玩具不能随便造。你会帮我去跟她说的对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did you marry for love?  'Cause I int sure your wife did.</Source>
      <Dest>你是为了爱情而结婚的吗？因为我肯定你妻子是这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So...can I have some?</Source>
      <Dest>所以……能给我一些吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Actually, I was gonna said that they look right stupid.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，我想说,他们看起来确实很蠢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No...maybe...I was lookin' at the pretty ladies down in the market and the paint they got on their face....</Source>
      <Dest>不…也许…我在看集市里貌美的姑娘和她们脸上的胭脂水粉…</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's okay.  I din't want it.</Source>
      <Dest>没关系。我不想要它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No.  Mebbie.   Shut up.</Source>
      <Dest>不，麦比，闭嘴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He's always covered in mud. And he tries to play wiv mudcrabs down by the river. They always try to pinch him. He's ok.</Source>
      <Dest>他总是像刚从泥巴堆里滚出来一样的。而且他还想在河边和河蟹们愉快地玩耍。它们总是想夹他。但他倒是没事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So some stink-faced boy gave me a sad bunch o flowers the other day. I dint know what to say.</Source>
      <Dest>前几天，一些臭着脸的男孩给了我一束糟糕的鲜花。我不知道该说什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, I killed a big fat one.  It bit me on the arm but I stuck it good.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，我宰了个又大又肥的。它咬我的胳膊被我狠狠地捅了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright...I'll keep at it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧...我会继续的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I in't getting it. I'm too stupid.</Source>
      <Dest>我没能得到它。我真的太蠢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That book you give me was too hard.</Source>
      <Dest>你给我的那本书实在太深奥了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I made it in the cooking pot, though. You might need to wash it out.</Source>
      <Dest>我用烹调罐做的。也许你需要洗一下它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I made up some poison for you. For bandit killing.</Source>
      <Dest>I made up some poison for you. For bandit killing.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, he was a stupid guard. I'm sick of hearing about his stupid knee.</Source>
      <Dest>Well, he was a stupid guard. I'm sick of hearing about his stupid knee.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry milady.  I couldn't help it.</Source>
      <Dest>万分抱歉，我的女士。我帮不上忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, maybe I had a bite.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，或许有我的一份。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No milady.  On my honor.</Source>
      <Dest>不，夫人。我发誓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eh, I don't need anyone but my stabber.  But if I did, I'd marry an adventurer, like you did with the Cap'n. </Source>
      <Dest>Eh, I don't need anyone but my stabber.  But if I did, I'd marry an adventurer, like you did with the Cap'n. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What about tomorrow?  Will I be old enough then?</Source>
      <Dest>明天又如何？我能等到那一天么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Isobel, you think you can forge me a sword?</Source>
      <Dest>伊莎贝尔, 你能帮我造把剑吗？</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
