<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And shall I be forced to wait until the end of the day as well? (Sigh) I will need to have a word with Urag regarding your training.</Source>
      <Dest>我还一定要等到今天的结束吗?哎，我还是得和乌拉葛谈谈关于你训练的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eleanor, the library is in disarray.  When books are strewn about here and there, it makes it impossible to determine if a book's been checked out.</Source>
      <Dest>艾莉诺，看看图书馆乱成什么样子了。书本随意散落在地上，这可没办法一一统计借出去的书啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And you say this chamber leads to the main hall?  Be ready, mages.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是你说的通向大厅的房间吗？做好准备，法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What you call destiny is a delusion, and I will prove it with your death.</Source>
      <Dest>你们称之为命运的东西不过是错觉而已，而我会用你们的死向你们证明这一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nelos!  It is time you answer for your crimes.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯！是时候为你的罪行付出代价了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dragonborn, I trust you know the way.</Source>
      <Dest>龙裔，我相信你知道如何做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mages!  Ready your wards!</Source>
      <Dest>法师！准备好你的结界！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And you say this chamber leads to the main hall?  Be ready, mages.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是你说的通向大厅的房间吗？做好准备，法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems the Radiant Dark were doing quite well for themselves.</Source>
      <Dest>似乎黑暗光辉们做的相当不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No doubt this tableau of riches is designed to soften unwitting mages, whether they be friend or foe.  </Source>
      <Dest>毫无疑问的是，无论这些精神错乱的法师们是友是敌，当下这笔财宝的景象是用来麻痹他们的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come, let us keep moving.  </Source>
      <Dest>来吧，我们继续前进。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What treachery is this!</Source>
      <Dest>这是何等糟糕的变节！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mercy?  I require no mercy, Nelos!  Only retribution!</Source>
      <Dest>Mercy?  I require no mercy, Nelos!  Only retribution!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nelos!</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will not lie.  The mage we face is one of the most dangerous I have ever known.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有说谎。我们面对的法师是我所知道的法师中最危险的一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet it is for that reason that he cannot be allowed to succeed.</Source>
      <Dest>然而这就是他不被允许成为继任者的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, I would be remiss if I said this was merely an act of duty.  </Source>
      <Dest>要是说这也是职责的话，那我还真是失职了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For all of you who have volunteered your service, at great personal risk...for your sacrifice, I am forever grateful.  Thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>你们所有人冒着极大的风险，无私地付出····你们做出的牺牲，我永远心存感激。谢谢你们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Excellent.  The four of us will depart for Pinefrost Tower at once.</Source>
      <Dest>好极了，我们四个人即刻前往松雾塔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My peers, if I may have your attention.</Source>
      <Dest>My peers, if I may have your attention.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My name is Olivia Meronin.  I am a former instructor at the Arcane University in Cyrodiil. </Source>
      <Dest>我的名字是奥莉薇雅·梅洛妮。我曾经是赛瑞迪尔奥数学院的一名导师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For the better part of my life, while others have toiled in personal research, I have devoted myself to the development of students such as yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>我生命中美好的时光，便是在他人醉心于其个人的研究探索时，我在全身心为像你一样的学生们创造光辉的未来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Had I chosen to do otherwise, I may have made new discoveries.  I could have achieved some personal acclaim.  Yet I do not regret a single day.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我当初改变一下做法的话，说不定我已经有了一些新的发现。没准还能变得小有名气。不过我到现在也没有后悔过一天。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, for the past ten years I have devoted my life to a different task.  To bringing justice to the mage who killed my father.  </Source>
      <Dest>在过去的10年里我一直投身于不同的任务中。为的是制裁那个杀害我父亲的法师。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am now arriving at the end of this pursuit.  It is all thanks to the one who stands beside me, the one you know as the Dragonborn.  </Source>
      <Dest>如今我触及了我所追求的顶端，这一切都要归功与在我身边一直支持着我的那个人，也就是被你们成为“龙裔”的人。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dragonborn, I trust you know the way.</Source>
      <Dest>龙裔，我相信你知道如何做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Excellent.  The five of us will depart for Pinefrost Tower at once.</Source>
      <Dest>好极了，我们五个人即刻前往松雾塔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If there are students of the college here, I demand your immediate attention.</Source>
      <Dest>要是这里有学院的学生，你得给我盯好他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My name is Olivia Meronin.  I am a former instructor at the Arcane University in Cyrodiil. </Source>
      <Dest>我的名字是奥莉薇雅·梅洛妮。我曾经是赛瑞迪尔奥数学院的一名导师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For the better part of my life, while others have toiled in personal research, I have devoted myself to the development of students.</Source>
      <Dest>我生命中美好的时光，便是在他人醉心于其个人的研究探索时，我在全身心为学生们创造光辉的未来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Had I chosen to do otherwise, I may have made new discoveries.  I could have achieved some personal acclaim.  Yet I do not regret a single day.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我当初改变一下做法的话，说不定我已经有了一些新的发现。没准还能变得小有名气。不过我到现在也没有后悔过一天。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, for the past ten years I have devoted my life to a different task.  To bringing justice to the mage who killed my father.  </Source>
      <Dest>在过去的10年里我一直投身于不同的任务中。为的是制裁那个杀害我父亲的法师。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am now arriving at the end of this pursuit.  It is all thanks to the one who stands beside me, the one you know as the Dragonborn.  </Source>
      <Dest>如今我触及了我所追求的顶端，这一切都要归功与在我身边一直支持着我的那个人，也就是被你们成为“龙裔”的人。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nevertheless, we are still in need of brave and able mages to accompany us in this final task.  Who among you will answer the call?</Source>
      <Dest>尽管如此，我们仍然需要有能力的勇敢法师们的协助，与我们共同面对最后的挑战。你们中有谁愿意加入我们？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Our business, however, is suspended for now, although I may need your assistance once more in the future.</Source>
      <Dest>关于你我的交易，虽然当下停止了，不过没准以后我还会需要你呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Whatever you say.</Source>
      <Dest>随你咋说.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let me again offer my sincerest thanks, on behalf of all mages, not just myself and Jadro'Ra.</Source>
      <Dest>让我再次代表所有的法师，而不仅仅是我和贾卓’拉，致以我最诚挚的感谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Whatever you say.</Source>
      <Dest>随你咋说.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The knowledge extracted from these texts may lead to great discoveries, and new frontiers.</Source>
      <Dest>从这些文献中摘录的知识可以带来重大的发现，甚至开拓出新的学术领域。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Whatever you say.</Source>
      <Dest>随你咋说.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Our business, however, is suspended for now, although I may need your assistance once more in the future.</Source>
      <Dest>关于你我的交易，虽然当下停止了，不过没准以后我还会需要你呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll do my best.</Source>
      <Dest>我会全力以赴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let me again offer my sincerest thanks, on behalf of all mages, not just myself and Jadro'Ra.</Source>
      <Dest>让我再次代表所有的法师，而不仅仅是我和贾卓’拉，致以我最诚挚的感谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll do my best.</Source>
      <Dest>我会全力以赴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The knowledge extracted from these texts may lead to great discoveries, and new frontiers.</Source>
      <Dest>从这些文献中摘录的知识可以带来重大的发现，甚至开拓出新的学术领域。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll do my best.</Source>
      <Dest>我会全力以赴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That you have.  I will have Urag get on rebinding the books immediately. In the meantime, I offer you this staff as a reward for your service.</Source>
      <Dest>就是它。我会让乌拉葛马上把这些残卷重新装订起来。此外，这样东西就送给你好了，作为你付出的回报吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It looks like I've recovered all the pages.</Source>
      <Dest>貌似所有的页面都集齐了 。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It has no celebrated history.  However, not all things powerful require such affectations, nor do they deprive you of the experience you have earned.</Source>
      <Dest>它的来历或许并不超凡。强大的物体并非一定要有虚伪浮夸的外表，也不会总是超脱于你丰富的阅历。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It looks like I've recovered all the pages.</Source>
      <Dest>貌似所有的页面都集齐了 。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Through these trials you have proven your ability as a mage is without peer, and for that reason your mission is not yet complete. </Source>
      <Dest>这些测试足以证明你拥有出类拔萃的法术才能，因此，天赋赋予你的使命也还未完成。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It looks like I've recovered all the pages.</Source>
      <Dest>貌似所有的页面都集齐了 。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For the knowledge and experience you have gained through this quest must be shared with your colleagues here at the College, so that all may benefit.</Source>
      <Dest>与你学院里的同学分享一下你在这次试炼中获得的宝贵知识和经验吧，这一定可以让大家受益终生的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It looks like I've recovered all the pages.</Source>
      <Dest>貌似所有的页面都集齐了 。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is unfortunate, but understandable.  Your shoulders are broad, yet you cannot carry the weight of the world.</Source>
      <Dest>令人遗憾，不过也可以理解。你的肩膀再强壮，也无法负担起世界的重量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, don't expect me to come saving you again.  I'm done.</Source>
      <Dest>好了，别指望我再救你了，我不干了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It would be a colossal failure on my part if I caused those shoulders to break.  So, if this is goodbye, I thank you.  For everything.</Source>
      <Dest>那是我工作的巨大失误导致我肩负着巨大的责任。好了，到了告别的时候了。谢谢你，谢谢你做的一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, don't expect me to come saving you again.  I'm done.</Source>
      <Dest>好了，别指望我再救你了，我不干了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An illusionist attacks the mind.  He plays the drums of courage and fear to convince both you and the bandits that they are invincible. </Source>
      <Dest>幻术直击人心。它可以在你和那群不可战胜的土匪之间鼓舞一方并恐惧另一方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about illusion mages.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲幻术法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Illusion can fool your eyes, become your heart's greatest desire, but it cannot fool all the senses, and that is where you will find truth.</Source>
      <Dest>幻觉可以欺骗你的双眼，满足你内心最强烈的欲望。但是它无法愚弄你的理智，用理智去寻求真相吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about illusion mages.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲幻术法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, the greatest illusion is not the product of any spell.  It is the doubt one has in the efficacy of Illusion magic.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，这个强烈的幻觉并不是任何法术的产物，这个效果是否是幻术还有待商榷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about illusion mages.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲幻术法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do not underestimate the illusion mage.  That is my advice to you.</Source>
      <Dest>不要小瞧了幻术师。这是我给你的建议。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about illusion mages.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲幻术法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will stay here and see if I can discover if there are any other members of the Radiant Dark in other parts of Tamriel.  </Source>
      <Dest>我将留在这里，看看我能否在泰姆瑞尔大陆其他区域找到别的黑暗光辉成员。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What will you do now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在有什么打算？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's unlikely that are many, given Nelos' distaste for those who lack strength.  </Source>
      <Dest>It's unlikely that are many, given Nelos' distaste for those who lack strength.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What will you do now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在有什么打算？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet that also means that anyone who was chosen will prove to be formidable.</Source>
      <Dest>然而这也意味着，命中注定之人都会最终成为强者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What will you do now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在有什么打算？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Indeed you must.  I will offer any assistance I can.</Source>
      <Dest>你是非去不可。我会全力协助你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have questions regarding the different schools of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>对不同的音乐流派我有疑问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I trust you say that in jest.  You are Arch-Mage of this College.  You are responsible for influencing young minds.</Source>
      <Dest>我就当您是在开玩笑。您是我们的首席法师，您也有责任引领年轻的灵魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, their philosophy makes perfect sense.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，他们的理念相当有意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A world that values power may serve your interests, but a true leader takes into account what is best for all.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管一个强者为王的世界会符合你的个人利益，但一位真正的领导者所考虑的应该是集体利益。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, their philosophy makes perfect sense.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，他们的理念相当有意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I trust you say that in jest.  You are a valued member of this College.  Your views may influence your peers.</Source>
      <Dest>我就当你说了个玩笑。你是这所学院的一名重要的成员。你的观点可以影响你的同辈们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, their philosophy makes perfect sense.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，他们的理念相当有意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A world that values power may serve your interests, but a true leader takes into account what is best for all.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管一个强者为王的世界会符合你的个人利益，但一位真正的领导者所考虑的应该是集体利益。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, their philosophy makes perfect sense.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，他们的理念相当有意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I suppose I owe you that much.  The truth is, my father loved Nelos more than he cared to admit.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，我想我欠你太多了。真相就是，我父亲爱纳洛斯的比他自己所承认的爱还要多得多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that it's over, I want to talk about Nelos and Brenil.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，已经结束。我想谈谈有关纳洛斯和Brenil。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was difficult for him to live in Morrowind.  He was different.  Not so much in terms of race, but in skill.</Source>
      <Dest>对他而言，他很难立足于晨风。他是与众不同的。倒不是因为种族，而是他的能力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that it's over, I want to talk about Nelos and Brenil.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，已经结束。我想谈谈有关纳洛斯和Brenil。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The other students, whether they be Dunmer, Argonian, or human, did not understand him the way Neloth-Shalal did.</Source>
      <Dest>其他学生，不论是暗精灵，亚龙人，或是人类，对他的理解都不及纳洛斯那般深刻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that it's over, I want to talk about Nelos and Brenil.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，已经结束。我想谈谈有关纳洛斯和Brenil。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In a way, the Dunmer had saved him.  All my father wanted was to return the favor.</Source>
      <Dest>某种意义上，那个黑精灵救了他。我父亲只想还上这个人情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Now that it's over, I want to talk about Nelos and Brenil.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，已经结束。我想谈谈有关纳洛斯和Brenil。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What little I know is this. I spent nearly a decade with Nelos, and not once did I meet the Dunmer my father spoke of from those days in Tel Branora.</Source>
      <Dest>我所知道的唯一一点是，我和纳洛斯在一起近十年了，但从来没遇到过我父亲叙述里那些当他还在泰尔‧布伦诺拉时所遇到的锻莫人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your father's relationship with Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于你父亲和纳洛斯的关系。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Neloth-Shalal was a bright, jovial and creative Elf, who thought beyond the boundaries of what lay in the common spell tome.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯曾是一个活泼，快乐和富有创造力的精灵，他的思想超出了普通魔法书所能及。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your father's relationship with Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于你父亲和纳洛斯的关系。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And no sooner did he make these discoveries that he shared them with his closest confidant.</Source>
      <Dest>不久他就做出了这些发现，然后把它们和自己最亲近的知己分享了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your father's relationship with Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于你父亲和纳洛斯的关系。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father claimed he would not be half the mage he was if not for his friend.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父亲说如果不是为了他朋友的话他根本不会成为一个法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your father's relationship with Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于你父亲和纳洛斯的关系。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet that was a far cry from the wizard I met in Cyrodiil.  The intellect remained, but little else.  He was distant.  Single-minded.  Obsessed.</Source>
      <Dest>这与我在赛瑞迪尔见到的术士相比相去甚远。一样的精明但是欠缺点什么。他该是冷漠的，专注的，令人着迷的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your father's relationship with Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于你父亲和纳洛斯的关系。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then it is not he who failed, but the one who instructed him. (Sigh) Hopefully I have not bungled this endeavor any further.  </Source>
      <Dest>那么事实是他并没有做错什么，而是因为有干扰才会失败。（叹气）希望我没有让这努力付诸东流。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He was foolish.  He disobeyed your orders and went after the mage.</Source>
      <Dest>他是个傻逼。他违背了你的命令，跟了那个法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Were you at least able to speak with him?  Or did he have any clues on his body?</Source>
      <Dest>你当时最起码是可以与他说上话的吧？或者他有什么关于他自己的身体的线索？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He was foolish.  He disobeyed your orders and went after the mage.</Source>
      <Dest>他是个傻逼。他违背了你的命令，跟了那个法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is a hard question.  Nelos had long been under the impression he was chosen for something greater.  </Source>
      <Dest>这是个让人犯难的问题。纳洛斯一直给人留下他是命中注定之人的印象，将来会去影响一件非常伟大的事件。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think happened to the man your father knew?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得在你父亲认识的那个人身上发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As to why, well, you would know better than I.</Source>
      <Dest>至于为什么，好吧，你应该比我更清楚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think happened to the man your father knew?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得在你父亲认识的那个人身上发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At first, I assumed it was merely an excuse to avoid instructing some of the lesser apprentices.</Source>
      <Dest>起初，我假定那仅仅是一个不想给一小部分学生作指导的借口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think happened to the man your father knew?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得在你父亲认识的那个人身上发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Over time, it was evident that he believed in this delusional prophecy he calls the "Long Night."</Source>
      <Dest>随着时间的推移，显然他相信了他所谓“长夜”的那个虚妄的预言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think happened to the man your father knew?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得在你父亲认识的那个人身上发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And it is far easier to commit heinous acts when you believe they have a higher purpose.</Source>
      <Dest>当你知道他们有更进一步的目标时，你就会清楚的意识到他们犯下滔天罪行是多么地随意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think happened to the man your father knew?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得在你父亲认识的那个人身上发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, thanks to your diligence, he will commit them no more.  </Source>
      <Dest>不过，感谢于你的积极援助，他将无法再侵扰他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think happened to the man your father knew?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得在你父亲认识的那个人身上发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Quite slow.  It seems the mages have placed additional layers of security on top of Galerion's original text.  </Source>
      <Dest>真麻烦，看来这些法师们在加里兰的原文上又附加了一层保险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the translation?</Source>
      <Dest>翻译进行的怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you may have noticed, the pages are littered with various magical runes, whose patterns transcribe into messages written in code.</Source>
      <Dest>As you may have noticed, the pages are littered with various magical runes, whose patterns transcribe into messages written in code.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the translation?</Source>
      <Dest>翻译进行的怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had hoped to depart from this location once the matter of the texts was concluded, but it appears I will need to conduct further research.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望我可以在得出一些关于文献上问题的结论后马上离开这个地方，不过看起来我需要更深入的研究才行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the translation?</Source>
      <Dest>翻译进行的怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Interesting...this journal references two names.  The name Drelas is mentioned repeatedly, but it is otherwise unfamiliar to me.</Source>
      <Dest>有趣......这日记里参考了两个名字。这个叫德拉斯的出现了很多次，但是我对这个人并不熟悉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've gathered some information on Jadro'Ra's killer.</Source>
      <Dest>我收集了一些关于贾卓拉的杀手的信息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This other name, however...</Source>
      <Dest>这个别名，怎么说呢....</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've gathered some information on Jadro'Ra's killer.</Source>
      <Dest>我收集了一些关于贾卓拉的杀手的信息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What don't you like about their methods?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得他们的方法有什么不妥么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although the necessity for research is vital, their failure to involve students in the process is disheartening.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管坚持的探索下去才是最重要的，但是在过程中学生们的失误还是令人沮丧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What don't you like about their methods?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得他们的方法有什么不妥么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whether it is fear for their safety or disinterest educating them, I cannot brook such a gross disinterest in the instruction of young minds.</Source>
      <Dest>无论是因为他们担忧自身安全亦或是对为人师长毫无兴趣，我都不能容忍对年轻人思想的教育如此漠不关心的态度。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What don't you like about their methods?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得他们的方法有什么不妥么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only Tolfdir seems interested in performing his duties responsibly, but I have reservations in the manner with which he carries them.</Source>
      <Dest>只有托夫迪尔乐于完成他自己的职责，不过我还是对他对于所谓职责的理解保持保留意见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on the College of Winterhold?</Source>
      <Dest>你对那个座落于冬堡的学院有什么看法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The College itself is a breathtaking wonder, a citadel of knowledge, standing high over the waves of ignorance.</Source>
      <Dest>魔法学院本身就是一个能让人屏息的奇迹，一座知识的城堡，傲然挺立于无知的浪潮之上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on the College of Winterhold?</Source>
      <Dest>你对那个座落于冬堡的学院有什么看法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is a fortress of higher thinking, buttressing its residents from the storms of indolence.</Source>
      <Dest>正是那座充满深远思想的城堡，庇佑着里面的居民远离懒惰的风暴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on the College of Winterhold?</Source>
      <Dest>你对那个座落于冬堡的学院有什么看法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, while the students show an alacrity to learn, I am not entirely fond of the professors, who seem far too concerned with their own research.</Source>
      <Dest>However, while the students show an alacrity to learn, I am not entirely fond of the professors, who seem far too concerned with their own research.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, you were right to tell me.  The gatekeepers between this world and the next are evidently sleeping on the job.  </Source>
      <Dest>不，你是应该告诉我。这个世界跟那边世界的门卫们明显都在上班时间打盹呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He figured as much.  I probably shouldn't have told you, you heartless shrew.</Source>
      <Dest>他全都知道了！我真他吗不该告诉你这个没良心的贱人！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is not something that should be encouraged.  People would cease to move forward if the dead were constantly revisiting the living.</Source>
      <Dest>It is not something that should be encouraged.  People would cease to move forward if the dead were constantly revisiting the living.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He figured as much.  I probably shouldn't have told you, you heartless shrew.</Source>
      <Dest>他全都知道了！我真他吗不该告诉你这个没良心的贱人！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If he shows his furry face again, let me know.  I will have a word with him.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他再顶着他那张毛茸茸的脸出现的话，告诉我一声。我会找他好好聊一聊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He figured as much.  I probably shouldn't have told you, you heartless shrew.</Source>
      <Dest>他全都知道了！我真他吗不该告诉你这个没良心的贱人！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Modesty is a virtue, but rarely is it ever displayed when all evidence points to the contrary.</Source>
      <Dest>谦逊是一种美德，但是从外表上总是很难看的出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I couldn't have done it without your help.</Source>
      <Dest>没有你的帮助我不可能完成这事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You are truly a hero for the ages, and it has nothing to do with your power.</Source>
      <Dest>你真是这个世纪真正的英雄，凭你的能力没有什么做不到的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I couldn't have done it without your help.</Source>
      <Dest>没有你的帮助我不可能完成这事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, it is just as important that you teach such humility to the next generation.  You must be an echo, or your deeds will fade like a whisper.</Source>
      <Dest>然而教会下一代人学会谦卑也是同样重要的事。你必须不断地重复这一点，不然你所付出的的一切都会如轻语般随时间慢慢地褪去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I couldn't have done it without your help.</Source>
      <Dest>没有你的帮助我不可能完成这事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is the measure of true progress.</Source>
      <Dest>这是在权衡真正的进步。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I couldn't have done it without your help.</Source>
      <Dest>没有你的帮助我不可能完成这事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any event, we must make sure this area is clear.  I will head on over to the east wing.</Source>
      <Dest>In any event, we must make sure this area is clear.  I will head on over to the east wing.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I couldn't have done it without your help.</Source>
      <Dest>没有你的帮助我不可能完成这事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You head over to the entrance.  We will meet back here.</Source>
      <Dest>你去入口处看看。我们一会儿回到这里碰头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I couldn't have done it without your help.</Source>
      <Dest>没有你的帮助我不可能完成这事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I shoulder much of the blame for what has transpired.  I will remain vigilant, however, in my efforts to rectify my missteps.</Source>
      <Dest>对，我承担了那件事发生的大部分责任。但我仍是个警戒者，无论如何，我会努力改正我的错误。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thus you had him ousted from the university.  So this is all your fault.</Source>
      <Dest>所以是你害得他被逐出了学校。这一切都是因为你！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then the rumors are true.  I had heard he was ill, and hastened his efforts as a result.</Source>
      <Dest>那么谣言是真的了。我是听说他病了，而且他因此也更加的努力了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Join the Radiant Dark) Nelos is dying.  His acolytes have left him for dead.</Source>
      <Dest>(加入黑暗光辉) 纳洛斯快死了。他的助手放任他死去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Moreover, it is hardly surprising that without him, his guild has crumbled.  Nelos would not dare deign to groom a successor.</Source>
      <Dest>此外，没有他的工会会瞬间土崩瓦解，这一点毋庸置疑。纳洛斯不屑去培养一个继任者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Join the Radiant Dark) Nelos is dying.  His acolytes have left him for dead.</Source>
      <Dest>(加入黑暗光辉) 纳洛斯快死了。他的助手放任他死去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet ill or not, he still must answer for his crimes, and we can do so by taking advantage of the very spells he covets.</Source>
      <Dest>无论他是不是病了，他都要为他的罪行负责，而且我们还要利用他觊觎已久的法术做一些事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Join the Radiant Dark) Nelos is dying.  His acolytes have left him for dead.</Source>
      <Dest>(加入黑暗光辉) 纳洛斯快死了。他的助手放任他死去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you know, we've only begun deciphering the books.  It does seem that the pages contain more than just the crafting of 5 spells.</Source>
      <Dest>你看，我们才刚刚开始破译这些书。看起来这些书页可能不止使用了五个法术来制造。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why was Nelos after Vanus Galerion's research?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么纳洛斯会继承万纳斯·加里兰的研究项目？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They also contain references to a hidden location where Vanus kept more of his research.  The ruins of Pinefrost Tower stand in its place.</Source>
      <Dest>他们还明确的提到了一个瓦纳斯收藏他的发现的地点。就在松雾塔的废墟上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why was Nelos after Vanus Galerion's research?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么纳洛斯会继承万纳斯·加里兰的研究项目？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This may be why the Radiant Dark have come to Skyrim.  Regardless, it bears investigating.  I can think of no better person than you for this task.</Source>
      <Dest>This may be why the Radiant Dark have come to Skyrim.  Regardless, it bears investigating.  I can think of no better person than you for this task.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why was Nelos after Vanus Galerion's research?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么纳洛斯会继承万纳斯·加里兰的研究项目？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In the meantime, I will be here, working on deciphering the pages and perhaps create working tomes of Vanus' spells.</Source>
      <Dest>与此同时我会在这里破解这页秘文，或许我还能制造出一个包含瓦纳斯的法术的卷轴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why was Nelos after Vanus Galerion's research?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么纳洛斯会继承万纳斯·加里兰的研究项目？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I fear we may need to make use of them in the near future.</Source>
      <Dest>我担心不久的将来我们就会用上它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why was Nelos after Vanus Galerion's research?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么纳洛斯会继承万纳斯·加里兰的研究项目？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a little callous of you.  He died in your service.</Source>
      <Dest>你还真有点无情，他是在你服务的过程中死掉的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Quite the contrary.  When I say he was a good mage it is perhaps the highest compliment I could ever pay him.</Source>
      <Dest>正好相反，我说他是一个好法师，或许就是我给他的最高称赞。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a little callous of you.  He died in your service.</Source>
      <Dest>你还真有点无情，他是在你服务的过程中死掉的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I knew the Khajiit for ten years. Do not pretend to understand our relationship, and do not presume you can better eulogize those you barely know.</Source>
      <Dest>我跟那个虎人相识已经整整十年。别假装你能理解我们两个之间的关系，也别胡乱推测那些你压根儿不知道的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a little callous of you.  He died in your service.</Source>
      <Dest>你还真有点无情，他是在你服务的过程中死掉的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is more insulting to his memory that we diverge toward a meaningless argument when the pages are still in the hands of rogue mages.  </Source>
      <Dest>当书还在那些流氓法师手里的时候我们却在为这种细枝末节的事儿争吵不休，这才是对他的大不敬啊。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a little callous of you.  He died in your service.</Source>
      <Dest>你还真有点无情，他是在你服务的过程中死掉的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, do you have any information for me, or not?</Source>
      <Dest>此刻你有没有什么要告诉我的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A fine choice.  What it lacks in awe it more than makes up for in results.</Source>
      <Dest>不错的选择。就结果来看它还是缺少了一些必要的敬畏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The paralysis spell.  I prefer magic that is more efficient and practical.</Source>
      <Dest>那是麻痹术吧。我比较倾向于有效率且易上手的法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My very own Dragon Priest army.  This is too good to pass up.</Source>
      <Dest>我自己的龙祭司的军队。真是好到让人难以拒绝呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A good choice.  It requires a surplus of magicka to cast it, but it will linger for a substantial period of time.</Source>
      <Dest>好主意。这东西需要大量的魔力来驱动，不过倒是可以维持住很长一段时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm...I had originally planned on recruiting a large portion of the faculty.  Yet if the guild is as destitute as you say...</Source>
      <Dest>嗯...我原本想把绝大多数教员都招募进来，不过要是这个公会真像你所说的一样穷的话......</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happens next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We can use this opportunity as a learning experience for the young apprentices.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以利用这次机会让年轻的学徒们长长见识。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happens next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Particularly, those who seem to be more motivated by mead than books.  Let's see if we can find anyone at the inn.</Source>
      <Dest>就某些方面来讲，比起那些书来说他们好像更关心蜜酒。让我们去酒馆儿里找找，看能发现什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happens next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We cannot afford to waste this opportunity.  We have a distinct advantage with Vanus' spells, but their numbers would overwhelm us.</Source>
      <Dest>我们绝不能浪费这个机会。我们拥有瓦纳斯的法术这个明显的优势，但是他们可以用数量来压垮我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll put this spell to good use.  What happens next?</Source>
      <Dest>我会玩好这个法术的。下面会发生什么事呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To put it simply, we need to increase our numbers.</Source>
      <Dest>简单来说，我们需要增加我们队伍的人数。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll put this spell to good use.  What happens next?</Source>
      <Dest>我会玩好这个法术的。下面会发生什么事呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, considering the number of incidents that have happened at this college, it would be irresponsible.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管如此，还是考虑一下最近发生在学院里的这些破事儿吧，要不就太不负责任了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll put this spell to good use.  What happens next?</Source>
      <Dest>我会玩好这个法术的。下面会发生什么事呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Too many students have been lost due to negligence.  I will not tolerate another.</Source>
      <Dest>太多学生因为他们自己的粗心大意而失败或者迷失自我，我再也不能更多的人这样了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll put this spell to good use.  What happens next?</Source>
      <Dest>我会玩好这个法术的。下面会发生什么事呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This means that I too, must join this fight.  Yet it will not be us alone.  I have spoken with Nelacar and another experienced mage.</Source>
      <Dest>我也是这个意思，我也要参战。不过我们不会是孤独的，我已经和娜拉卡还有其他有经验的法师们谈过了此事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll put this spell to good use.  What happens next?</Source>
      <Dest>我会玩好这个法术的。下面会发生什么事呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Both have agreed to join us in our efforts.</Source>
      <Dest>他们被我们说服了，愿意加入我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll put this spell to good use.  What happens next?</Source>
      <Dest>我会玩好这个法术的。下面会发生什么事呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hybrid) Tell me about the second tome.</Source>
      <Dest>(混合) 告诉我第二册的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The hybrid spell combines paralysis with elements of fire.</Source>
      <Dest>这个混合法术融合了麻痹的效果和火焰的伤害。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hybrid) Tell me about the second tome.</Source>
      <Dest>(混合) 告诉我第二册的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Originally, the spell incorporated facets of illusion, transforming foes into allies to fight on your behalf.</Source>
      <Dest>本来，这条咒语的效果包括幻觉，让你的敌人转换成为你的盟友为你而战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hybrid) Tell me about the second tome.</Source>
      <Dest>(混合) 告诉我第二册的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, unlike enchanting, weaving spells together proved rather...unpredictable.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，和附魔不同的是，编织法术带来的效果经常......令人难以预料。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hybrid) Tell me about the second tome.</Source>
      <Dest>(混合) 告诉我第二册的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems your enemies will not become allies so much as they will be overcome with rage and attack anyone within sight.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你的敌人们克制不了见谁砍谁的暴脾气，看起来他们就永远没办法结盟。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hybrid) Tell me about the second tome.</Source>
      <Dest>(混合) 告诉我第二册的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nevertheless, the flame attribute works in tandem with the paralysis, allowing your enemies to burn as the lay motionless.</Source>
      <Dest>不过，火焰属性和麻痹属性倒是蛮搭配的，能让你的敌人一边保持静态一边燃烧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hybrid) Tell me about the second tome.</Source>
      <Dest>(混合) 告诉我第二册的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While it is not what Vanus envisioned, a combination spell such as this is almost unheard of, and will prove useful.</Source>
      <Dest>While it is not what Vanus envisioned, a combination spell such as this is almost unheard of, and will prove useful.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Conjuration) Tell me about the first tome.</Source>
      <Dest>（恳求）请告诉我关于第一卷的内容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, Vanus' notes were originally rather ambitious.  It describes an army of dead bursting from the ground. It's a frightening proposition.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，瓦纳斯的笔记里本来描写的更加雄心壮志。它描述的是一只亡灵大军从地下世界蜂拥而出。这可真是个可怕的设想。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Conjuration) Tell me about the first tome.</Source>
      <Dest>（恳求）请告诉我关于第一卷的内容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, after many failed attempts to harness the energy required for such a task, he chose a more efficient spell.</Source>
      <Dest>然而经过几次失败的驾驭任务所需要的能量后，他选择了另一种更高效的法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Conjuration) Tell me about the first tome.</Source>
      <Dest>（恳求）请告诉我关于第一卷的内容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's in essence a conjuration chain, or to put it more mildly, conjuring a conjurer.</Source>
      <Dest>本质上讲这是一种召唤出的禁锢，说的温和一点是，召唤出一个召唤者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Conjuration) Tell me about the first tome.</Source>
      <Dest>（恳求）请告诉我关于第一卷的内容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To start this chain, you would need to summon a creature with a large wellspring of magicka.  </Source>
      <Dest>这一节开始，你得召唤出一个拥有庞大魔力的召唤生物。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Conjuration) Tell me about the first tome.</Source>
      <Dest>（恳求）请告诉我关于第一卷的内容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This creature would conjure servants, who would then conjure lesser beings, effectively creating an army without draining your own magicka reserve.</Source>
      <Dest>这种生物还会召唤更加弱小的生物，即使召唤出整只军队也不需要耗费你自己的魔力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Conjuration) Tell me about the first tome.</Source>
      <Dest>（恳求）请告诉我关于第一卷的内容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is what this spell tome is.  The knowledge to summon a dragon priest.</Source>
      <Dest>这本咒语书就是这样。记载了召唤龙祭司的知识。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Dunmer I met was incredibly civil.</Source>
      <Dest>我遇到的那个丹莫真是难以置信的文明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nelos has always spoken in measured tones.  It's the words that are unreasonable.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯言行谈吐一向谨慎。这些话压根没道理。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were able to develop them?</Source>
      <Dest>你能开发出它们？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have managed to develop two tomes.  One for the each of us.  Although I am not entirely sure they work as Vanus intended.</Source>
      <Dest>我准备开发两卷法术，我们一人拿一卷。不过我不能肯定能达到瓦纳斯期望的效果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why?  It's not like he has better things to do in the afterlife.</Source>
      <Dest>为啥？寄望于来世可不像他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I confess I do not know what sort of power it requires to return to the mortal plane, but it cannot be easy, nor should it be encouraged.</Source>
      <Dest>我承认我不知道需要何种力量才能重回人间，但这事绝不轻松，也绝不应该被鼓励。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why?  It's not like he has better things to do in the afterlife.</Source>
      <Dest>为啥？寄望于来世可不像他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People would cease to move forward if the dead were constantly revisiting the living.</Source>
      <Dest>若是死者不断地复活回到人间，那生者就会停滞不前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why?  It's not like he has better things to do in the afterlife.</Source>
      <Dest>为啥？寄望于来世可不像他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If he shows his furry face again, let me know.  I will have a word with him.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他再顶着他那张毛茸茸的脸出现的话，告诉我一声。我会找他好好聊一聊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I did all the work.  You should be rewarding me, not thanking me.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我做了所有的工作。你应该奖励我，不是感谢我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I did, or do you require more praise than mere words?  I would say you have that as well, with the tome I provided.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，或者说你想要的不只是口头上的赞美？那我得说你已经得到奖赏了啊，我提供的可是法术啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I did all the work.  You should be rewarding me, not thanking me.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我做了所有的工作。你应该奖励我，不是感谢我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That and a better world will have to suffice.  And even then, your work is not done.</Source>
      <Dest>That and a better world will have to suffice.  And even then, your work is not done.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I did all the work.  You should be rewarding me, not thanking me.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我做了所有的工作。你应该奖励我，不是感谢我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We are always teaching the next generation.  Our voice must be an echo, or it will die like a whisper.</Source>
      <Dest>我们总是在教育下一代。我们的教诲应像回声一样不断延续，而不是像轻语一般消逝在风中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I did all the work.  You should be rewarding me, not thanking me.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我做了所有的工作。你应该奖励我，不是感谢我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is the measure of true progress.</Source>
      <Dest>这是在权衡真正的进步。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I did all the work.  You should be rewarding me, not thanking me.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我做了所有的工作。你应该奖励我，不是感谢我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any event, we must make sure this area is clear. I will head over to the east wing.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我们必须确保这个区域是安全的。我将带头前往东面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I did all the work.  You should be rewarding me, not thanking me.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我做了所有的工作。你应该奖励我，不是感谢我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You head over to the entrance.  We will meet back here.</Source>
      <Dest>你去入口处看看。我们一会儿回到这里碰头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like this fight is almost personal.</Source>
      <Dest>看来这只是一场私斗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps.  This is why it is all the more imperative I maintain my distance and direct you from afar.  I must ensure that my mind is clear.</Source>
      <Dest>也许吧。这就是我一直保持距离，把你远远支开的理由。我必须确保我的头脑是清晰的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I was very impressed by what Nelos is building. Very, very impressed.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯正在建造的东西震撼了我。非常，非常震撼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You would do well not to countenance your admiration for a rogue mage while on this campus.</Source>
      <Dest>You would do well not to countenance your admiration for a rogue mage while on this campus.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I was very impressed by what Nelos is building. Very, very impressed.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯正在建造的东西震撼了我。非常，非常震撼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We have already lost many naive apprentices to his cause, and I will not brook you encouraging others to join them.</Source>
      <Dest>许多脑袋不那么精明的学生已经死于他手，我不能再让你怂恿其他人去送死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I was very impressed by what Nelos is building. Very, very impressed.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯正在建造的东西震撼了我。非常，非常震撼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thankfully, his rebellion is all but extinct, now that we have obtained and developed a few of Vanus' spells.</Source>
      <Dest>谢天谢地，他的反叛行动几乎宣告失败。而如今我们已经获得并改良了几个瓦纳斯的魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I understand the risk, but the need is great.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道风险, 但需要却是如此之大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good.  Jadro'Ra last left for Solitude, but it is unlikely he is still there.  I would start with the caverns near the shoreline.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。贾卓’拉后来动身去了独孤城，不过他不太可能还留在那里。我会从海岸线附近的洞穴开始找起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I understand the risk, but the need is great.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道风险, 但需要却是如此之大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mages use these caves to conduct research away from prying eyes.  If you find him, and find him well, he may ask for a passphrase.</Source>
      <Dest>法师老爱在山洞里搞研究，这样也能远离偷窥的视线。如果你能找到他，并看他还活的好好的，也许他会问你一个密码。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I understand the risk, but the need is great.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道风险, 但需要却是如此之大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In most cases I abhor the need for such conventions, but circumstances required a measure of precaution.</Source>
      <Dest>In most cases I abhor the need for such conventions, but circumstances required a measure of precaution.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll find out what happened to him.</Source>
      <Dest>我要弄清楚他发生了什么事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Finally someone with initiative.  I need someone to scout the area he was investigating and search for clues of his whereabouts.</Source>
      <Dest>总算有个有点主动性的人了。我需要有人搜索他正在调查的地方，然后找到他所处位置的线索。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll find out what happened to him.</Source>
      <Dest>我要弄清楚他发生了什么事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your safety is paramount.  If the mage in question is at the site, do not attempt to confront him, even if it Jadro'Ra is in imminent danger.</Source>
      <Dest>你的安危才是最重要的。要是那个麻烦的法师也在那里，不要试图和他较量，即使贾卓’拉的性命受到威胁也不要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'll find out what happened to him.</Source>
      <Dest>我要弄清楚他发生了什么事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Khajiit is a crafty one.  He will leave clues behind even in death.  Yet if you sacrifice both your lives, both your efforts will be squandered.</Source>
      <Dest>这个虎人是个精明的家伙。即使他死了也会留下不少线索。不过要是你们俩都死了的话，你们两人的努力可就全打水漂了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They sound dangerous, but not nearly as dangerous as me.</Source>
      <Dest>他们听起来似乎很危险, 但是并不如我危险.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, and in their twisted logic, their destruction would bring out your true potential, and thus validate their view.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，用他们扭曲的逻辑来讲，他们用毁灭术可以激发出你真正的潜力，从而证明他们的观点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They sound dangerous, but not nearly as dangerous as me.</Source>
      <Dest>他们听起来似乎很危险, 但是并不如我危险.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As your opinion holds weight at this college, it will do no good to defeat the Radiant Dark but let its ideals poison this institution.</Source>
      <Dest>看来你的意见在这所学院中挺有分量的，打败黑暗光辉并没有什么好处，除非让它的思想渗透进学院，荼毒众人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>On second thought, I changed my mind.</Source>
      <Dest>再次想来,我改变了我的主意。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well, if you would like to reconsider, I will be here in the meantime.  I am afraid, however, that I cannot afford to tarry much longer.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，如果你想重新考虑，在此期间我会呆在这里。然而恐怕我不能久留。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Everyone is hungry for power.  I just want to eat a nice, juicy steak.</Source>
      <Dest>人人都垂涎功名利禄，我只垂涎一块汁多味美的牛排。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is not the time for levity, and I question whether you understand the gravity of the situation!</Source>
      <Dest>没时间吊儿郎当了，我很怀疑你究竟知不知道情况的严重性。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Everyone is hungry for power.  I just want to eat a nice, juicy steak.</Source>
      <Dest>人人都垂涎功名利禄，我只垂涎一块汁多味美的牛排。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Moreover, you misunderstood what I said.  The Synod are hungry for power.  The Radiant Dark wish to unleash it.</Source>
      <Dest>Moreover, you misunderstood what I said.  The Synod are hungry for power.  The Radiant Dark wish to unleash it.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you find out anything, you can call upon my service.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你发现了什么，你可以找我帮忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Excellent.  I will no doubt do so.  Dragonborn, I thank you.  For everything.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了。我当然会这么做。谢谢你，龙裔，谢谢你为我们所做的一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about conjurers.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于魔法师的事.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is a mistake to assume the conjurer hides behind the beasts he summons, for such a mage can conjure a dagger as easily as a dremora.</Source>
      <Dest>总是以为施法者会躲在他的召唤兽身后是错误的，是个法师都可以像召唤魔人一样随意的召唤出一把锋利的匕首。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about conjurers.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于魔法师的事.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There are those who conjure atronachs to support them from the rear, whereas other will conjure bows to lend aid to their armies. </Source>
      <Dest>一些人召唤出元素侍灵并在后方支援它们，而另一些则召唤魔法弓箭来帮助他们的军队。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about conjurers.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于魔法师的事.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you enter their chamber, take note of the bodies strewn about, as they are weapons hoisted on a rack, to be retrieved at the time of battle.</Source>
      <Dest>当你进入他们的房间，要注意观察尸体的状态、散落在架子上的武器，好还原战斗时发生的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about conjurers.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于魔法师的事.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, like any weapon, they are slaves to the one who wields them, and are as much a tool as they are a foe.</Source>
      <Dest>然后就如武器一样，它们对于驱使它们的召唤者来说就是奴隶，比起工具来说倒不如更像是敌人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm more interested in the details of your life.</Source>
      <Dest>我对于你生活中的小细节更感兴趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You flatter me, but not all of us can have childhood's as interesting as Vanus Galerion's.  If the Divines are good, no one ever will.</Source>
      <Dest>您过奖了，不过我们中没有人的童年时光像万纳斯·加里兰那样有趣。无人如圣灵般美好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One for each member of the supreme council of the Mages Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>法师公会高级理事会的成员人手一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were six members on the council, if I'm not mistaken, but at the very least you demonstrate some knowledge of Tamrielic history, albeit wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>我记得不错的话，议会由六个人组成，不过至少你还是展示出了一些有关泰姆瑞尔大陆来历的知识，就算可能并非如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One for each member of the supreme council of the Mages Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>法师公会高级理事会的成员人手一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not all things are meant to be complex.  Sometimes one grasps for answers within the stars when their quarry lies right under their nose.</Source>
      <Dest>并不是所有的事情都是复杂的。有些时候人们仰着头苦苦追寻着的答案就在他们的鼻子底下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One for each member of the supreme council of the Mages Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>法师公会高级理事会的成员人手一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Five texts corresponds with five schools of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>五份文本与五类魔法学派相对应。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Trechtus.  A forgotten name for a powerful man.  Founder of the Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>崔特斯。一个强大的人及他被遗忘的姓名。公会的创始人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Indeed.  Although I doubt that name lacks reverence here.  This is an institution of higher learning, I hope.</Source>
      <Dest>确实。虽然我怀疑这名字缺乏敬意。但这是一个高等学府，希望如此。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Trechtus.  A forgotten name for a powerful man.  Founder of the Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>崔特斯。一个强大的人及他被遗忘的姓名。公会的创始人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It certainly has the pretension of one.</Source>
      <Dest>It certainly has the pretension of one.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I know him.  Nelos and Drelas are one in the same.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道他，纳洛斯和卓拉斯是同一个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I surmised as much.  Even in Skyrim, the only way Nelos could operate out in the open is with an assumed name.</Source>
      <Dest>我也是这么推测的。就算在天际省，纳洛斯若想公开活动也只能使用化名。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I know him.  Nelos and Drelas are one in the same.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道他，纳洛斯和卓拉斯是同一个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And as Nelos goes, so does the Radiant Dark.</Source>
      <Dest>而当纳洛斯离去时，黑暗光辉也消失了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>May I see the texts?</Source>
      <Dest>我能看下这篇文章吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm afraid not.  The texts are evidence, and the methods Galerion used to encode the journals must undergo further study.</Source>
      <Dest>我不那么认为。这些文本就是证据，而加里兰所使用的给这日志加密的方法还需要进一步的研究。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>May I see the texts?</Source>
      <Dest>我能看下这篇文章吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Once I have informed Urag of his omission, he will add the works to this library's collection, along with the missing pages should they be retrieved.</Source>
      <Dest>一旦我把乌拉葛的遗漏告诉他，他就会把这些丢失的书页恢复，加入他的图书馆收藏工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>May I see the texts?</Source>
      <Dest>我能看下这篇文章吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you have a scholarly interest, however, I can share with you the five tales of Galerion's youth. They are quite interesting.</Source>
      <Dest>不过要是你有学术方面的兴趣，我可以跟你分享加里兰年轻时的五个故事。都很有趣的哟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well.  Return to me if you seek my counsel.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，如果你想寻求我的建议的话就请再来找我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's all I needed to know.</Source>
      <Dest>我要了解的就是这些了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The sentimental fool...wasting his energy coming back here.  And yet he hides from me?  </Source>
      <Dest>那个多愁善感的笨蛋......耗费了精力回到这里，却躲着不见我？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I saw Jadro'Ra's ghost.</Source>
      <Dest>我看见贾卓’拉的鬼魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmph.  The Khajiit knows I would give him a good scolding.</Source>
      <Dest>哼。这个虎人好像知道我会责骂他一顿的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I saw Jadro'Ra's ghost.</Source>
      <Dest>我看见贾卓’拉的鬼魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No.  It can never be about that.  Vengeance would mean I sought only Nelos' death.  And all mortals die.</Source>
      <Dest>不。这和那无关。复仇意味着我要的只是纳洛斯的死。而凡人都会死亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can say it.  You wanted vengeance.</Source>
      <Dest>你就直说吧。你想报复。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nelos' danger lies in the ideals and the foundation he built for the Radiant Dark.  If those are allowed to persist, all is for naught.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯的危险之处在于，他的理想和根基都是为黑暗光辉服务的。如果这些被允许存在，那所有的一切都会化为乌有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can say it.  You wanted vengeance.</Source>
      <Dest>你就直说吧。你想报复。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We are always teaching the next generation.  Our voice must be an echo, or it will die like a whisper.</Source>
      <Dest>我们总是在教育下一代。我们的教诲应像回声一样不断延续，而不是像轻语一般消逝在风中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can say it.  You wanted vengeance.</Source>
      <Dest>你就直说吧。你想报复。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is the measure of true progress.</Source>
      <Dest>这是在权衡真正的进步。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can say it.  You wanted vengeance.</Source>
      <Dest>你就直说吧。你想报复。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any event, we must make sure this area is clear. I will head over to the east wing.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我们必须确保这个区域是安全的。我将带头前往东面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can say it.  You wanted vengeance.</Source>
      <Dest>你就直说吧。你想报复。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You head over to the entrance.  We will meet back here.</Source>
      <Dest>你去入口处看看。我们一会儿回到这里碰头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can say it.  You wanted vengeance.</Source>
      <Dest>你就直说吧。你想报复。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Being enamored with your instructor does not mean you are learning from him.</Source>
      <Dest>仰慕你的老师可不代表你是在向他学习。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>His current students seem rather enamored with him.</Source>
      <Dest>他现在的学生似乎比他陷得更深。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So they did not have time to develop the spells themselves. I had feared our actions were too late, given Jadro'Ra was allowed to live.</Source>
      <Dest>所以他们没有时间来钻研他们的法术。我挺担心我们行动的太晚了，给了贾卓’拉活下来的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nelos is building some sort of army, but he needs Vanus' spells.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯正在创建某种军队，但他需要万纳斯的法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, it seems I have underestimated the craftiness of my assistant.  Nelos did not discover his identity until after we had thwarted his plans.</Source>
      <Dest>不过，看起来我低估了我的助手的狡猾程度。直到我们挫败了纳洛斯的计划，他也没被纳洛斯认清他的身份。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nelos is building some sort of army, but he needs Vanus' spells.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯正在创建某种军队，但他需要万纳斯的法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While I doubt he countenanced his disappointment, we have nonetheless struck a major blow to his plans.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然我怀疑他会承认他的失败，不过我们还是给了他的计划一个沉重的打击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nelos is building some sort of army, but he needs Vanus' spells.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯正在创建某种军队，但他需要万纳斯的法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And armed with Vanus' spells, I am confident we will extinguish his rebellion before it has even begun.</Source>
      <Dest>而且有了万纳斯的魔法后，我敢肯定我们会把他的反叛行动扼杀在摇篮里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nelos is building some sort of army, but he needs Vanus' spells.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯正在创建某种军队，但他需要万纳斯的法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you underestimate the strength of your opponent, you weaken yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>当你低估你的对手时，也就是在削弱你自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I doubt it.  Nelos was the Radiant Dark.  The rest were weaklings.</Source>
      <Dest>我不确定。 纳洛斯是黑暗光辉。其他人都是软蛋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You will do well to keep on your guard.  However, I do not need you here.  This time, I truly believe our business is concluded.  </Source>
      <Dest>你作为守卫一如既往的出色。不过我目前已经不需要你的护卫了。此刻，我们的协议就此结束。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I doubt it.  Nelos was the Radiant Dark.  The rest were weaklings.</Source>
      <Dest>我不确定。 纳洛斯是黑暗光辉。其他人都是软蛋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you, Dragonborn.  For everything.</Source>
      <Dest>感谢你所做的一切，龙裔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I doubt it.  Nelos was the Radiant Dark.  The rest were weaklings.</Source>
      <Dest>我不确定。 纳洛斯是黑暗光辉。其他人都是软蛋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about alteration mages.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于变换魔法.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To know that reality is a falsehood is the essence of alteration magic. </Source>
      <Dest>要知道真理即是谎言才是变化系法术的精髓。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about alteration mages.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于变换魔法.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While illusion effects only the caster and the target, alteration is to change the very fabric of our world so that all are affected.</Source>
      <Dest>当幻术只能影响施法者和施法对象的时候， 变换系却改变了我们世界的结构，以至于让所有人都受到影响。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about alteration mages.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于变换魔法.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alteration can be used to blind your opponent with magelight, or turn your flesh into steel.  </Source>
      <Dest>Alteration can be used to blind your opponent with magelight, or turn your flesh into steel.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about alteration mages.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于变换魔法.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is a magic that prevents stealth, as a mage can detect your presence while cloaking his own.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一个防止隐身的魔法，作为一个法师可以在洞察你的存在的同时隐蔽自身。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about alteration mages.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于变换魔法.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alteration does not have an offensive spell.  What it does is use endurance as a weapon.  </Source>
      <Dest>变化系的法术不存在攻击性。它已提升自身的耐性来作为武器。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about alteration mages.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我关于变换魔法.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whether it be with potions of health, stamina or magicka, one must be prepared for a long fight.</Source>
      <Dest>不论有没有带上生命，体力或魔法药剂，你总得为一场持久战做好准备。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm not even aware the number of troubadours was a matter of public knowledge.  </Source>
      <Dest>我甚至根本没意识到游吟诗人的数量对公众知识水平有什么影响。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One for each of the troubadours who brought Valerion to the Psijics.</Source>
      <Dest>把 Valerion 带给赛伊克人的游吟诗人人手一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such a strange and dare I say...esoteric response could have only been conjured form the void itself.  Or perhaps some other nether region.</Source>
      <Dest>我的说法是多么奇特和大胆...深奥的响应只会在从湮灭虚空本身或者也许是从下界的某区域中被召唤出。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One for each of the troubadours who brought Valerion to the Psijics.</Source>
      <Dest>把 Valerion 带给赛伊克人的游吟诗人人手一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All things equal, it is best to opt for the simple answer.  Five texts corresponds with the five schools of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>大家都平等是答案里最简单的那个选择。五份文本与五类魔法学派相对应。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One for each of the troubadours who brought Valerion to the Psijics.</Source>
      <Dest>把 Valerion 带给赛伊克人的游吟诗人人手一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fantastic.  Although I will have to verify if the text is real.  One can never be too careful with an illusionist.</Source>
      <Dest>Fantastic.  Although I will have to verify if the text is real.  One can never be too careful with an illusionist.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've recovered the illusion pages.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经重新取得了幻想的页面</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm...this does not seem to be the right page. Be careful with illusion mages. Things are not always what they seem.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯......这一页看起来不是正确的那页。小心幻术师做的手脚，事物很可能不是它们看起来的样子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've recovered the illusion pages.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经重新取得了幻想的页面</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That makes sense. A passphrase could be useful in identifying friend or foe.</Source>
      <Dest>这是有道理的。暗号可能有助于识别朋友或敌人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Indeed. The problem is, I seem to have forgotten that inscrutable Khajiit word he gave me.  So in exchange, I ask you to tell him this.</Source>
      <Dest>确实如此。问题是，我好想记不清那个神秘的虎人和我了什么了。作为交换，我请求你能告诉他这个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That makes sense. A passphrase could be useful in identifying friend or foe.</Source>
      <Dest>这是有道理的。暗号可能有助于识别朋友或敌人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell him how when I met him, I mocked his whiskers, how they were as black as an Imperial's hair.  </Source>
      <Dest>告诉他当我遇见他时，我会如何嘲笑他的胡须。它们黑的就像是帝国人的毛发！ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That makes sense. A passphrase could be useful in identifying friend or foe.</Source>
      <Dest>这是有道理的。暗号可能有助于识别朋友或敌人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell him that his eyes are so narrow, that even when he laughs he looks unhappy, yet their color still shines as bright as the sun.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉他他的眼睛太小，以至于大笑的时候看起来也不像开心的样子，不过他的瞳孔中放射着太阳一般的光辉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That makes sense. A passphrase could be useful in identifying friend or foe.</Source>
      <Dest>这是有道理的。暗号可能有助于识别朋友或敌人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And if he finds that too sentimental, tell him he was more valuable as a rug.</Source>
      <Dest>要是他要是再继续感情用事的话，不如告诉他他还不如一块地毯更有价值。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That makes sense. A passphrase could be useful in identifying friend or foe.</Source>
      <Dest>这是有道理的。暗号可能有助于识别朋友或敌人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when he accidentally lights his fur on fire, he would be no longer be worth anything to anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>当他不小心点燃他的毛皮那一刻，他对任何人而言都变得不值一提。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's your connection to Nelos?</Source>
      <Dest>你跟纳洛斯是什么关系？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We are...old acquaintances.  Or rather, he was well acquainted with my father.  Brenil Meronin.   They were childhood friends.</Source>
      <Dest>我们......认识很久了。倒不如说，他与我父亲，布莱尼尔.麦罗尼很亲近。他们曾是孩提时的玩伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's your connection to Nelos?</Source>
      <Dest>你跟纳洛斯是什么关系？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Back then, he was known as Neloth-Shalal.  Yet I knew him as Master Nelos, a professor at the Arcane University in Cyrodiil.</Source>
      <Dest>在那时，人们叫他纳洛斯•沙尔。而我认识他时，他则是纳洛斯大师——赛瑞迪尔奥术学院的一名教授。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's your connection to Nelos?</Source>
      <Dest>你跟纳洛斯是什么关系？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He was a great sorcerer and a poor educator.  Not surprisingly, we did not see eye to eye.</Source>
      <Dest>他在学术上有极高的造诣，不过却不怎么擅长教导他人。所以我们之间总是意见相左也在我的意料之中。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The location wasn't a research facility.  It was a hideout for the Radiant Dark.</Source>
      <Dest>这儿并非一个研究场所。它是黑暗光辉的一个隐秘据点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I apologize for putting you in such danger.  Yet you are here, safe and alive.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉置你处于这样的危险中。不过你回来了，平安地活着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The location wasn't a research facility.  It was a hideout for the Radiant Dark.</Source>
      <Dest>这儿并非一个研究场所。它是黑暗光辉的一个隐秘据点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No doubt, as Nelos intended.  However, his arrogance blinds him if he thinks you can be turned.  What information did you glean from this visit?</Source>
      <Dest>毫无疑问，纳洛斯正打算这样。不过他的傲慢自大也让他盲目地以为可以策反你。你从这次会面中获得了些什么信息？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么关系么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>出了什么事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A page from one of these texts, and four others.  Torn right from the spine!  </Source>
      <Dest>这页纸是文献中的，还有另外四页纸，被沿着书脊撕掉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么关系么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>出了什么事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've consulted with Urag's apprentice girl, and she insisted, rather emphatically, that none of these tomes have been checked out for years.</Source>
      <Dest>我咨询了一下给乌拉葛打下手的那个妹子，她着重强调了这些书这些年都没被借出去过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么关系么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>出了什么事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I told the girl that wouldn't preclude a thief from browsing the cases, however.  </Source>
      <Dest>我告诉过那姑娘，狗是改不了吃屎的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么关系么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>出了什么事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't blame her though.  It's the head librarian's duty to keep more sensitive texts behind sealed doors.</Source>
      <Dest>但我并不怪她，将那些包含敏感信息的文献锁在保险柜中是图书管理者的责任。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么关系么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>出了什么事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or perhaps it's the fault of the one who trained him, not to be more perceptive of sensitive texts.</Source>
      <Dest>或许是某个训练他的人的错，让他对含有敏感内容的文本不加警觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么关系么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>出了什么事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In either case, the result is the same.  It is as I feared, someone has managed to steal key pages from the writings of Trechtus.</Source>
      <Dest>In either case, the result is the same.  It is as I feared, someone has managed to steal key pages from the writings of Trechtus.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know about the Radiant Dark?</Source>
      <Dest>有关黑暗光辉你都知道些什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They are a cult, led by a rogue mage. </Source>
      <Dest>他们是群被恶劣法师领导的狂热分子。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know about the Radiant Dark?</Source>
      <Dest>有关黑暗光辉你都知道些什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They believe the only way to advance the field of magic is to destroy the very institutions that ensure its safe use.</Source>
      <Dest>他们相信打破固有的概念可以促进某一领域内法术的进步，并确保这些法术使用起来很安全。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know about the Radiant Dark?</Source>
      <Dest>有关黑暗光辉你都知道些什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Synod may be hungry for relics of power, but they at least hold some accountability for its use.</Source>
      <Dest>希诺人也许对于遗迹的力量十分着迷，但是至少他们认为应该负责任的使用它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know about the Radiant Dark?</Source>
      <Dest>有关黑暗光辉你都知道些什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Radiant Dark would unleash destruction upon the land and view it as a remedy for the weak, and a test of the strong.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗光辉将在这片土地上释放毁灭之力，并视此为对弱者的救赎，对强者的考验。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me the story from the 3rd text.</Source>
      <Dest>从第三辑开始给我讲那个故事。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vanus' father died from the crime of literacy.  He was hung, his body left out for weeks as the sweltering heat bubbled the skin of his fetid corpse.</Source>
      <Dest>Vanus' father died from the crime of literacy.  He was hung, his body left out for weeks as the sweltering heat bubbled the skin of his fetid corpse.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me the story from the 3rd text.</Source>
      <Dest>从第三辑开始给我讲那个故事。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The effigy itself was gruesome, but so was the cruelty of the Lord Gyrnasse.</Source>
      <Dest>这个雕像就很吓人了，正式因为如此残忍无情的盖尔纳斯领主。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me the story from the 3rd text.</Source>
      <Dest>从第三辑开始给我讲那个故事。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He forced Galerion to scrub the gallows every day as his father hung lifelessly above him.</Source>
      <Dest>他强迫加里兰每天擦洗那个将他附近吊死在上面的绞刑架。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me the story from the 3rd text.</Source>
      <Dest>从第三辑开始给我讲那个故事。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He held the lessons of his father close to his heart, and never spoke an indignant word, no matter how callously the nobleman prodded him.</Source>
      <Dest>他从内心深处学会了他父亲的教训，并再也没有咒骂过一句，哪怕那个贵族冷酷无情的用针来刺痛他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me the story from the 3rd text.</Source>
      <Dest>从第三辑开始给我讲那个故事。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, if one stayed awake past the dead of night, one could hear the violence echoing from the basement of the servants' quarters.</Source>
      <Dest>However, if one stayed awake past the dead of night, one could hear the violence echoing from the basement of the servants' quarters.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No one will miss a few pages from the works of some nameless scribe.</Source>
      <Dest>没有人会错过那些无名的抄写员笔下的作品，哪怕是错过几页。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You need to brush up on your history.  Or stop to listen when the professors are lecturing. Although I admit, Tolfdir's voice is its own sleep spell.</Source>
      <Dest>你需要补习补习历史知识了。要不去听听教授们的讲座。不过我得说，托夫迪尔的声音本身就是一种催眠魔咒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No one will miss a few pages from the works of some nameless scribe.</Source>
      <Dest>没有人会错过那些无名的抄写员笔下的作品，哪怕是错过几页。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This nameless scribe you speak of is Vanus Galerion, founder of the Mages Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>这个无名的抄写师就是你所说的万纳斯·加里兰，法师公会的创始人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I met a Dark Elf named Gilsi who mentioned him.  Over and over again.</Source>
      <Dest>我遇到过一个名叫歌尔西的黑暗精灵，反复提到过他的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gilsi...Urag mentioned a student by that name, among dozens of others who left the college in the days following the theft.</Source>
      <Dest>歌尔西...乌拉葛曾经提到一个同名的学生，是在那次失窃事件后离开学院的众多学生之一。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I met a Dark Elf named Gilsi who mentioned him.  Over and over again.</Source>
      <Dest>我遇到过一个名叫歌尔西的黑暗精灵，反复提到过他的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If only Savos had kept a tighter watch, Jadro'Ra might have found her before he managed to track down Nelos.</Source>
      <Dest>如果萨沃斯监视的再仔细一点，贾卓’拉也许已经在设法追踪到纳洛斯前就找到她了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I met a Dark Elf named Gilsi who mentioned him.  Over and over again.</Source>
      <Dest>我遇到过一个名叫歌尔西的黑暗精灵，反复提到过他的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any event, this only serves to confirm my fears. The Radiant Dark has come to Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样，这个证明了我的担忧。黑暗光辉已经来到了天际省。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The theory goes that Galerion was on the verge of completing five new spells, one for each school.  </Source>
      <Dest>加里兰的理念让这五个法术近似完美，每个学派都包含一个。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Spells of such tremendous power that even the immortal armies of Mannimarco would countenance their fear.</Source>
      <Dest>如此惊天的咒术之力，就连曼尼马克的不朽大军都吓得魂飞魄散。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unfortunately, Galerion's obsession with his nemesis deprived him of his patience.  </Source>
      <Dest>不幸的是，加里兰被他的对手困扰直至失去了耐心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nevertheless, before he embarked for The Great Battle, he left notes encoded in five works, so others could continue his research.</Source>
      <Dest>Nevertheless, before he embarked for The Great Battle, he left notes encoded in five works, so others could continue his research.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do the schools of magic relate to the nature of the text?</Source>
      <Dest>魔法的分类与文字的性质有什么联系？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is well known that Galerion's gifts for magic were quite diverse.  </Source>
      <Dest>加里兰对不同派系魔法都极具天赋是妇孺皆知的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do the schools of magic relate to the nature of the text?</Source>
      <Dest>魔法的分类与文字的性质有什么联系？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He could restore a rose to full bloom not long after burning it aflame, all while fooling the mind into believing its scent had rotted away.</Source>
      <Dest>他让一朵玫瑰花重新盛开后不久又将它付之一炬。只是因为他愚蠢的认为，那朵花的香味已经腐朽了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do the schools of magic relate to the nature of the text?</Source>
      <Dest>魔法的分类与文字的性质有什么联系？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is thought that his nemesis Mannimarco was his singular obsession, yet he did allow for others when the trail for his rival grew cold.</Source>
      <Dest>据说他只把他的宿敌曼尼马克当做是个困扰，尽管迹象表明他的敌人愈发的冷酷了，但他还是被其他事分了心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do the schools of magic relate to the nature of the text?</Source>
      <Dest>魔法的分类与文字的性质有什么联系？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or perhaps it was his very obsession with the King of Worms that led to his research of new magics.  </Source>
      <Dest>或许就是因为他如此的痴迷蠕虫之王的过程，引领着他探索新的魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Trechtus.  You speak of the King of Worms.</Source>
      <Dest>崔特斯. 你提到蠕虫之王。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, but I suppose the names Vanus Galerion and Mannimarco are inexorably linked in the annals of history. </Source>
      <Dest>不，但我认为万纳斯·加里兰和曼尼马克这两个名字在历史中一定是有什么关联的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Trechtus.  You speak of the King of Worms.</Source>
      <Dest>崔特斯. 你提到蠕虫之王。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, as their ideals were diametrically opposed, your guess couldn't have been more wrong, even as it was so close to being right.  </Source>
      <Dest>然而，他们的理念截然相反，你认为这两者相距甚远的时候，却也发现它们也惊人的相似。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could find more information on the names mentioned in the journal.</Source>
      <Dest>在这日记里我可以找到关于这些被提及名字的更多信息。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That won't be necessary.  While the majority of the journal is unclear, the name Nelos alone speaks volumes.</Source>
      <Dest>没那个必要。尽管日记的内容虽然没怎么细看，但出现纳洛斯这个名字就说明很多问题了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I could find more information on the names mentioned in the journal.</Source>
      <Dest>在这日记里我可以找到关于这些被提及名字的更多信息。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It appears the Radiant Dark has come to Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>看来黑暗光辉已经到天际省来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Enough with the quizzes lady.  Just tell me.</Source>
      <Dest>游戏玩够了女士，直接告诉我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It pains me to see a member of the college struggling with such a simple query.</Source>
      <Dest>看到这么多学院的成员为这么个简单的问题困扰，真是让我心痛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Enough with the quizzes lady.  Just tell me.</Source>
      <Dest>游戏玩够了女士，直接告诉我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you so daft as to be unaware that there are five schools of magic being taught here?  </Source>
      <Dest>你是不是真的愚蠢到都没注意到这里同时传授着五种学派的魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Enough with the quizzes lady.  Just tell me.</Source>
      <Dest>游戏玩够了女士，直接告诉我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I apologize, the onus is not on the students, but the professors tasked with curing them of their ignorance.</Source>
      <Dest>No, I apologize, the onus is not on the students, but the professors tasked with curing them of their ignorance.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Enough with the quizzes lady.  Just tell me.</Source>
      <Dest>游戏玩够了女士，直接告诉我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What a sad state of affairs, when the college Archmage cannot even unravel a simple query.</Source>
      <Dest>事情发展的也太糟糕了吧，学院的首席法师都无法解决如此简单的疑问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Enough with the quizzes lady.  Just tell me.</Source>
      <Dest>游戏玩够了女士，直接告诉我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Have you already forgotten the number of schools of magic this institution teaches?  Are you that unaware of the curriculum here at the college?</Source>
      <Dest>你已经忘了这些魔法学派的教学安排了？你是不是真的不知道学院的课程表呀？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Enough with the quizzes lady.  Just tell me.</Source>
      <Dest>游戏玩够了女士，直接告诉我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could forgive such an omission of intelligence from the novices, but you are the head of this college.  </Source>
      <Dest>我可以原谅一个缺乏智慧的初学者，但你可是这个学院的头头啊。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Enough with the quizzes lady.  Just tell me.</Source>
      <Dest>游戏玩够了女士，直接告诉我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) But I digress, for while I do not wish to diminish the repercussions of your folly, that is not my most immediate concern.</Source>
      <Dest>（叹气）说点题外话，我此刻希望不要因为你的愚蠢行径而带来什么糟糕的影响，我现在就关心这个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That old Orc must be drinking on the job again.</Source>
      <Dest>那个老兽人一定又在工作中喝酒了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's unlikely mead had anything to do with it.   Although, I agree with your assessment that spirits of any kind have no place in a library.</Source>
      <Dest>蜂蜜酒未必能起到什么作用。不过我同意你的评价，图书馆里没有地方来陈列任何酒品。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That old Orc must be drinking on the job again.</Source>
      <Dest>那个老兽人一定又在工作中喝酒了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's more plausible that Urag failed to see the merit of a controversial theory, and in defiance made the text available to anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>貌似确实如此，乌拉葛没有看出某个备受争议的理论的价值就把这份文献轻蔑的公布给了大众。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How is it Master gro-Shub made such an obvious error?</Source>
      <Dest>大师格洛-舒布怎么会犯下如此一个明显的错误？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is not an error. It is far more likely that Urag holds an opposing position regarding the substance of these texts.</Source>
      <Dest>这并不是个错误，而是很可能乌拉葛本身就对那些文献持相反的观点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How is it Master gro-Shub made such an obvious error?</Source>
      <Dest>大师格洛-舒布怎么会犯下如此一个明显的错误？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not to mention a stubborn refusal to recognize that a controversial theory might actually have merit.</Source>
      <Dest>更不必说他始终顽固的认为饱受争议的理论没有丝毫可取之处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What exactly is in these texts?</Source>
      <Dest>那些文本里到底写了些什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mentioned pages from five separate texts were stolen.  This is no coincidence.  I'm sure you can divine why.</Source>
      <Dest>我提到的那些记录是来自那五个被偷走的文本。这不是巧合。我确信你能猜出原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about restoration mages.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲回复系法师</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The most infuriating of opponents, for every blow you strike, every spell you cast, is nullified by their unyielding ability to heal.</Source>
      <Dest>对手最让你头疼的是，无论你的攻击，或是你释放的法术，都被他们的治疗法术带来的回复效果而化为乌有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about restoration mages.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲回复系法师</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Moreover, when such a mage is surrounded by powerful warriors, their strength grows by leaps and bounds, as all are healed that stand beside him.</Source>
      <Dest>此外，当强力的战士们簇拥在法师周围时，法师便使出法力，周围的人都可以得到他的治疗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about restoration mages.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲回复系法师</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such a mage will confine himself into a small area, to increase the efficacy of his healing spell.  However, this tactic provides an opening.</Source>
      <Dest>法师们会呆在一个较小的范围里以增强法术的治疗效果。无论如何，这也为战术的制定提供了一个契机。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about restoration mages.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我讲讲回复系法师</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just as many can be healed, many can be damaged, and the cost of restoration is far greater than destruction.</Source>
      <Dest>正如事物可以被治愈，事物也可以被破坏，但是为治愈所付出的代价远比为破坏要多很多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right.  He was a good mage.</Source>
      <Dest>你说得对。他是个好巫师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were those who questioned my wits when I showed up with that beggar.  Yet I do not judge those on their beginnings, regardless of how humble.</Source>
      <Dest>There were those who questioned my wits when I showed up with that beggar.  Yet I do not judge those on their beginnings, regardless of how humble.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right.  He was a good mage.</Source>
      <Dest>你说得对。他是个好巫师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I did not err in selecting Jadro'Ra as one of my students, nor making him my assistant.  I can only hope I have not failed him as an instructor.  </Source>
      <Dest>我认为我选择贾卓’拉作为我的学生，后来成为了我的助手，这个决定是对的。我只希望作为他的导师，我没有辜负了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right.  He was a good mage.</Source>
      <Dest>你说得对。他是个好巫师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Apropos of that, you still have not addressed the question of the missing pages.</Source>
      <Dest>说到这了，你还是没能解决好丢失的书页的问题啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One for each school of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>每种魔法都有一个。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Exactly.  According to the theory, there was purpose to Galerion's decision to divide his childhood journals into five parts.</Source>
      <Dest>一点儿没错。根据这一理论，加里兰决定将他的童年日志划分成五个部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One for each school of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>每种魔法都有一个。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Contained within each was a tale that alluded to spells and techniques authored by a specific school.</Source>
      <Dest>每一本都提到了关于一个特别的学派的法术和技艺的传说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Trechtus.  The birth name of the mage Shalidor.</Source>
      <Dest>崔特斯.  是术士沙利多出生时的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Shalidor created Labyrinthian, and his imprint echoes across Skyrim, but I speak of another.  </Source>
      <Dest>纱利多创造的迷宫，有关他的痕迹遍布天际省，但我谈及的是另一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Trechtus.  The birth name of the mage Shalidor.</Source>
      <Dest>崔特斯.  是术士沙利多出生时的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Trechtus is the birth name of Vanus Galerion, former Psijic Monk, student of Iachesis, and founder of the Mages Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>崔塔斯是万纳斯·加里兰出生时的名字，他曾是赛伊克教团的僧侣，伊切瑟斯的学生，法师公会的创始人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I was going to suggest this Lathgwen is the killer.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我觉得拉斯戈文是凶手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) Even if your assumption is correct, the matter at hand is larger than Jadro'Ra.  The mention of Nelos is the most pertinent information.</Source>
      <Dest>（叹气）即使你的假设是正确的，眼前的问题比贾卓’拉的问题要大。提及纳洛斯的有关信息才正是现在所需要的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I was going to suggest this Lathgwen is the killer.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我觉得拉斯戈文是凶手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It appears the Radiant Dark has come to Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>看来黑暗光辉已经到天际省来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have any idea who stole the pages?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道谁偷走了那些页面?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have an inkling.  There are rumors that the Synod is here in Skyrim, although I cannot confirm it is the texts of Galerion they seek. </Source>
      <Dest>我对此略知一二。有传闻称说希诺就在天际省, 我对此略知一二。有传言说希诺人就在天际省，虽然我也不确定这个就是他们寻找的加里兰的文献。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have any idea who stole the pages?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道谁偷走了那些页面?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Regardless, only a practiced mage is permitted entrance into the College.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样，只有熟练的法师才会被允许进入魔法学院。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have any idea who stole the pages?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道谁偷走了那些页面?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Albeit one wonders, given the pathetic wards placed at the entrance, if even a novice or a sufficiently determined troll could shatter it.</Source>
      <Dest>人们不禁会好奇，入口处的守卫如此孱弱，即使一个初心者甚至一只横冲直撞的巨魔都可以将他们粉碎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have any idea who stole the pages?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道谁偷走了那些页面?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, the culprit would have to be one familiar with Galerion's experimental research. And he would come here himself. He would not trust a proxy.</Source>
      <Dest>看来，罪犯是一个熟悉加里兰的实验调查的人。而且他一定会亲自前来，他不会放心把这件事交给手下的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have any idea who stole the pages?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道谁偷走了那些页面?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, I was able to glean some clues based on my interviews of the residents of Winterhold, who seem far more observant of mages than the faculty.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，我完全可以从冬堡的居民那里收集一些线索，他们看起来比学院的教员们还了解这些法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have any idea who stole the pages?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道谁偷走了那些页面?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I sent my assistant, Jadro'Ra, to investigate the matter further, but I fear something grave has befallen him.  He has not returned in over a week.</Source>
      <Dest>我派出我的助手，贾卓’拉，去深入调查此事。但是我担心他凶多吉少，让一个星期前就该回来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have any idea who stole the pages?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道谁偷走了那些页面?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am in need of someone capable to locate him and any possible information he may have retrieved regarding the missing pages.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在需要一个有能力的人可以定位到他，并得到他可能已经获得的关于这些丢失的书页的信息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've recovered the destruction pages.</Source>
      <Dest>我把 毁灭 那些页面找回来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wonderful.  Be sure to check with Colette if you have any injuries.</Source>
      <Dest>非常好。如果受伤了记得和欧列特联系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm interested in how Galerion encoded his texts.</Source>
      <Dest>我对加里兰怎麽对他的文本进行编写很感兴趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Each book is a cleverly crafted tale that hints toward the ideals of particular school of magic. </Source>
      <Dest>每本书都精心构思了一个神奇传说，暗示了每一个学派的最终理念。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm interested in how Galerion encoded his texts.</Source>
      <Dest>我对加里兰怎麽对他的文本进行编写很感兴趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, the overall narrative is unimportant.  From what I have gathered in my time here, it seems the school of magic is simply a mechanism.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，记叙下来的内容并不重要。从我目前收集到的资料来看，这个魔法学派的技巧并不复杂。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm interested in how Galerion encoded his texts.</Source>
      <Dest>我对加里兰怎麽对他的文本进行编写很感兴趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For instance, I found lighting a text with an alteration spell revealed a hidden message written in an ink altered to mimic a human soul.</Source>
      <Dest>比如说，我用变化法术标注了一段文字，显示出了一些隐藏的信息。那些信息是用灵魂墨水写成的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm interested in how Galerion encoded his texts.</Source>
      <Dest>我对加里兰怎麽对他的文本进行编写很感兴趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, without the knowledge to light the aura of life aglow, the mage's search would end there.  </Source>
      <Dest>当然了，足够的知识储备才可以让一个法师点亮他的生命之光，否则他没有探索这个世界的能力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm interested in how Galerion encoded his texts.</Source>
      <Dest>我对加里兰怎麽对他的文本进行编写很感兴趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The chain continues until one reaches the destination.  The final pages that contained detailed notes on the crafting of a new spell.</Source>
      <Dest>经过一页一页的筛选，直到其达到了目标。这最后一页上详细记载了制造一个新法术的方法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wish to hear the tale from the 2nd text.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望听到第二个版本的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Galerion's mother was an old fashioned woman, one comfortable with her station. She never wanted to deprive Galerion of knowledge.</Source>
      <Dest>加里兰的母亲是一个保守的老女人，对她的身份地位很满足。她。她从未剥夺加里兰探求知识的权力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wish to hear the tale from the 2nd text.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望听到第二个版本的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was, however, fearful of the consequences.  A seed of dread was planted in her mind and grew into a forest of despair.</Source>
      <Dest>她总是畏惧结果。一颗恐惧的种子已经在她心中生根发芽，长成一片绝望的森林。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wish to hear the tale from the 2nd text.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望听到第二个版本的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was only a matter of time before her husband or her child would slip and betray their literacy.</Source>
      <Dest>她的丈夫或是孩子摆脱直至背弃道德的禁锢只是时间问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wish to hear the tale from the 2nd text.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望听到第二个版本的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In truth, Lord Gyrnasse suspected nothing, but in her reality she saw her husband on the gallows, and through her actions, she made it true.</Source>
      <Dest>真相是，盖尔纳斯大人并没有这样怀疑，但是她认为她的丈夫应该上绞刑架，就她的一贯作风来讲，她也会让此事成真。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would like to hear the story from the 4th text.</Source>
      <Dest>我想听第四版的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As a child, Vanus Galerion escaped his birth home of Sollicich-on-Ker.  He simply crept out of his quarters one night and ran.</Source>
      <Dest>孩提时期的万纳斯·加里兰就逃出了他的出生地，那是苏里斯克-昂-科的一所房子。他采用了最简单的方式，溜出住所后一路狂奔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would like to hear the story from the 4th text.</Source>
      <Dest>我想听第四版的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He never stopped running.  He had trekked halfway across the Summerset Isle when he reached the shores of Alinor.  There was nowhere left to run.</Source>
      <Dest>他未曾停下过脚步，他甚至差点就横穿了整个夏暮岛，但当他抵达阿里诺尔海岸时，他已无处可逃了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would like to hear the story from the 4th text.</Source>
      <Dest>我想听第四版的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Exhausted, he collapsed in a ditch.  It is there that a band of troubadours found his body, and nursed him back to health.  </Source>
      <Dest>Exhausted, he collapsed in a ditch.  It is there that a band of troubadours found his body, and nursed him back to health.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would like to hear the story from the 4th text.</Source>
      <Dest>我想听第四版的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They employed him as an errand boy and gave him food and shelter.  And the life he had seemingly lost, was somehow returned to him.</Source>
      <Dest>他们把他雇为一个跟班儿，给了他食物与庇护所。他看起来已经暗淡失色的人生又回光返照了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think the Synod is responsible for the missing pages?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为希诺应该为那些缺页负责吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have not ruled that out, although the Synod seems more interested in securing existing artifacts of power. </Source>
      <Dest>I have not ruled that out, although the Synod seems more interested in securing existing artifacts of power. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think the Synod is responsible for the missing pages?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为希诺应该为那些缺页负责吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Galerion's research, while potentially powerful, was still incomplete.  There is no guarantee that any of the five spells can even be crafted.</Source>
      <Dest>加里兰的研究项目，虽然潜力巨大，但仍未完成。那五种魔法恐怕没有一个能保证可以完成。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think the Synod is responsible for the missing pages?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为希诺应该为那些缺页负责吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is not to imply the documents are not dangerous.  The secrecy of Galerion's methods are a substantial indicator of the level of risk.</Source>
      <Dest>这不代表这些文件没有任何危险性。加里兰用来使用的加密手段里就包括大量使用有风险的试剂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think the Synod is responsible for the missing pages?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为希诺应该为那些缺页负责吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, the Synod does not have the patience nor the foresight to recognize what these texts represent.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，希诺人既没有耐心也没有远见来理解这些文献中的真谛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You carry yourself with some authority.  Who are you exactly?</Source>
      <Dest>你给人感觉很有范儿的样子啊。你到底是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My name is Olivia Meronin, a former member of the Mages Guild at the Arcane University in Cyrodiil.  </Source>
      <Dest>我叫奥莉薇雅·梅洛妮，以前在赛瑞迪尔奥术大学，也是法师公会的一名成员。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You carry yourself with some authority.  Who are you exactly?</Source>
      <Dest>你给人感觉很有范儿的样子啊。你到底是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When the Guild disbanded, many of my colleagues regrouped to form the Synod.</Source>
      <Dest>当公会解散的时候，我的许多同僚聚集在一起，重新组建成了希诺.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You carry yourself with some authority.  Who are you exactly?</Source>
      <Dest>你给人感觉很有范儿的样子啊。你到底是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, their objectives do not align with the tenets Galerion and the council established when they founded the Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，他们的目标与加里兰的原则、公会建立后成立的理事会的宗旨背道而驰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You carry yourself with some authority.  Who are you exactly?</Source>
      <Dest>你给人感觉很有范儿的样子啊。你到底是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nor do they abide by the teachings we have stood by in the centuries that followed.  Theirs is an organization based on cupidity and lust for power.</Source>
      <Dest>他们也不遵循我们追随了百年之久的教条。他们的组织只建立在贪婪和权利欲之上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Find someone else to do your dirty work.</Source>
      <Dest>找其他人来干你的脏话儿吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had not asked for your help specifically, although I would be lying if I told you the question did not broach my mind.</Source>
      <Dest>我并没有刻意寻求你的帮助，不过要说这个问题没有让我焦头烂额的话那的确是谎言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Find someone else to do your dirty work.</Source>
      <Dest>找其他人来干你的脏话儿吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Therefore, if you would like to reconsider, I will be here for the meantime.  I am afraid, however, that I cannot afford to tarry much longer.</Source>
      <Dest>因此，要是你还想考虑一下这件事，近期我会呆在这里，不过我肯定不会等太久。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like my kind of people.</Source>
      <Dest>像是我的菜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I question the sense of your professors.  As they are the ones who so glibly allowed your admittance into this institution.</Source>
      <Dest>那我就得问问你的教授们的看法了。因为他们就是如此随随便便就允许你进入这个机构。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like my kind of people.</Source>
      <Dest>像是我的菜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I must question why the professors here are insisting that you lead this college.  </Source>
      <Dest>那我必须询问为什么这里的那些教授都坚持让你来领导这学院。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like my kind of people.</Source>
      <Dest>像是我的菜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Leadership is not just about strength.  Your philosophy will impact the direction of the entire curriculum.</Source>
      <Dest>力量并不是领导能力的全部。你的人生观会影响整个课程的发展方向。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's enough about Galerion's journals.</Source>
      <Dest>够了，别再说加里兰的日志了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you will.</Source>
      <Dest>如你所愿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Let's go to the beginning. Tell me the 1st story.</Source>
      <Dest>来我们从头开始。告诉我第一个故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As a young child, Galerion's father bought books from smugglers in order teach his son how to read.</Source>
      <Dest>当加里兰还是个孩子的时候，他的父亲从走私贩手中购买了许多书籍，为的是教他识字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Let's go to the beginning. Tell me the 1st story.</Source>
      <Dest>来我们从头开始。告诉我第一个故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As serfs of a minor nobleman, Lord Gyrnasse of Sollicich-on-Ker, such knowledge was strictly forbidden.</Source>
      <Dest>作为次级贵族，苏里斯克-昂-科的领主盖尔纳斯的农奴，拥有这样的知识是被十分忌讳的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Let's go to the beginning. Tell me the 1st story.</Source>
      <Dest>来我们从头开始。告诉我第一个故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Galerion recounted how his father taught him to avert his eyes at every sign post and to speak with improper diction.</Source>
      <Dest>加里兰描述了他的父亲教导他不要被各种记号所迷惑，说话要清晰准确。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Let's go to the beginning. Tell me the 1st story.</Source>
      <Dest>来我们从头开始。告诉我第一个故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Most of all he warned him not to reference the tales he read, but more importantly, the cities, beasts, and forests contained therein.</Source>
      <Dest>重要的是，他告诫他不要去引用他读到的传奇，但最最重要的是，不要提及里面出现的城市、猛兽和森林。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Let's go to the beginning. Tell me the 1st story.</Source>
      <Dest>来我们从头开始。告诉我第一个故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For the spell would be broken the instant their Lord realized the boy knew things his eyes could not see.</Source>
      <Dest>就在这个法术即将破灭殆尽的时候，他们的领主意识到自己看不穿这个男孩能看穿的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So why search for them, if scholars believe them worthless?</Source>
      <Dest>那么为什么要去找它们呢，既然学者们认为它们毫无用处？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There are some, however, who attribute the texts to a different origin.  Not the young Trechtus, but the elder Vanus Galerion.</Source>
      <Dest>不过有一些人，他们认为那些文献是从别处来的。不是年轻的崔特斯，而是老瓦纳斯·加里兰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So why search for them, if scholars believe them worthless?</Source>
      <Dest>那么为什么要去找它们呢，既然学者们认为它们毫无用处？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The theory states that Vanus wrote the text in the guise of his younger self, precisely so that scholars would question its authenticity.</Source>
      <Dest>这个理论声明，瓦纳斯的这篇文章创作于他的青年时期是一个幌子，以至于学者们开始怀疑它的真实性。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So why search for them, if scholars believe them worthless?</Source>
      <Dest>那么为什么要去找它们呢，既然学者们认为它们毫无用处？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By diverting the eyes of those who seek power, it provided an extra layer of security, in addition to the cryptic nature of the text itself.</Source>
      <Dest>通过转移那些寻求力量的人的注意力，这给这份神秘的文献有上加上了一层额外的保险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain this theory.</Source>
      <Dest>解释下这个原理。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The majority of scholars are split between two disparate camps.</Source>
      <Dest>大多学者分成了两个对立的阵容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain this theory.</Source>
      <Dest>解释下这个原理。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some believe the texts are worthless scribbles written by a child, one who had yet to grasp the vastness of his destiny.</Source>
      <Dest>一些人认为这些文献毫无价值，只是一个不知天文地理，参悟不透天命的小孩子的胡乱涂鸦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain this theory.</Source>
      <Dest>解释下这个原理。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Others contend the author is not Vanus himself, but a pretender hoping to profit from the mage's name.</Source>
      <Dest>其他人推测作者并不是瓦努斯本人，而是一个企图从中渔利的冒充者。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain this theory.</Source>
      <Dest>解释下这个原理。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Both camps, however, are in agreement that the texts themselves have no intellectual merit.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样，这两个阵营在判定这些文本有无学术价值一事上意见一致。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain this theory.</Source>
      <Dest>解释下这个原理。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They are either an amusing reference for biographers and historians, or an elaborate hoax that vexes the very same.</Source>
      <Dest>这些素材既可以在文学家和史学家笔下精彩生辉，也可以让恶作剧变得令人生厌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell the tale from the 5th and final text, and the last school of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>从第五辑和最后一辑开始讲吧，最后的魔法学派。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vanus Galerion once ran with a group of troubadours. They performed from city to city, regaling crowds with their song and flair.</Source>
      <Dest>有一次，万纳斯·加里兰加入了一伙吟游诗人，他们在城市间巡回演出，并给人们带去歌声与欢笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell the tale from the 5th and final text, and the last school of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>从第五辑和最后一辑开始讲吧，最后的魔法学派。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One of them was a former jester, a man with deft hands.  From out of the ether he would withdraw a bouquet of flowers, or a septim from your ear.</Source>
      <Dest>他们其中一人曾是一名功夫了得的魔术师，能凭空变出一束花，或者从你耳朵里揪出个赛普汀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell the tale from the 5th and final text, and the last school of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>从第五辑和最后一辑开始讲吧，最后的魔法学派。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, it was the group as a whole who cast a spell on the young boy, drawing a smile that had been lost to the void.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，也就是这伙人为这个小男孩释放了一个法术，那是一个笑脸儿，随后在空气中慢慢的消散了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've recovered the restoration pages.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经找到回复的残页。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stupendous.  I hope you did not cause too much collateral damage in procuring these.</Source>
      <Dest>令人惊叹。我希望你搞定这些的时候没有造成什么间接损害。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Olivia, about your father...</Source>
      <Dest>奥莉薇雅，关于你的父亲……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dragonborn, this is not the time to concern yourself with personal matters.  What did you discover at the site?</Source>
      <Dest>龙裔，现在不是你关心你的个人问题的时候。快说说你在那个地方发现了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Confound it all...this page too...that makes five in total.  This is unacceptable!</Source>
      <Dest>乱七八糟......这页也是......最终制造出5份。这是令人难以接受的结果！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My sincerest apologies, but I need time alone to think.  Meet me in the Arcanaeum later if you have something you wish to discuss.</Source>
      <Dest>向你致以我最诚挚的歉意，我现在需要时间去独立思考下。要是你想和我探讨点什么，待会儿来秘藏馆找我吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're back.  What did you find?</Source>
      <Dest>你回来了，你有什么发现吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's finally over.   And I owe you my thanks.  With the Radiant Dark finished, many of us will rest easy tonight.  Living...and dead.</Source>
      <Dest>终于结束了。我还欠你句感谢。黑暗光辉被终结了，我们中的很多人都可以放下重负。平凡地生活...然后死去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did you find anything?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么发现吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have news regarding your assistant.</Source>
      <Dest>我有关于你的助手的消息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well done.  What have you learned?</Source>
      <Dest>干得好！你有没有从中学到什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He was able to procure these notes.</Source>
      <Dest>他是有能力取得这些笔记的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let me see those...this is precisely what we needed.  You have done admirably, as did my assistant in delivering these to you.</Source>
      <Dest>让我看一下...哦这正是我们所需要的啊。你完成得太完美了，这些东西简直就像是我的助手转交给你的一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He was able to procure these notes.</Source>
      <Dest>他是有能力取得这些笔记的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now that you are entrenched in this matter, I have no doubt that you are the only one capable of pursuing it to the end.</Source>
      <Dest>既然你在处理这个问题，只有你能结束这个事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He was able to procure these notes.</Source>
      <Dest>他是有能力取得这些笔记的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is far more perilous than the previous job, but I believe you will reward my confidence in you.</Source>
      <Dest>这次的工作比你以前做的还要危险，不过我相信你一定可以完成。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right. What comes next?</Source>
      <Dest>行了，然后怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He was able to procure these notes.</Source>
      <Dest>他是有能力取得这些笔记的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you may have guessed, the five locations listed are likely secluded areas where the mages can conduct their individual research.</Source>
      <Dest>你也许都猜到了，这五个地方很可能是法师们为了进行独立研究而寻找的僻静场所。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right. What comes next?</Source>
      <Dest>行了，然后怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He was able to procure these notes.</Source>
      <Dest>他是有能力取得这些笔记的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One mage for each school of magic.  To defeat them will require skill and cunning, and an understanding of the strengths and weaknesses of each art.</Source>
      <Dest>若想击败每种学派的法师们，需要的不光是技巧和灵巧，还需要理解每种流派的优势和劣势。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right. What comes next?</Source>
      <Dest>行了，然后怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He was able to procure these notes.</Source>
      <Dest>他是有能力取得这些笔记的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The notes will provide their locations, and you can consult me for any advice regarding their procurement.  Do you have any questions before you go?</Source>
      <Dest>这笔记里提供了他们的位置，你可以向我咨询任何有关他们的事。你走之前还有什么疑问吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm afraid Jadro'Ra is dead.</Source>
      <Dest>我恐怕贾卓’拉已经死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is unfortunate.  He was a good mage.  Were you able to procure any information at all?</Source>
      <Dest>真不幸，他是个好法师。你还能不能获得一些情报？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Or you could maybe say goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>或者你也许应该说再见了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes...but I have had one too many today, and...I am all out of tears.</Source>
      <Dest>Yes...but I have had one too many today, and...I am all out of tears.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Four of us, to be exact.   Me, you, your father and Jadro'Ra.</Source>
      <Dest>确切的说是我们四个，我，你，你父亲还有贾卓’拉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Three of the four, perhaps.  My work is not yet complete, however.  Nelos may be dead, but his ideals, research, and influence remain.</Source>
      <Dest>大概四分之三吧，我还没有完成我的工作。虽然纳洛斯已经死了，但他的思想，研究， 影响还并没有消失。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Four of us, to be exact.   Me, you, your father and Jadro'Ra.</Source>
      <Dest>确切的说是我们四个，我，你，你父亲还有贾卓’拉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If those are allowed to persist, then all is for naught.</Source>
      <Dest>如果这些都得以保存，那一切努力都付诸流水了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Four of us, to be exact.   Me, you, your father and Jadro'Ra.</Source>
      <Dest>确切的说是我们四个，我，你，你父亲还有贾卓’拉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We are always teaching the next generation.  Our voice must be an echo, or it will die like a whisper.</Source>
      <Dest>我们总是在教育下一代。我们的教诲应像回声一样不断延续，而不是像轻语一般消逝在风中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Four of us, to be exact.   Me, you, your father and Jadro'Ra.</Source>
      <Dest>确切的说是我们四个，我，你，你父亲还有贾卓’拉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is the measure of true progress.</Source>
      <Dest>这是在权衡真正的进步。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Four of us, to be exact.   Me, you, your father and Jadro'Ra.</Source>
      <Dest>确切的说是我们四个，我，你，你父亲还有贾卓’拉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any event, we must make sure this area is clear. I will head over to the east wing.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我们必须确保这个区域是安全的。我将带头前往东面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Four of us, to be exact.   Me, you, your father and Jadro'Ra.</Source>
      <Dest>确切的说是我们四个，我，你，你父亲还有贾卓’拉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You head over to the entrance.  We will meet back here.</Source>
      <Dest>你去入口处看看。我们一会儿回到这里碰头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not everyone can be as disciplined an educator as you.</Source>
      <Dest>并不是所有人都能成为像你这样的训练有素的教育者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Teaching is not a competition.  It is a cooperative effort.  Nelos' difficulties stemmed not from his methodology, but his desire.</Source>
      <Dest>教学并不是竞争，而是师徒合作的成果。纳洛斯的困难并不源于他的方法，而是欲望使然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Radiant Dark are dysfunctional. They can't even agree on a philosophy.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗光辉很不正常。我甚至在理念上都无法认同他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You would do well to consider the reasons why.  Leadership is about more than power.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该好好思考一下其中的真谛。领导能力包含的不单单只是力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Radiant Dark are dysfunctional. They can't even agree on a philosophy.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗光辉很不正常。我甚至在理念上都无法认同他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nelos will tell you he gives his apprentices the freedom to make their own choices.  The result is a complete lack of guidance.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯会跟你说，他会给他的学徒们自己作选择的自由。结果就是学徒们没有获得指导。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Radiant Dark are dysfunctional. They can't even agree on a philosophy.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗光辉很不正常。我甚至在理念上都无法认同他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As Arch-Mage, I hope you are taking note of his shortcomings.</Source>
      <Dest>作为首席法师，我希望你能注意到他的缺点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Radiant Dark are dysfunctional. They can't even agree on a philosophy.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗光辉很不正常。我甚至在理念上都无法认同他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Regardless, the Radiant Dark still pose an unmistakable threat.  Yet with Vanus' spells, we will extinguish his rebellion before it has even begun.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样，黑暗光辉还是做出一副他们极具威胁的样子。目前我们有了瓦纳斯的法术，可以在他们叛乱之前就击败他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Radiant Dark are dysfunctional. They can't even agree on a philosophy.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗光辉很不正常。我甚至在理念上都无法认同他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You would do well to consider the reasons why.  Leadership is about more than power.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该好好思考一下其中的真谛。领导能力包含的不单单只是力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Radiant Dark are dysfunctional. They can't even agree on a philosophy.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗光辉很不正常。我甚至在理念上都无法认同他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nelos will tell you he gives his apprentices the freedom to make their own choices.  The result is a complete lack of guidance.</Source>
      <Dest>纳洛斯会跟你说，他会给他的学徒们自己作选择的自由。结果就是学徒们没有获得指导。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Radiant Dark are dysfunctional. They can't even agree on a philosophy.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗光辉很不正常。我甚至在理念上都无法认同他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The master wizards here would be wise to take note of his shortcomings.</Source>
      <Dest>巫术大师看破了他的不足。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Radiant Dark are dysfunctional. They can't even agree on a philosophy.</Source>
      <Dest>黑暗光辉很不正常。我甚至在理念上都无法认同他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Regardless, the Radiant Dark still pose an unmistakable threat.  Yet with Vanus' spells, we will extinguish his rebellion before it has even begun.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样，黑暗光辉还是做出一副他们极具威胁的样子。目前我们有了瓦纳斯的法术，可以在他们叛乱之前就击败他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've recovered the alteration pages.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经恢复了变化系的页面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is tremendous news. If you are running low on potions, be sure to stock up at Birna's.</Source>
      <Dest>That is tremendous news. If you are running low on potions, be sure to stock up at Birna's.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We could try to lure them here.  Then torture them.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以试着在这里引诱他们。接着折磨他们。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know you are pleased with our victory, as am I.  Yet I do not tolerate such statements, even in jest.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你为我们的胜利感到喜悦，我也是。然而我还是不喜欢这种说笑般的表述方式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We could try to lure them here.  Then torture them.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以试着在这里引诱他们。接着折磨他们。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nevertheless, it is possible that some members were set to arrive here in the coming days.</Source>
      <Dest>不过，未来几天还是有学徒可能到达这里的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We could try to lure them here.  Then torture them.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以试着在这里引诱他们。接着折磨他们。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If that happens, I will deal with them in the appropriate manner. In the meantime, I thank you, Dragonborn.  For everything.</Source>
      <Dest>要是那件事发生了，我会采用适当的方式解决他们。此刻，谢谢你，谢谢你为我们做的一切。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about destruction mages.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲那个毁灭法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The name destruction implies havoc, and while such magic is capable of immense damage, it is not as inelegant as one might presume.</Source>
      <Dest>毁灭术这个名字就意味着破坏，尽管这类魔法能够造成极大的破坏性，但也不像人们所认为的那样粗鲁不雅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about destruction mages.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲那个毁灭法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lightning, ice, and fire. Each element has applications beyond the inflicting of pain. </Source>
      <Dest>闪电，寒霜，还有烈火。每一种元素除了造成破坏与痛苦之外都有别的用途。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about destruction mages.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲那个毁灭法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A bolt of lightning can disarm a trained mage, sapping him of his magicka.  The swiftest runner will find it difficult to wade through briars of ice.</Source>
      <Dest>闪电箭可以搞定训练有素的法师，榨干他的法力。冰霜形成的荆棘则可以让最迅捷的跑者也无法穿越。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about destruction mages.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲那个毁灭法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Flames will turn your own tunic into a weapon, draining your health as it burns through your skin.</Source>
      <Dest>火焰将你自的袍子转化成为武器，燃烧你的肌肤的同时吞噬你的生命力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about destruction mages.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲讲那个毁灭法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To defeat a master of destruction magic, one must use their wards wisely, for there is more than just health one must account for.</Source>
      <Dest>To defeat a master of destruction magic, one must use their wards wisely, for there is more than just health one must account for.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Had I known he was Jadro'Ra's killer, he would've died in that cottage.</Source>
      <Dest>Had I known he was Jadro'Ra's killer, he would've died in that cottage.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then it is fortunate you did not.  You are a formdiable adversary, but I am not entirely sure you possess the means to kill him.</Source>
      <Dest>你该庆幸你没那么鲁莽。你的确是个难缠的对手，但是我并不认为你有本事可以杀了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He said he'd be waiting for you on the other side.</Source>
      <Dest>他说过他会在另外一边等你。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The cat always did have a knack for stating the obvious.  Indeed he will be waiting, and likely ignoring another task to do so.</Source>
      <Dest>猫科动物显然都明白一个诀窍。等待时机，不按套路出牌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He said he'd be waiting for you on the other side.</Source>
      <Dest>他说过他会在另外一边等你。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will remind him of that when I see him.</Source>
      <Dest>等我再见到他的时候我会提醒他的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've recovered the conjuration pages.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经修复了召唤部分的书页。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Excellent. To defeat a conjurer is to defeat the armies of Oblivion and death.  No small feat.</Source>
      <Dest>干得漂亮。击败一个召唤师等同于击败了一只湮灭中的不死军队，这可是大功一件。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We must do what we can to protect the innocent.</Source>
      <Dest>我们必须尽我们所能来保护无辜之人.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I agree.  Our principles will not win us this war, but without them we are no different than the ones we oppose.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意，坚持我们的原则可能无法赢得战争，但是如果摒弃了它们，那我们就与我们与之战斗的东西毫无区别了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until next time.</Source>
      <Dest>下回见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, Arch-Mage.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会，首席法师。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
