<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are Wood Elves even allowed to be farmers?</Source>
      <Dest>难道木精灵允许从农吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You sound like Valindor.  He never stops with the Green Pact and all this other religious nonsense.</Source>
      <Dest>You sound like Valindor.  He never stops with the Green Pact and all this other religious nonsense.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are Wood Elves even allowed to be farmers?</Source>
      <Dest>难道木精灵允许从农吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I can't pick a cabbage from the garden, but if a Nord picks that same cabbage and sells it to me to eat, it's okay?</Source>
      <Dest>所以我不能在自己菜园里摘卷心菜，但如果有个诺德人把卷心菜摘起来卖给我吃，这就合理了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are Wood Elves even allowed to be farmers?</Source>
      <Dest>难道木精灵允许从农吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The whole concept seems a little silly to me. </Source>
      <Dest> 我觉得整个想法有点傻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are Wood Elves even allowed to be farmers?</Source>
      <Dest>难道木精灵允许从农吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you're not going to eat vegetables, that's one thing, but don't look down on me for harvesting crops when there's plenty of green on your plate.</Source>
      <Dest>你不吃蔬菜是一回事，你居然敢在盘里装满菜时看不起我的劳动成果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a matter of fact, I was in Helgen when the dragon attacked.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，当海尔根被龙袭击时我就在场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, and you survived? Is it true that Alduin has 3 heads and 12 eyes? That he eats Bretons, but only the ugly ones? That his scales are pink?</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，而你居然生还了？奥杜因是不是真的有三头六臂？它是不是真只吃那些长得很抱歉的布莱顿人？他的鳞片是粉红色的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a matter of fact, I was in Helgen when the dragon attacked.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，当海尔根被龙袭击时我就在场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh never mind, you don't have to answer that.  Even I realize how silly that sounds. </Source>
      <Dest>哦，没关系，你不必回答。就连我也知道这听起来有多蠢。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a matter of fact, I was in Helgen when the dragon attacked.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，当海尔根被龙袭击时我就在场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, I never thought someone like you would choose me as a conversation partner.</Source>
      <Dest>我仍然不敢相信像你这么重要的人会愿意跟我说话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Taffy, pie, and sweet rolls mostly.</Source>
      <Dest>大部分是太妃糖、派，还有甜卷饼.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You've got a sweet tooth then.  That's not very healthy.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说你喜欢甜食了。这不是很健康。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Taffy, pie, and sweet rolls mostly.</Source>
      <Dest>大部分是太妃糖、派，还有甜卷饼.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I suppose most people nowadays just eat what they want and drink a  potion afterward.  If you can afford it, who am I to judge.</Source>
      <Dest>但是今时今日人们胡吃海塞，事后一瓶神奇药水搞定。如果人家有钱去搞这个，我又有什么权利去批判别人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about her made you change your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>她是怎样让你改变想法的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was the perfect embodiment of a Nord woman. Tall, pretty, and fair of skin. Only there was something strange about the way she spoke.</Source>
      <Dest>她是诺德女人的完美典范。修长，动人，皮肤白皙。只是她说话的方式有点奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about her made you change your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>她是怎样让你改变想法的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She called skeevers 'cave rats,' Falmer 'goblins,' and constantly complained about the cold. (Laughs) I was more of a Nord than she ever would be.  </Source>
      <Dest>她把雪鼠叫做“穴鼠“雪精灵叫做”地精“，还没完没了的抱怨寒冷的天气。（笑声）我和她比起来我更像个地道的诺德人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about her made you change your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>她是怎样让你改变想法的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's when I realized I didn't need to travel halfway across Tamriel to find my home. I was already here.</Source>
      <Dest>那正是我意识到我无需穿越半个泰瑞玛尔大陆寻找我的家乡，因为我已身置其中了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you ever thought about visiting Valenwood?</Source>
      <Dest>你有想过拜访威木省吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have. For a long time that was all I thought about. And it wasn't just to shut Valindor up. I really wanted to know about my heritage.  My home.</Source>
      <Dest>我想过。我曾经对此一直念念不忘。不仅仅是为让瓦林多闭上嘴，我真的想了解有关于我先祖的遗产，还有我的家园。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you ever thought about visiting Valenwood?</Source>
      <Dest>你有想过拜访威木省吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So every day I would skip a meal or pick a few more potatoes and eventually saved enough to make the trip.</Source>
      <Dest>所以每一天我都少吃一顿饭或者多挖点儿土豆，终于攒够了钱出去旅行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you ever thought about visiting Valenwood?</Source>
      <Dest>你有想过拜访威木省吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had everything packed.  All that was left was to say goodbye.  I thanked Addvild and Leonara for having me, and all my friends at the bunkhouse.</Source>
      <Dest>我一切都打包好了。接下来的就是离别。我感谢款待了我的阿德维尔德和莱奥娜，还有工棚里我所有的朋友们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you ever thought about visiting Valenwood?</Source>
      <Dest>你有想过拜访威木省吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>On my way to Solitude I made a stop in Morthal.  That's where I met this tavern maid. </Source>
      <Dest>我在去独孤城的路上在墨索尔城歇了一会，我正是在那里遇到这位侍女的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If nothing else, bears are the most annoying.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，熊是最惹人厌的东西了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Somebody once told me a bear won't attack you unless it feels threatened.  Now I realize he was trying to murder me.</Source>
      <Dest>以前有人告诉我除非熊觉得自己受到威胁，否则不会袭击人类。现在我明白了，他是想糊弄我害我被杀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As it so happens, I've joined the College of Winterhold.</Source>
      <Dest>真巧，我已经加入了冬堡学院。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Shouldn't you be studying then?  I'm not sure how talking to me will help you any.</Source>
      <Dest>Shouldn't you be studying then?  I'm not sure how talking to me will help you any.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Cooked meats, fish, and poultry.</Source>
      <Dest>煮熟的肉、鱼、和家禽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must be a warrior then, someone who likes their meat as bloody as their battles.  Although I did meet a soldier once who only ate vegetables.</Source>
      <Dest>你一定也是个战士吧，很多战士喜欢吃肉跟战斗一样血肉四溅。不过我也遇到过只吃蔬菜的士兵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Cooked meats, fish, and poultry.</Source>
      <Dest>煮熟的肉、鱼、和家禽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She came to the farm to pick the leeks and potatoes, so she could boil them in a stew.</Source>
      <Dest>她来农场摘了点大葱和土豆，然后她用它们煮成乱炖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Cooked meats, fish, and poultry.</Source>
      <Dest>煮熟的肉、鱼、和家禽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And the best part was, she was bigger and stronger than all the farm guards put together.</Source>
      <Dest>而最好的是，她比所有的农场守卫加起来个头还要大，还要强壮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm fine.  You?</Source>
      <Dest>我还好。你呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm doing okay.  (Sigh)  It's just another day with not a lot going on.  Is there anything in particular I can help you with?</Source>
      <Dest>我还好。  (叹息)  又是漫漫无趣的一天。有什么好事要我帮忙的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Seriously, just let me kill the guy. Problem solved.</Source>
      <Dest>说真的，让我干掉那家伙。问题解决。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It must be awfully convenient to go through life just murdering the people you don't like.</Source>
      <Dest>要是看谁不顺眼就杀谁，这日子不是活得容易到家了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Seriously, just let me kill the guy. Problem solved.</Source>
      <Dest>说真的，让我干掉那家伙。问题解决。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I'm thankful to have met Valindor.  Even the folks you don't get along with can teach you valuable things about yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>但我很庆幸遇见瓦林多。甚至那些我相处得不太好的家伙，也能教会我一些有用的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I prefer a balanced diet.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢均衡的膳食。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've heard that's the healthiest way to eat.  Although I'm not sure it matters if you know a good alchemist.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说那是最健康的饮食方法。不过如果你认识位出色的炼金师的话，那就是完全另外一回事了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Spiders.  All other answers are invalid.</Source>
      <Dest>是蜘蛛，没有别的可能了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm inclined to agree.  It's the hairs more than anything.  If spiders shaved, I don't think people would hate them as much.</Source>
      <Dest>我完全同意。体毛是重中之重。如果蜘蛛会剃毛，人们应该就不会那么讨厌蜘蛛了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does he make you feel ashamed?</Source>
      <Dest>他如何使你蒙羞？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've told Valindor many times that I've never been outside of Skyrim, but he'll still ask me what my favorite memories of our homeland are.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经多次跟瓦林多说过我从未离开过天际省，但他仍然会问我在我们的家乡最甜蜜的记忆是什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does he make you feel ashamed?</Source>
      <Dest>他如何使你蒙羞？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whenever I mention how beautiful the fall forest is, he'll tell me how the leaves in Silvenar turn with twice the color.</Source>
      <Dest>每当我提起希尔维纳有多美，他总会告诉我塞尔维那的树叶一年会变两次颜色。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does he make you feel ashamed?</Source>
      <Dest>他如何使你蒙羞？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or he and Ungrien will share stories about the way the cities rumble under your feet, or how a crop of new aromas bloom with each spring.</Source>
      <Dest>或他与安圭恩共诉轶事，使其城市驻于汝脚下隆隆作响，又或是春暖花开多纷的芬芳。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does he make you feel ashamed?</Source>
      <Dest>他如何使你蒙羞？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And none of it means anything to me.  When I sit at that table, I can't help but feel excluded.  As if I have to apologize for who I am.</Source>
      <Dest>而这一切对我来说毫无意义。每当我坐在那张桌前，我不禁干到排斥。仿佛我得顾影自怜似的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't you like Valindor?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会讨厌瓦林多？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He's not a bad person or anything.  It's just the way he's always going on about Valenwood.  It makes me feel like such an outsider.</Source>
      <Dest>他其实不是坏人什么的。他只是以自己的方式面对威木省。这让我觉得像一个局外人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why don't you like Valindor?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会讨厌瓦林多？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I may be a Bosmer by blood, but I was born and raised here, and someday I'll die here too. I shouldn't have to be ashamed of that.</Source>
      <Dest>也许从血统上来讲，我是个木精灵。但我在这里土生土长，总有一天也会死在这里。没什么好羞耻的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fantastic!  Thanks for asking!</Source>
      <Dest>棒极了!  感谢邀请!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You seem excited.  Tell Svana I'll have whatever you're having.  Maybe it'll help me forget how many leeks I picked for Addvild today.</Source>
      <Dest>你看起来很兴奋。跟丝瓦娜说，你要什么我跟你一样。也许能让我忘掉今天在雪蹄农场摘了多少韭菜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fantastic!  Thanks for asking!</Source>
      <Dest>棒极了!  感谢邀请!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, is there anything I can help you with?</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，有没有什么事是我能帮上你的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fantastic!  Thanks for asking!</Source>
      <Dest>棒极了!  感谢邀请!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You seem jubilant.  I tried that once, and I think it made my stomach ill.  I'd rather spend another eight hours on the farm.</Source>
      <Dest>你气色不错。我曾尝试过直到我的胃翻腾不止。我宁愿每天农场里辛苦八小时。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fantastic!  Thanks for asking!</Source>
      <Dest>棒极了!  感谢邀请!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, is there anything I can help you with?</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，有没有什么事是我能帮上你的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to ask you some questions.</Source>
      <Dest>我想问你些问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that's something that doesn't happen everyday.  You want to ask me questions?  </Source>
      <Dest>好吧，这种事可不会每天发生。你想问我什么问题吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to ask you some questions.</Source>
      <Dest>我想问你些问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm just a farmhand.  On the list of important folks in this town, I'm about as low and common as a borrowed robe.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是个农民。为镇上的重要人士列张表的话，我就是角落的一个小污点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to ask you some questions.</Source>
      <Dest>我想问你些问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I don't know who you think I am stranger, but I'm not at all interesting.  You on the other hand, I bet you've gone on all sorts of adventures.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我跟你说，陌生人，我不知道你认为我是谁而且我不鸟你。不过你就另当别论了，我打赌你一定有各式各样冒险故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Probably mammoths.</Source>
      <Dest>可能是猛犸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've never seen one.  Which might sound odd, considering I've lived in Skyrim all my life. </Source>
      <Dest>我都在天际住了一辈子了，一只也没见过，听起来很奇怪是吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Probably mammoths.</Source>
      <Dest>可能是猛犸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've heard they're mostly harmless though, unless you poke them.</Source>
      <Dest>I've heard they're mostly harmless though, unless you poke them.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Niluva?  The skooma addict?</Source>
      <Dest>尼路佤？那个斯库玛瘾君子？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nobody's perfect.  Well, besides Maven Black-Briar.  </Source>
      <Dest>没有人是完美的。呃，除了玛雯·黑荆棘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vegetables.  Strictly vegetables.</Source>
      <Dest>蔬菜，百分百蔬菜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not the answer I'd expect coming from a fellow Bosmer. Don't worry, I'm a farmer.  I'm the last person who's going to scold you about the Green Pact.</Source>
      <Dest>这可不像是一个木精灵作风。没关系，我是个农民。我可不会在绿色条约这点上指责你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vegetables.  Strictly vegetables.</Source>
      <Dest>蔬菜，百分百蔬菜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet you're as stout and hearty as any meat eater.  I'm beginning to wonder if I should switch to an all vegetable diet myself.</Source>
      <Dest>不过你比任何一个吃肉的都要结实。害我不得不考虑要做个百分百素食者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Farming is honorable work.</Source>
      <Dest>干农活儿是件体面活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know about honorable.  At least, I don't work the fields out of some sense duty, or for someone else's admiration.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不知道什么叫体面。反正我在这块地上耕作不是为了什么责任，也不是为了得到别人的赞许。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Farming is honorable work.</Source>
      <Dest>干农活儿是件体面活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do it so I won't go hungry. Sometimes it happens anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>我干这活是为了不挨饿。尽管如此，有时我还是得挨饿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ah, Sadrin.  He will never climb those verdant hills.</Source>
      <Dest>什么，萨汀。他不可能会去爬这些荒山的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, he is quite a character.  It's funny how he insists on staying at Haelga's when he clearly can afford better.</Source>
      <Dest>Yes, he is quite a character.  It's funny how he insists on staying at Haelga's when he clearly can afford better.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've yet to meet this Sadrin.</Source>
      <Dest>我至今还没见过这位萨汀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I hope you like talking about Haelga, because that's pretty much all he cares about.</Source>
      <Dest>Well, I hope you like talking about Haelga, because that's pretty much all he cares about.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay, fine. Is there anything you want to ask me?</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，好吧。你有什么要问我的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure.  For starters, um...what's your favorite thing to eat in Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>当然。对于开胃菜，嗯...在天际省里你最喜欢吃什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That depends on whether you're willing to loan me some money.</Source>
      <Dest>这取决于你愿不愿意借给我钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I don't have any to spare.  You might be better off asking Addvild.  The Snow-Shods take care of their farm hands.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，我可没什么好施舍的。你最好还是问问阿德维尔德，雪蹄农场对员工挺好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That depends on whether you're willing to loan me some money.</Source>
      <Dest>这取决于你愿不愿意借给我钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I work the farm, but not in any official capacity.  Addvild just buys the crops I pick.  Is there anything else you needed?</Source>
      <Dest>我在农场干活，但不是什么正式的生计。我只是为阿德维尔德挑选要购买的庄稼。你还有什么需求吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Terrible.  I have this urge to just punch whatever's in front of me.</Source>
      <Dest>真糟。我有一股不顾眼前一切都一拳头招呼的冲动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then do you mind turning around?  I'd rather not take a chance.  I've got enough aches already working the farm for Addvild.</Source>
      <Dest>那么你介意掉头回去么？我宁愿不冒险一试。我在阿德维尔德的农场工作时已经够火大了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Niluva?  Who's that?</Source>
      <Dest>尼路佤？谁在那？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You haven't met her?  She's a Dunmer woman with eyes like ebony and a voice as smooth as the surface of Lake Honrich.</Source>
      <Dest>你还没见过她吗？她是一个有着一双如玄曜石般璀璨双眼的丹莫女人，她的声音如同亨利奇湖的水面一般温和。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If Valenwood was so great, he never would've left.</Source>
      <Dest>要是威木省真的那么好，他根本不会离开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My thoughts exactly.  I think he pities me, but I should be the one pitying him.  He's the one who left his home and abandoned his craft, not me.</Source>
      <Dest>My thoughts exactly.  I think he pities me, but I should be the one pitying him.  He's the one who left his home and abandoned his craft, not me.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you spend your whole life in a cave, you'd never know the sun's warmth.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你耗其一生于洞穴，又怎能了解阳光的温暖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe so, but from what I hear, not everyone finds it warm.  Sometimes it's too hot, sometimes it burns. </Source>
      <Dest>Maybe so, but from what I hear, not everyone finds it warm.  Sometimes it's too hot, sometimes it burns. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you spend your whole life in a cave, you'd never know the sun's warmth.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你耗其一生于洞穴，又怎能了解阳光的温暖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why seek the sun when you're comfortable in the shade?</Source>
      <Dest>当你可在阴影中快活时为何寻求烈阳？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A simple life is best.  Having riches makes you fearful of losing it.</Source>
      <Dest>简单的生活才是最好的，过于富有让你患得患失。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're right.  I always hear about how the Black-Briars are scheming, or how their children are getting into trouble.</Source>
      <Dest>你说得对。我总是听说黑色荆棘如何费尽心机且功于心计，或者是他们的孩子是麻烦精。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A simple life is best.  Having riches makes you fearful of losing it.</Source>
      <Dest>简单的生活才是最好的，过于富有让你患得患失。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Meanwhile, Vulwulf and Asgeir storm about Riften as if there were a nail lodged in their bottoms.</Source>
      <Dest>与此同时，冯尔乌和艾斯盖尔冲向裂谷城像屁股钉了铁钉似的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I enjoy conversing with everyday people.  There's always something to learn.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢和平凡人说话。总是能学到点东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, then ask your questions, and I'll try my best to impart what little wisdom I have.  Although I'd still rather talk about you.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，问吧，我会倾囊相授的。不过我依然宁愿谈论下你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are there are a lot of contract farmers like yourself?</Source>
      <Dest>像你这样的佃农很多吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A lot of travelers come by and help out, but ever since Hagravi left about five years ago, there hasn't been another steady farmhand since.</Source>
      <Dest>以前很多过路的旅行者都过来帮忙，但是自从大约五年前海格威离开，那以后再也没有稳定的农场工人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are there are a lot of contract farmers like yourself?</Source>
      <Dest>像你这样的佃农很多吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vulwulf will never admit it though.  I've always said when they bury him, they're going to need three coffins.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然冯尔乌永远不会承认。他们在埋他的时候，我总是会跟他们说他们得准备三幅棺材。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are there are a lot of contract farmers like yourself?</Source>
      <Dest>像你这样的佃农很多吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One for him, one for his pride, and one for that cauldron he calls a belly.</Source>
      <Dest>一副装他人，一副装他的骄傲，还有一副被装他那个沙锅大的肥肚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you ever consider working for the Snow-Shods?</Source>
      <Dest>你有考虑过为雪蹄家族做事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course.  Merryfair Farm can't afford to hire another hand, while the Snow-Shods have enough to pay a dozen farmers and a score of guards.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了。美瑞菲尔农场雇不起另一个人了，但是雪蹄农场还有足够的钱雇上一打的雇农和一大票护卫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you ever consider working for the Snow-Shods?</Source>
      <Dest>你有考虑过为雪蹄家族做事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only the Snow-Shods only hire other Nords.  True Sons of Skyrim, basically.  </Source>
      <Dest>基本上雪蹄家族只雇佣诺德人。天际的真传人！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you ever consider working for the Snow-Shods?</Source>
      <Dest>你有考虑过为雪蹄家族做事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe things might be different under Asgeir, but I don't have my fingers crossed.  He's pretty much a mirror of his father.</Source>
      <Dest>也许艾斯盖尔接过手，情况会有所不同，但是我觉得希望不大。他简直是他父亲的翻版。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you ever consider working for the Snow-Shods?</Source>
      <Dest>你有考虑过为雪蹄家族做事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They'd never hire me, even though I'm pretty sure they need me.  </Source>
      <Dest>尽管我非常确信他们需要我，但他们完全没有打算雇佣我。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I enjoy a good warm stew.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢美味的热汤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must spend a lot of time up north. Stew's good, but it's not too popular in Riften. But in a place like Dawnstar, I bet there's nothing finer.</Source>
      <Dest>You must spend a lot of time up north. Stew's good, but it's not too popular in Riften. But in a place like Dawnstar, I bet there's nothing finer.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything else?</Source>
      <Dest>还有其他事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything else?</Source>
      <Dest>还有其他事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, that's it.  I guess I can't even ask interesting questions.</Source>
      <Dest>没了，就是这样。看来我连问点有趣的事都不行啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does Addvild offer you room and board?</Source>
      <Dest>阿德维尔德给你提供食宿吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, but I don't mind.  Haelga's Bunkhouse isn't too expensive, the beds are cozy enough, and Niluva's easy on the eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>No, but I don't mind.  Haelga's Bunkhouse isn't too expensive, the beds are cozy enough, and Niluva's easy on the eyes.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does Addvild offer you room and board?</Source>
      <Dest>阿德维尔德给你提供食宿吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know Sadrin thinks all of Mundus revolves around Haelga, and Svana has her share of suitors, but I don't know, neither of them strike my fancy.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道萨汀认为全宇宙都围着哈尔嘉转，丝瓦娜也有不少追求者，但我不明白的是，她们两个对我都不具诱惑力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does Addvild offer you room and board?</Source>
      <Dest>阿德维尔德给你提供食宿吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At least, not the way Niluva does.  To be honest, I love everything about the Bunkhouse, except maybe Valindor.</Source>
      <Dest>至少，尼路瓦不会这么做。老实说，我喜欢这房子的一切，当然，除了瓦林多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does Addvild offer you room and board?</Source>
      <Dest>阿德维尔德给你提供食宿吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, but I don't mind.  Haelga's Bunkhouse isn't too expensive, the beds are cozy enough, and Niluva's easy on the eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>No, but I don't mind.  Haelga's Bunkhouse isn't too expensive, the beds are cozy enough, and Niluva's easy on the eyes.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does Addvild offer you room and board?</Source>
      <Dest>阿德维尔德给你提供食宿吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know Sadrin thinks all of Mundus revolves around Haelga, and Svana has her share of suitors, but I don't know, neither of them strike my fancy.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道萨汀认为全宇宙都围着哈尔嘉转，丝瓦娜也有不少追求者，但我不明白的是，她们两个对我都不具诱惑力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does Addvild offer you room and board?</Source>
      <Dest>阿德维尔德给你提供食宿吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At least, not the way Niluva does.  To be honest, I love everything about the Bunkhouse.  </Source>
      <Dest>至少，这不是尼路佤的风格。说实话，我喜欢哈尔嘉工棚里的一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does Addvild offer you room and board?</Source>
      <Dest>阿德维尔德给你提供食宿吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I admit, I didn't always feel that way.  Valindor used to bug me, but...but I never wanted him dead.</Source>
      <Dest>我承认。我感觉有点不太对。 瓦林多确实很困扰我，但……但我从没想要他死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>People.</Source>
      <Dest>大家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?  I hope you don't like Wood Elves.  May I recommend a nice, hefty, Snow-Shod steak?</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗？我希望你讨厌木精灵。允许我向你推荐一块鲜美，多汁的雪蹄肉排。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>People.</Source>
      <Dest>大家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm kidding of course.  But if you're serious, you might want to head west.  Bolli's friend Kleppr lives in Markarth, and there's been rumors.</Source>
      <Dest>我当然是开玩笑的。但如果你是认真的，也许你可以往西走。有传言说，波利的朋友克莱珀就住在马卡斯城。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure he means no harm. He just misses Valenwood.</Source>
      <Dest>我确信他没有恶意，他只是太想念骠木省。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know, I don't mean to say he doesn't like me.  It's much, much worse.  He pities me.  </Source>
      <Dest>我知道，我不是说他不喜欢我。而是，他对我有一种更糟，更糟的感情，他（居然）怜悯我。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've got the witches' pox and I need to blow my nose. Quick, lend me your tunic.</Source>
      <Dest>我得了女巫的瘟疫，而且我流鼻涕。快，把外套借给我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't think that's a good idea.  You might want to head over to Elgrim's and buy a potion for that.  Although you don't look sick to me.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得这不是个好主意。你也许该去艾尔格瑞姆的店里买瓶药水。虽说我看你没多大病。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've got the witches' pox and I need to blow my nose. Quick, lend me your tunic.</Source>
      <Dest>我得了女巫的瘟疫，而且我流鼻涕。快，把外套借给我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you get a health potion with it, maybe you can send half that bottle my way.  The Divines know I need one after picking leeks all day.</Source>
      <Dest>If you get a health potion with it, maybe you can send half that bottle my way.  The Divines know I need one after picking leeks all day.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Valindor is a cruel Elf and should be thrown in jail for his callousness.</Source>
      <Dest>瓦林多是一个残忍的精灵，他应以残忍为罪名而扔进监狱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, okay, I get it. Maybe I'm being a bit melodramatic. I know he just misses his home, but I don't see why he has to pile his frustrations on me. </Source>
      <Dest>Okay, okay, I get it. Maybe I'm being a bit melodramatic. I know he just misses his home, but I don't see why he has to pile his frustrations on me. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Remain Silent)</Source>
      <Dest>（保持沉默）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't like your look stranger.  There's malice behind those eyes.  </Source>
      <Dest>我不喜欢你的目光陌生人，那双眼睛后面隐藏着恶意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Remain Silent)</Source>
      <Dest>（保持沉默）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can't see why you'd want to hurt me though, I'm not important enough to have made any enemies.</Source>
      <Dest>我还是不明白你为什么想要伤害我。我还没重要到能四处树敌的地步。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I can kill Valindor. Then the bunkhouse will be perfect.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以杀了瓦林多。那么工棚就没事了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh no, I don't want him dead!  He hasn't broken any laws.</Source>
      <Dest>哦不，我不想让他死！他什么罪也没犯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>More than you know.  You stand before the Dragonborn.</Source>
      <Dest>何止如此。你正站在龙裔面前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you...you slay dragons?  If I ever did something like that, the people of Riften wouldn't hear the end of it.  </Source>
      <Dest>所以你……你屠龙？如果我曾经做过像那样的事情，裂谷城的人们会不知疲倦的讨论我的丰功伟绩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>More than you know.  You stand before the Dragonborn.</Source>
      <Dest>何止如此。你正站在龙裔面前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd change my name to Peragorn the Dragonslayer or something, and I'd have Addvild fetch my boots.</Source>
      <Dest>我倒宁肯把自己的名字改成屠龙者佩勒根或者类似的什么东西,这样我就能随便使唤阿德威尔德那个家伙啦.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>More than you know.  You stand before the Dragonborn.</Source>
      <Dest>何止如此。你正站在龙裔面前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wouldn't be asking him questions about his life, that's for sure.  So I'm not sure why you want to talk to me.</Source>
      <Dest>我不会对他的生活问这问那的，我敢保证。所以我有点没弄明白为什么你想跟我谈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I did join the Thieves Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>我的确加入了盗贼工会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd be more worried if I actually had coin you could steal.  You'd probably be better off picking wheat than picking my pocket.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我口袋里真的有几个小钱能让你偷的话我会更焦虑的。（所以说）比起使劲地想从我口袋里挖出几个钱来，你还是去挖小麦靠谱一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I did join the Thieves Guild.</Source>
      <Dest>我的确加入了盗贼工会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which means you came here to talk.  I'm not sure about what.  I don't even have any gossip to share.</Source>
      <Dest>这说明你是过来聊天的。这点我不是很确信，因为我根本没什么小道消息可以与你分享嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the best way to pull potatoes from the soil?</Source>
      <Dest>要把土豆从地里拔出来最好的办法是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have to sort of ease the stalk out of the ground, and then claw around the dirt.  It's still pretty easy compared to the farm work up north.</Source>
      <Dest>你得犒劳一下看守的人，在土里忙活几下。比起北方的农场这活还算是轻松的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the best way to pull potatoes from the soil?</Source>
      <Dest>要把土豆从地里拔出来最好的办法是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've got a bad back though, and I have to spend half my earnings over at Elgrim's Elixirs.</Source>
      <Dest>我的背不太好，光是在艾尔格瑞姆神药那里就花掉我一半的收入。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the best way to pull potatoes from the soil?</Source>
      <Dest>要把土豆从地里拔出来最好的办法是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The rest I spend on food, shelter, and maybe the occasional bottle of mead.  I've got no complaints though.</Source>
      <Dest>其余部分我花费在食，住，也许偶尔会弄一瓶蜂蜜酒。起码我不抱怨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the best way to pull potatoes from the soil?</Source>
      <Dest>要把土豆从地里拔出来最好的办法是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I had money, I'm not sure what to spend it on.</Source>
      <Dest>我就算有钱也不知道该怎么花。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's life on the farm working out for you?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得在农场里的生活怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good. The climate here in Riften is ideal for the crops we grow.  </Source>
      <Dest>好极了。裂谷城的气候对于我们种植的农作物非常理想。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's life on the farm working out for you?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得在农场里的生活怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The soil is warm, but not too warm where the tubers revert to leaves.  In some places the ground is so hard you need a shovel to harvest things.</Source>
      <Dest>块茎发芽的这片土壤温度适宜，但是别太暖和了。在一些地方土地硬到你需要一把铁铲来收获作物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's life on the farm working out for you?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得在农场里的生活怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here, you can pull out the leeks by the stems.  The potatoes require a little more care, so as not to damage them.</Source>
      <Dest>Here, you can pull out the leeks by the stems.  The potatoes require a little more care, so as not to damage them.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Mortals.  The most dangerous beast, the most challenging game.</Source>
      <Dest>凡人。最危险的野兽，最具挑战性的游戏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're probably right.  Luckily, around here you don't get too many bandits or mages, but there are plenty of thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>也许你是对的。幸运的是，在这里你不会遇到强盗或者法师，但这里小偷多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've mostly just scavenged and wandered.  Nothing special.</Source>
      <Dest>我一般除了觅食就是瞎逛，没啥特别的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You've seen more in one day than I've seen in all my life.  I don't mean that in a negative way though.  I don't really care to see it.</Source>
      <Dest>你一天的经历事比我一辈子都多。我也不是说这很消极或什么坏事。我见到的话我也不会反感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've mostly just scavenged and wandered.  Nothing special.</Source>
      <Dest>我一般除了觅食就是瞎逛，没啥特别的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My life is here, harvesting crops for the Snow-Shods.  It's a simple life, but I can't see what I have to offer you beyond how to pick potatoes.</Source>
      <Dest>我在这里给雪蹄收获作物，以此为生。生活的简简单单，我实在不知道除了教你如何挑选土豆以外，我还能为你做些什么了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm suffering from bone break fever and highly contagious.</Source>
      <Dest>我患有骨痛热并伴有高度传染性.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Contagious?  Don't you need broken bones to catch bone break fever?  Oh wait, does that mean you're going to break mine?</Source>
      <Dest>会感染的？不是你得骨头断才能得骨痛热吗？等等，难道说你要打断我的骨头？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm suffering from bone break fever and highly contagious.</Source>
      <Dest>我患有骨痛热并伴有高度传染性.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I guess I've already broken my back picking wheat for the Snow-Shods, so one more won't make a difference.</Source>
      <Dest>但我想我已经在替雪蹄收获小麦的时候伤了我的背，所以再多一个也没啥区别啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, hello there. How are you?</Source>
      <Dest>噢，你好啊。最近过的怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is the obvious answer, but dragons.</Source>
      <Dest>这个答案很明显吧，而龙的话就太。。。。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, right.  Some farmers will tell you a swarm of locusts is scarier than any dragon.  But I don't know, locusts don't breathe fire.</Source>
      <Dest>噢对，一些农民会告诉你蝗虫群比任何一条龙都要令人胆寒。但是我反正是不懂，蝗虫可不会喷火。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>More coin, more problems.  Mainly, the problem of unlimited happiness.</Source>
      <Dest>钱越多，问题越多。不过主要问题还是钱太多，太爽了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm not sure I agree.  The Snow-Shods and Black-Briars have enough gold to fill the Ratways, but they don't seem all that happy about it.</Source>
      <Dest>我也不知道我该不该同意你这个看法。雪蹄家和黑荆棘家的金子多得都能塞满整条鼠道了，但他们也没快乐到哪里去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>More coin, more problems.  Mainly, the problem of unlimited happiness.</Source>
      <Dest>钱越多，问题越多。不过主要问题还是钱太多，太爽了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes I'm glad I don't work under Vulwulf.  I don't make as much as Addvild or Leonara, but I can make my own hours and work at my own pace.</Source>
      <Dest>有事我会很庆幸自己不在乌尔武夫手底下工作。我做的东西不像阿德维尔德或利奥娜拉那么多，但我可以自己安排时间，以自己的节奏做工。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Raw meats, fruits, and vegetables.  Whatever I can scrape together.</Source>
      <Dest>生肉，水果，蔬菜。任何东西我都可以炖一块去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I imagine that's what you have to eat, but it can't be your favorite thing to eat, can it?  If so, you're missing out.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜这是你得吃的食物，而不是你想吃的食物，对吧？如果是这样的话，你可错过好东西了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Raw meats, fruits, and vegetables.  Whatever I can scrape together.</Source>
      <Dest>生肉，水果，蔬菜。任何东西我都可以炖一块去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then again, who am I to tell you that.  I've lived my whole life by taking pride in the simple things.</Source>
      <Dest>其次，我又有什么资格跟你说。我一生为简单美好的食物感到满足。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Raw meats, fruits, and vegetables.  Whatever I can scrape together.</Source>
      <Dest>生肉，水果，蔬菜。任何东西我都可以炖一块去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And my idea of a fancy meal is a rabbit haunch with a side of freshly cut cabbage.</Source>
      <Dest>而我心目中的美味佳肴则是一块儿兔腰加一份新鲜出土的卷心菜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My spouse.</Source>
      <Dest>我的爱人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ooh, I wouldn't touch that subject with a pair of enchanted gloves.  Riften is full of happy newlyweds.  The priests don't take kindly to negativity.</Source>
      <Dest>哦。我不会碰这副有魔力的手套，裂谷城住着许多的新婚夫妇，祭司肯定不会对这有负面影响的东西友好。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My spouse.</Source>
      <Dest>我的爱人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, at least until Jade joined the Temple.  They say every marriage she blesses is doomed to fall apart.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，至少让玉洁加入神庙吧。人们都说凡是被她祝福的婚姻后来都以破裂告终。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should be ashamed of yourself, the way you spit on your ancestors.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该为辱没祖宗感到羞愧。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My parents migrated to Skyrim before I was born.  Whatever connection I share with Valenwood starts and ends in the mirror.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父母在我出生前就搬家到天际省了。我同威木省之间的联系如同镜花水月一般，无始无终。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should be ashamed of yourself, the way you spit on your ancestors.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该为辱没祖宗感到羞愧。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's funny. Valindor pities who I am, but if he were to meet someone here and have children, they'd look like him, but resemble me.</Source>
      <Dest>有趣的是，瓦林多开始可怜我，可如果他是来跟谁碰头带走孩子，他们看起来像他,但跟我相似。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If my conversation partners were limited to my peers, I'd be a mute.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我的聊天对象只限于和我同等的人，我就无话可谈了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, but you still could aim a little higher than me.  The Jarl's keep has plenty of interesting folks, I recommend you talk to them.</Source>
      <Dest>对，不过你的目标还是得比我高点儿。领主的城堡里有趣的家伙有的是。我建议你跟他们好好聊聊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If my conversation partners were limited to my peers, I'd be a mute.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我的聊天对象只限于和我同等的人，我就无话可谈了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you're that intent on asking me questions, go ahead.  But I'd much rather talk about you.</Source>
      <Dest>不过你要是有事想问我，就尽管问。我更想聊聊你的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is that all?</Source>
      <Dest>就这样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is that all?</Source>
      <Dest>就这样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, no, I got more.  I think.  Okay, how about this.  What do you think is the most fearsome beast in Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>不，不，我想，我还有更多的，好吧，你认为在天际省最可怕的野兽是什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until next time.</Source>
      <Dest>下回见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tidings.</Source>
      <Dest>怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么心事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么想法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How can I help you?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么我能效劳的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is it?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose there's no harm in that. What did you have in mind?</Source>
      <Dest>我想这有益无害。你怎么看？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know, next to Jade, you're probably the last person I should ask for advice.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道，仅次于玉洁，你也许是我最不该寻求建议的人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry Sadrin.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉萨汀.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Haelga?  No, not that I'm aware of.  Although she did ask me once if I've ever seen a woman wear Daedric boots...</Source>
      <Dest>Haelga?  No, not that I'm aware of.  Although she did ask me once if I've ever seen a woman wear Daedric boots...</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
