<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What manner of spell is this?  I am curious.</Source>
      <Dest>我很好奇这究竟是一种怎样的魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A great calm has swept over me.</Source>
      <Dest>一个卓越的平静术扫过了我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My claws feel sharper, as does my mind.</Source>
      <Dest>我的爪子更锋利了,同样的我的头脑也无比的清晰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh! I am invisible!  This is not permanent, I hope.</Source>
      <Dest>噢！我隐身了！希望这不是永久的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A healing spell!  If body language speaks eloquently, I hope my vigor expresses the proper amount of thanks.</Source>
      <Dest>治愈法术!  如果肢体语言比划得富有表现力的话，希望这气势能表达出足够的感谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, that feels good.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，那感觉真不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Interesting that these vampires worship the same master as the dog, yet the two are hostile toward each other. Chaos rules the walls of this shrine.</Source>
      <Dest>有趣的是这些吸血鬼跟那些狗崇拜的对象都是一样的，而这两方居然相互敌对。混沌统治着这祭坛的墙壁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The source of the mist lies ahead. Do you sense it? It is death rising from the ash.</Source>
      <Dest>迷雾的源头就在前面。你感觉到了吗？那是灰烬中升起的死亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The enchantments on these spiders are but a jester's trick. Their true power still lies in the poison that drips from their fangs.</Source>
      <Dest>在这些蜘蛛上的魔法只是供人嘲笑的把戏。 它们真正的力量仍然在它们的尖齿滴下的毒汁之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A spider den. We must be cautious, for the hasty fly will soon discover it can no longer flap its wings.</Source>
      <Dest>一个蜘蛛巢穴。我们必须谨慎点，不然只会像仓促的飞行一样，不久之后就会发现再也无力挥动翅膀</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The first was a test of speed.  Is this the same, or does it require cunning? The Greybeards would not have sent you here without the answer.</Source>
      <Dest>首先是速度的测试。这是跟之前一样，还是说需要耍点小聪明呢？如果没有答案的话，灰胡子就不会送你来这儿了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There she is.  A bird of Hircine.  And she is alone.  It seems this flock does not fly as one.  This is to our advantage.</Source>
      <Dest>她在那。一只海尔辛之鸟。并且只有她一个，看起来她们没有结伴而行。这对我们很有利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If the sentries outside were any indication, there is something in this cave they wish to conceal.  It could be a treasure, or it could be a crime.</Source>
      <Dest>如果警卫外面有任何的迹象,那么他们希望隐藏洞穴里某样东西。  这可能是一件财宝,或也有可能是一名罪犯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Shivers) This grotto is as cold as the Jerall Mountains it lays beside.  It feels as if I am wearing a coat of icicles.</Source>
      <Dest>（颤抖着）这个洞穴冷地好像杰哈尔山脉就在旁边一样。感觉我好像穿了一件冰织成的大衣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So the Elf flees impatiently, taking the Golden Claw with him.  At times like this, I like to meditate, and let the solution present itself.</Source>
      <Dest>于是那只精灵带着那黄金龙爪急急忙忙地逃跑了。在这种时候，我更希望去谋划，然后让解决方法自然而然地浮现出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A thrall.  That one is a lesser vampire, but we should be careful that we do not stir the rest of the coven when we mount our attack.</Source>
      <Dest>一个奴隶。看来那是只低级吸血鬼，不过我们还是要小心进攻的时候别打搅到其余的大聚会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Necromancers.  We must be swift, and kill them before they raise their pets from their slumber.</Source>
      <Dest>亡灵法师。我们必须速战速决，在他们唤醒沉睡的宠物之前干掉他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Foes block our path.  Balance can only be restored when one side perishes.</Source>
      <Dest>敌人挡住了我们的路。只有在其中一方死去的时候，平衡才能得以恢复。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is a spectacular sight. Knowing the ordeals we have endured, Meridia grants us a reprieve, and blesses us with this view of her domain.</Source>
      <Dest>这个景象真壮观，梅瑞迪亚知晓我们一路所受的磨难，便给我们稍事缓解，同时用她领土中的美景祝福我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dwarven machinations are a wonder to behold, but they are dangerous as well. We should not be caught looking.</Source>
      <Dest>矮人的阴谋是一个奇迹,但同时，它们很危险。我们不应该陷进去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Simply magnificent!  A fitting mausoleum for the founder of the Greybeards.  Only a handful of mortals will ever witness what we are now seeing.</Source>
      <Dest>简洁而不失华丽!  一个灰胡子追随者应得的陵墓.  只有极少数凡人得以见证我们今天看到的一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So this is Nightingale Hall.  It is...understated, yet a powerful visual nonetheless.  A perfect hideout for the servants of Nocturnal.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，这就是夜莺大厅了。它……低调而不失华丽。诺克图娜尔仆人的完美藏身处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The guards are many.  Stay calm, and wait for the opportunity to open.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫很多，冷静下来，等待机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Never in all my years at the temple did I think I would witness such a mechanical wonder.  Even dormant, its effects are palpable.</Source>
      <Dest>我在庙里那么多年都没看到过这么神奇的机械.  做梦都没有, 效果显着.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>More vampires.  Sun and stars hidden from sight, the moonflower blooms in this cavern of night.  But not for much longer.</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼更多了。太阳和星星不见踪影，月光花在夜晚的洞穴中盛开，但这种现状不会存在太久了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One of the keepers lays in that coffin.  But beware.  The light shines on the stage, but danger lurks in the audience.</Source>
      <Dest>其中一个守卫躺在那个棺材里。小心，舞台上灯光闪烁，舞台下危机暗伏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Brittleshin Pass.  Much like Azura's shrine, some of the world's most decorative sights are built to welcome travelers.</Source>
      <Dest>布莱特辛山隘。有点像阿祖拉神坛, 这个世界上最美妙的景观就为那些旅行者们敞开大门。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lamia, vampires, and succubi.  All use beauty to seduce their prey, but only the Spriggan uses the beauty of nature.  This grove is one such trap.  </Source>
      <Dest>妖妇，吸血鬼，还有女妖 。它们都通过美貌来引诱它们的猎物。但只有树精用自然之美诱惑众生。 这片树林就是这样的一个陷阱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dwemer Museum!  I have heard that this collection is second only to that excavated from the ruins in Stros M'Kai.</Source>
      <Dest>锻莫博物馆！我听说这里的藏品的丰富程度仅次于图尔斯·迈凯那儿的遗迹所出土的文物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A dragon wall!  To find such splendor in this cave, is to find a diamond lodged in a muddy road.  I am glad to have walked it.</Source>
      <Dest>一堵龙墙!  在这洞穴中找如此辉煌的东西，简直就像在泥泞小路上找钻石。  我很乐意走一趟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such a sight!  Qa'Dojo is pleased to have witnessed this wonder.</Source>
      <Dest>好漂亮！奎兜啾很高兴见证这一奇迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dwemer built great cities that almost stand the test of time. Yet no structure can or should stand forever.  Time willing.</Source>
      <Dest>锻莫修建的伟大城市几乎经得起时间的考验。但没有建筑能够永远屹立不倒。时间会证明一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A cave.  Let us enter.  We should not fear the darkness, as it is as much a part of life as the light.</Source>
      <Dest>一个洞穴。我们进去吧。黑暗不会让我们恐惧, 因为它和光明都是我们生命中的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Nords seek to defy the final arbiter, but if time will not take their souls, he will claim their flesh, and chaos will take their minds.</Source>
      <Dest>那些诺德人搜寻并反抗最后的仲裁者。但即使时间没有磨灭他们的灵魂，也会索取他们的肉体，使他们的精神产生混乱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>哈啰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wish to thank you.  Wisdom is always the best gift, but today this will have to suffice.</Source>
      <Dest>我要谢谢你，智慧永远是最好的赠礼，但是今天的话这个就很足够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your words are kind.  Although I would've liked to hear a parable.</Source>
      <Dest>你的话很贴切，尽管我不喜欢听寓言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) I did not realize you enjoyed my parables.  In fact, I thought you may have grown tired of them.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 没想到你竟然对我的寓言感兴趣。事实上，我原本以为你会慢慢对它们感到厌倦呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your words are kind.  Although I would've liked to hear a parable.</Source>
      <Dest>你的话很贴切，尽管我不喜欢听寓言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, if you wish to hear another, it may be wise for you to become the fisherman, rather than request another fish.</Source>
      <Dest>可是，如果你愿听别的。 最明智的做法是你学会自己干，而不是问人拿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you were to train as a monk, perhaps in twenty or thirty years, you too will learn to recall a story whenever you seek philosophical guidance.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你想被训练成一名修道士，在二三十年之后，你也许同样会在每次寻求哲学的指引之时回忆起一个故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your words are kind.  Although I would've liked to hear a parable.</Source>
      <Dest>你的话很贴切，尽管我不喜欢听寓言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your words are kind.  Although I would've liked to hear a parable.</Source>
      <Dest>你的话很贴切，尽管我不喜欢听寓言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until then, I will be more than happy to feed you the occasional parable, should the inspiration strike.</Source>
      <Dest>如果到时候我有灵感的话，我会很乐意用当时想到的喻意指导你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Aedra and Daedra are not Gods.  They are extremely powerful mortals.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵和魔族不是神，但她们都拥有比凡人们强大的力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Much like Talos, many believe divinity can be acquired through achievement.  It reminds me of the tale of the acclaimed assassin from Black Marsh. </Source>
      <Dest>很多人相信获得足够多的成就能让他们获得神格，就像塔洛斯一样。这使我想起了那个从黑沼泽省来的声名远扬的刺客的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Guildmaster in Riften requested the assassin train his thieves in matters of stealth.  However, the assassin refused.</Source>
      <Dest>裂谷城的公会首领要求这名刺客教他的盗贼手下一些潜行的技巧。然而这名刺客拒绝了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Aedra and Daedra are not Gods.  They are extremely powerful mortals.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵和魔族不是神，但她们都拥有比凡人们强大的力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For while in the swamps of Black Marsh he was a master, in the forests of Riften he was but a novice.</Source>
      <Dest>当在黑沼泽的湿地中时他是大师，而在裂谷城的森林里他却只是一个菜鸟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Aedra and Daedra are not Gods.  They are extremely powerful mortals.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵和魔族不是神，但她们都拥有比凡人们强大的力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Aedra and Daedra are not Gods.  They are extremely powerful mortals.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵和魔族不是神，但她们都拥有比凡人们强大的力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A great mortal is a master of their own plane, where a God is a limited by none.</Source>
      <Dest>一名了不起的凡人只有在他自己领域的时候才是大师，而神却是全知全能的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm.  That is unfortunate, for even the most shallow of relationships are teaching experiences, and the loss of another should be mourned.</Source>
      <Dest>哼嗯，真是不幸，即使只有最浅显的师生之谊也是如此。而且我们应该为我们失去的另外那人而默哀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you joking?  I barely knew Savrot Iron and Miriam Irvine.</Source>
      <Dest>你是在开玩笑吗？我几乎都没听说过Savrot Iron 和Miriam Irvine。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And Namira willing, even death itself has much to teach us.  I am reminded of a parable, if you wish to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>即使死亡本身使我们懂得了很多，娜米拉依旧渴望着。  我想起一个寓言,不知你是否愿意听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you joking?  I barely knew Savrot Iron and Miriam Irvine.</Source>
      <Dest>你是在开玩笑吗？我几乎都没听说过Savrot Iron 和Miriam Irvine。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am on nobody's side but my own.  You'd do well to remember that.</Source>
      <Dest>我只服务与自己，不倾向任何人，你最好记住这一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course.  But, just as Sanguine brings merriment through desire, a selfish action may affect others in ways that seem selfless.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了.但是，正如血腥凭借欲望给人以快感，一个自私的行为可能会以看似无私的方式影响到其他人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am on nobody's side but my own.  You'd do well to remember that.</Source>
      <Dest>我只服务与自己，不倾向任何人，你最好记住这一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You sought only personal glory and gain, but through this ambition, the balance of our world has been restored.</Source>
      <Dest>你寻求的仅是个人荣誉和利益，但这野心会导致我们世界的平衡恢复到原先的样子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am on nobody's side but my own.  You'd do well to remember that.</Source>
      <Dest>我只服务与自己，不倾向任何人，你最好记住这一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like Molag Bal, you swell with power, and if that power becomes a danger, Boethiah will strike from the shadows.</Source>
      <Dest>就像莫拉格·巴尔, 你的能力随着这种力量不断增强，假如某天这力量变为威胁，那波耶西亚就会从黑暗中突袭而来.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am on nobody's side but my own.  You'd do well to remember that.</Source>
      <Dest>我只服务与自己，不倾向任何人，你最好记住这一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This, you would do well to remember, for there is always a counterbalance, whether it be a formidable foe or a convincing idea.</Source>
      <Dest>这一点，你要好好记住，总是有一个平衡的，无论是一个强大的敌人还一个有说服力的观点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And here I was feeling guilty about wanting to destroy you.</Source>
      <Dest>对于刚刚我想杀了你，我感到很内疚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That reminds me of a tale of the Khajiit who lost his wife.  Upon her death, he promised her he would never remarry.</Source>
      <Dest>这使我想起了一个关于一个丧妻的虎人的故事。妻子去世的时候，他答应过她永远不会再娶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And here I was feeling guilty about wanting to destroy you.</Source>
      <Dest>对于刚刚我想杀了你，我感到很内疚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She warned him that if he broke his promise, she would haunt him as a spirit for the rest of his life. </Source>
      <Dest>她警告他说如果他背叛了自己的诺言，她就会化作鬼魂，后半生永远纠缠着他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And here I was feeling guilty about wanting to destroy you.</Source>
      <Dest>对于刚刚我想杀了你，我感到很内疚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>His loneliness outweighed his guilt, and he fell in love with another.  Sure enough, his dead wife began to haunt him.  </Source>
      <Dest>然而最终孤独战胜了他的内疚，他还是与别人产生了爱情。然后他亡妻的鬼魂就开始纠缠他了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And here I was feeling guilty about wanting to destroy you.</Source>
      <Dest>对于刚刚我想杀了你，我感到很内疚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The dead wife seemed to know everything.  She knew about his forays to the brothel, and his gambling at the pits.</Source>
      <Dest>妻子的鬼魂似乎什么都知道。她知道他冲进妓院的事情，也知道他在斗兽场赌博的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And here I was feeling guilty about wanting to destroy you.</Source>
      <Dest>对于刚刚我想杀了你，我感到很内疚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When he sought the guidance of the priest, the priest told him to ask the ghost a question even the man himself did not know.  </Source>
      <Dest>虎人向一名祭司寻求帮助，祭司叫他问妻子的幽灵一件连他自己也不知道的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And here I was feeling guilty about wanting to destroy you.</Source>
      <Dest>对于刚刚我想杀了你，我感到很内疚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For if she truly knew everything, then she was indeed a ghost.  But if she knew only what the man knew, it was more likely he was haunting himself.  </Source>
      <Dest>因为如果她真的什么事情都知道，那么她就真的是一个幽灵。但如果她只知道这个男人知道的事情，那么这看起来更像是这个男人的愧疚感使他无法原谅他自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And here I was feeling guilty about wanting to destroy you.</Source>
      <Dest>对于刚刚我想杀了你，我感到很内疚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such is the power of guilt, that it drives us to maintain our virtue.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是愧疚的力量，它的存在使得我们能够维持我们的品德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh boy, here we go...</Source>
      <Dest>来吧，我们走……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In my vision I was standing in the atrium of a castle of glass, canvassed by an iridescent sky.  In the stars I saw the Aedra and Daedra.</Source>
      <Dest>在我的眼中，我正站在一座玻璃城堡的中庭，头上是绚丽的彩虹色天空。在星光中我仿佛看到了圣灵与魔神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They stood side by side, and beckoned me to follow a new path.  One that made no distinction between the Gods.  For one were all, and all were one.</Source>
      <Dest>他们肩靠肩地站着, 然后招手示意我跟随一条新路径。众神中谁都没有区别。一即是万物，万物即是一。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh boy, here we go...</Source>
      <Dest>来吧，我们走……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is one interpretation.  The priestess, overwhelmed by her master's kindness, would realize the error of her ways.</Source>
      <Dest>有一种说法。这名女祭司被祭司长的善良打动，认识到了自己所犯的错误。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He never knew the thief's identity, did he.</Source>
      <Dest>你从来都不知道他是小偷，对吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He never knew the thief's identity, did he.</Source>
      <Dest>你从来都不知道他是小偷，对吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps driven by guilt, she would expose herself as the thief, and through her bravery, truly achieve the forgiveness of her peers.</Source>
      <Dest>也许出于愧疚感的驱使，她会站出来说明自己就是那个小偷，然后由于她的勇敢，她将真正获得其他人的宽恕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He never knew the thief's identity, did he.</Source>
      <Dest>你从来都不知道他是小偷，对吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For any other path would result in bitterness and resentment, although these provide their own lessons, should the head priest choose to teach them.</Source>
      <Dest>因为通过其他途径最终会导致痛苦和怨恨，所以即使这些会让他们受到教训，但祭司长也应选择这样教他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet only time will tell the true effect of our actions.  I am reminded of a parable, if you would like to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>不过只有时间才能证明我们所做之事的真正效果。我想起一个寓言，不知你有没有兴趣听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's that island they live on.  I bet it triples your magical abilities.</Source>
      <Dest>那就是他们生活的岛屿，我打赌，一上去你的法力就能提升三倍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An interesting proposition.  Although I do not think what you mean is the island itself, but the people who reside there.</Source>
      <Dest>这主意不错。虽然我不认为你所指的是岛屿本身，而是上面的居民才对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's that island they live on.  I bet it triples your magical abilities.</Source>
      <Dest>那就是他们生活的岛屿，我打赌，一上去你的法力就能提升三倍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A monk once told me that if I spent a day around humor, by night I would be a jester, but by the morrow, I would revert to my former self.</Source>
      <Dest>有个僧侣跟我说，如果我花一整天研究幽默，到了晚上就会变成个小丑，可第二天一早，就又变回我原来的自己了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's that island they live on.  I bet it triples your magical abilities.</Source>
      <Dest>那就是他们生活的岛屿，我打赌，一上去你的法力就能提升三倍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Could it be that their isolation from the outside world sustains them? In this way they are always surrounded by magic, and tomorrow never comes.</Source>
      <Dest>也许是他们与外界的隔离状态支撑着他们？这样他们会一直被魔法包围，第二天永远不会来到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The blessing of Hircine is a gift.  You ought to try it.</Source>
      <Dest>海尔辛的祝福是一种天赋。你太应该试一下了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you, my friend, but I am no hunter.  I do not long for mead halls or hunting grounds, but perhaps there is a place for me elsewhere.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你，我的朋友。但我不是个猎人。我也不憧憬蜜酒大厅或是狩猎场，不过可能有别的地方适合我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The blessing of Hircine is a gift.  You ought to try it.</Source>
      <Dest>海尔辛的祝福是一种天赋。你太应该试一下了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is not to disparage your choice, for in the end there are many paths, but no clear solution.</Source>
      <Dest>条条大路通罗马，我不是否定你的选择，可并没有明确的方式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The blessing of Hircine is a gift.  You ought to try it.</Source>
      <Dest>海尔辛的祝福是一种天赋。你太应该试一下了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is the fate of mortals in life and in death. We must make decisions based on incomplete information, from a group of imperfect choices.</Source>
      <Dest>对于凡人来说，生死自有命。我们的从那些信息不完整的选择中做出决定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you admit that Nocturnal's power holds sway over the darkness.  It is not a corrupting force, however.  The act of stealing is not always a crime.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你承认诺克图娜尔的力量掌控着黑暗了。然而，这不是种破坏之力。偷窃行为并不总是犯罪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I did this for the Guild.  Luck has been hard to come by.</Source>
      <Dest>我这么做是为了公会。运气一直很差。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet, your past disappointments keep you humble, and help balance the events of the present, when you have every reason to be arrogant.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，你过去经受的挫折让你自卑。当你有足够的理由重获自信时，就帮忙协调目前的事件吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I try not to think about the past myself.  It's too depressing.</Source>
      <Dest>我尽力不去回忆自己那伤感的过去.  .</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I try not to think about the past myself.  It's too depressing.</Source>
      <Dest>我尽力不去回忆自己那伤感的过去.  .</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is why the Aedra and Daedra have saw fit to make you their champion.  You accept power, but you do not necessarily seek it.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是艾德拉和魔族让你成为他的战士的原因，你不必寻找它就能接受能力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How odd.  I thought cats landed on their feet.</Source>
      <Dest>真奇怪，我还以为猫都是用脚着地的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We Khajiit are quite adept, but the Divines saw fit to change that.  When I struck my head on the ground, I lost consciousness, but gained clarity.</Source>
      <Dest>我们虎人相当擅长于此，但圣灵们认为应该改变一下。当我的头撞到地上的时候，我失去了意识，思路却明晰了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How odd.  I thought cats landed on their feet.</Source>
      <Dest>真奇怪，我还以为猫都是用脚着地的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I saw Aedra and Daedra in the stars, side by side.  They made no distinction between themselves.  For one were all, and all were one.</Source>
      <Dest>我看见圣灵与魔族在星辰上并肩而立。他们之间没什么区别。一即是万物，万物即是一。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Which ones ask to me kill?  Those are the ones I like.</Source>
      <Dest>你要我杀掉哪一个？这几个都是我想做掉的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One should not simply follow the path of temptation without questioning why they are tempted.</Source>
      <Dest>人不应该简单地被诱惑牵着鼻子走，而不去想想它为什么会产生诱惑力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Which ones ask to me kill?  Those are the ones I like.</Source>
      <Dest>你要我杀掉哪一个？这几个都是我想做掉的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For water has no form without a cauldron or bucket, nor do the moons have shape without the darkness to light them.</Source>
      <Dest>就像没有容器，水就没有形状，没有黑暗的衬托，我们也不会看清双月的轮廓一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I worship myself.  It's working out pretty well for me.</Source>
      <Dest>我崇拜我自己。这对我来说很有用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The mortal who makes a temple of himself neglects himself.  For it is our relationship with others that allow our hearts and minds to prosper.</Source>
      <Dest>那个为自己建造一座庙宇的凡人将忽略掉自身。因为正是我们与他人之间的种种关系才使得我们的心灵和思想渐渐成长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's nothing to write home about.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是什么值得大书特书的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Strange, for the accounts I heard speak of a great wonder, a statue so grand it holds the sun and the moon in its palms.</Source>
      <Dest>真奇怪，我听说过一个伟大的奇迹，说的是一座掌中托着太阳与月亮的巨大雕像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's nothing to write home about.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是什么值得大书特书的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, such is the mortal understanding of things.  It lies in the concept rather than the object.</Source>
      <Dest>然而这就是凡人理解事物的方式。在于事物代表的概念而不是事物本身。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's nothing to write home about.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是什么值得大书特书的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When that concept is twisted, we do not see things as they are.  Our minds are distorted by the running water.</Source>
      <Dest>当事物的概念被扭曲的时候，我们就难以看到其本质。于是我们的思维也随之歪曲了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's nothing to write home about.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是什么值得大书特书的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet our reflections can only be seen when the river is calm.  Only then can we bestow the Daedra their rightful place in the balance of all things.</Source>
      <Dest>只有在河水平静的时候我们才能看见自己在水中的倒影，同样只有这样，我们才可以在万物平衡当中端正自己对于魔族的心态，把它们放到本该所处的位置上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In this world there are good intentions gone bad, and beautiful mistakes.</Source>
      <Dest>世界上有很多好心做成了坏事，也有很多错误变成好事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such is the complexity of life, for all intentions, all actions, flow on the waves of balance.  </Source>
      <Dest>生命的复杂性也是如此，因为所有的想法、所有的行为都在平衡的波浪中流动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In this world there are good intentions gone bad, and beautiful mistakes.</Source>
      <Dest>世界上有很多好心做成了坏事，也有很多错误变成好事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is the story of a monk who traveled through a busy market, where a butcher was peddling his meats.</Source>
      <Dest>有这样一个故事，一名修道士穿过热闹的市场，屠夫正沿街叫卖着肉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In this world there are good intentions gone bad, and beautiful mistakes.</Source>
      <Dest>世界上有很多好心做成了坏事，也有很多错误变成好事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The monk asked the butcher which meat was the tastiest, and the butcher promptly replied, "All of it.  Everything I sell is tastier than the other."</Source>
      <Dest>这名僧侣问屠夫哪块肉最好吃，屠夫迅速回答说，“它们全都很好吃。我卖的每一块肉都比别处更好吃。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In this world there are good intentions gone bad, and beautiful mistakes.</Source>
      <Dest>世界上有很多好心做成了坏事，也有很多错误变成好事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when the monk understood the butcher's lies were true, he gained a fragment of wisdom.</Source>
      <Dest>当僧侣领悟到屠夫所说的其实并非谎言的时候，他顿觉醍醐灌顶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You beat them, that's how.</Source>
      <Dest>你击败了他们，这怎么办到的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is a method preferred by many monks.  Some beat with a stick.  Others use a bucket and sponge.</Source>
      <Dest>那是一种被很多修道士偏爱的方法。有些修道士用木棍击打，其他人用水桶和海绵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You beat them, that's how.</Source>
      <Dest>你击败了他们，这怎么办到的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is a tale of a monk who worked a disciple to death, for failing to pray to the Divines before eating his meal.</Source>
      <Dest>这个故事讲的是一名修道士让他的弟子一直干活直到累死，原因是他吃饭前没向诸神念餐前祝文。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You beat them, that's how.</Source>
      <Dest>你击败了他们，这怎么办到的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The disciple's father stormed up the temple steps, before kneeling and thanking the monk for the patience he showed with his foolish son.</Source>
      <Dest>弟子的父亲疯狂地冲上了神庙的台阶，却未曾对这名修道士为他愚蠢的儿子耗尽心思而跪拜或是感谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met traveler.  I am Qa'Dojo, a monk making the pilgrimage to the Shrine of Azura.</Source>
      <Dest>见到你很高兴，旅行者。我是奎兜啾，一名向着阿祖拉祭坛的方向进行朝圣之旅的修道士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You'll enjoy it.  It's very statuesque.</Source>
      <Dest>你会喜欢它。这看起来体态非常的优美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, the Shrine of Azura is said to be one of the great wonders of Tamriel, built by the Dunmer to pay homage to the Daedric Prince.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，阿祖拉的祭坛被誉为泰姆瑞尔大陆上最伟大的奇迹之一。据说矮人为了向魔神王子展现他们的敬意而建造了它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You'll enjoy it.  It's very statuesque.</Source>
      <Dest>你会喜欢它。这看起来体态非常的优美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have heard that she does indeed look east to Morrowind, offering sanctuary to her humble servants.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说她确实是望向东方的晨风，并为她虔诚的拥护者提供庇护。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some may frown upon worship of the Daedra, as if the Aedra held a monopoly on the forces of good.</Source>
      <Dest>有的人可能会对她魔族的身份感到反感，就好像只有圣灵才能垄断代表正义的力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You'll enjoy it.  It's very statuesque.</Source>
      <Dest>你会喜欢它。这看起来体态非常的优美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You'll enjoy it.  It's very statuesque.</Source>
      <Dest>你会喜欢它。这看起来体态非常的优美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When in truth, both the Aedra and the Daedra are capable of love and mercy.</Source>
      <Dest>而事实上，不管是圣灵还是魔族，他们都能够心怀爱与仁慈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One must not focus on a person's chest, lest they neglect the person's bottom.</Source>
      <Dest>我们不能老是看着别人的胸部，这会使得无法看清那个人的本质。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You could not join a monastery.  They say that a monk must avoid the carnal pursuits to achieve true wisdom.</Source>
      <Dest>你加入不了修道院的。他们说一名修道士必须戒欲才能实现真正的智慧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One must not focus on a person's chest, lest they neglect the person's bottom.</Source>
      <Dest>我们不能老是看着别人的胸部，这会使得无法看清那个人的本质。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some will deny all contact with their desires, for fear they will succumb to weakness.  </Source>
      <Dest>有些人会全盘拒绝接触他们渴望的事情，因为他们害怕自己会屈服于自己的软弱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One must not focus on a person's chest, lest they neglect the person's bottom.</Source>
      <Dest>我们不能老是看着别人的胸部，这会使得无法看清那个人的本质。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, while lustful objects are not present in the room, they are present in the mind.</Source>
      <Dest>然而那些欲望和诱惑即使不在他们眼前出现，它们也会出现在脑海里，意识中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is better to leave such thoughts with the objects in question than with the imagination.</Source>
      <Dest>对于那样的想法，把它们当做一种尚有疑问的观点要比将它们想像成具体的事物好一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One must not focus on a person's chest, lest they neglect the person's bottom.</Source>
      <Dest>我们不能老是看着别人的胸部，这会使得无法看清那个人的本质。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My chief concern was escape.  It wasn't about either of them.</Source>
      <Dest>那时我最在乎的就是逃出去，跟他们谁都无关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And still, so many things change based on a single action.  Your escape is Madanach's freedom, and Markarth's war.</Source>
      <Dest>另外，很多事物因简单的行为而改变。你逃避则迈德纳奇自由，同时马卡斯城引来战争。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My chief concern was escape.  It wasn't about either of them.</Source>
      <Dest>那时我最在乎的就是逃出去，跟他们谁都无关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet only time will tell the true effect of our actions.  I am reminded of a parable, if you would like to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>不过只有时间才能证明我们所做之事的真正效果。我想起一个寓言，不知你有没有兴趣听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My chief concern was escape.  It wasn't about either of them.</Source>
      <Dest>那时我最在乎的就是逃出去，跟他们谁都无关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And still, so many things change based on a single action.  Your escape is Madanach's death, and Thonar's gain.</Source>
      <Dest>另外，很多事物因简单的行为而改变。你逃避则迈德纳奇自由，同时马卡斯城陷入战火。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My chief concern was escape.  It wasn't about either of them.</Source>
      <Dest>那时我最在乎的就是逃出去，跟他们谁都无关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet only time will tell the true effect of our actions.  I am reminded of a parable, if you would like to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>不过只有时间才能证明我们所做之事的真正效果。我想起一个寓言，不知你有没有兴趣听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It is their devotion to the Old Ways that give the Psijics power.</Source>
      <Dest>他们对古老之道的奉献会给予赛伊克人力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I see.  That would explain why in all their years, the Mages' Guild never matched the power of the Psijics, despite being founded by a former monk.</Source>
      <Dest>我懂了。这就解释了法师公会同样是先前的修道士创建，但这些年来力量完全不能与赛伊克人匹敌的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It is their devotion to the Old Ways that give the Psijics power.</Source>
      <Dest>他们对古老之道的奉献会给予赛伊克人力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vanus Galerion sought a change to the Old Ways to bring magic to the world, yet it is almost as if that diluted its strength.</Source>
      <Dest>万纳斯·加里兰试图改变将魔法之力引到这个世界的老方法，但是好像那基本上只能削弱魔法的强度。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It is their devotion to the Old Ways that give the Psijics power.</Source>
      <Dest>他们对古老之道的奉献会给予赛伊克人力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One wonders if the power of Aetherius is a limited resource, like iron or gold, and the Psijics move their island in order to tap veins of energy.</Source>
      <Dest>我好奇光界的力量是否如铁矿或金矿那样，是不可再生资源，而赛伊克教团是为了捕捉光界的能流而移动他们的小岛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It is their devotion to the Old Ways that give the Psijics power.</Source>
      <Dest>他们对古老之道的奉献会给予赛伊克人力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In that sense, the Elder Way is a strategy of conservation.  A way to hoard the power of Aetherius for to chosen few.  An interesting thought.</Source>
      <Dest>在这一意义上，上古之道是一种保护策略。一种为被选中的少数人积蓄艾瑟瑞斯之力的方式。真有趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I disagree that it is a curse, for that word carries with it a negative connotation.  </Source>
      <Dest>诅咒这个词不怎么恰当吧，它可不是什么褒义词。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It may be a gift to some, but it's a curse to me.</Source>
      <Dest>对某些人来说或许是个礼赞，但对我来说那不过只是个挥之不去的梦魇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It may be a gift to some, but it's a curse to me.</Source>
      <Dest>对某些人来说或许是个礼赞，但对我来说那不过只是个挥之不去的梦魇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is simply another option, one that is not suitable for you and a few of your Shield-Siblings.</Source>
      <Dest>这单纯是另一种选择，一种不太适合你也不太适合你某几个盾牌同胞的选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It may be a gift to some, but it's a curse to me.</Source>
      <Dest>对某些人来说或许是个礼赞，但对我来说那不过只是个挥之不去的梦魇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We should not disparage those who choose it, however, for in the end there are many paths, but no clear solution.</Source>
      <Dest>无论是谁选择了它，我们都不应看不起，不管怎样，因为在最后都会有很多方法，但并没有明确的方式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is the fate of mortals in life and in death. We must make decisions based on incomplete information, from a group of imperfect choices.</Source>
      <Dest>对于凡人来说，生死自有命。我们的从那些信息不完整的选择中做出决定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It may be a gift to some, but it's a curse to me.</Source>
      <Dest>对某些人来说或许是个礼赞，但对我来说那不过只是个挥之不去的梦魇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't care for Nocturnal. Karliah thought it was necessary so I played along.</Source>
      <Dest>我才不在乎什么诺克图娜尔. 只是卡莉亚觉得有必要，我就配合一下而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, you formed the trinity, if not for your own sake, but for the others.  Nocturnal's influence is an important part of their lives.</Source>
      <Dest>不过，如果不是为了你自己，而是为了其他人的话，你应该和他俩共进退。诺克图娜尔的影响在他们生命中至关重要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I like to reminisce as well.  About all the throats I've cut.</Source>
      <Dest>我也喜欢回忆。回忆那些被我杀死的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Gods made you what you are, and it cannot be helped. </Source>
      <Dest>众神把你捏成啥样儿就啥样儿，这是天生的，没救了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I like to reminisce as well.  About all the throats I've cut.</Source>
      <Dest>我也喜欢回忆。回忆那些被我杀死的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just know that while you dream of the past, there are those who dream of a day when the throat that's cut is yours.</Source>
      <Dest>Just know that while you dream of the past, there are those who dream of a day when the throat that's cut is yours.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain this doctrine of yours.</Source>
      <Dest>请解释一下你们的教义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I follow the path of balance through opposition.  The Aedra and Daedra are the embodiment of this mantra.</Source>
      <Dest>我通过对立来追求平衡之道，而魔族与圣灵的对立正是这奇妙平衡的具体表现。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain this doctrine of yours.</Source>
      <Dest>请解释一下你们的教义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is a common misconception that these balancing forces are the spirit of good and evil.  A reductive and flawed interpretation.</Source>
      <Dest>这种相互平衡的力量经常被误解为正义与邪恶的精神力量，不得不说这种误解充满人类的臆想与揣测。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain this doctrine of yours.</Source>
      <Dest>请解释一下你们的教义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Aedra are the agents of stasis and order.  The Daedra are the essence of change and chaos.  For chaos itself cannot be an agent of anything.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵代表着静态和秩序，魔族是改变和混乱的化身。至于混乱本身却不能代表任何事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain this doctrine of yours.</Source>
      <Dest>请解释一下你们的教义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When the two are in balance, time progresses at its natural flow.  The world changes as it stays the same.</Source>
      <Dest>当这二者处于平衡状态时，时间就会按照本身的自然状态流动。世界是静止的，同时它也在变化着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain this doctrine of yours.</Source>
      <Dest>请解释一下你们的教义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although in truth, it is not for us to attach labels to the creators.  </Source>
      <Dest>然而事实是，我们是没资格给创始者们随便扣帽子的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Explain this doctrine of yours.</Source>
      <Dest>请解释一下你们的教义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If mortals cannot divine the nature of themselves, it is quite presumptuous to try the same with the Gods.  </Source>
      <Dest>如果凡人连他们自己的本质都无法预知，那么如此去揣测神的本质则更显放肆无礼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not everyday I meet a Daedric monk.</Source>
      <Dest>这可不是天天都能见到一个魔族修道士啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then today will be no different than any other. </Source>
      <Dest>那今天就与以往的日子没有任何区别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not everyday I meet a Daedric monk.</Source>
      <Dest>这可不是天天都能见到一个魔族修道士啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For while I recognize Azura's place in the pantheon of the Divines, the Daedra hold no particular favor in the doctrine I follow.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然我认为阿祖拉在诸圣灵中拥有一席之地，但魔族并没有特别青眛我的教条。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not everyday I meet a Daedric monk.</Source>
      <Dest>这可不是天天都能见到一个魔族修道士啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some may see the line between Aedra and Daedra as a means of separation, when the divide itself is the true nature of our existence.</Source>
      <Dest>有的人可能把圣灵与魔族之间分的很清楚，然而对于我们来说，分隔本身是我们存在的真实本质。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not everyday I meet a Daedric monk.</Source>
      <Dest>这可不是天天都能见到一个魔族修道士啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is in the eye of the storm that one finds balance, and with balance comes the flourishing of life.</Source>
      <Dest>只有在暴风眼中才能寻得平衡，只有平衡才能衍生出生生不息的生命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have more questions regarding your philosophy.</Source>
      <Dest>我有更多的关于你的哲学的问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I implore you to ask them.  To ask a question is to risk being a fool, but to cling to silence is to remain one.</Source>
      <Dest>那么我希望你把这些都问题提出来。虽然问问题可能会被人当成愚蠢的人，但是保持沉默才是最愚蠢的行为。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The other students jeered.  They saw the frustration on his face, and suggested he use the calm spell on himself first.</Source>
      <Dest>其他同学都乐了。他们看到他脸上的窘态，建议他先给自己来一发平静术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The monk continued to cast spell after spell in vain.  He wanted to quit, to end his humiliation, but the master would not allow it.</Source>
      <Dest>这个修道士在施法失败后一直在尝试。他想放弃，想抛弃他自己的人性，但是大师不会允许这么做的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He realized that the only way out was to drive the dog into a frenzy and force the master to kill it.</Source>
      <Dest>他意识到唯一的办法就是让狗发狂，迫使主人去杀掉它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so, distracted by neither desire, ambition, pride nor shame, he cast the spell once more and the dog fell into a deep sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>这一次，没有被任何因素干扰，欲望，野心，骄傲或者耻辱……他又一次施展了那个法术，让那条狗深深地沉睡了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hall of the Vigilant) Enlighten me.</Source>
      <Dest>(警戒者会堂) 请教教我吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The apprentice was distraught, but the master was not angry. He looked at the young monk, his eyes rinsed in the moonlight, and said these words:</Source>
      <Dest>学徒被吓坏了，但大师没有生气。他注视着这个年轻的修道士，目光似月般澄澈，说出如下话语：</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hall of the Vigilant) Enlighten me.</Source>
      <Dest>(警戒者会堂) 请教教我吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hall of the Vigilant) Enlighten me.</Source>
      <Dest>(警戒者会堂) 请教教我吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Vigilants of Stendarr are much like the apprentice. They seek to restore order, but to eliminate chaos is to tamper with balance.</Source>
      <Dest>斯丹达尔警戒者就像天真的学徒一样。他们试图恢复秩序，但事实恰恰相反，消除混沌便是干扰平衡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Smiling, he penned a note to the Arkay priest, informing him of his foolishness. </Source>
      <Dest>微笑着,他写下了一张便条,告诉阿尔凯牧师他的愚笨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet as he set off to deliver it, a mischievous boy stole the missive from his hand.</Source>
      <Dest>但当他动身去交付它时，一个调皮的男孩从他手里偷信件。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Khajiit chased him up a roof, only to watch as the boy shredded the letter into flakes of snow.</Source>
      <Dest>虎人在一个屋顶上抓到了他，却只能眼睁睁的看着男孩儿把信撕成了碎片。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Months later, the Khajiit is walking up the steps to the temple, when he hears an apprentice call his late master's name.</Source>
      <Dest>几个月后，那个虎人终于抵达了神殿，就在那时，他突然听到有个学徒叫着他最后一任主人的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Surprised, he looks to his left, and then to his right, and only when he sees nothing does he realize the master they beckon is him.</Source>
      <Dest> 惊奇的是，他左瞧瞧，再右瞧瞧，当他什么也没发现时才明白大师叫的是他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Gildergreen) Tell me this parable you speak of.</Source>
      <Dest>(翠苒树)告诉我你谈到的比喻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A young khajiit monk is called to the temple, where his master waits with grave news.</Source>
      <Dest>一个年轻的虎人修道士被叫去了神殿，他的主人在那里等着他，要告诉他一个重大消息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Gildergreen) Tell me this parable you speak of.</Source>
      <Dest>(翠苒树)告诉我你谈到的比喻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A priest of Arkay says that in three days time, snow will fall in the summer, and when the last flake falls the master will die.</Source>
      <Dest>有个阿尔凯祭司把这话念了三天，那夏天会有一场大雪，最后一片雪花落下时，主人也就升天啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Gildergreen) Tell me this parable you speak of.</Source>
      <Dest>(翠苒树)告诉我你谈到的比喻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Gildergreen) Tell me this parable you speak of.</Source>
      <Dest>(翠苒树)告诉我你谈到的比喻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Three days passed, and on the third day, the Khajiit looked to the sky, and found only the scorching sun.</Source>
      <Dest>三天过去了，在第三天，虎人望向天空，只见到炎炎烈日。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hall of the Vigilant) Enlighten me.</Source>
      <Dest>(警戒者会堂) 请教教我吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In the summer, the sweltering heat brought a plague of mosquitoes upon a Khajiit master's temple.</Source>
      <Dest>在那个夏天，令人窒息的闷热使得一座虎人大师神庙里的蚊子泛滥成灾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hall of the Vigilant) Enlighten me.</Source>
      <Dest>(警戒者会堂) 请教教我吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although dragonflies hunted mosquitoes, the alchemists had ravaged their numbers. An apprentice suggested introducing a new predator.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然蜻蜓会吃蚊虫，炼金术士们还是苦于蚊虫的数量众多。一个学徒建议引进一种新的蚊虫捕食者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hall of the Vigilant) Enlighten me.</Source>
      <Dest>(警戒者会堂) 请教教我吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A trader had brought a species of toad from the forests of Valenwood.  It held no alchemical properties, and was poisonous to predators.</Source>
      <Dest>一个贸易商带来了一种原产于威木省森林的蟾蜍。它不具有炼金特性，对肉食者而言是有毒的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hall of the Vigilant) Enlighten me.</Source>
      <Dest>(警戒者会堂) 请教教我吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Within days, the mosquito population had diminished.  However, the toad's appetite could not be sated by mere insects.</Source>
      <Dest>几天内这群蚊子就被消灭了。但蟾蜍的胃口可不是几只昆虫就能满足的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Hall of the Vigilant) Enlighten me.</Source>
      <Dest>(警戒者会堂) 请教教我吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Rodents, reptiles, and even small birds fell prey to this voracious hunter.  In time, only the toads were left.</Source>
      <Dest>啮齿动物，爬行动物，甚至小鸟儿都成为了这个贪婪猎人的牺牲品。最后，只有蟾蜍幸免于难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Winterhold) Alright.  Tell me a story, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>(冬堡) 好的大师，给我讲个故事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A young monk, just out of the litter, trained at the temple in the art of casting spells.</Source>
      <Dest>一个年轻的僧侣，刚刚离开自己的小窝，在修道院里接受了艺术班的施法培训。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Winterhold) Alright.  Tell me a story, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>(冬堡) 好的大师，给我讲个故事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although many of the students were his seniors, there was one female Wood Elf with whom he shared an age, and they became fast friends.</Source>
      <Dest>即使很多学生都是他的长者，这里面还是有一个女性木精灵和他一起共同度日，并且还和他成了挚友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Winterhold) Alright.  Tell me a story, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>(冬堡) 好的大师，给我讲个故事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The first lesson was in illusion.  The master cast a fury spell on a stray hound, and each student took turns calming it.</Source>
      <Dest>第一节是幻术课。大师给流浪狗施展愤怒法术，然后每个学生都得试着让狗平静下来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Winterhold) Alright.  Tell me a story, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>(冬堡) 好的大师，给我讲个故事吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The monk wanted very much to impress the young Elf. Yet his attempts to calm the beast failed, and each subsequent attempt only incensed it further.</Source>
      <Dest>修道士非常想给年轻的精灵留下印象。但他想让它平静下来的企图都失败了，每次尝试的结果都只是让它更愤怒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's crazy talk.  Daedra aren't Divines.  They're evil.</Source>
      <Dest>这真是胡说八道。魔族是不是圣灵。他们是邪恶的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A Nord man lies in the field and sleeps away the day.  His family lives on the brink of starvation, unable to extricate themselves from their poverty</Source>
      <Dest>一名诺德人躺在田地并睡了一整天。他的家人生活在饥饿边缘，贫穷如影随形。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One day a wayward sabrecat stalks through the field.  It attacks the man, wounding him severely before he manages to flee.</Source>
      <Dest>有一天，一头狡猾的剑齿虎悄悄接近了田地。在那诺德人艰难地跑出田地前，它袭击并重创了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's crazy talk.  Daedra aren't Divines.  They're evil.</Source>
      <Dest>这真是胡说八道。魔族是不是圣灵。他们是邪恶的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's crazy talk.  Daedra aren't Divines.  They're evil.</Source>
      <Dest>这真是胡说八道。魔族是不是圣灵。他们是邪恶的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With the husband bedridden, the wife awakes from her stupor.  She weaves fabrics and works the field to provide for her children.</Source>
      <Dest>由于丈夫重伤卧床不起，她的妻子不得不振作起来。她编织布料和在田里做活来养活孩子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's crazy talk.  Daedra aren't Divines.  They're evil.</Source>
      <Dest>这真是胡说八道。魔族是不是圣灵。他们是邪恶的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The man's son learns to hunt.  He seeks revenge on the sabrecat that nearly killed his father.</Source>
      <Dest>那个男人的儿子也开始学习狩猎。他要找到那只差点杀死他父亲的剑齿虎并复仇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's crazy talk.  Daedra aren't Divines.  They're evil.</Source>
      <Dest>这真是胡说八道。魔族是不是圣灵。他们是邪恶的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The man's daughter trains in alchemy, to help restore her father's vigor.  </Source>
      <Dest>那男人的女儿则是为了帮助她父亲维持生命开始学习。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As the children mature, the family becomes a valuable pillar of the village.  One might say they have the sabrecat to thank.</Source>
      <Dest>当孩子们长大成人之后，这个家庭成了整个村子的中流砥柱。有些人甚至认为他们应该感谢当初那只剑齿虎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's crazy talk.  Daedra aren't Divines.  They're evil.</Source>
      <Dest>这真是胡说八道。魔族是不是圣灵。他们是邪恶的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think there will come a time when dragons and mortals co-exist?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得会不会有一天龙族能跟人类和平共处呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This I do not know.  Things that cannot adapt to the world's natural harmony will inevitably become extinct.</Source>
      <Dest>我不懂这个。物竞天择,适者生存。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This Way of the Voice, however, may provide a solution.  Much like in the parable of the ill-tempered Khajiit, anger is a choice.</Source>
      <Dest>这吼声之道，无论如何，可能会提供一个解决方案。就像这个寓言中脾气暴躁的虎人，愤怒也是一种选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think there will come a time when dragons and mortals co-exist?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得会不会有一天龙族能跟人类和平共处呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think there will come a time when dragons and mortals co-exist?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得会不会有一天龙族能跟人类和平共处呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This I do not know.  Things that cannot adapt to the world's natural harmony will inevitably become extinct.</Source>
      <Dest>我不懂这个。物竞天择,适者生存。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This Way of the Voice, however, may provide a solution.  Much like in the parable of the ill-tempered Khajiit, anger is a choice.</Source>
      <Dest>这吼声之道，无论如何，可能会提供一个解决方案。就像这个寓言中脾气暴躁的虎人，愤怒也是一种选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think there will come a time when dragons and mortals co-exist?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得会不会有一天龙族能跟人类和平共处呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, as the dragon who preached it is slain, it is far more likely that should the dragons be reborn again, it will end in their demise or ours.</Source>
      <Dest>可是,就像那头说是被宰了的龙一样, 更有可能的是，龙再次复活，最后以它们或者我们的死亡而结束</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think there will come a time when dragons and mortals co-exist?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得会不会有一天龙族能跟人类和平共处呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did the monk say?</Source>
      <Dest>那个僧侣说了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The monk replied, "Because you are never ill, you do not pray at the Temple."</Source>
      <Dest>修道士回答说，“因为你从不生病，所以你不在神殿里祈祷。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did the monk say?</Source>
      <Dest>那个僧侣说了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did the monk say?</Source>
      <Dest>那个僧侣说了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did the monk say?</Source>
      <Dest>那个僧侣说了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With that, the Elf laid a septim in the monk's palm.  And every day after, one could find him at the shrines, in the markets, or with a friend.</Source>
      <Dest> 接着，那个精灵给了僧人一个金币。在那之后的每一天你都会发现他在市场的神龛前，有时和一个朋友一起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right, let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，说来让我们听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright, let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，让我们听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was a once a young Elf who lived in a village, but only young by appearance.</Source>
      <Dest>曾经有个年轻的精灵居住在一个小村子里，但只是看上去年轻罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right, let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，说来让我们听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He had been in the village for thousands of years, yet his face was no older than a season.   </Source>
      <Dest>他已经在村里生活了好几千年，但他的面容始终未变。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright, let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，让我们听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right, let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，说来让我们听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One day the Elf happened upon a traveling monk.  The monk was dressed in rags, poor and disheveled, seeking alms in exchange for healing.</Source>
      <Dest>一天，精灵发现一个云游僧，这云游僧破衣烂衫，看起来十分贫穷与落魄，以治疗作为交换乞求他人的施舍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright, let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，让我们听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right, let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，说来让我们听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright, let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，让我们听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The monk asked the Elf if he would pay him a Septim in exchange for his services.  The Elf balked at the notion.  He was in perfect health.</Source>
      <Dest>僧人问那个精灵是否愿意拿一块钱买他的服务。精灵断然拒绝。他的身体好得很。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When the bee is drawn to the flowers for nectar, it serves to pollinate the entire garden.  </Source>
      <Dest>当一只蜜蜂被一朵花的花蜜吸引之后，它也将为整座花园授粉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So slavery, rape, and destruction are part of the grand scheme. Good to know.</Source>
      <Dest>因此，奴役，强奸，毁灭都是这个宏伟计划的一部分？了解了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is not clear whether the machinery of life is driven by motive, or works to shape it.  What is clear is that all things depend on each other.</Source>
      <Dest>尚不清楚生命的运转到底是被自身的动机还是产生生命的程式所驱使。已经清楚的是，所有的事物都与其他事物息息相关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So slavery, rape, and destruction are part of the grand scheme. Good to know.</Source>
      <Dest>因此，奴役，强奸，毁灭都是这个宏伟计划的一部分？了解了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Removing the Daedra from this plane would disrupt the balance of life, like burning a hive of bees in response to a few stings.</Source>
      <Dest>如果将魔族从世界中抹除，那么生命的平衡将被扰乱，这就像因为几次蛰痛而烧掉整个蜂巢一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So slavery, rape, and destruction are part of the grand scheme. Good to know.</Source>
      <Dest>因此，奴役，强奸，毁灭都是这个宏伟计划的一部分？了解了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I will not admonish those who resent the Gods, or punish them for their hate. For hate itself is its own punishment, as it works to consume them.</Source>
      <Dest>然而我并不会去劝告那些怨恨着神的人们，也不会去惩戒他们的恨意。因为仇恨本身就是一种惩罚，它将慢慢磨损人的生命力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So slavery, rape, and destruction are part of the grand scheme. Good to know.</Source>
      <Dest>因此，奴役，强奸，毁灭都是这个宏伟计划的一部分？了解了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible that some Daedra can be categorized as evil?</Source>
      <Dest>是有可能，一些魔族可以被归类为邪恶？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Boethiah is the Prince of plots, deceit, and conspiracy.  Such words are sinister when spoken in the void.</Source>
      <Dest>波耶西亚是阴谋、欺骗与叛乱的魔神巨头。这几个词一说出来的时候，仿佛空气中都盘旋着阴险的气氛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible that some Daedra can be categorized as evil?</Source>
      <Dest>是有可能，一些魔族可以被归类为邪恶？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet when the scales of power tip toward tyranny, when the strength of the dishonorable cannot be vanquished by a frontal assault, Boethiah is there.</Source>
      <Dest>然而当权力的天平倒向暴君之时，当正面对抗无法消灭那些卑鄙无耻的势力之时，波耶西亚就会出现。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible that some Daedra can be categorized as evil?</Source>
      <Dest>是有可能，一些魔族可以被归类为邪恶？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Molag Bal, meanwhile, is her nemesis, for he is strength and domination, and those who enslave others do so in his name.   </Source>
      <Dest>莫拉格·巴尔是她的主要敌人，因为他代表了强权与支配，也代表着那些以巴尔之名奴役他人无恶不作的恶徒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although Boethiah teaches us that strength can be vanquished, Molag Bal demonstrates that weakness is not a virtue.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然波耶西亚教导我们强权是可以被击溃的，但莫拉格．巴尔同时也证明了软弱并不是一种美德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible that some Daedra can be categorized as evil?</Source>
      <Dest>是有可能，一些魔族可以被归类为邪恶？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mehrunes Dagon is the facilitator of destruction, the great equalizer of this plane.  </Source>
      <Dest>梅鲁涅斯．大衮是毁灭的促进者，在这个世界扮演着重要作用的平衡者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible that some Daedra can be categorized as evil?</Source>
      <Dest>是有可能，一些魔族可以被归类为邪恶？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is it possible that some Daedra can be categorized as evil?</Source>
      <Dest>是有可能，一些魔族可以被归类为邪恶？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For when life is allowed to grow unchecked, it will wither from its own abundance.</Source>
      <Dest>因为当生命被允许不受抑制地生长之时，它反而会因自己的过度放纵而凋零。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The path of balance requires you to steel your heart against that which is deplorable, and calm your emotions at that which brings you joy.</Source>
      <Dest>追求平衡之道将让你不以物喜，不以己悲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I can respect that.</Source>
      <Dest>我尊重这一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is through the evenness of mind that one can see through the shroud of passion, and be blessed with the clarity of enlightenment.</Source>
      <Dest>正是通过达到心灵的平衡才使得智慧可以穿透被情绪笼罩的迷雾，最终得到清晰启迪的祝福。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I can respect that.</Source>
      <Dest>我尊重这一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The painting was hung over the bed chamber, and while it seemed to be a perfect fit, the Count nevertheless told the carpenter to take it down.</Source>
      <Dest>画被挂在了卧室，虽然看上去它摆放的位置是那么完美，但伯爵仍旧让木匠取下来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right. Tell me the story.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，把整件事说给我听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Back and forth the pair went, from the study to the great hall, each time the Count requesting the carpenter to hang the painting, then remove it.</Source>
      <Dest>他俩就在书房和大厅之间徘徊，伯爵一次又一次地要求木匠挂上然后又取下那幅画。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right. Tell me the story.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，把整件事说给我听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>After walking the breadth of the castle, at long last they returned to the bed chamber.</Source>
      <Dest>在逛遍了整个城堡后了之后，他们又把它挂回了卧室。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right. Tell me the story.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，把整件事说给我听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only this time, when the painting was hung, the Count was satisfied, for only by seeing all other alternatives did he know his choice was true.</Source>
      <Dest>只有这一次，当那幅油画被挂起的时候，伯爵显得很满意。因为只有看过了所有其他的油画，他才能肯定他最终的选择是正确的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right. Tell me the story.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，把整件事说给我听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And thus my request is this.  If you will do me the honor of being my carpenter, and I yours, then I will forever be in your debt.</Source>
      <Dest>因此我的要求是这样的。如果你愿意赏光做我的木匠，那我就是你的，我将永远都欠你一份人情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>All right. Tell me the story.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，把整件事说给我听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm...one must have both purpose and flexibility. He may walk a path of many roads to the same destination.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，一个人必须目的与灵活性兼备。他应该有很多种方法达成同样目标。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you plan on staying in Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>你计划待在天际省？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He may not know where the destination lies until the moment he arrives at it, and even then, it may not fulfill his true purpose.</Source>
      <Dest>在在真正完成之前，其实根本没有什么最后的结果可言；甚至到最后，结局也可能并不是当初想要的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you plan on staying in Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>你计划待在天际省？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am reminded of the story of a carpenter who was tasked with hanging a painting for the Count.</Source>
      <Dest>这让我想起了一个关于为伯爵挂画的木匠的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you plan on staying in Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>你计划待在天际省？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can the Aedra be sinister?</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵可能是邪恶的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Aedra are thought to be callous because they are indifferent, too often leaving mortals to their own devices.  </Source>
      <Dest>圣灵们被认为是冷酷无情的，因为他们常常把凡人留在困境中不管不顾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It reminds me of the parable of the acolyte priestess who stole from the alms bowl.  </Source>
      <Dest>这使我想起了那个关于从神的金钵里偷东西的女祭司的寓言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can the Aedra be sinister?</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵可能是邪恶的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can the Aedra be sinister?</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵可能是邪恶的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The other acolytes beseeched the head priest to investigate the matter and cast the thief out.</Source>
      <Dest>其他的僧侣恳求祭司长调查偷窃事件并抓出窃贼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can the Aedra be sinister?</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵可能是邪恶的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet the priest replied that he already knew the identity of the thief.   The acolytes, angered, threatened to leave if the culprit was not revealed.</Source>
      <Dest>然而祭司长却回答说他已经知道了窃贼的身份。其他的僧侣非常生气，他们威胁道，如果不揭穿小偷的身份，他们就要全部离开这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can the Aedra be sinister?</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵可能是邪恶的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I cast the thief out, he replied, how will he ever learn remorse? If you leave, how will I ever teach you forgiveness?</Source>
      <Dest>如果我指出了那名窃贼，祭司长说，他怎么能学会自责呢？如果你都离开了，我能么能教会你宽恕呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I see.  That very greed consumed Ancano, just as the Augur foretold.  Yet perhaps greed is what motivated you to conquer him.</Source>
      <Dest>我懂了。安卡诺的贪婪欲望已经无法控制，正如预言师杜兰所言。然而，或许贪婪正是你打败他的契机。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would have killed them myself to become Arch-Mage.</Source>
      <Dest>为了成为首席法师，我会亲手杀了他们的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thus, when your power becomes out of control, another will appear.  You will live in fear, but that is also a good thing.</Source>
      <Dest>因此，当你的力量失控之时，另一个会出现。你会生活在恐惧之中，但这也是件好事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would have killed them myself to become Arch-Mage.</Source>
      <Dest>为了成为首席法师，我会亲手杀了他们的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To live without fear is to live according to the parable of the Elf.  I can tell you the story, if you are inclined to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>想要过没有恐惧的生活就要遵守精灵的预言。我可以给你讲述这些故事，如果你很想听的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would have killed them myself to become Arch-Mage.</Source>
      <Dest>为了成为首席法师，我会亲手杀了他们的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes.  Incredibly bittersweet.  Blessings of the Divines to both of them.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，真是苦乐参半啊。愿圣灵保佑他们两个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Indeed.  I pray Namira will consume them, and Arkay will guide them to Aetherius.  We shall mourn, but we should not be sad.</Source>
      <Dest>确实如此。我祈祷娜米拉把他们吃掉，而阿尔凯引导他们的灵魂去往艾瑟瑞斯。我们可以悼念，但没必要悲伤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such is the cycle of death and life.  It reminds me of a parable, if you wish to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>这是生和死的一个轮回。它让我想起了一个寓言，如果你想听的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes.  Incredibly bittersweet.  Blessings of the Divines to both of them.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，真是苦乐参半啊。愿圣灵保佑他们两个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was all luck.  I'm no hero.  I'm a fraud.</Source>
      <Dest>那都是侥幸。我不是英雄，我是个骗子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is a saying that mortals have.  It is not a parable, but it has wisdom all the same.  They say "It is better to be lucky than good."</Source>
      <Dest>凡人们有句谚语。虽然通俗但依旧智慧。他们说：“好运胜过实力。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Many good warriors die in battle.  Many great heroes, mages, and thieves are vanquished by the forces of evil.</Source>
      <Dest>很多优秀的战士战死沙场。很多伟大的英雄、法师、盗贼被邪恶的力量所征服。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was all luck.  I'm no hero.  I'm a fraud.</Source>
      <Dest>那都是侥幸。我不是英雄，我是个骗子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, no one has ever called a dead man lucky.  No one has ever said that the defeated are fortunate.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，从未有一个人夸死人是幸运的。也没有一个人说失败是幸运的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was all luck.  I'm no hero.  I'm a fraud.</Source>
      <Dest>那都是侥幸。我不是英雄，我是个骗子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Pray to Nocturnal and thank her for her blessing. She has brought you many spoils, and to deny them would be an insult she would not take kindly.</Source>
      <Dest>向诺克图娜尔祈祷并感谢她的赐福。她会给你带来了许多战利品，而如果拒绝它们的话，诺克图娜尔会将这视为一种无法接受的侮辱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was all luck.  I'm no hero.  I'm a fraud.</Source>
      <Dest>那都是侥幸。我不是英雄，我是个骗子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And that's how a dumb priest lost everything to a single thief.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是一个愚蠢的牧师如何被一个小偷偷走所有东西的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is not a tale that has an ending, so yours is as valid as any.  Yet you cannot say that the thief took everything.</Source>
      <Dest>这个故事并没有结尾，所以你可以尽情想像它的结局。但是你不能说这个贼偷走了所有东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And that's how a dumb priest lost everything to a single thief.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是一个愚蠢的牧师如何被一个小偷偷走所有东西的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For one cannot steal wisdom, and the words imparted by the priest were meant not only for the thief, but the ears of his acolytes.</Source>
      <Dest>因为人不能偷走智慧，并且这名祭司长的话不仅仅对这个贼有意义，还有那些接受了他智慧的修道士们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was placed on the top of a high bookshelf.  Now they say those who hurry only slow themselves in the end.  If only I heeded such sage advice.</Source>
      <Dest>它被放在一个高书架的顶部。他们说欲速则不达。真希望我听从了这样的忠告。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where did you find it?</Source>
      <Dest>你在哪儿找到的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Instead of reaching for the footstool, I attempted to climb the shelf, only to fall flat on my tail.</Source>
      <Dest>我没去找凳子，而是试着坐上了架子，这样我的尾巴才好放。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where did you find it?</Source>
      <Dest>你在哪儿找到的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, as it so happens, I lost my balance but gained my footing.  For when my head struck the ground, I had a vision.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，就是那么凑巧啊，我失去了平衡且摔在地面。因头着地而头晕目眩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where did you find it?</Source>
      <Dest>你在哪儿找到的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you come to adopt this philosophy?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎样形成这种的理念的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was trained as priest of Stendarr, but I felt the Temple did not do enough to disavow the militants who walk the land in his name.</Source>
      <Dest>我受训成为一名斯丹达尔祭司，但是我感觉这座神庙做得还不够，没有否认那些以它之名四处奔走的激进分子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you come to adopt this philosophy?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎样形成这种的理念的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I considered converting to the Temple of Julianos, and had packed for the great chapel in Skingrad to begin my training.</Source>
      <Dest>我打算转到尤里安诺思的神庙，并收拾行李到斯金格勒的大教堂开始我的训练。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you come to adopt this philosophy?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎样形成这种的理念的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was only one item I could not find, my copy of the book "Aedra and Daedra."  I scoured every corner of my quarters, until at last I saw it.</Source>
      <Dest>但是有一样东西我始终找不到了，是我手抄的“圣灵与魔神”这本书。我找遍了住所里所有的角落，直到最后我终于看到了它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Possession of a thing can change, just as often as a piece of coin.  This applies to the Reach, as well as the banner of justice.</Source>
      <Dest>什么东西的价值都是变动的，就像物价一样波动。在瑞驰也是这样，在正义的旗帜下也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet only time will tell whether our actions have shifted the balance.  I am reminded of a parable, if you would like to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，只有时间才能告诉我们，我们的行动是否扭转了形势。如果你愿意听的话，我想起了一个寓言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Possession of a thing can change, just as often as a piece of coin.  This applies to the Reach, as well as the banner of justice.</Source>
      <Dest>什么东西的价值都是变动的，就像物价一样波动。在瑞驰也是这样，在正义的旗帜下也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet only time will tell whether our actions have shifted the balance.  I am reminded of a parable, if you would like to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，只有时间才能告诉我们，我们的行动是否扭转了形势。如果你愿意听的话，我想起了一个寓言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suspected as much.  You know very well that I view the world from such a prism, with all things balanced, all things reliant on each other.</Source>
      <Dest>我有些怀疑。你清楚的知道我从一个棱镜中观察这个世界，万物和谐，相互依靠的世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Both. Meditation helps develop magical skill, philosophy ensures it proper use.</Source>
      <Dest>两者都有。冥想有助于提升魔法技能，人生观确保它正确的适用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thus the Elder Way is about developing magic, as much as it is hindering its use.</Source>
      <Dest>因此这个古老的方法既发展了魔法也同时阻碍了它的使用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Both. Meditation helps develop magical skill, philosophy ensures it proper use.</Source>
      <Dest>两者都有。冥想有助于提升魔法技能，人生观确保它正确的适用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had feared, however, that my biases would fog my mind and prevent me from seeing any other answer. I thank you for alleviating me of my concerns.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾恐惧,不管怎样，那是偏见蒙蔽了我.谢谢你减轻了我的忧虑.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Both. Meditation helps develop magical skill, philosophy ensures it proper use.</Source>
      <Dest>两者都有。冥想有助于提升魔法技能，人生观确保它正确的适用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can't trust Hircine.  You'd agree if you didn't fall and bang your head.</Source>
      <Dest>你不能信任海尔辛。如果你没有摔倒并撞到你的头颅的话，你会同意的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was a hard fall, yes, but I assure you, my mind has never been so clear.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一个艰难的秋天，但我向你保证，我的内心从来没有如此的明朗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Consider, for instance, the difference between a domesticated hound and a feral dog.</Source>
      <Dest>考虑一下吧，举个例子，这就像是一只被驯化的猎犬和一只凶猛的狗之间的区别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can't trust Hircine.  You'd agree if you didn't fall and bang your head.</Source>
      <Dest>你不能信任海尔辛。如果你没有摔倒并撞到你的头颅的话，你会同意的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One is free to hunt, but if he fails he will starve.  The other never hungers, but roams only where his master commands.</Source>
      <Dest>一种人弄能够自由狩猎，但是如果他失败了他就得挨饿。其另一种人永远不会挨饿，但是只能在他的主人划分的区域下走动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can't trust Hircine.  You'd agree if you didn't fall and bang your head.</Source>
      <Dest>你不能信任海尔辛。如果你没有摔倒并撞到你的头颅的话，你会同意的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Both are free, and yet neither can act freely.  In life and in death, there is no perfect choice.  There is only what is right for yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>你俩都是自由的，但都不能自由行动。在生死之间，没有完美的选项。只有适合自己的选项。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can't trust Hircine.  You'd agree if you didn't fall and bang your head.</Source>
      <Dest>你不能信任海尔辛。如果你没有摔倒并撞到你的头颅的话，你会同意的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, a warrior once told me that wisdom was a poor substitute for a good mace.  But a tool only becomes a weapon when one knows how to wield it.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，一名战士曾告诉我，以智慧来代替一柄好用的狼牙棒可不是一个好主意。但一样工具，只有使用的人懂得如何运用，它才会变成武器。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your advice is amusing, but it won't help me slay a dragon.  Better you stay.</Source>
      <Dest>你的建议很有趣，不过对屠龙的事情帮不上忙。所以还是老实呆着吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, I trust you do not suffer from such deficiencies.  It is I who has learned much from our experiences together.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，我相信你并不会受这些问题困扰。与你同行的经历让我获益良多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your advice is amusing, but it won't help me slay a dragon.  Better you stay.</Source>
      <Dest>你的建议很有趣，不过对屠龙的事情帮不上忙。所以还是老实呆着吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is my regret that I cannot follow you to the end. Yet, while this path is meant to be walked by a single person, it will not walked be alone.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉不能跟你一路走到最后。但是，虽然得你一个人走，可你并不是一个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your advice is amusing, but it won't help me slay a dragon.  Better you stay.</Source>
      <Dest>你的建议很有趣，不过对屠龙的事情帮不上忙。所以还是老实呆着吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your advice is amusing, but it won't help me slay a dragon.  Better you stay.</Source>
      <Dest>你的建议很有趣，不过对屠龙的事情帮不上忙。所以还是老实呆着吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All of Nirn, and all the Gods, Aedra and Daedra, walk in harmony with your steps.  As do I.</Source>
      <Dest>奈恩的所有生物, 以及所有的众神，神族和魔族, 都与你的步伐一致。我也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you seek Nocturnal's favor, that is not the way.  Clutch the bird too tightly, and it will suffocate. Clutch it too lightly, and it will fly away.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你在寻求诺克图娜尔的帮助，那你的方式错了。就像将小鸟抓在掌心一样，如果你握得太紧，它就会窒息，而如果你握得太松，那它就会飞走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, I plan on worshipping her forever whether she likes it or not.</Source>
      <Dest>反正我这辈子就拜她了，管她愿不愿意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of fish do you like best?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢什么样的鱼？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is difficult to choose.  The other monks preferred the salmon, as did I, when all we did was salt the fish.</Source>
      <Dest>这很难去选。当我们之中只有腌鱼的时候，其他修道士却更喜欢大马哈鱼，我也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet in my travels across Tamriel, I tasted a longfin seared with onions, parsley, fresh garlic, and a squeeze of lemon, and I thought that was best.</Source>
      <Dest>但在我游历泰姆瑞尔大陆过程中，我尝过用洋葱，香菜，新鲜大蒜来搭配，并挤了点柠檬汁的长鳍鱼。我认为这么吃是最好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of fish do you like best?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢什么样的鱼？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so on and so forth, from raw to cooked, from the River Betty to the tuna and back to the salmon.  So, I will say the best is yet to come.</Source>
      <Dest>诸如此类，从生肉到熟食，从Betty河到金枪鱼，或者鲑鱼。所以，我觉得最好的美味总是需要等待。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of fish do you like best?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢什么样的鱼？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, and you are now prior of this monastery, a steward of magical knowledge.  You are the Arch-Mage.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，你现在是修道院的先驱，魔法知识的管理者。你是首席法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The College is safe, Ancano is dead, and the Eye is contained.</Source>
      <Dest>冬堡学院安全了, 虽然安卡诺死去了, 但是Eye被控制住了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When one is awarded such a position, it is often bittersweet, for it comes at the resignation of another.</Source>
      <Dest>当一个人被授予了这样一个职位，那么这常常是苦乐参半的，因为这来源于另一位的辞退。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The College is safe, Ancano is dead, and the Eye is contained.</Source>
      <Dest>冬堡学院安全了, 虽然安卡诺死去了, 但是Eye被控制住了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet such is the natural order of things.  Seasons turn, the old wither and die, and as Namira rots, Arkay gives way to new beginnings.</Source>
      <Dest>然而这就是自然的法则。四季转换，生物枯萎，死去，就像是娜米拉的腐朽，阿尔凯则给了我们一个新的开始。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The College is safe, Ancano is dead, and the Eye is contained.</Source>
      <Dest>冬堡学院安全了, 虽然安卡诺死去了, 但是Eye被控制住了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am reminded of the story of a chef who was summoned at the last minute to prepare a meal for his Jarl.  </Source>
      <Dest>我想起了一个关于一个匆匆被领主唤去准备餐点的厨师的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, those are the Daedra I like.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，这些都是我喜欢的魔族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, those are the Daedra I like.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，这些都是我喜欢的魔族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Pressed for time, he scurried to the garden and lopped off the tops from a patch of scallions and chives.  </Source>
      <Dest>由于时间紧迫，他匆忙地跑进菜园割一些葱和韭菜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unbeknownst to the chef, there was a green serpent amongst the vegetables, which he chopped and threw into the soup.</Source>
      <Dest>厨师并不知道的是，有一条绿色的小蛇就盘伏在那些他扔进汤里的蔬菜中间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, those are the Daedra I like.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，这些都是我喜欢的魔族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He had just realized his error when the Jarl and his housecarls entered the kitchen and greeted the chef.</Source>
      <Dest>当领主和他的侍卫来到厨房视察的时候，厨师才意识到自己犯的错误。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, those are the Daedra I like.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，这些都是我喜欢的魔族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Jarl was eager to try the chef's soup and quickly clutched the ladle, in spite of the chef's humble protest.</Source>
      <Dest>领主迫不及待地想要尝尝厨师做的汤，他抓起了汤匙并忽略了厨师低声下气的反对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, those are the Daedra I like.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，这些都是我喜欢的魔族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The chef cringed as the Jarl brought the soup to his lips, kissing the snake head as it floated to the surface.</Source>
      <Dest>领主将汤放到了嘴边，他的唇已经接触到了那条浮在汤表面的蛇头。厨师吓得畏缩了起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, those are the Daedra I like.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，这些都是我喜欢的魔族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, those are the Daedra I like.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，这些都是我喜欢的魔族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet the Jarl beamed.  It was the most delicious soup he had ever tasted.  </Source>
      <Dest>然而领主却是满脸笑容，他表示这是他尝过的最好喝的汤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An adventurer treads through a cave, when he is attacked by trolls.  He runs toward a ledge, and attempts to descend down a vine of hanging moss.</Source>
      <Dest>一名冒险者被一只巨魔袭击了，他不得不跑进一个洞穴。他跑向一块岩石突出的边缘，抓着悬苔的藤蔓试图降到下面去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is then that he discovers a pack of wolves at the bottom, waiting hungrily for his arrival.  Only the moss sustains him.  </Source>
      <Dest>然而他发现下面还有一群饿狼正饥肠辘辘地等着他下来。这时只有藤蔓支撑着他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If he waits, he knows that help may arrive.  The cave is frequented by warriors and adventurers alike.  </Source>
      <Dest>如果他等在那里，他知道也许救援会来。这个山洞好像经常有战士和冒险者出没。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is then that he notices the dagger lodged in the rock beside him.  </Source>
      <Dest>就在那时他发现他身后的石头上有一把匕首。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is just beyond his reach, but he thinks he can lunge for it, if he lets go of the moss.</Source>
      <Dest>那把匕首正巧比他能触及的范围远了一点点，但是他觉得他放开藤蔓的话，他可以一跃抓到那把匕首。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A wealthy Jarl requests a bard to craft him a verse for his children.  The verse must convey his desire for their happiness.</Source>
      <Dest>一名富有的领主要求一个吟游诗人为他的孩子们作一首诗，诗里要包含领主对他孩子们幸福的祝愿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The bard meditates on the subject, before returning with his verse.  He stands before the Jarl and recites the following:</Source>
      <Dest>诗人思考了一会，然后就开始吟唱。他站在领主面前唱出了如下诗句：</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Jarl leaps angrily from his throne, and demands the bard explain this insult.</Source>
      <Dest>领主听了之后，气得从他的宝座上跳了起来，然后要求诗人解释他刚才的无礼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The bard deftly replies, "Forgive me, my Jarl. You asked me to write a verse that conveys the spirit of true happiness."</Source>
      <Dest>诗人巧妙地答道：“请原谅我，我的领主。您刚才要求我写一首承载着真正幸福精神的诗歌”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The ambitious young swordsman visited the Hall of the Companions, in hopes of becoming a great warrior.</Source>
      <Dest>一个抱着成为一个伟大勇士梦想的富有野心的剑士来到了战友团。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Upon meeting the Harbinger, the swordsman asked, "If I start now, how long before I can become a Companion?"</Source>
      <Dest>当面见先驱的时候，那位剑士问道，"如果从现在开始算的话，我要多久才能成为战友团的一员呢？"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Harbinger stroked his gray beard and replied, "10 years."  The swordsman could not wait that long.  "What if I trained every day?" he asked.</Source>
      <Dest>先驱抚摸着他灰色的胡子然后说道，“10年。”  这个剑客等不了那么久。“如果我每天都训练呢？”他问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me a parable, monk.</Source>
      <Dest>给我讲个寓言吧，僧侣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Harbinger looked him in the eye and cracked a wry smile.  "Oh, it makes sense," he said, "for you see, those who hurry are slow to learn."</Source>
      <Dest>先驱看着他的眼睛并露出一个苦笑。“哦，那很有意义，”他说“正像你看见的，那些急于求成的人反而学不到东西。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I am eager to see what the winds of change have in store for Markarth.  The result will likely not be as either Madanach or the Jarl intends.</Source>
      <Dest>而我渴望看到变革之风为马卡斯城带来的是什么。结果或许会超出迈德纳奇亦或是领主的计划。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet only time will tell the true effect of our actions.  I am reminded of a parable, if you would like to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>不过只有时间才能证明我们所做之事的真正效果。我想起一个寓言，不知你有没有兴趣听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Forsworn are a blight on the Reach and had to be disposed.</Source>
      <Dest>那些弃誓者完全是瑞驰上的毒瘤，越早消灭越好！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And you have dealt a great blow, cutting the head off the snake.  Or it could be the Forsworn are like a worm, and each cut serves only to multiply.</Source>
      <Dest>你下手还真重，直接把那条蛇的脑袋给砍下来了。不过说不定弃誓者都跟蚯蚓一样，对半砍断了还能直接变出两只来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet only time will tell the true effects of our actions.  I am reminded of a parable, if you would like to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>到这一步，只有时间会证明我们行动的影响了……我想到一个寓言，要听么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Forsworn are a blight on the Reach and had to be disposed.</Source>
      <Dest>那些弃誓者完全是瑞驰上的毒瘤，越早消灭越好！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, which is why I value your counsel most of all.  If are minds were similar, we would undoubtedly come to the same conclusion.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，这就是我给你忠告的最主要原因。如果我们的思想彼此类似，那么毫无疑问，我们会得出一致的结论。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why in Oblivion are you asking me?  I just smash things.</Source>
      <Dest>你干毛要问我呢？我只是打杂的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Without an opposing viewpoint, I would not be forced to defend or reconsider my position, thus weakening its argument.</Source>
      <Dest>没有反方观点的话，我就没法据理力争或是重新考量己方观点，也就不能发起辩论。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why in Oblivion are you asking me?  I just smash things.</Source>
      <Dest>你干毛要问我呢？我只是打杂的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why in Oblivion are you asking me?  I just smash things.</Source>
      <Dest>你干毛要问我呢？我只是打杂的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it seems this topic does not interest you in the slightest.  Very well, perhaps there will be other things we can discuss later.</Source>
      <Dest>但你似乎对这个话题一点也提不起兴趣。好吧,也许我们一会儿可以讨论些其他事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So it is safe to say that you have no desire to spend eternity in Sovngarde.  But is it the Hunting Grounds of Hircine you seek?</Source>
      <Dest>那么说你对去松加德成就永生没什么兴趣准没错。或许海尔辛的狩猎场才是你所追寻的地方？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True. I would go mad if I had to live in a mead hall for the rest of my life.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，如果让我在蜂蜜酒地度过余生我会发疯的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One with your destiny can choose from many paths, but in the end, there is no clear solution.</Source>
      <Dest>你的一支命运能通过许多方式达到到，但最终，并没有明确的方式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True. I would go mad if I had to live in a mead hall for the rest of my life.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，如果让我在蜂蜜酒地度过余生我会发疯的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is the fate of mortals in life and in death. We must make decisions based on incomplete information, from a group of imperfect choices.</Source>
      <Dest>对于凡人来说，生死自有命。我们的从那些信息不完整的选择中做出决定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True. I would go mad if I had to live in a mead hall for the rest of my life.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，如果让我在蜂蜜酒地度过余生我会发疯的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And yet, the wisdom I have imparted is but a fraction of what I have learned through the experiences we have shared.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，我所被赋予的智慧只是从我们所分享的经验中所学到的东西中的一小部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm thankful to have had your wisdom through this journey.</Source>
      <Dest>这一路上有你的智慧相陪伴，我非常感激。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hope to weave your story into a new parable, for even the plight of a great hero may echo the struggles of all mortals.</Source>
      <Dest>我期望把你的故事编制入一个新的寓言中，因为一个伟大的英雄的困境会折射出所有凡人的挣扎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm thankful to have had your wisdom through this journey.</Source>
      <Dest>这一路上有你的智慧相陪伴，我非常感激。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thus it is my regret that I cannot follow you to the end. Yet, while this path is meant to be walked by a single person, it will not walked be alone.</Source>
      <Dest>因此我很抱歉不能陪你走到最后。虽然这条路注定只能一人前进，但你不会是一个人孤零零的上路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm thankful to have had your wisdom through this journey.</Source>
      <Dest>这一路上有你的智慧相陪伴，我非常感激。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm thankful to have had your wisdom through this journey.</Source>
      <Dest>这一路上有你的智慧相陪伴，我非常感激。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All of Nirn, and all the Gods, Aedra and Daedra, walk in harmony with your steps.  As do I.</Source>
      <Dest>奈恩的所有生物, 以及所有的众神，神族和魔族, 都与你的步伐一致。我也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) If I were you, I would not say that in front of her.  The capricious are also known to be vindictive.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑)我要是你，就绝不会在他面前说那样的话。那种任性通常也是很有报复心的呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like she's just lazy to me.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来她只是对我厌倦了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do not think so.  The Khajiit are desert people, Dragonborn, and there are very few fish that swim through sand.</Source>
      <Dest>我不这样认为。虎人是荒漠的人，龙裔, 在沙子中游过的鱼屈指可数。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's probably because you're a cat.  Cats like fish.  It is known.</Source>
      <Dest>很可能因为你是猫，猫喜欢鱼，众所周知。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Many, of course, prefer a different kind of fishing altogether, but Stendarr willed that I take a less traditional path.</Source>
      <Dest>许多人肯定会更喜欢一种另类的方法来捕鱼，但是斯丹纳尔却坚持认为我很少走传统的路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's probably because you're a cat.  Cats like fish.  It is known.</Source>
      <Dest>很可能因为你是猫，猫喜欢鱼，众所周知。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I pay homage to the Divines as a whole, and the invisible thread that is woven between them.  </Source>
      <Dest>整体来说，我对神灵还有那些交织在他们中间的无形的线表达敬意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you worship all Aedra and Daedra?</Source>
      <Dest>所以你信仰着所有的圣灵跟魔族？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One does not look at a centipede and see fifteen separate segments.  One cannot focus on a leaf, for in doing so he will neglect the whole tree.</Source>
      <Dest>某人看见一只蜈蚣时，看到的不会是十五个彼此独立的片段。同样也不会把全部注意力仅仅集中在一片叶子上，因为那样他将会忽略整棵树。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you worship all Aedra and Daedra?</Source>
      <Dest>所以你信仰着所有的圣灵跟魔族？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Very well. I'd be honored to hear your words.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了！我将十分荣幸听您讲话！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Say what you want to say.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，想说什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wish to thank you.  You are what the blacksmiths call a touchstone.  A standard bearer for all mortals.</Source>
      <Dest>我想谢谢你。你就是铁匠们所谓的“试金石”。一个供世人参照的楷模。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For time and time again you have sacrificed your life so that we may live.</Source>
      <Dest>你一次又一次，不惜性命拯救我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Very well. I'd be honored to hear your words.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了！我将十分荣幸听您讲话！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Say what you want to say.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，想说什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Very well. I'd be honored to hear your words.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了！我将十分荣幸听您讲话！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Say what you want to say.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，想说什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, I am not one who loathes dragons, for the fly cannot begrudge the spider for spinning its web.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，我不再是那些讨厌龙的人之一了，苍蝇不能因为蜘蛛结网就嫉妒它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, unlike the dragons of the wild, Alduin did not live in harmony with this world, for the world itself was his prey.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，跟其他的龙不一样，奥杜因不可能同这个世界和谐共处。因为世界本身就是他的猎物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Very well. I'd be honored to hear your words.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了！我将十分荣幸听您讲话！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Say what you want to say.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，想说什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was either him or us.  And as a member of the mortal race, I am glad that you were on our side.</Source>
      <Dest>不是他就是我们。作为人类的一员，我很高兴你在我们这边。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Very well. I'd be honored to hear your words.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了！我将十分荣幸听您讲话！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Say what you want to say.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，想说什么就说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Very well. I'd be honored to hear your words.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了！我将十分荣幸听您讲话！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wish to thank you.  You are what the blacksmiths call a touchstone.  A standard bearer for all mortals.</Source>
      <Dest>我想谢谢你。你就是铁匠们所谓的“试金石”。一个供世人参照的楷模。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For time and time again you have sacrificed your life so that we may live.</Source>
      <Dest>你一次又一次，不惜性命拯救我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Very well. I'd be honored to hear your words.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了！我将十分荣幸听您讲话！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Very well. I'd be honored to hear your words.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了！我将十分荣幸听您讲话！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, I am not one who loathes dragons, for the fly cannot begrudge the spider for spinning its web.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，我不再是那些讨厌龙的人之一了，苍蝇不能因为蜘蛛结网就嫉妒它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, unlike the dragons of the wild, Alduin did not live in harmony with this world, for the world itself was his prey.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，跟其他的龙不一样，奥杜因不可能同这个世界和谐共处。因为世界本身就是他的猎物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Very well. I'd be honored to hear your words.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了！我将十分荣幸听您讲话！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was either him or us.  And as a member of the mortal race, I am glad that you were on our side.</Source>
      <Dest>不是他就是我们。作为人类的一员，我很高兴你在我们这边。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Very well. I'd be honored to hear your words.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了！我将十分荣幸听您讲话！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alduin is no more. It's finally over.</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因不过如此。他最后还是被终结了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, you have returned victorious.  I suspect I should provide you with a parable to commemorate your triumph.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你胜利归来了。我想我应该给你撰写一则寓言，以此庆祝你的胜利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alduin is no more. It's finally over.</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因不过如此。他最后还是被终结了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet on this occasion, I wish to offer you my own words, and to speak to you not as a monk, but as a Khajiit.</Source>
      <Dest>但是，在这场合想, 我想送给你一句话，不是以一名修道士，而是作为一名虎人对你说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He is the wealthier of the two, yes, but men like him did not build their wealth by being generous.</Source>
      <Dest>两者中他更土豪，没错，不过这样的人可不是靠慷慨大方成为土豪的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thonar is wealthy and I assumed he would offer the greater boon.</Source>
      <Dest>托纳尔很富有而且我猜测他会提供更好的福利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And by choosing Thonar, Markarth will sustain its current order.  Thonar will grow stronger, and one wonders what it will take to return the balance.</Source>
      <Dest>通过托纳尔，马卡斯城得以维持其本来的秩序。然而随着托纳尔势力的强大，人们也开始担忧他所带来的势力平衡究竟会变成什么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thonar is wealthy and I assumed he would offer the greater boon.</Source>
      <Dest>托纳尔很富有而且我猜测他会提供更好的福利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet only time will tell the true effect of our actions.  I am reminded of a parable, if you would like to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>不过只有时间才能证明我们所做之事的真正效果。我想起一个寓言，不知你有没有兴趣听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thonar is wealthy and I assumed he would offer the greater boon.</Source>
      <Dest>托纳尔很富有而且我猜测他会提供更好的福利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For both yourself and for Markarth.  At times, order is like a pesky weed.  It must be pulled from the root, or it will return to its original size.</Source>
      <Dest>为了你自己，也为了马卡斯城。有时，秩序就如讨厌的杂草。斩草必除根，否则春风吹又生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Killing both seemed to be the most rewarding solution.</Source>
      <Dest>最好的解决方法就是把双方都给杀了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet only time will tell the true effect of our actions.  I am reminded of a parable, if you would like to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>不过只有时间才能证明我们所做之事的真正效果。我想起一个寓言，不知你有没有兴趣听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Killing both seemed to be the most rewarding solution.</Source>
      <Dest>最好的解决方法就是把双方都给杀了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So like Vanus Galerion before you, it is your belief that the Psijic's magic can exist outside the Elder Way.</Source>
      <Dest>正如像在你之前的万纳斯·加里兰一般，赛伊克人的魔法可以存在上古之道之外这点正是你的信仰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Psijic's magic is real.  I suspect the rest is philosophical troll manure.</Source>
      <Dest>赛伊克人的魔法是真实的。我怀疑其余部分只是故弄玄虚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Psijic's magic is real.  I suspect the rest is philosophical troll manure.</Source>
      <Dest>赛伊克人的魔法是真实的。我怀疑其余部分只是故弄玄虚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, one cannot say that guilds of Tamriel can compare to the power of the Psijics, despite having a larger pool of applicants.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，尽管它们有更多的申请者，我们仍不能说泰姆瑞尔的公会能与赛伊克的相提并论。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if indeed this is proof that the Elder Way is in fact the true key to harnessing one's magical potential.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道这是否可以证明：上古之道实则是控制一个人魔法潜能的关键。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Psijic's magic is real.  I suspect the rest is philosophical troll manure.</Source>
      <Dest>赛伊克人的魔法是真实的。我怀疑其余部分只是故弄玄虚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I just want power in this life.  I'll worry about the next when I'm dead.</Source>
      <Dest>我只想在活着时拥有力量。死后会如何我很担心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, but it is this life which determines your path to the next.  The two are connected, one constantly influencing the other.</Source>
      <Dest>哎，这就是命啊，此路未完又是一路。两路相连，总是在不停地互相影响的对方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I just want power in this life.  I'll worry about the next when I'm dead.</Source>
      <Dest>我只想在活着时拥有力量。死后会如何我很担心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For Kodlak, the anxiety of death altered his path in life.  For you, your myopic view of life will determine your path in death.</Source>
      <Dest>对于克拉科来说, 死亡的焦虑改变了他生命的轨迹。对于你来说，你人生观的短视决定你死亡的轨迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I just want power in this life.  I'll worry about the next when I'm dead.</Source>
      <Dest>我只想在活着时拥有力量。死后会如何我很担心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>After all, a wolf must serve Hircine for eternity.  One can seek a cure before their death, but few among us know when that day will come.</Source>
      <Dest>一头狼终归还是得为海尔辛服务的。他或许可以在死之前找到治疗的方法，但只有我们之中的少数人才知道死亡会在何时降临。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, that is a good question.  While I may have experienced some, they are all part of who I am.</Source>
      <Dest>啊, 这是一个很好的问题。虽然我大概经历了一些，那些都是我的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hold on.  How many of these parables were about your life?</Source>
      <Dest>稍等。你生活中有多少这样的故事啊？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For what are parables but lessons of life, experiences we all share, yet we can only learn from them when viewed from distance.</Source>
      <Dest>寓言就是生命的课程，经验我们都有，然而只有在事情过去以后我们回顾过去时才会学到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hold on.  How many of these parables were about your life?</Source>
      <Dest>稍等。你生活中有多少这样的故事啊？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To that end, this experience you will face is one that echoes the plight of many others.  So while you venture off by yourself, you do not go alone.</Source>
      <Dest>为此， 你面临的这经历会有得到许多人的回应。所以当你独自去冒险时，你并不孤单。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hold on.  How many of these parables were about your life?</Source>
      <Dest>稍等。你生活中有多少这样的故事啊？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hold on.  How many of these parables were about your life?</Source>
      <Dest>稍等。你生活中有多少这样的故事啊？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All of Nirn, and all the Gods, Aedra and Daedra, walk in harmony with your steps.  As do I.</Source>
      <Dest>奈恩的所有生物, 以及所有的众神，神族和魔族, 都与你的步伐一致。我也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I understand.  Respect the darkness, but don't depend on it.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了。敬畏黑暗，而不是依赖它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, for all darkness is temporary, as ephemeral as Nocturnal's favor.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，所有的黑暗是暂时的，就像诺克图娜尔的恩赐一样转瞬即逝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not so, my friend.  Today I was able to spend the day with the Dragonborn, as we made the journey to High Hrothgar.</Source>
      <Dest>不是那样，我的朋友。今天我能一直和龙裔在一块儿，一同踏上前往高吼峰的旅程。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>People recall the past fondly, but it used to be the present, and that's awful.</Source>
      <Dest>人们老是天真地怀念过去，可过去曾经也是当下，真可怕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was unlike any other day that has ever been lived, and when the future comes, I will look on this day as fondly as my days as a monk, if not more.</Source>
      <Dest>这一天和我曾经活过的每一天都不一样，而以后我也会牢牢记住这一天，至少和我做修道士的日子一样印象深刻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>People recall the past fondly, but it used to be the present, and that's awful.</Source>
      <Dest>人们老是天真地怀念过去，可过去曾经也是当下，真可怕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were torchbugs and luna moths, and flowers that seem to light up like candles in the shadow of the blood moon.</Source>
      <Dest>这里有火虫和月蛾，在绯色的月光下，簇簇花朵如同阴影中的烛光点点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of wonders?</Source>
      <Dest>什么样的奇迹？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As she was fearful of the dark, she did not stay.  Yet by the time she made her way home, she vowed to return to the garden the next morning.</Source>
      <Dest>因为她怕黑，所以没留下。但她回家的时候承诺说第二天早上会回花园的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of wonders?</Source>
      <Dest>什么样的奇迹？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only when she did, she was ultimately disappointed.  For while her fears were washed away by the light, so too was the mystery.</Source>
      <Dest>只有当她试过了，她才会失望。虽然她的恐惧和神秘感也一同被光明洗去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What sort of wonders?</Source>
      <Dest>什么样的奇迹？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When the four were at dinner, he slipped a vial of frenzy poison into his drink, just enough to make the second pupil irritable.</Source>
      <Dest>当四个人吃晚饭时，他悄悄把一小瓶狂乱药剂倒进酒里，剂量刚好够让第二个徒弟发疯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That night, when they returned to the shrine to meditate, the first pupil stepped on the second's foot.  "Watch it!" he screamed in anger.</Source>
      <Dest>那天晚上，当他们回到祭坛冥想的时候，打头的学生踩到了第二个学生的脚。“小心点儿！”他生气的喊道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The third pupil, shocked the second had broken his vow, said "Hush!  We are not supposed to talk!"</Source>
      <Dest>第三个学生，因第二个学生打破了他的誓言而震惊，“嘘！我们不应该说话的！”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The first pupil, who was dear friends with the third, exclaimed "No! Why did you speak? It was only supposed to be him!" </Source>
      <Dest>第一个学生，是第三个学生的密友，他高声喊道：“不！为什么你要这么说？唯一的可能是他！” </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And the fourth pupil, watching them, shook his head and said, "All three of you are fools.  I am the only one who has yet to break his vow."</Source>
      <Dest>而第四个学生,看着他们, 摇着他的头说, "你们三个都是傻瓜。我就是那个打破誓言的人"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did he do?</Source>
      <Dest>他做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Four pupils visited the Temple of Julianos, in hopes of learning the essence of wisdom.</Source>
      <Dest>四个学徒拜访了尤里安诺思神庙，希望学到智慧的真谛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright. Let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，让我们听听吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Priest suggested they take a vow of silence, so that they may learn to listen rather than speak.</Source>
      <Dest>那个牧师建议他们发誓“默言”，这样他们就会更加懂得倾听而不只会叽里呱啦地讲了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright. Let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，让我们听听吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The first pupil, however, did not like the second one, and made it his mission to ensure he would be the first to break.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，第一个学生不喜欢第二个学生，并把确保第一个取得突破当成了他的使命.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright. Let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，让我们听听吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes. As Nocturnal is the Goddess of the Dark, I am reminded of the story of the young child who wandered too far from home.</Source>
      <Dest>是的。提起诺克图娜尔——黑暗女神，我就想起了那个游走得离家太远的孩子的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nocturnal.  Does she remind you of a parable?</Source>
      <Dest>诺克图娜尔，她有没有让你回想起一个寓言？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lost and alone, the child followed the northern star, knowing it would guide her back to the village by the shore.</Source>
      <Dest>迷失和孤独，孩子跟着北斗星，知道它能引导她回到村里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nocturnal.  Does she remind you of a parable?</Source>
      <Dest>诺克图娜尔，她有没有让你回想起一个寓言？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet on the way, she found herself in a peculiar garden.  Suddenly, all around her were tiny wonders.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，在路上，她发现身处于一个奇怪的花园中。忽然之间，她四周都充满着微小的奇迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nocturnal.  Does she remind you of a parable?</Source>
      <Dest>诺克图娜尔，她有没有让你回想起一个寓言？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was an act of the Divines.  As was the placement of the book, and the title of the book itself.</Source>
      <Dest>那是圣灵的行为。就如同那本书放置的场所，还有它本身的标题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait. So the doctrine you follow is based on a head injury?</Source>
      <Dest>等等，你所遵守的信条该不会是在你撞坏了脑子的时候制定出来的吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait. So the doctrine you follow is based on a head injury?</Source>
      <Dest>等等，你所遵守的信条该不会是在你撞坏了脑子的时候制定出来的吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In my vision I saw a constellation of Gods.  Aedra and Daedra.  They made no distinction between themselves.  For one were all, and all were one.</Source>
      <Dest>在眼前，我看到了星座上的神灵们。他们之间并没有什么区别。一就是万物，万物是一。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Khajiit was confused.  "It is not something I can just show you," he said.  The priest replied, "Then it is not your true nature."</Source>
      <Dest>那个虎人被搞糊涂了。他说“这不是能直接展现给你看的东西”。祭司回答说，“那这就不是你的天性使然。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did the Khajiit say?</Source>
      <Dest>那个虎人说了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so I learned a valuable lesson that day.  I learned my actions were a choice, and I alone was responsible for the consequences.</Source>
      <Dest>所以那天我学到了宝贵的一课。我明白了我的行为是一个选择,而我得为自己的选择承担后果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did the Khajiit say?</Source>
      <Dest>那个虎人说了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>From that day on I vowed to always make the right choices, to always walk on level sands.</Source>
      <Dest>从那天起，我就发誓要一直做出正确的选择，这样才能一直行走在沙地之上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did the Khajiit say?</Source>
      <Dest>那个虎人说了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And yet in all my years, I have never made a finer choice than the day I decided to follow your path.</Source>
      <Dest>我至今仍然觉得，当初决定跟随你是我这辈子做的最出色的决定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did the Khajiit say?</Source>
      <Dest>那个虎人说了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It has been an honor, Dragonborn.  I thank you for allowing me to accompany you on this journey.</Source>
      <Dest>荣幸之至，龙裔。谢谢你允许我和你一起旅行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did the Khajiit say?</Source>
      <Dest>那个虎人说了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, it is regarding this Forsworn Conspiracy that you have unraveled.  I am curious as to why you chose Thonar over Madanach.</Source>
      <Dest>对，你弄清楚了弃誓者叛乱的那档子事儿。我很好奇为什么你选择了托纳尔而不是迈德纳奇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Forsworn Conspiracy) You look like you have something on your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>(弃誓者叛乱) 貌似你在想什么事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He is the one who imprisoned you, and the order that exists in Markarth is a mirage of his making.  Were you not tempted to disrupt it with chaos?</Source>
      <Dest>他就是那个监禁你的人，还有所有出马卡斯城存在的秩序都是他所制造出的幻象。难道你不打算利用混乱破坏这一切么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Forsworn Conspiracy) You look like you have something on your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>(弃誓者叛乱) 貌似你在想什么事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, it is regarding this Forsworn Conspiracy that you have unraveled.  I am curious as to why you chose Madanach over Thonar.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，看来你好像解决了弃誓者叛乱这个问题。我很好奇你为什么会选迈德纳奇而不是托纳尔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Forsworn Conspiracy) You look like you have something on your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>(弃誓者叛乱) 貌似你在想什么事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The temptation to maintain the existing order must have been great, despite it being a mirage.</Source>
      <Dest>倾向于保持现有秩序是很好，虽然只是一厢情愿而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Forsworn Conspiracy) You look like you have something on your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>(弃誓者叛乱) 貌似你在想什么事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Forsworn Conspiracy) You look like you have something on your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>(弃誓者叛乱) 貌似你在想什么事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, it is regarding this Forsworn Conspiracy that you have unraveled.  I am curious as to your decision regarding Madanach and Thonar.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，看来你好像解决了弃誓者叛乱这个问题。我很好奇你在迈德纳奇和托纳尔之间做出的选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Mages Guild Quest) You look like you have something on your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>(法师公会任务) 你看起来有点心事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As a matter of fact, I do.  It is regarding one of the text you retrieved from Fellglow Keep.  The one on Artaeum.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上,我做了。这关系到你在光落塔楼取回的一份资料。在阿泰翁岛的那份。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Mages Guild Quest) You look like you have something on your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>(法师公会任务) 你看起来有点心事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It appears that, true to their name, the Psijic are monks who practice meditation and philosophy as I do, as part of their "Elder Way."</Source>
      <Dest>它出现了，正如其名。赛伊克人都是些如我一样练习冥想以及思考哲理的修道士，是他们 "上古之道"的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Mages Guild Quest) You look like you have something on your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>(法师公会任务) 你看起来有点心事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am curious what you think of the link between developing one's magical abilities in concert with developing one's mind.</Source>
      <Dest>我很好奇你对一个人魔法能力的提升和其思想的发展之间的联系怎么看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Mages Guild Quest) You look like you have something on your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>(法师公会任务) 你看起来有点心事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is magic a dangerous force which requires a philosophy to control?  Or is the Elder Way a means to achieving powerful magic?</Source>
      <Dest>魔法的危险力量需要信念来控制？或是上古之道就是获得强魔力的手段？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Mages Guild Quest) You look like you have something on your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>(法师公会任务) 你看起来有点心事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fundamentally, do you believe that one can exist without the other?</Source>
      <Dest>从根本上说，你相信一个个体可以脱离群体独立存在吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, and so the tale of our hero is coming to its climax.  It reminds me of the parable of the young Khajiit who asked a priest for Stendarr's mercy.</Source>
      <Dest>啊,然后我们英雄的传说迎来了它的巅峰。这让我想起了那个请求牧师施展斯坦达之恕的年轻虎人的寓言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) We've done it.  Odahviing will take me to Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>（龙临堡）我们成功了。傲达威英会带我去松加德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) We've done it.  Odahviing will take me to Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>（龙临堡）我们成功了。傲达威英会带我去松加德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Khajiit told the priest he had a terrible temper, and it thrust his body into fits of violence.</Source>
      <Dest>这个虎人告诉祭司他脾气很坏。而且这脾气把他的身体搞得越来越适应暴力了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) We've done it.  Odahviing will take me to Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>（龙临堡）我们成功了。傲达威英会带我去松加德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The priest asked the young cat to demonstrate this temper, so he might see it.  </Source>
      <Dest>祭司让这只小虎猫展示下它那暴脾气给他看看，所以他大概会看到的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am pleased you asked.  There appears to be a divide in the Hall of Jorrvaskr between those who embrace the wolf, and those who shun it.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴你能提问。貌似那些信奉狼和回避狼的人在月瓦斯卡大厅中有一道分界线。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Companions Quest) What are your thoughts on the Companions and the Circle?</Source>
      <Dest>（战友团任务）您对于同伴和圆环有什么想法么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Companions Quest) What are your thoughts on the Companions and the Circle?</Source>
      <Dest>（战友团任务）您对于同伴和圆环有什么想法么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To me, this divide is merely a product of perspective.   For when you see Hircine as evil, to serve him is tantamount to slavery.</Source>
      <Dest>对我来说，这个界限就在于你是否能看的清。当你把海尔辛当做恶魔来看时，服侍他就和做他的奴隶无异。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Another might say Hircine serves his hunters, by providing them with a purpose, and an eternity of prey.</Source>
      <Dest>别人可会说是海尔辛为他的猎人效力，为他们提供目的，和永远存在的猎物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Companions Quest) What are your thoughts on the Companions and the Circle?</Source>
      <Dest>（战友团任务）您对于同伴和圆环有什么想法么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If Sovngarde is a mead hall of drink and festivities, I imagine someone like Aela would find it a chore.</Source>
      <Dest>如果松加德是买醉和狂欢的酒馆，像艾拉那样的人会发现这是一个苦差事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Companions Quest) What are your thoughts on the Companions and the Circle?</Source>
      <Dest>（战友团任务）您对于同伴和圆环有什么想法么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Companions Quest) What are your thoughts on the Companions and the Circle?</Source>
      <Dest>（战友团任务）您对于同伴和圆环有什么想法么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such is the diversity of mortals.  Sovngarde may be a utopia for some, but for others it is an Oblivion, a nightmare from which there is no escape.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是凡人的分歧。松加德也许对一些人来说是个乐园，但对其他人来说，这里就是湮灭领域，一个无法逃脱的噩梦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Thieves Guild) Is what Karliah said about Nocturnal true?</Source>
      <Dest>（盗贼公会）卡莉亚所说的诺克图娜尔的真相是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That she revels in your suffering and your success?  That she is as capricious as the wind?</Source>
      <Dest>她沉溺于你的痛苦，却又着迷于你的成功？她像风那样的反复无常吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Thieves Guild) Is what Karliah said about Nocturnal true?</Source>
      <Dest>（盗贼公会）卡莉亚所说的诺克图娜尔的真相是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, it is all true, and all lies.  She is a paradox.  She despises those who worship her, but punishes those who neglect.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，全是真的，又全是假的。她是矛盾的集合体。她鄙视那些崇拜她的人，却又惩罚那些怠慢她的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She will grant you her blessing but mock those who rely on it.  Such is the mantra of the thief, and the way of the shadow.</Source>
      <Dest>她会给你祝福，但却会嘲笑那些依赖它的人。这就是盗贼的颂歌，还有阴影之路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Thieves Guild) Is what Karliah said about Nocturnal true?</Source>
      <Dest>（盗贼公会）卡莉亚所说的诺克图娜尔的真相是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Thieves Guild) Is what Karliah said about Nocturnal true?</Source>
      <Dest>（盗贼公会）卡莉亚所说的诺克图娜尔的真相是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And yet through the chaos there is purpose.  Those who follow Nocturnal learn self-reliance, but also learn respect.</Source>
      <Dest>然而这场混乱也是有所作用的。那些追随着诺克图娜尔的人学会了自立，也学会了尊重。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Way of the Voice) Being here must bring back memories of being a monk.</Source>
      <Dest>（吼声之道）在这儿肯定能唤起你僧侣的记忆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, it does. We did not have 7,000 steps mind you, but the monastery was perched high.</Source>
      <Dest>对，我们还没有到7000步呢，但修道院就在那么高的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thus the younger acolytes were given the privilege of fetching the water and fish from the river below.</Source>
      <Dest>因此那年轻的祀祭被授予了从河底取水和鱼的特权</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Way of the Voice) Being here must bring back memories of being a monk.</Source>
      <Dest>（吼声之道）在这儿肯定能唤起你僧侣的记忆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Way of the Voice) Being here must bring back memories of being a monk.</Source>
      <Dest>（吼声之道）在这儿肯定能唤起你僧侣的记忆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do not know if my fondness for fish was a result of my longing for those halcyon days, or if the fish itself gave me nostalgia for the mundane.</Source>
      <Dest>我不清楚我对鱼的喜爱是否源于我对宁静生活的向往，或是否鱼本身让我产生了思乡之情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There was nothing natural about their deaths.  Savos and Mirabelle were killed.</Source>
      <Dest>他们的死亡不是天生的。萨沃斯和米拉贝勒是被杀的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, but it was.  It is because any moment can bring death, that we learn to value life.  I am reminded of a parable, if you wish to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，但曾经是。恰恰是因为随时会死，所以我学会珍惜生命。我想起一个寓言，你想听一下吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May you be safe, wherever you go.</Source>
      <Dest>无论你去哪，愿平安常伴你左右。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May safety and prosperity find you, wherever you go.</Source>
      <Dest>无论你去哪，愿平安与成功常伴你左右。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, traveler.</Source>
      <Dest>你好，旅行者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>哈啰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good to see you again.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴再次见到你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, you return.</Source>
      <Dest>啊,你回来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What can Qa'Dojo do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>奎兜啾能为你做些什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The drop is steep, but perhaps if we can climb down the walls, we can avoid learning the hard way if the water is shallow.</Source>
      <Dest>太陡了，可如果我们能从墙上爬下去，就不用冒险去赌下面的水浅不浅啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One wonders how many have passed under the watchful gaze of these twin eagles. For them, we are but tomorrow's history.</Source>
      <Dest>人们不知道有多少人已经在这双鹰的密切注意中逝去了。对它们来说，我们只不过是明日的历史。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So we have trekked through a cave teeming with violence, and have come to a calm. Yet this tableau of serenity belies the danger ahead. Be ready.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我们已经跋涉越过了一个充斥着暴力的洞穴，来到了这一处宁静所在。但是这平静的表面不过是掩盖了其下的危险。多加小心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A shrine to Julianos. As you can see, it is not only the Daedra who have their ideals twisted by mortals.</Source>
      <Dest>尤里安诺斯的祭坛呢...喏，如你所见，在人间的认知被扭曲的可不止魔族而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This cave paints an interesting picture. The light shines on this dark ritual, to grow the seeds of evil.</Source>
      <Dest>这个洞穴描绘出了一幅有趣的画面。光线洒在这黑暗的仪式上，邪恶的种子破土生长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A foul mist walks these ruins, but it is not the work of Peryite. It does not end life, but corrupts it.</Source>
      <Dest>一个邪恶的灵体在这废墟上飘荡, 但这并不是魄伊特干的。它不会杀死生命,但会腐化它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems I was wrong. This does not appear to be a misunderstood wonder, but rather a dark ritual disguised as something wondrous.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来我错了。这好像是个误会，但也总比一个被伪装成奇妙的魔法的黑暗仪式要好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am proof that a steep fall is not always such a bad thing. It may lead you to unexpected places.</Source>
      <Dest>我证明，一次急剧的坠落不一定都是坏事。也行会带你到一处意想不到的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The drop is steep, but perhaps if we can climb down the walls, we can avoid learning the hard way if the water is shallow.</Source>
      <Dest>太陡了，可如果我们能从墙上爬下去，就不用冒险去赌下面的水浅不浅啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good.  Our things are many.  Let us find the appropriate balance.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。我们还有很多事儿要做。让我们在这之中寻找一个恰当的平衡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here for a moment.</Source>
      <Dest>在这儿等一下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here.</Source>
      <Dest>在这里等着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I understand.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need you to do something for me.</Source>
      <Dest>我需要你为我做件事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What can Qa'Dojo do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>奎兜啾能为你做些什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's nothing. Never mind.</Source>
      <Dest>没什么事，不用担心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes. Let me show you.</Source>
      <Dest>不错，你看看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take your time.</Source>
      <Dest>抓紧时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take your time.</Source>
      <Dest>慢慢儿来。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Departs}</Source>
      <Dest>{离开 }</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well.  Perhaps like the Count and the carpenter, I will return to whence I came.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。也许跟那位伯爵和那木匠一样，我会回到原先的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then let us wander these white sands and find our destination.</Source>
      <Dest>我们好好在这白沙上走一走，找找我们的目的地吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is there anything else?</Source>
      <Dest>还有别的么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am sorry, but it cannot be done.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉，但我做不到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I understand.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take your time.</Source>
      <Dest>抓紧时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take your time.</Source>
      <Dest>慢慢儿来。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Zzzzz...</Source>
      <Dest>Zzzzz……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So Leifnarr is dead.  The question now is, who stands to gain from the sale of Heartwood Mill?  Answer that, and you find his murderer.</Source>
      <Dest>那么雷夫纳尔已经死了。问题在于，谁会因出售心木磨坊而得益？找到这问题的答案，就找到了谋杀他的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You were a Companion before, but now you are one they trust.  I suspect it will not be long before you are truly family...in name, and in blood.</Source>
      <Dest>你之前是一个同伴，但现在你是他们信赖之人。你会成为他们真正的家人……在名义上如此，血液之中也如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The steps here remind me of a monastery.  Perhaps this place was once known as the Temple of the Silent Moons.</Source>
      <Dest>这里的台阶让我回想起一座修道院来。也许这个地方曾经被称为静月神殿呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When words fail, a good brawl is a healthy way to vent one's frustrations.  To bottle them inside will only make things worse in the end.</Source>
      <Dest>当无法用言语表达时，打一架或许是个不错的发泄方法。压制他们只能让事情变得更糟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So this is not a cave of conjurers, but rather an excavation of some kind.  What manner of ruin is this, for it to attract such dark forces?</Source>
      <Dest>所以这不是一个巫师的洞穴，而更像是某种古迹。这是怎样的废墟才会吸引如此的黑暗之力呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>From the egg of creation, the next world attempts to hatch.  Yet the fox lurks outside the coop, and we need not guile to enter.  The fence is open.</Source>
      <Dest>从蛋被创造之日起，就准备被孵化出来。但狐狸就潜伏在鸡舍里，我们无需计谋就能进入。栅栏已经被打开了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is said that the dragon priests worshipped power.  Yet the irony is, it appears the Staff of Magnus is designed to contain it.  </Source>
      <Dest>据说，龙祭祀崇尚着力量。然而讽刺的是，看起来，玛格努斯之杖，是用来牵制力量的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We seem to be descending further and further.  As if entering the bowels of some cavernous beast.</Source>
      <Dest>我们好像在一直向下走。感觉就像我们走进了某种穴居生物的肠道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goblets.  Ewers.  Fine rugs and noble chairs.  Yet elegance cannot conceal the vampire's true nature, as evidenced by this cage.</Source>
      <Dest>酒杯。注壶。柔软的地摊和精致的凳子。然而，优雅无法掩饰的吸血鬼的本性，通过这鲜血淋淋的笼子就得以证明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By Azura!  To have fought in this Arena, to have challenged a dragon of bone and breath...I am a foolish monk, and a lucky one.</Source>
      <Dest>阿祖拉在上！在这个竞技场里战斗，去挑战龙之骸骨和龙息……我真是个愚蠢的修道士，也是个幸运至极的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The mage we seek is called the Augur of Dunlain, and to "augur" is to prophesize. Funny how often believing a prophecy is what leads to its fruition.</Source>
      <Dest>我们找的魔法叫预言师杜兰, 然后 "预兆"是做出预言。有趣的是，经常是Funny how often believing a prophecy is what leads to its fruition.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you have spared The Caller, despite knowing her practices.  Is this because you fear her magic, despise vampires, or prefer a peaceful solution?</Source>
      <Dest>所以你就算知道她的做法了，也还是宽恕了来访者。这到底是因为你怕了她的魔法了，还是轻视吸血鬼？亦或是想找到一个更为和平的解决方法？?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder what the true effects are of The Caller's death.  Will the vampires thrive in her absence? It is a curious question, but one with no answer.</Source>
      <Dest>我很好奇召唤者死亡的真正影响。她已不存在的情况下，吸血鬼还能活得好好的吗？这是一个令人饶有兴趣的问题，却没有答案。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is much you have not told us about this Caller, Orthorn.  All conjurers are callers, but what makes her special?  Who, or what, does she call?</Source>
      <Dest>奥松恩，你好像没跟我们说清楚关于这位“召唤者”小姐的事。所有的召唤师都会召唤，那她这个名字有什么特别的？还是她能特别召唤谁？还是什么东西？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Rogue mages and alchemists experiment with vampire dust for its magical properties.  But one need only chew on it to "see" its effects, so to speak.</Source>
      <Dest>流浪的法师和炼金术士因为吸血鬼之尘的特性而去用它进行试验。恕我直言，但有人只是需要咀嚼它去“看”它的效果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Curiously, there were only 2 points of emphasis on the map.  It seems all of Tamriel has its eyes on Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>奇怪的是，这地图上只有两个需要重视的要点。看起来全泰姆瑞尔大陆的目光都集中在天际省上了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Things have calmed here, but back at the College, the storm rages.  We should return.</Source>
      <Dest>这边的情况稳定了，可学院那边还有风暴在肆虐。我们必须回去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What strange jewel have we uncovered, and more importantly, what has this discovery set into motion?  This is only the beginning, I am afraid.</Source>
      <Dest>我们发现的这是什么奇怪的宝石啊？更重要的是，这个发现会引发什么事情。这恐怕仅仅是个开始。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It appears this aqueduct is central to this place. The water is pumped in, boiled, and transformed into the vapor which breathes life into this ruin.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来这条管子像是这里的核心。外面的水被抽进来烧开，变成蒸汽为这个遗迹提供动力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When mages dig into the unknown, it is often an accident waiting to happen.  Yet the word "accident" does not imply a negative result.</Source>
      <Dest>当法师们在未知的世界里上下求索时，意外常常不期而至。然而“意外”并不总意味着糟糕的后果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you are now a student of the College.  I am glad to see this Tolfdir is your instructor.  Let us hope he is as principled as he is cautious.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你现在是这个学院的学生。很高兴看到托夫迪尔成为你的导师。因为他有着既谨慎又刚正的性格。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In war, it is often iron that turns the tide. 5 farmers with cheaply made iron swords, may vanquish a well-paid knight dressed in steel.</Source>
      <Dest>在战争时代，铁器就是王道。五个菜刀老农能砍倒钢甲骑兵呢！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Many children's tales that tell the virtue of hard work, but in reality, there are relationships like Birna's and Ranmir's where laziness rules.</Source>
      <Dest>有很多童话故事讲述着辛勤工作的美德，可现实中确实有Birna和Ranmir那样的奉行懒惰至上的家庭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There are those here who fear what they do not understand, and there are others who bravely tamper with the unknown.  In the end, both are dangerous.</Source>
      <Dest>有的人害怕他们不懂的事物，也有的人勇敢地玩弄着未知。最终，都是危险的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A long hallway and a single door.  It is almost as if they are testing our patience.  For it is easy to rush ahead when there is no other path.</Source>
      <Dest>漫长的走廊和孤零零的一道门。鉴于没有别的路可走很容易冲过去的情况下，这几乎就像是在考验我们的耐性。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In these catacombs there are Draugr who lie down to sleep, and Draugr who lie in wait.</Source>
      <Dest>这些墓穴里沉眠着无数的尸鬼，他们之中有些已然长眠，有些却静静等待着侵入者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The will of the Gods is evident.  Vaermina's influence will inspire the people here, but you intervened before it could corrupt.</Source>
      <Dest>神的意愿很清楚。瓦尔迷纳的声望激励着这里的人民, 但你在失控之前介入了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anska, sometimes our family bonds give us strength. Other times our bloodline makes us dependent on ghosts. I hope your mind is clear.</Source>
      <Dest>Anska, sometimes our family bonds give us strength. Other times our bloodline makes us dependent on ghosts.  I hope your mind is clear.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Clearpine Pond.  Life grows here in abundance, and in Tamriel, with life comes magic. Those who seek its power come in many forms.</Source>
      <Dest>清松池塘。生命在这里欣欣向荣，同时在塔玛瑞尔，魔法伴随生命而来，那些寻求魔法之力的人也变得各式各样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Madness and genius are intertwined. This priest calls Vaermina evil, because he fails to see that evil does not exist.</Source>
      <Dest>疯狂与天才是交织在一起的。这个牧师把维尔米那叫做恶魔，是因为他没法认识到其实恶魔并不存在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The beliefs of this temple are fickle.   But Eight or Nine, Aedra or Daedra, the Gods are Gods.  It is not up to mortals to decide.</Source>
      <Dest>这寺庙的信仰变化无常。但是无论八圣还是九圣，圣灵还是魔族，神就是神。这不是凡人所能决定的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Gold Ribbon of Merit.  To me, it is very much a story of chaos and order; a duel between a marksman of the wild and a tournament champion. </Source>
      <Dest>象征着功勋的金缎带。对我来说，这更多的是一个关于混沌与秩序的故事，一场荒野神射手与锦标赛冠军之间的较量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do not see the need for so many clothes.  A monk has a single robe, and he wears it like his own fur.</Source>
      <Dest>我不觉得有必要弄这么多衣服。每个僧侣都有自己的长袍，而他会把这长袍当作自己的皮毛穿着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A wise monk once said, when one returns from a long journey, they may find their home much smaller than when they left it.</Source>
      <Dest>子曾经曰过，归家的游子一定会觉得自己家比印象中要小。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To destroy Dragon Bridge is to cut off the enemy's reinforcements.  Yet I have a feeling this bridge has survived many such attempts.</Source>
      <Dest>毁灭龙桥就是切断了敌人的后援。但我感觉这桥已经在很多次这样的尝试下幸存.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A persistent dog will often choose his own master, and not allow that master to refuse.  One wonders who is truly in charge.</Source>
      <Dest>固执的老狗一般会自己选主人，而且拒绝接受主人的回绝。这让好奇谁才是主人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Skulls and enchantment tables.  Blacksmith tools and bottles of wine.  The items here are a timeline, showing a history of this fort's occupants.</Source>
      <Dest>Skulls and enchantment tables.  Blacksmith tools and bottles of wine.  The items here are a timeline, showing a history of this fort's occupants.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Someone has already raided this crypt.  And whoever it was did not care how many of his companions had fallen.</Source>
      <Dest>有人已经洗劫过这个地穴了，是那种根本不在乎自己队伍战损的亡命之徒干的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Movarth was a wicked creature, yet one can't help but admire the tenacity it took to survive for centuries. Not to mention strength, guile, and luck.</Source>
      <Dest>莫瓦斯是个邪恶的生物，但我不得不佩服一下他生存了几百年的坚韧劲儿。更别说是他的力量，狡诈，和运气了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While some prefer to study the composition of ingredients, this Lami chooses to rely on random chance. Who is to say which will yield better results?</Source>
      <Dest>在别人学习药剂配方的时候，拉米这家伙选择去碰运气。你说，是谁有好结果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hroggar's actions are not unusual. The vampire is like a moonflower. It blooms only at night, petals as white as Secunda. Beautiful and poisonous. </Source>
      <Dest>赫鲁加的行为再正常不过了。吸血鬼就如同一朵只在黑夜中绽放的月光花，花瓣洁白如塞康达。美丽却致命。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say a woman who lives here abandoned her family to join the Stormcloaks.  Perhaps to abandon the Gods was the far greater crime.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说一位住在这的女人抛弃了她的家庭而加入风暴斗篷。 也许抛弃了诸神才是更大的罪行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We must approach this investigation with caution.  Do not be tempted by the easy answer, especially when there is no evidence to support it.</Source>
      <Dest>你要仔细调查这个，不要轻信那些显而易见的结论，尤其是没有明确的证据支持你的判断的时候.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In one room, a beautiful courtyard.  Down the hall, a torture chamber.  And so in a matter of seconds we are shown the duality of mortals.</Source>
      <Dest>在一个漂亮院子的房间中。沿着走廊下来，有一个酷刑室。不止如此，几秒钟内我们看到了人类的善恶多变.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What could have killed these men?  Falmer?  Dwarves?  Judging by the cups and position of the bodies, it was a combination of neglect and fear.</Source>
      <Dest>什么玩意儿害死了这些人？雪精灵？锻模？由这些杯子和尸体的位置判断，他们死前处于一种懈怠和恐慌交织在一起的情绪中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is a privilege to adventure with an archer of your skill.  There will be little trouble hunting for food in the wild.</Source>
      <Dest>对一名冒险者来说，跟一个有助于你的弓箭手在一起是种荣幸。在野外猎取食物的时候会有点儿麻烦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The two-handed weapon is a dangerous sword.  Always tumbling forward,  dragging its owner behind it.  It is up to you to provide the counterweight.</Source>
      <Dest>双手武器是一种危险的武器。永远横冲直撞，拖拽着它的主人向前。你只不过是向它提供平衡而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have known Daedric blood to have magical properties, but I was not aware of its use in smithing.  One learns something new every day.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道魔族的血有神奇的特性,但我没意识到把它用到锻造上。知识日新月异啊</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In war, it is often iron that turns the tide.  5 farmers with cheaply made iron swords, may vanquish a well-paid knight dressed in steel.</Source>
      <Dest>在战争时代，铁器就是王道。五个菜刀老农还能砍倒钢甲骑兵呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say a beast will grow as large as its surroundings will allow.  Judging by the size of this excavation, Nimhe will be a formidable foe.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说，一头野兽能尽环境允许的量尽情成长变大。根据开凿出来的洞穴大小，尼姆赫会是个强大的对手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Thalmor insist on creating resentment, as a weakened Empire benefits only them.  We should not assist them further.</Source>
      <Dest>因为一个虚弱的帝国不仅仅能让他们收益，所以梭默才会那样执着于制造纷争。我们不应该再协助他们了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, here you are, free from Cidhna Mine.  It was smart to submit to the guards.  An opening always presents itself to those who wait for it.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你来了，从希讷矿场出来了。向守卫示弱是很聪明的举动。道路总会为愿意寻路的人打开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Beware.  Whatever killed these two still lurks about.  Or perhaps is merely playing dead.</Source>
      <Dest>小心，杀掉这两个的不管是什么，可能仍然在周围潜伏着。也有可能仅仅是在装死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This Lurbuk does not let criticism dissuade him.  Yet it is his confidence that is the true deterrent to his growth as a bard.</Source>
      <Dest>这个卢布克根本听不进别人说他不好。而就是他的这种自负，成为了他吟游诗人道路上的绊脚石。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So the Orc bard has perished.  It is unfortunate, but things that are...unnatural tend to have a difficult time surviving.</Source>
      <Dest>所以那个兽人吟游诗人已经挂了。真是不幸，但凡事都是如此……异类往往难以生存。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Boethiah and Molag Bal.  You see, there are Daedra who consider each other adversaries, just as there are those who consider the Aedra to be allies.</Source>
      <Dest>波耶西亚与莫拉格·巴尔。你瞧，他们是那些互相对方是敌人的魔族，就像那些认为神族是同盟的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There are many things in this world that eat the dead.  Perhaps not enough, if the Draugr are any indication.</Source>
      <Dest>这个世界上吃尸体的玩意儿多的是。这些尸鬼可能预示着什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Verulus and Eola. Arkay and Namira. An eternal struggle, as is fitting for those who rule the realm of eternity.  Who will you side with on this day?</Source>
      <Dest>维鲁鲁斯和爱欧拉. 阿尔凯和娜米拉.一场永恒的争斗, 为的是拟定谁统治领地。这一天，你要站在哪一方？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Namira's presence is strong in these Warrens, just as Mephala's haunts the rest of Markarth.</Source>
      <Dest>娜米拉的灵魂在这些贫民窟中十分强大,就如梅法拉在马卡斯城部分地区经常出没一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is not uncommon for an elder mage or warrior to find an isolated cabin like this, so that she may meditate and find her own absolution.</Source>
      <Dest>年老的法师或者战士寻找一个像是这样偏僻的小屋并不是什么怪事，看起来她也许在寻找她自己救赎的方式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So the old mage was a witch.  This in itself is not enough to condemn her.  This did not have to end in death, had she shown more restraint.</Source>
      <Dest>那么这个老法师是个女巫。就这个事实而言谴责她是不够的，但是这件事没必要以死亡收尾，毕竟她已经表现的相当克制。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is a great honor to join a Temple, and to devote yourself to service.  You should not worry about this child Sybil, or her family.</Source>
      <Dest>加入寺庙并献身服务其中是个巨大的荣耀，你用不着担心西比尔这孩子或者是她的家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There are many paths to success.  Persistence, luck, necessity, divine intervention...This boy may need all to compensate for his lack of talent.</Source>
      <Dest>导向成功的因素有很多，毅力、运气、资源、神的帮助……那孩子缺乏天赋，因而他需要上面的提及到的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Silver-Bloods believe wealth equals power, but to buy alliances with gold means to deal with those willing to sell their honor.</Source>
      <Dest>银血相信财富等同于力量，但用钱来买联盟则意味着要耍手段来对付那些愿意背弃自身荣耀的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When twin moons are trapped in a pail of water, only when that water is spilled are they set free.  This conspiracy is a pail about to tip over.</Source>
      <Dest>当两个月亮被困于一桶水里的时候，只有把水泼掉才能还它们自由。这个阴谋就是那个该被翻倒的桶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I find it admirable that in the face of adversity, these miners still find time to fuss over the mundane.  It shows their strength.</Source>
      <Dest>对于这些矿工在面对逆境时，仍然有时间去操心世俗之事，我真的深感敬佩。这显露了他们的强大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Elders like Bothela have shed a lifetime of sweat and tears.  Only now, as their bodies are empty of moisture, are their minds full of wisdom.</Source>
      <Dest>像波塞拉那样的老人已然经历了悲喜交杂的一声。如今，她们干枯的身躯中已只余无穷的智慧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is no surprise the Forsworn rely on Boethiah.  When strength fails, subterfuge is a tool that allows the oppressed to achieve a balance.</Source>
      <Dest>弃誓者依赖波耶西亚毫不奇怪。当力量不足时，阴谋诡计则成为受压迫者反抗的工具。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Even a destructive force such as Mehrunes Dagon has a purpose.  These pieces of the Mythic Dawn show us how tenuous our lives are.</Source>
      <Dest>即使是如梅鲁涅斯．大衮一般的毁灭性的力量也是有意义的。这些神话黎明让我们明白了我们的生命有多么脆弱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These miners often complain about hard work.  But then how will they face life's challenges, when nothing of value comes easy?</Source>
      <Dest>这些矿工们总是抱怨干活太累。但像他们这样该怎么面对人生中的挑战呢？天下没有免费的午餐啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Many of the locals here ask me how best to pass the time. I tell them to treasure every moment, for each second is the first and last of its kind.</Source>
      <Dest>很多当地人问我怎么才能最好的打发时间。我告诉他们珍惜每一个瞬间，因为每秒钟的经历都是这辈子第一也是最后一次。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This shrine is a reminder.  Just as bandits can pray to the Aedra, so too can good mortals pray to the Daedra.</Source>
      <Dest>这座祭坛提醒了我。正如强盗也可以向神族祈祷的那样，当然也可以有好人向魔族祈祷啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, the Hunter's Rest.  A home for those who have none.  A mead hall where the roof is the roof of the world.</Source>
      <Dest>啊,猎人休息处。无家可归之人的家。A mead hall where the roof is the roof of the world.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you have joined this Temple of Valor, this Hall of Companions. The word companion is apt, for shield-brother and shield-sister fight as family.</Source>
      <Dest>你已经成为这座战友团勇气大厅的一员了。战友这个词如此平易，因为盾牌兄弟和盾牌姐妹们如一家人一般并肩作战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Moons protect us!  The tower...it's been completely obliterated!</Source>
      <Dest>月亮庇佑我们！那座塔...已经被完全摧毁了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whiterun is the very fulcrum of Skyrim.  If a dragon attacks here, all will know.  There will be no denying they have returned.</Source>
      <Dest>雪漫城是天际省的轴心。如果有龙袭击了这里，所有人都会知道的。龙的回归将无可否认。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, so now the other piece falls into place.  On one side, the return of the dragons.  And to balance it, the rise of the dragonborn.</Source>
      <Dest>所有事情都是相生相克，遵循着矛盾的逻辑。一方面是龙族以不可阻挡之势回归，同时冥冥之中也早已注定龙裔的崛起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have slain a dragon, become Thane of Whiterun, and now the Greybeards have called you.  Truly, the winds of fate swirl around you.</Source>
      <Dest>你已经杀了一条龙，成为了雪漫城的男爵。而现在，灰胡子在呼唤于你。的确，命运之风在索绕着你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have heard the Greybeards do not like to alter the course of history.  But to do nothing is an act that has just as many consequences.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说灰胡子不喜欢干涉历史的发展进程。但毫无作为同样也是一种影响结果的方式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Companions grieve, and they weep.  Because death is always unexpected, even when it is the one thing we can all expect.</Source>
      <Dest>战友团的人悲痛着，哭泣着。因为死亡总是突如其来的。即使那也是我们所期待的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Riften is renowned for its fishery. I would very much like to taste the salmon steak, or perhaps, chef willing, a flounder marinated in tomato sauce.</Source>
      <Dest>裂谷城因其丰富的渔产而闻名。我很想尝尝鲑鱼排，或者，如果厨师愿意做的话，更想尝尝比目鱼番茄酱汤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if stores like this are having their prices undercut by the Khajiit caravans, and whether they will brook such behavior as profits dwindle.</Source>
      <Dest>我怀疑像这样的商店会不会像虎人商店那样削价, 并接受由此带来的收益下降.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A fellow monk once asked me how I can endure such lengthy travel. "You carry many burdens," I told him, "but the foremost rest in your mind."</Source>
      <Dest>有一次修道士随从问我是怎样才忍受如此漫长的旅途。“尽管你带了很多行李，”我对他说道，“但最重要的休息在你脑海里。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The stores in Skyrim are well and good, but I wonder if one pays for the atmosphere.</Source>
      <Dest>天际省的商店令人满意, 但我不知是否有人为大气埋单.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Giants are the living embodiment of the delicate balance between cities and the wild. Their strength ensures the land will not be poisoned by order.</Source>
      <Dest>巨人就是让城市与野外达成微妙平衡的化身。它们的强大让自然不至于被人类所破坏殆尽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is fascinating to think entire civilizations begin in mines like this, where a single piece of ore is cut out from the crust of rock.</Source>
      <Dest>真是令人惊讶啊，想想整个一座城市的建立就是从这样的矿坑里的一片石头开凿出一片矿石开始的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The opinions of mortals are like the cups of an inn.  They overflow and must be emptied if they are to learn the way.</Source>
      <Dest>凡人的意见就如旅店里的杯子。已经溢出了，如果他们学会方法的话，那么该清空一下了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you give someone a gift, say thank you. For if you seek thanks and are not yourself thankful, then your aim is to be admired, not benevolent.</Source>
      <Dest>若你给某人一份礼物，那么说声谢谢。对于你只是想听别人感谢而不是自身真的想帮助人，那么你的目的令人敬佩，却不仁慈的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A wise monk once said a burden spoken is one relieved.</Source>
      <Dest>一位睿智的修道士曾说过：倾之以诉，如释重负；缄默不语，心中自痛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Both the Khajiit and Redguard are desert people, but Skyrim is not as harsh when your mind is clear and you carry your own coat.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然说虎人和红卫皆为荒漠之人，不过倘若他们动动脑子穿得暖和些，其实在天际也没那么难受。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, a cemetery.  From nothing they came, to nothing they return, and from nothing they will return again.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，墓地。 他们赤裸裸的生，赤裸裸的死，然后再次赤裸裸的回到这个世上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have visited many shrines dedicated to both the Aedra and Daedra, and yet all pale in comparison to Azura.</Source>
      <Dest>我见过各色各样的伊德拉和魔族圣殿。然而它们与阿祖拉的相比则显得如此苍白无力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were once many small towns like this that gave food and shelter to a monk in need.  Sadly, those days have long passed.</Source>
      <Dest>曾经有很多像这样的小镇，会在修道士危难之时提供给他们食物和住所。可悲的是，那些日子早已过去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Shrine of Azura.  What mortal can look upon such magnificence, and claim its builders were inspired by evil?</Source>
      <Dest>阿祖拉圣地。有谁会认为这座辉煌之物和它建造者的灵感都来自于邪恶？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh!  It is snowing!  I would like to make a snowcat.  We can use the flower stems as whiskers.</Source>
      <Dest>噢！下雪了！我要堆一只雪猫。咱们找点花茎杆来当胡须。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As students, we climbed steps like this every day, with buckets of water from the well below.  Perhaps not 7000 steps, but there were many.</Source>
      <Dest>如学生一般，我们每天都像这样拿着一桶从井里打来的水一步一个脚印地向上爬。也许不止7000步，反正很多就是了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is a tale of a clumsy monk who spilled water from his bucket whenever he climbed to the temple, and from it bloomed a garden.</Source>
      <Dest>据说是有一个笨笨的僧人，每次挑水上神殿去都会一路洒出很多水，就这样把这儿灌溉成了花园。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is a tension in the air here.  The balance is fragile.  We would do well not to mettle.</Source>
      <Dest>空气中透着些许紧张气氛。平衡很快就会被打破。我们会尽全力示弱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>State your beliefs, but think twice before speaking. Measure every word, but let your words be forceful. The Greybeards remind me of such teachings.</Source>
      <Dest>说出你的信念，但是在说之前要三思。斟酌你的用词，但要话语要有力。灰胡子给了我这样的教诲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say there are two prisons in Markarth, the mine and the warrens.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说马卡斯城有两所监狱，矿洞和贫民窟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dawnstar. Many believe this to be the end of the world.  The ocean is nothing more than an empty space on a page, the end of a chapter, not the book.</Source>
      <Dest>晨星城。很多人认为这里是世界尽头。大海仅只是世界长卷上的空白页，是章节而非全书的终点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think the tavern girl here likes me.  She was very complimentary of my coat.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得旅馆中的那女孩喜欢我，她每次都在赞美我的大衣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The road is long, and it is wise to rest on occasion.  There must also be time to meditate, as the two are not the same.</Source>
      <Dest>路途是漫长的,要聪明地利用时间休息。同样，还要留够时间来进行策划，因为两者是不同的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Talos.  His ascension proves we are all part of the heavens and the earth, and we all have a part in the harmony.</Source>
      <Dest>塔洛斯。他的成神证明了我们皆为天堂和地球的一部分，并且我们皆为协调的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can always tell whether I will like a city by their selection of fish.</Source>
      <Dest>我只看居民怎么挑选鱼货就能判断出我是否喜欢这座城市。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Windhelm.  This city has always made my whiskers tingle.</Source>
      <Dest>风盔城。这座城市总是让我连胡子都在哆嗦啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I once knew a Khajiit who said his ears would twitch whenever someone spoke of him.  I wonder if someone speaks of me now.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾听到过一个虎人说每当有人说起它时，它的耳朵都会抽搐。我很好奇现在是不是有人提及我？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bandits.  The fates are not kind to them.</Source>
      <Dest>强盗们。命运对他们不公平。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was once a village like this outside the temple where I trained.  They brought alms, and we offered wisdom in return.</Source>
      <Dest>在我受训的神庙外面也有这样一个小镇。他们捐助我们物品，我们回赠他们智慧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vampires.  Now would not be a good time to be one.</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼。现在可不是加入他们的好时机。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The days and seasons change, as do all things.  It is the blood of Padomay, the Daedra, who are the agents.</Source>
      <Dest>时移世易，所有事物都会变化。魔族，帕杜梅的血脉，同时也是其代理者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is very important that we refer to the Aedra as such, and not the Divines, less mortals raise their status beyond their counterparts.</Source>
      <Dest>我们指的是神族什么的，而不是圣灵，这点很重要。基本没几个凡人把神族的地位放在和他们地位相同的圣灵之上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Does this farm have leeks?  Qa'Dojo is fond of leeks.  They go quite well with steamed fish.</Source>
      <Dest>这个农场有韭菜？奎兜啾最喜欢韭菜，韭菜跟鱼一起蒸的味道，超赞！！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say there is a thin line between mages and warlocks.  Sometimes, perhaps.  Other times it is very thick.  Such is the trouble with labels.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说法师和术士之间没什么区别。也许有时是这样，但更多时候两者之间的差别很大。这就是被打上标签的麻烦之处啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is far more gray on my fur then I remember.  It comes so slowly, yet so suddenly.</Source>
      <Dest>我毛发上的银丝比我印象中多了很多。它们来的如此缓慢，却又如此突然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is wise for all returning travelers to pray at a shrine. When chaos rules our bodies, it may infect the next mortal, so we ask the Aedra for calm.</Source>
      <Dest>这是所有归来者在神庙里祈求的愿望. 当混沌占据我们的身体时, 它会感染周边的人, 所以我们向神族祈求平息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why do they call liquor "spirits?"  Although I have heard the spiced wine here is indeed heavenly.</Source>
      <Dest>他们为什么把兑水的酒精叫做“烈酒”呢？尽管我听说这里的加香葡萄酒宛如天物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While it is safer to use the main roads and thoroughfares, a brisk walk off the path may provide an opportunity to contemplate nature.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然在主要干道行走更为安全，不过在羊肠小道上蹦跶蹦跶或能让我们更亲近大自然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The forest is thinning here.  The trees are finding new life as catapults.</Source>
      <Dest>在这里，森林正在变小。树木正在离开这里谋求新生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Any coastal town ought to have good fishing.  But the people here seem only to fish for rocks.</Source>
      <Dest>一般港口小镇都该有像样的渔业。可这里的人好像捕捞的都是石头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder where machines fall in the balance of all things.  Surely they have a place.</Source>
      <Dest>我想知道机器处于所有事物平衡中的哪里。他们肯定有一份位置的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Could it not be said that we are all machines in some respects?  Our bones are metal, blood is oil, and our tails, well, it's not a perfect analogy.</Source>
      <Dest>难道它没说在一些方面来上说我们都是机器?我们的骨头为金属，血液为油！还有我们的尾巴，嗯，这并非完美。诸如此类。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The lake here looks like a good spot to fish, and an even better place to meditate.</Source>
      <Dest>这湖看起来是个捕鱼的好地方，更是冥想的好地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In Morthal, rumors float through the air like dandelion seeds.  Be careful not to let the weeds take root.</Source>
      <Dest>在墨索尔城,谣言像蒲公英种子漂浮在空中。小心不要节外生枝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This town looks cozy, and its people warm.</Source>
      <Dest>这个小镇看上去很安详，这的人们也挺热心的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is strange that the undead are mostly human.  It is possible the beast races are not easily bewitched by immortality's promise.</Source>
      <Dest>奇怪的是，亡灵大多数都是人类。也许是兽族不容易被永恒之诺施法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that all?</Source>
      <Dest>就这样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that all?</Source>
      <Dest>就这样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've suffered worse!</Source>
      <Dest>I've suffered worse!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your blows do not hurt me!</Source>
      <Dest>你的攻击伤不了我！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hrrragh!</Source>
      <Dest>喝啊啊啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hyargh!</Source>
      <Dest>嘿呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eyargh!</Source>
      <Dest>咿呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Arrrgh!</Source>
      <Dest>啊啊啊呀!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The day is yours!  I yield!</Source>
      <Dest>你赢了，我投降！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You are wounded!</Source>
      <Dest>你受伤了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Growing weary?</Source>
      <Dest>厌烦了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will vanquish you, dragon!</Source>
      <Dest>我会战胜你的，龙！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You cannot win!</Source>
      <Dest>你赢不了的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is over, before it begins!</Source>
      <Dest>还没开始就结束了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will send you into the light!</Source>
      <Dest>我要把你净化掉！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will vanquish you, dragon!</Source>
      <Dest>我会战胜你的，龙！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You cannot win!</Source>
      <Dest>你赢不了的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will send you into the light!</Source>
      <Dest>我要把你净化掉！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, Peryite. One should not cast aspersions on the power of disease. For sometimes it is the infection that provides the cure.</Source>
      <Dest>哎！魄伊特。无人该质疑瘟疾之力。因为瘟疾之力时无解药。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I would like to investigate this Wolfskull cave. When this farmer speaks of the unnatural, he could very well be speaking of the exotic.</Source>
      <Dest>我想调查这个狼骨洞穴。而这个农民说话的时候不怎么自然，我想他可能带着很重的外乡口音。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like the salmon they fish, the bandits of Orphan's Tear head straight toward their death, simply out of instinct.</Source>
      <Dest>孤儿之泪上的强盗们本能地冲向了死亡，就像他们捕捞的鲑鱼一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These necromancers were blinded by power. Potema cannot be controlled, as her mind is chaos, and chaos is a wildfire that burns without direction.</Source>
      <Dest>那些亡灵巫师被力量蒙蔽了。波特玛是不会被控制的，她的思想混沌，混沌如同野火般燃烧而没有方向。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems Meridia has chosen a worthy champion for her blade. Use it well, and use it wisely.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来美瑞蒂亚为自己的剑选择了一个优秀的守护者。好好使用，还有明智的使用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Rueful Axe. Most fathers would be insulted with such a gift. Did the wizard keep it out of fear, greed, or for its intended purpose?</Source>
      <Dest>悔恨之斧。多数父辈都会以带着这东西为辱。这个巫师是出自恐惧，贪婪，还是为了自己的目的而留着这东西？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Meridia's light is dim without the beacon. We must restore it, so that all will know there are Daedra who espouse the pure.</Source>
      <Dest>美瑞蒂亚之光没了灯塔，暗淡无比。我们必须恢复它，这样所以人都会知道，魔族还有着纯粹的拥护者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When a pack outgrows its food source, the cubs will starve, and the pack will die. Peryite blesses them with disease to balance their numbers.</Source>
      <Dest>当一个族群繁殖的量超过了它的食物来源，幼仔就会饿死，族群就会消灭。魄伊特用瘟疫赐予它们数量均衡的祝福</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It would seem that Barbas is Vile's better half, but one can never be certain with Daedra. Chaos by nature means there is no clear choice.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来巴巴斯是邪恶的另一半儿，但没人能肯定它跟魔族有关。混沌本身就意味着没有明确的选择。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps the Wood Elf here assumed he could tame these wild beasts and make them the guardians of his treasure. But even with magic, wild is wild.</Source>
      <Dest>大概这儿的木精灵假定他能驯服这些野兽作为他财富的守卫。但即使是用魔法，野生的就是野生的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An Elder Scroll! Incredible! The very nature of duality flows through it, and it will balance our strength against Alduin's.</Source>
      <Dest>上古卷轴！难以置信啊！那里面流淌着二元真理之源，可以使我们的力量与奥杜因平衡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The music of the Crimson Nirnroot that grows here is both haunting and soothing. It mirrors the very ambiance of this cavern.</Source>
      <Dest>生长在这红色奈恩根的音乐如此地舒缓又如此地让人难以忘怀，它完全反映出了这个洞穴里的气氛。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, so you have spoken to Clavicus Vile. His wishes are said to be cursed, yet perhaps it is the wisher who knows not what he desires.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说你和克拉维斯麦尔交谈过了。据说他的希望是被诅咒的，或许不去弄清他的欲望的人才是更机智的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These people serve the Falmer. Like their masters before them, they have thrown away their rights as mortals.</Source>
      <Dest>这些人为雪精灵服务。如同他们的主人以前的所作所为一样，他们也舍弃了自己作为凡人的权利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alchemy and enchanting tables, fireplaces and dining chairs, and they all face away from the door. Your back is turned from danger, as is your mind.</Source>
      <Dest>炼金室和附魔台，火炉和就餐椅，所有这些都背对着门。你的后背毫无防备，如同的你的心一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There are times when wisdom and madness are two sides of the same coin. If this man were a coin, it would have two tails.</Source>
      <Dest>俗话说天才与疯子就像硬币的正反面。如果这个人是枚硬币的话，那他应该有两个反面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>An ancient ruin frozen solid. Thus this once great temple is preserved, even as it is destroyed.</Source>
      <Dest>一名祖先毁掉了冰冻立方体。因此即使是被毁掉了，但这一伟大的寺庙依然保存了下来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The problem with the Greybeards and the Blades is their adherence to absolutes. It makes things difficult when they need each other's counsel.</Source>
      <Dest>灰胡子和刀锋会之间的问题是他们各自秉持自己的思想。于是在他们需要彼此的建议时，这让一切变得阻难重重。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And so we ascend the mountain once more, for the world demands a savior, just as it demands to be consumed.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我们再次登上了那座山。因为世界需要一个救世主，正如世界需要被毁灭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Gildergreen.  It is the very symbol of Whiterun.  It reminds me of a parable, if you wish to hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>翠苒树。这是雪漫城的象征。这让我想起了一则寓言故事，你想听吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While the level of education is different, all schools follow the same formula of training.  I am recalling a story.  Would you like to hear it?</Source>
      <Dest>虽然教育等级不同，但所有的学校都遵循一个训练公式。我正在回述一个故事。你要来听听么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Vigilants do not know that their enthusiasm will only result in their ruin.  It reminds me of a parable.  Would you like to hear it?</Source>
      <Dest>警戒者不知道他们的热忱只会导致灭亡。这让我想起一个比喻。你想听吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We must be careful when entering an old ruin. Time changes owners, and this Akaviri Temple may be Haven to something far more sinister than the sky.</Source>
      <Dest>进入古代废墟的时候我们一定要小心。时间会改变所有权，这虽然是阿卡维尔的神殿可也会被某种比天神更危险的东西占据的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In a time like this, one must take only what is needed.  One must not let temptation distort this fact.</Source>
      <Dest>在这样的时代，一个人必须要做必要的事儿。而且还不能让诱惑歪曲了事实。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Brilliance and insanity are partners in the same dance.  When speaking with Esbern, we can only wonder which of the two will lead.</Source>
      <Dest>才华和疯狂是同一支舞里的合作伙伴.当我与伊思本说话的时候，我们只是想知道它们两个哪个在领舞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While ostensibly you work alone, there will be many guests at the Embassy from all parts of Skyrim. Perhaps you will find another ally among them.</Source>
      <Dest>你在大使馆里独自行动的时候，大使馆里会有来自天际省各处的人。或许你能在他们中间找到盟友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You escaped the Embassy...walked right into the belly of the whale, and came out clean on the other side. Hmm...perhaps that is not the best analogy.</Source>
      <Dest>你逃离了大使馆...就像钻进一头鲸鱼的肚子却毫发无伤地从另一端钻了出来似的。嗯...这个比喻可能并不贴切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Horn is in Riverwood then.  Despite all the trials that required the Whirlwind Sprint, it seems we are still one step behind.  </Source>
      <Dest>号角在河木镇。尽管所有的测试都需要旋风冲刺，但看样子我们还是落后一步</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It appears the dragons are multiplying, but so are those who seek to vanquish them.  Now with Delphine, you have another ally.</Source>
      <Dest>看来龙的数量一直在增加，但仍有些人试图要打败它们。现在再加上戴尔菲娜，你有另一个盟友了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dried fish, salted meats...Klimmek's food reminds me of my days as a monk.</Source>
      <Dest>鱼干，腌肉……科林麦的食物让我想起自己当修士的日子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As the conjurers and the Draugr fight each other, it seems our path is made easier, but the survivor of this arena will be a formidable foe.</Source>
      <Dest>尸鬼和法师在对着干呢，这样看来我们可以坐收渔翁之利了，不过在这个竞技场中获胜的人将会成为我们可怕的对手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ivarstead.  To reach the Greybeards, we must climb the 7,000 steps.  An overwhelming number to be sure, but all journeys begin and end with one.</Source>
      <Dest>在紫杉镇，为了到达灰胡子那里,我们必须得爬7000级台阶。台阶的数量当然很多。但所有旅途的开始和结束都和这7000级台阶息息相关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is odd that Greybeards are in favor of letting you skip the mental training.  For that is what gives you the discipline to control your power.</Source>
      <Dest>灰胡子居然赞同让你跳过精神训练，很奇怪。精神训练毕竟能让你获得控制自己力量的能力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One wonders just how far the Thieves Guild has fallen, if two vagrants were planning to undermine it.</Source>
      <Dest>如果这两个流浪者计划去暗中破坏的话，盗贼工会的一个奇迹会掉多远呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The first test for any new member is more than a test of aptitude.  These thieves wish to test your ability to do the unsavory.  To face your victim.</Source>
      <Dest>第一个测试对任何新成员而言，不仅仅是对能力的考验。这些小偷想测试你在面对你的受害者时，做坏事的能力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is natural for the owner of Goldenglow Estate to rebel, given Maven's actions and how weak the Guild is.  He could not have foreseen your arrival.</Source>
      <Dest>对金辉庄园的拥有者来说，产生反抗的念头是很自然的。鉴于玛雯的行动和公会是多么脆弱。他只是没有预见你的到来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The balance of any potion, whether it is mead or medicine, is very delicate. The  poison will alter the composition just enough to avoid suspicion.</Source>
      <Dest>不管是蜜酒还是药物，饮料的配制都是非常细致的。药剂会一直调配直到无可挑剔为止。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mercer insists this mystery backer slipped up, but looking at the bill of sale, there was no need to mention the agent by name, even by an alias.</Source>
      <Dest>墨瑟强调神秘赞助者遛了，但看这销售的账单，根本没必要提到代理的名字或别名。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mercer insists this mystery backer slipped up, but looking at the bill of sale, there was no need to mention the agent by name, even by an alias.</Source>
      <Dest>墨瑟强调神秘赞助者遛了，但看这销售的账单，根本没必要提到代理的名字或别名。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say that the world of business is very cutthroat.  One wonders if Maven Black-Briar takes this term literally.</Source>
      <Dest>他们都说商场如战场，感觉这已经被玛雯·黑荆棘奉为准则。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every action has a consequence.  When the Arch-Mage casts a madman out, he may quarantine his school, but he poisons the world.</Source>
      <Dest>凡事有因必有果。当一个首席法师把一个疯子释放出来，他也许把他的学院隔离开了，但还是对这个世界产生了些不好的影响。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At last, our broker has a name.  Karliah.  Perhaps Mercer will be able to fill in the rest.</Source>
      <Dest>最后，我们的经纪人有一个名字。卡莱雅。也许墨瑟会填补剩下的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It appears your fate is now tied to Karliah's.  To prove her innocence is to prove your own.</Source>
      <Dest>这表明你的命运已经和卡莱雅连在了一起. 证明她的清白便是证明了你的清白.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How does one pick an unbreakable lock?  To know the solution, one simply must ask, how does any miracle happen?  The answer is quite clear.</Source>
      <Dest>如何选择一个牢不可破的锁？这个答案等同于，如何才能使奇迹发生呢？答案是十分明确的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems Mercer has been plotting for some time, but Karliah's presence has hastened his plans.  Let us hope his haste causes him to falter.</Source>
      <Dest>看情况墨瑟那家伙密谋很久了。但卡莉亚的出现让他不得不把计划提前。让我们祈祷他因为仓促行动而导致计划失败吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mercer has quite the audacity if he defiles Nocturnal's temple.  A mortal with a God complex is his own worst enemy.</Source>
      <Dest>如果墨瑟亵渎了诺克图娜尔的神庙，那这家伙就太放肆了。一个把自己当做神的凡人是他自己最可怕的敌人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, the three of you are safe.  The cave collapsed, and I feared it did not bode well for your escape.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你们仨都安全了。看见那洞塌了，我还担心恐怕你们出不来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In a short time, the callow thief has become the guildmaster. Yet if one only looks only at the calendar, he ignores the depth of experiences within.</Source>
      <Dest>在短短的时间里,那年轻的盗贼已经成为了会长。但如果一个人仅从日历的数字来看的话，那么这人会忽略掉期间所经历过的事物的深度。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have 3 choices regarding the skeleton key. You can return it, keep it, or wait until it has exhausted its use.  Nocturnal awaits your decision.</Source>
      <Dest>关于骷髅钥匙，你有三个选择。你可以归还它，继续保留它，或是等待到它再也不能用。诺克图娜尔等待你的决定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you aim to join the Thieves Guild.  Many are quick to disparage the role of the thief, but do not include the locksmith or the guard among them.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你的目标是加入盗贼工会。大多数人都草率的贬低着盗贼的作用，除了锁匠和警卫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You are now the Harbinger.  You are the leader, and yet no Companion answers to anyone.  It is a system that mimics the very world we live in.</Source>
      <Dest>你现在是先驱了。你是领头人，但没有一个战友把这件事告诉任何人。这套体系正是效仿了我们所生活的世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Kodlak has made many choices, but his fate will be decided by his choice of Companions.  Let us see where they stack up against the original ones.</Source>
      <Dest>克拉科做过许多选择，但他的命运在他决定加入战友团的那一刻就确定了。让我们看看这一次次积累起来的选择会如何挑战传统。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The timing of Kodlak's death is tragic, and curious.  One wonders if Hircine set the Silver Hand in motion, so that he could claim his vassal.</Source>
      <Dest>克拉科死亡的时机悲惨且稀奇.有人好奇海尔辛是否会兴奋地设置银手，这样他就能索取他的奴仆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This rogue mage Stalleo speaks of is nowhere to be found, but the evidence is overwhelming.  Whoever lived here was no ordinary enchanter.</Source>
      <Dest>这个流氓魔法师斯塔莱奥而且他一事无成，但是证据是压倒性的。在这住着的人没有一般的巫师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Kodlak insists his predecessor was tricked, but I am not sure.  One does not make a contract with witches that is so one-sided.</Source>
      <Dest>克拉科坚持认为他的祖先被骗了，但我不敢苟同。那个人也没跟女巫们签个合同，这太片面了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The man has reclaimed his castle, yet his life is in shambles.  The rogue mage has won, even when he has lost.</Source>
      <Dest>男人夺回了他的城堡，而他的生命摇摇欲坠。那流氓的法师成功了，即使他刚刚被击败。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me. I need your help.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着我。我需要你的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then let us wander these white sands, and find our destination.</Source>
      <Dest>然后让我们漫步于这白色的沙滩，并找到我们的目的地吧。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May your road lead you to warm sands.</Source>
      <Dest>愿你的前路是温暖的沙地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Moons guide us.</Source>
      <Dest>月亮引领着我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A long conversation is a feast of wisdom.  Remember to savor every bite.</Source>
      <Dest>一次深长的谈话时一场智慧盛宴。要记得细细品味。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The timing of Kodlak's death is tragic, and curious.  One wonders if Hircine set the Silver Hand in motion, so that he could claim his vassal.</Source>
      <Dest>克拉科死亡的时机悲惨且稀奇.有人好奇海尔辛是否会兴奋地设置银手，这样他就能索取他的奴仆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How about a drink?  The night is still young, and even a monk desires a spirit every now and then.</Source>
      <Dest>来几杯如何？夜还未深，就连修士时不时都会想喝点酒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One should never speed up to catch up with life.  One should slow life down to walk at your pace.</Source>
      <Dest>人们绝不应该加快脚步急急度过人生。人们应该放慢人生追随在您的脚步之下</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, we have stopped.  I patiently await your counsel.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，我们停下了。我会耐心等待你的计划的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, you return.</Source>
      <Dest>啊,你回来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, traveler.</Source>
      <Dest>你好，旅行者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May our steps move in harmony.</Source>
      <Dest>愿我们的步伐处于平衡之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Be careful!</Source>
      <Dest>小心！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am on your side!</Source>
      <Dest>我就在你身边！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stop that!</Source>
      <Dest>停下来！</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
