<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They have, but a Dragonborn has come to vanquish them.</Source>
      <Dest>他们那么做了，但是现在一个龙裔前来降服他们了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So the legends are true then. But even a Dragonborn could use a little help. If it were me, I would wear a necklace of chicken beaks at all times.</Source>
      <Dest>看来风评所传不虚. 不过就算是伟大的龙裔怕是也需要帮助的不是么。以我之见，我倒宁愿用鸡喙穿成项链戴它一辈子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They have, but a Dragonborn has come to vanquish them.</Source>
      <Dest>他们那么做了，但是现在一个龙裔前来降服他们了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Those are always good for curing your voice when you're hoarse. I imagine all the shouting means you have to keep it sharper than any blade.</Source>
      <Dest>这些对治疗声音嘶哑的很有帮助的。我认为所有的吼声都是为了达到超越刀剑的境界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You might not believe this, but I was there when Helgen was attacked.</Source>
      <Dest>说出来怕你不信，当时海尔根出事的时候我就在现场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ysmir's beard, and you survived? You must have had an eagle claw in your pocket, or a pig snout at the very least.</Source>
      <Dest>伊斯谟的胡须在上，你居然活了下来？你口袋里要么是有鹰爪，要么就是有猪鼻子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You might not believe this, but I was there when Helgen was attacked.</Source>
      <Dest>说出来怕你不信，当时海尔根出事的时候我就在现场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You always need a little luck in times like these, which is why I keep both.</Source>
      <Dest>在这样的时候，你总是缺乏点儿运气，这就是我把那俩东西一直揣在身上的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's all a hoax. There are no dragons. Just pigs with wings.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一场骗局。根本没有什么巨龙，那些不过是长翅膀的猪猡罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Frodnar will be pleased to hear that. He would love having a nice, juicy pig roast for dinner. He doesn't realize I'm the one who has to cook it.</Source>
      <Dest>Frodnar will be pleased to hear that. He would love having a nice, juicy pig roast for dinner. He doesn't realize I'm the one who has to cook it.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's all a hoax. There are no dragons. Just pigs with wings.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一场骗局。根本没有什么巨龙，那些不过是长翅膀的猪猡罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But there won't be any flying creatures coming this way. We keep a dead bird by the mantle every season to ward them off.</Source>
      <Dest>但是所有能飞的生物估计都没办法从这条路进来。我们每个季节都会在墙上挂只死鸟来吓走它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's all a hoax. There are no dragons. Just pigs with wings.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一场骗局。根本没有什么巨龙，那些不过是长翅膀的猪猡罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although right now it's just the feathers.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然现在只有一堆羽毛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They have. Helgen was destroyed.</Source>
      <Dest>他们已经那样了，海尔根被毁了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such a shame. But this is what happens when people forget the old ways.</Source>
      <Dest>真丢人。但人们确实是会忘本的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They have. Helgen was destroyed.</Source>
      <Dest>他们已经那样了，海尔根被毁了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every home should keep a dead bird over the mantle to ward off flying creatures. It's not just for crows. Even feathers will do.</Source>
      <Dest>每户人家都应该在外墙上挂上一只死鸟来吓跑那些飞鸟。不光是乌鸦。就算弄点羽毛也有效。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think I've lost my appetite.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有食慾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Never seen a skull before? You must be from the city. Here, family stays with family, even after death.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑声）以前从没有见过人头骨？你肯定是从城里来的。在我们这里，一家人总是呆在一起，死后亦是如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why not bury the boy?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么不抛弃那个男孩？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And leave him to the worms? No, that wouldn't be right. He belongs with his family.</Source>
      <Dest>把他丢进虫堆吗？不，那不对。他属于他的家族。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did your boy die?</Source>
      <Dest>你的男孩怎么去世的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's simple. The poor boy didn't listen to his mother.</Source>
      <Dest>这很简单，那个男孩没有听他母亲的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did your boy die?</Source>
      <Dest>你的男孩怎么去世的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't tell you how many times he'd stay out past curfew, or forgot to leave the rabbits' feet hanging by the railing.</Source>
      <Dest>我都数不清他有多少次在宵禁的时候还在外边转悠，或是忘了把兔腿挂在栏杆上了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did your boy die?</Source>
      <Dest>你的男孩怎么去世的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So one day, he came home too late, and it was his body hanging out by the railing instead.</Source>
      <Dest>因此有一天，他回家太晚了，结果他的尸体取而代之挂在了外面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did your boy die?</Source>
      <Dest>你的男孩怎么去世的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't mean to be callous, but it's the truth.</Source>
      <Dest>不是我冷酷无情，但是事实确是如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a bit strange, keeping your son's skull.</Source>
      <Dest>保存着你儿子的骷髅，感觉怪怪的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must not be from around these parts. You go into any Nord home and you're likely to find somebody's skull lying about.</Source>
      <Dest>你肯定不是这一带的人。随便进到一个诺德人的家里，你都很有可能会发现不知是谁的头骨就那么随便放着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Children are disgusting little creatures. No offense to yours.</Source>
      <Dest>孩子们讨厌小动物。没有冒犯你的意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You only say that because you've never sired one. When you hold your own flesh and blood in your arms, it's a feeling like no other.</Source>
      <Dest>你只说是因为你没生育过。如果你怀抱你自己的亲生骨肉，你会知道那种感觉无可替代。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Children are disgusting little creatures. No offense to yours.</Source>
      <Dest>孩子们讨厌小动物。没有冒犯你的意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, there's some out there who will try and raise other people's children. I've heard they even sell them at some place called an orphanage.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，外面是有些人会想办法养大别人的孩子。听说他们还会把他们卖到一个叫孤儿院的地方去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Children are disgusting little creatures. No offense to yours.</Source>
      <Dest>孩子们讨厌小动物。没有冒犯你的意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's a heathen practice, this thing called adoption, and I'm glad no one at this table will stand for it.</Source>
      <Dest>这是野蛮人的行径，这类事被叫做领养，我很高兴在这张桌子上没人能忍受它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't have any children at the moment.</Source>
      <Dest>我那时没有任何的孩子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, you're still young, you have time yet. Some people are in such a rush though, they try raising children that aren't their own.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，你还年轻，你还有的是时间。有些人却过得匆匆忙忙，他们想去抚养一个不是亲生的孩子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't have any children at the moment.</Source>
      <Dest>我那时没有任何的孩子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A disgusting practice, this whole notion of adoption.</Source>
      <Dest>这种收养的做法真是恶心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've had a children. Raising them is another matter entirely.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经有孩子了。把他们养大可是完全不同的问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I suppose it can't be helped. You can't feed them all, and sometimes the weak ones must be sacrificed for the good of the family.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我想这大概也没什么用处。你不可能喂饱所有的孩子，某些时候，为了整个家庭，得牺牲掉最弱小的那些（孩子）。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've had a children. Raising them is another matter entirely.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经有孩子了。把他们养大可是完全不同的问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's the natural order of the world, and to upset it is nothing short of blasphemy.</Source>
      <Dest>这是世界的自然秩序，而打破它则是不折不扣的亵渎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've adopted a child.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经领养了一个小孩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Surely you jest! What sort of sick deviant would raise a child that was not his own flesh and blood!</Source>
      <Dest>Surely you jest! What sort of sick deviant would raise a child that was not his own flesh and blood!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I understand we're having chaurus stew. How did you obtain such a rare meat?</Source>
      <Dest>咱今天要喝的是查鲁斯肉汤！你们哪儿弄的这稀罕玩意？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My husband does like to exaggerate. Most adventurers can't tell the difference between chaurus and chickens.</Source>
      <Dest>我丈夫确实喜欢夸大事实。大部分冒险家分不清查鲁斯和小鸡的区别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I understand we're having chaurus stew. How did you obtain such a rare meat?</Source>
      <Dest>咱今天要喝的是查鲁斯肉汤！你们哪儿弄的这稀罕玩意？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Last time it was dolphin pie. But if you look close, you'll see the flint of silver he keeps under his tongue.</Source>
      <Dest>上次是海豚饼。如果你仔细观察，你会看到他藏在舌头下的发财秘密（详情见故事the flint）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I understand we're having chaurus stew. How did you obtain such a rare meat?</Source>
      <Dest>咱今天要喝的是查鲁斯肉汤！你们哪儿弄的这稀罕玩意？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But for being a good sport, why don't you have a quick taste. Chickens or chaurus, I'm sure you'll like it.</Source>
      <Dest>But for being a good sport, why don't you have a quick taste. Chickens or chaurus, I'm sure you'll like it.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you need any help with the cooking?</Source>
      <Dest>你需要烹饪方面的帮助吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you dearie, but I would be a terrible host if I let you anywhere near the pot.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的，谢谢了。但是我想如果留下你在厨房帮忙的话，我可能就会变成最不称职的东道主了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you need any help with the cooking?</Source>
      <Dest>你需要烹饪方面的帮助吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But maybe you knew that already. You're a clever little bee, aren't you. Always outsmarting the busy ones.</Source>
      <Dest>也许你已经知道了。你是一只聪明的小蜜蜂，对不对。聪明人总是忙碌的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you need any help with the cooking?</Source>
      <Dest>你需要烹饪方面的帮助吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I tell you what, you can have a taste if you like, but make it quick.</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉你，如果你喜欢你可以尝一尝，但动作要快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I came to warn you about a witch.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上我来警告你小心那个巫婆。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You wouldn't be the first. Adventurers are always coming to us with stories about witches and Falmer and bandits, but we never see any of them.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该不是第一个。冒险者们经常跟我们讲什么女巫啊血精灵还有强盗什么的故事，可我们从没亲眼见过任何一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I came to warn you about a witch.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上我来警告你小心那个巫婆。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's probably because we keep snowberries by the door and acorns in our dressers, to ward off the bad folks.</Source>
      <Dest>这也许是因为我们一直把雪浆果放在门口，把橡子放到梳妆台里，用以避开坏人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I came to warn you about a witch.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上我来警告你小心那个巫婆。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, our family's also been blessed with long earlobes. Where I come from, that's good luck. Say, you've got a nice pair yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>当然我们的家人都有饱满的耳垂，在我的家乡，那是好运的象征。你看，你也有一对饱满的耳垂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure, but I can't stay long.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，但我不能呆太久。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that's too bad, but we're just thankful to have the company. It's been about a month since the last adventurer came by.</Source>
      <Dest>Well, that's too bad, but we're just thankful to have the company. It's been about a month since the last adventurer came by.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure, but I can't stay long.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，但我不能呆太久。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My little one's been rubbing her earlobes for good luck. I have to remind her that only works when you wash them first.</Source>
      <Dest>我的小家伙们摩擦她的耳垂来祝她好运。我只是想提醒她这招只在她洗过耳垂后才管用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure, but I can't stay long.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，但我不能呆太久。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Say, you've got a nice pair yourself. Maybe if you spend the night, some of that luck will rub off on us.</Source>
      <Dest>你看，你自己已经得到了一位美好的另一半。也许你今晚在这过夜的话，我们没准能沾沾你的运气的光呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My feet are never weary. Look at me. I'm a specimen.</Source>
      <Dest>我从不停止脚步。看看我，我就是一个榜样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That you are, my friend. You've got a good shape about you, and a good tan. I doubt you spend your days riding in gilded chariots.</Source>
      <Dest>那是你，朋友。你的身材不错，皮肤也是健康的小麦色。我怀疑你把你的时间都花在了驾驶镀金的战车上面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My feet are never weary. Look at me. I'm a specimen.</Source>
      <Dest>我从不停止脚步。看看我，我就是一个榜样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And best of all, you've got a healthy set of earlobes.  Nice and thick. Where I come from, that's good luck.</Source>
      <Dest>最棒的是，你有一对儿健康的耳垂。又好又厚。在我们那里，这是好运的象征。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thank you sir, I am tired and in need of a rest.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你，先生。我十分疲惫并且需要休息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, no, don't thank me. My wife and I enjoy the company. My little one even more so.</Source>
      <Dest>No, no, don't thank me. My wife and I enjoy the company. My little one even more so.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thank you sir, I am tired and in need of a rest.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你，先生。我十分疲惫并且需要休息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Say, you've got a nice set of earlobes on you. Where I come from, those are good luck. And good luck is contagious. You must stay the night.</Source>
      <Dest>我得说，你有一双漂亮的耳垂。在我的故乡，这是好运的象征。让我们沾沾光。你就留下来过夜吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Welcome, traveler! It's been a long time since we've had an adventurer come through these parts!</Source>
      <Dest>欢迎欢迎，旅行者！我们这儿好久没有冒险者造访了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Surely you'll want to come in and rest your weary feet!</Source>
      <Dest>你肯定想进来歇歇脚！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What would I ever do without my Renni. Do you have any children, traveler?</Source>
      <Dest>没了我的伦妮我该怎么活。你有过孩子吗，旅行者？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, we have the jaw in a drawer for safekeeping.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样，我们把那块儿颚骨放在抽屉里保管。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you must be the visitor Renni told me about! Let me get a good look at you.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你一定是伦妮提到那个的客人！让我好好看看你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I like the shape of your nose. I had a dream about a Falmer once, and he had the exact same one.</Source>
      <Dest>噢, 我喜欢你鼻子的样子. 有次我梦见一个雪精灵, 他有一个一模一样的鼻子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That Falmer in my dream was very old, but had good skin. Which means you'll age just as well.</Source>
      <Dest>我梦里的那只雪精灵非常老，但皮肤很好。这意味着你的年龄其实不打紧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But excuse my manners. My name's Bette, the little one's Renni, and you've met my husband Frodmar.</Source>
      <Dest>请原谅我的态度。我叫蓓特，这个小个子的是伦妮，当然你已经见过我的丈夫福德马了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So is it true what they say? Have the dragons returned?</Source>
      <Dest>所以他们说的是真的吗？龙回归了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not anymore papa. Not after you took away his teeth.</Source>
      <Dest>我再也不会了爸爸。只要你把他的牙弄走我就不会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, the last one didn't stay for very long. I warned you about her. She had a mole on her left cheek that was clearly a Daedric mark of some kind.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，最后一个人没有呆很长时间。我告诉过你该提防她。她的左脸有颗痣，那显然是恶魔做出的某种标记。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're right, love, this is a joyous occasion. Our first visitor in what is it, months?</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的，亲爱的。这是个让人高兴的时刻。我们的第一个客人多久没来了，几个月？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There you go again, husband, making things awkward for our guest. Can we just enjoy this nice meal I've cooked for all of you?</Source>
      <Dest>你又来了，老公，让我们的客人感觉不自在了。我们能好好的一起享受我为大家精心准备的饭菜吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, he was our boy, and hopefully the Gods won't mind us keeping his skull as a memento.</Source>
      <Dest>他仍然是我们的孩子。希望众神不要介意我们把他的头骨保存下来作为纪念的行为。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Aye, that would have been in poor taste.  You don't want to honor a child so foolhardy.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，这种滋味儿糟透了。你不会想尊重太过于淘气的孩子的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, Frodmar wanted to have Rengeir stuffed, but thankfully the wolves didn't leave much save the bones.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，福德马想要伦吉尓的头骨，但幸运的是狼群除了骨头还真没留下多少东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, let the girl have her fun. We can put the stew back in the pot for now and let it warm up some more.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，让那女孩自己玩吧。现在咱可以把汤倒回锅里再热热。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can I kill the chicken, papa?</Source>
      <Dest>爸爸，我能杀了那只鸡吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry friend, but we have to cut this meal short. The Gods wait for no one. Feel free to stay and finish your stew.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉朋友，我们必须先行离席了。神灵不等人。您请自便。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Honey, I thought you were taking care of it. Damn, we can't have another season like the last one.</Source>
      <Dest>实话说，我以为你打点好了。该死的，我们不能让上一季的情况重演。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Honey, I thought you were taking care of it. Damn! We can't...we can't...</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的，我还以为你在处理。该死的！我们不能…我们不能…</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, right. What about this season? Did you remember to leave the sacrifices by the altar?</Source>
      <Dest>Oh, right. What about this season? Did you remember to leave the sacrifices by the altar?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We killed the last sheep two seasons ago, as a sacrifice for the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>我们最后一次杀羊是在两个时令之前，那是作为众神的献祭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not that you could spot it, the way you've been lately. Have you been putting the sheep's blood in your eyes every morning like I told you?</Source>
      <Dest>并不是说你能发现这个，在这些日子里你就入门了。你有没有按我说的每天早晨用羊血滴眼睛？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, southerners with their troubles. Dragons shmagons. It's what they get for living in such hot weather! (Laughs)</Source>
      <Dest>啊，南方人也有他们自己的麻烦，比如龙啊那些。这就是他们选择在这样炎热的天候下生活的代价啊！（大笑）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh no you don't. The guest eats first. But not before we have a little conversation to whet our appetites.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，不，先别动嘴。让客人先吃。但不久前我们谈论的那个小话题确实勾起了我们的胃口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dear Gods, take this chicken as an offering, and bless us with good health this season.</Source>
      <Dest>敬爱的神明啊，我们将这只鸡作为贡品，希望在这一季节里您能保佑我们身体健康。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you're old enough, child. For now, just watch your father and learn from him.</Source>
      <Dest>等你够老了再说，孩子。现在，就看你的父亲，向他学习。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, that's right. Poor Renni was scared Rengeir's skull would eat her collection, so I had the lower jaw removed.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，没错。可怜的伦妮会害怕Rengeir的头骨可能吃掉她的收藏品。所以，我就把下颚骨切下来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Children have such wild imaginations.</Source>
      <Dest>孩子们有天马行空的想象力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your brother always did enjoy playing with bugs. Eating them too.</Source>
      <Dest>你的兄弟在玩弄那些虫子的时候总是很开心，在吃它们的时候也是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yay! It's really impressive! I keep it on that table over there next to Rengeir's skull. He keeps an eye on it for me.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊！这令人钦佩！我把它紧挨着放在Rengeir的头盖骨旁边了。他为我特别留意了这件事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>After you've finished your stew.</Source>
      <Dest>在你做完炖菜之后。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mama, can I show the nice man my bug collection?</Source>
      <Dest>妈妈，我能拿我的昆虫收藏给这个好人看吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mama, can I show the nice lady my bug collection?</Source>
      <Dest>妈妈，我能给这位可爱的女士展示我的虫子收藏吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're right. I apologize for making things so dour. My, that smells delicious!</Source>
      <Dest>你说的对。抱歉把事情弄得这么沉闷。哦，这闻起来真香！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh Frodmar, you're going to scare our guest.  He knows what is and isn't a sin.</Source>
      <Dest>哦福德马，你会吓到我们的客人的。他知道什么是罪过，什么不是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh Frodmar, you're going to scare our guest. She knows what is and isn't a sin.</Source>
      <Dest>噢福德马，你这样会吓到客人的。干什么事情犯不犯王法她还是知道的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you're done, go on and grab a seat at the head of the table. It's bad luck for the guest of honor to sit anywhere else.</Source>
      <Dest>等你完事后，到桌子的那一头找个座位坐下。一位荣耀的客人坐在其他任何地方都不合适。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When you're feeling blue, the color's true. When you're feeling high, use shades of night.</Source>
      <Dest>当你感觉那是蓝色时，那颜色是真的。当你感觉身在高处时，这却是因为夜晚的阴影而产生的错觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Silly me. How's that rhyme go again?</Source>
      <Dest>（笑）我真傻。怎么又没押上韵？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh love, purple? You didn't leave nightshade under the pot again, did you? I told you, it goes under your pillow.</Source>
      <Dest>哦亲爱的，紫色？你不会又把夜茄忘在锅底了吧，你不是吧？我告诉你，它毁了你的小枕头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've been doing that and chewing on them as well. Plus I put one of those purple flowers under the cooking pot and the bed.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经弄完了也正咀嚼着它们。加上我还在那些紫花中弄了一朵放在蒸煮罐和床下面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did you place the Elves Ear in your boot like I told you? It wards off the soreness.</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉过你要把精灵耳塞到鞋子里，你照做了吗？它能消除酸痛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is the meal ready yet, my love? The more I work, the hungrier I get, and it's been a long week.</Source>
      <Dest>饭做好了吗，亲爱的？干的活儿越多，我就越饿。这一周过得可真漫长啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, judging by the smell, it looks like we're having stew. I hope you like chaurus.</Source>
      <Dest>通常情况下，从我们闻到的味道来看，我们貌似要有炖肉吃了。我希望你喜欢查鲁斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And remind her to sprinkle the salt on the floorboards by the entrance. The home has to be purified before our guest steps inside.</Source>
      <Dest>还有记得提醒她在门口地板上多撒些盐。好让客人来之前打扫干净。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course my darling. Now go tell your mother we have a guest.</Source>
      <Dest>当然可以亲爱的. 去告诉你的母亲我们有客人来了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really? You mean it papa?</Source>
      <Dest>真的? 你是那个意思么，爸爸？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know child, we won't know until he takes off his shoes.</Source>
      <Dest>I don't know child, we won't know until he takes off his shoes.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But my money's on you, little Giant. You and your mother were blessed with very large feet. </Source>
      <Dest>但我看好你，小巨人。你和你的母亲都幸运地有着一双非常大的脚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But my money's on you, little Giant. You and your mother were blessed with very large feet. </Source>
      <Dest>但我是在你身上下的注，小巨人。大脚长在你和你的母亲的身上是一种幸运啊。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know child, we won't know until she takes off her shoes.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道，孩子。在她脱掉她的鞋之前我们都不知道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But my money's on you, little Giant. You and your mother were blessed with very large feet.</Source>
      <Dest>但我看好你，小巨人。你和你的母亲都幸运地有着一双非常大的脚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But my money's on you, little Giant. You and your mother were blessed with very large feet.</Source>
      <Dest>但我是在你身上下的注，小巨人。大脚长在你和你的母亲的身上是一种幸运啊。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really papa? What about his toes? Are they big too? You said toes bring the best luck.</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗老爸？那他的脚趾呢？是不是也很大？你说过脚趾是最能带来好运的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really papa? What about her toes? Are they big too? You said toes bring the best luck.</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗爸爸？那她的脚趾大吗？你说过脚趾会带来好运的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, you're still around. I hope you enjoyed the meal. Best get on your way. </Source>
      <Dest>Oh, you're still around. I hope you enjoyed the meal. Best get on your way. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Feel free to stop by anytime.</Source>
      <Dest>随时过来坐坐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My wife loves having you.</Source>
      <Dest>我妻子对你的到来非常高兴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come again.</Source>
      <Dest>记得再回来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come by for dinner any time.</Source>
      <Dest>随时欢迎你来蹭饭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mama? Papa? What happened to them?</Source>
      <Dest>妈妈？爸爸？他们怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Papa says mama died. At least Rengeir will have company.</Source>
      <Dest>爸爸说妈妈去世了。至少Rengeir路上有伴儿了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mama says papa died. At least Rengeir will have company.</Source>
      <Dest>妈妈说爸爸死了。至少伦吉尔路上有伴儿了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have nothing to say to you. Leave.</Source>
      <Dest>我没什么好跟你说的。滚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have nothing to say to you. Leave.</Source>
      <Dest>我没什么好跟你说的。滚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you again for the company.</Source>
      <Dest>再次感谢你的陪伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What can I do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么可以效劳的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What can I do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么可以效劳的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
