<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This view would be a lot more amazing if I wasn't terrified at the prospect of a bandit creeping up behind us.</Source>
      <Dest>要是我之前没有被身后埋伏的强盗吓着的话现在的场面应该更壮观。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A tunnel of blades and a room full of coffins.  So a vivisection followed by a burial!  Wonderful.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，一条充满刀片的隧道，一个都是棺材的房间！太好了，他们可以解剖了什么人以后立刻把它埋起来！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh look, a Dwarven ruin! And Falmer huts! Those are like the barnacles of the underground sea.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，看，一个矮人废墟！还有那些雪精灵小屋！这些小屋看起来就像是附着在海底的藤壶一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So did they just run out of bones when making those chimes? Because there seems to be a huge gap in the middle where we can walk right through.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说他们做那些编钟的时候把骨头都用完了吗？因为那边看起来中间有个畅通无阻的大缺口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whenever I come across one of these Dwarven ruins, I always pray I won't see an actual Dwarf.  That would mean I've disappeared too.</Source>
      <Dest>任何時候我來這些矮人遺跡時，我總是祈禱不要讓我遇上真正的矮人。　那意味著我將從去另外一个世界了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bandits ahead. Please resist the temptation to start mining the ore around us.</Source>
      <Dest>前方有贼。请勿采矿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, another giant orb.  This one's even bigger than the one in Winterhold. Maybe it's the other one's armor.</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，另一个巨大的球体。甚至比冬堡的那个更大，也许这是某个巨人的盔甲.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look at all this construction.  Maybe these vampires are tunneling their way to Akavir.  Maybe someone told them their rivers flow with blood.</Source>
      <Dest>瞧瞧这儿的建筑。也许这些吸血鬼在搞一条通往Akavir的隧道。难道说有人告诉他们那些河里流淌的都是血吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Spider webs! Wait, spiders are coordinating the caravan attacks? Wow. I'm trying really hard not to admire them but it's not as easy as you'd think.</Source>
      <Dest>蜘蛛网！等等，蜘蛛与马车遭袭有关？哇哦，我一直努力地不去吸引蜘蛛的注意力但要做到这点比你想象得要难啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You found a Nord ruin.  You're so good at adventuring it scares me.  I'm the same way with procrastination.</Source>
      <Dest>你找到了个诺德遗迹。你在探险方面的天赋真让我吃惊。虽然我觉得我在拖延症上的天赋足够和你找寻遗迹的天赋媲美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let's reunite a talking dog with its master by killing a cult of vampires! Just another sentence that has never been uttered by anyone ever.</Source>
      <Dest>让我们把这窖吸血鬼全杀了，好让一个会说话的狗和他的主人团聚吧。我只是有啥说啥罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, I know it's kind of late to be bringing this up now, but do you really think we should save Fjola? Her husband didn't exactly seem...sane.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我知道现在有点儿晚了，但你真的认为我们应该救下菲欧拉吗？她的丈夫看起来完全没有……理智。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Seems like it'd be trading one prison for another. Only this one's more of an asylum.</Source>
      <Dest>感觉像是从一个监牢被带到了另一个监牢.只是这个监牢更像一个庇护所。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, a healing spell.  Is there anything you can't do?  If there is, it's probably something stupid anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>喔哦，治愈魔法。难道没有什么你不擅长的么？如果有的话，反正是什么微不足道的傻事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's a witch.  Just one though. How many heads did we need to get, anyway?  I'm asking because they'll probably start to smell after a day or two.</Source>
      <Dest>这儿有个女巫，尽管只有一个。话说回来我们需要多少个脑袋来着？[我的意思是说她们的脑袋在一两天之后大概就发臭了]。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look. A cave. Plenty of gold inside, I hope.</Source>
      <Dest>看，一个山洞。希望里面有很多财宝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, look at me!  Did I always have these muscles?  Ask me for directions so I can show them to you.</Source>
      <Dest>喔，看着我！我是不是很强壮？快这样问我，我就能把我的肌肉展示给你看了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look at the size of that spider! Funny thing is, it's huge, but I bet it's the worst mage out of all of them.</Source>
      <Dest>看看那些庞大的蜘蛛！虽然他们长得那么大，我打赌一个最糟糕的法师也能从他们那里逃出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, that feels good.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，那感觉很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dwemer Museum.  Are there Dwarven sphere jousts and taffy treats made by Centurions?  Huh?  Of course I've been to a museum before.</Source>
      <Dest>矮人博物馆。这些矮人球和太妃糖条是由百夫长制造的么？呵呵？我之前当然去过博物馆了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What did you do?  Wait...let me guess.  You've turned me into a woman.  No, an Orc!  A goat?  Funny, I don't feel like chewing cud.</Source>
      <Dest>你干什么了？等等……让我猜猜看。你把我变成了一个女人。不，一个兽人！难不成是一只山羊吗？真有趣，不过我不喜欢咀嚼反刍的食物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, look at this place.  I wonder who it was that was buried here before the Gauldur boy.</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，看看这地方。我挺想知道是谁在高尔多那家伙之前就被埋到这儿的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think I see danger ahead.  And wouldn't you know it, I think my back just went out on me.  Really.</Source>
      <Dest>我想前面会有危险等着我。你难道不相信我说的？我想此去是凶多吉少了，真的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh good, a river! I'm so tired of drinking wine and snow.</Source>
      <Dest>哦太好了，一条河！我已经厌倦用雪和葡萄酒解渴了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Brittleshin Pass.  Last time I was here, there was an icicle sticking out of the Nord sculpture's nose.  Oh, it's still there.  How embarrassing.</Source>
      <Dest>脆胫关。我上次来这的时候，那个诺德塑像鼻子下面挂着个冰柱。啊欧，冰柱还在。真是无法直视...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I thought I recognized this place. This is Pinewatch. They know me here. Although they don't really like me, either.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，我想我认识这个地方。这是松木哨塔。这的人认识我，尽管他们不怎么喜欢我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Danger ahead. This is the part where we both conjure up some courage. If only I knew the spell.</Source>
      <Dest>前方有危险！到了这儿咱俩都得鼓起勇气才行。我要是会那个法术就好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A vampire thrall.  Aw...it looks so peaceful sitting there, with its wine and its bowl of bloody skulls.</Source>
      <Dest>一个吸血鬼奴仆。哦......它坐在那儿时看起来真是“人畜无害”，瞧瞧它那酒和那一碗盛满鲜血的头骨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Invisible at last.  Think of all the things we can do, and all the things we can get away with.  This is permanent, right?</Source>
      <Dest>总算是隐形了。试想一下我们现在能做的事，再想想我们能逃脱的那些处罚！这个效果是永久的，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh good, more mages.  I'm rather enjoying killing them.   Damn conjurers are always looking down on us bladebinders.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，太好了，一堆法师。我就是喜欢干掉他们。该死的施法者老是瞧不起我们武士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A cave. What will we find, trouble or treasure?</Source>
      <Dest>有个洞穴。里面会有什么呢，危险还是宝藏？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Huh. I smell mead. I must be going crazy.</Source>
      <Dest>哈。我闻到蜜酒的味道了。我一定快疯了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How can that pressure plate be connected to anything? It's smack dab in the middle of nowhere. I say we just walk across. It's a bluff.</Source>
      <Dest>哪儿有什么机关链接到那个踏板啊？它附近什么东西也没有。要我说咱就走过去算了，完全是虚张声势。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder what we'll find in this cave. Vampires? Trolls? Spiders? With our luck it'll probably be vampire trolls mounted on spiders.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道我们会在这个洞穴里发现什么。吸血鬼？巨魔？蜘蛛？或许我们运气很好的是吸血鬼、巨魔加蜘蛛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ooh, Jazbay grapes. It used to be illegal to pick those, back when they had more flavor. But now that they're bland nobody cares.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，架子湾葡萄。在过去，采摘它们是违法的，因为那时的味道无比香醇。但现在，那味道平淡的无人问津。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh Gods, I can actually breathe again! Well, I could breathe back in that ruin, but it was rather unpleasant to do so. Oh, and look, a nice view!</Source>
      <Dest>哦天哪，我终于又能呼吸了！呃，其实我在遗迹也能呼吸，但那么做感觉挺恶心的。噢，看哪，这风景太美了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is an impressive little cave. Although not as impressive as moving that boulder away from the entrance. I still don't know how Karliah did that.</Source>
      <Dest>这真是个不错的小洞窟。不过不比卡莉亚清开入口那些巨石那样令人震惊。我一直不知道她是如何做到的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So given where we are and the sentries posted outside, I think this might be a smuggling operation.  I hope I don't run into anyone I know.</Source>
      <Dest>从我们所处的位置以及外面这一大堆站岗的哨兵来看，我觉着这大概是个走私行为吧。但愿我不会撞见熟人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sure whatever's beyond that fence is extremely dangerous. You know, just once I'd like to look behind one of them and find a basket of kittens.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢说围墙外面的东西肯定都极端地危险。你知道，有一次我看出去居然看见了一篮子小猫哎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Suddenly I don't feel like fighting.  But I do feel like taking a nap.  I think I'll do that.</Source>
      <Dest>我突然就不想干架了。我想睡午觉。我觉得我会这么做的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh Gods, something's coming out of the water!  Griffins!  Run for your life!   Run for..oh.  They're just statues.  My mistake.  </Source>
      <Dest>哦神啊，水里有东西出来了！Grffins！快逃命！快逃。。。哦。只是雕像。不好意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Cave up ahead. Tread carefully.</Source>
      <Dest>你先进洞. 小心脚下.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Excuse me, I think I dropped my jaw somewhere.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉，我惊呆了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, I'm not sure whose turn it is to pay the bandit toll, but I'd rather not be squished by boulders. I suppose we could just go around.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我不确定轮到谁来付强盗们的买路财了，不过我可不想被那些大石头砸成泥。我觉得我们应该走别的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would you mind cooking something for me?</Source>
      <Dest>你介意帮我煮点吃的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would you mind cooking something for me?</Source>
      <Dest>你介意帮我煮点吃的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Question. Are you by chance interested in me?</Source>
      <Dest>请问，你可能对我感兴趣吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your old place would suit us just fine.</Source>
      <Dest>你的老地方会很适合我们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How about my house in Windhelm?</Source>
      <Dest>我在风盔城的房子怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Has the store made any money?</Source>
      <Dest>这商店能赚钱吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Honeyside, my house in Riften.</Source>
      <Dest>我在裂谷城的房子在甜蜜湾附近。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My house in Markarth would be perfect.</Source>
      <Dest>我在马卡斯城的房子将会很完美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Let's live in my house in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>让我们住在我在独孤城的房子里吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interested in me, are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你对我有兴趣，没错吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, just thinking maybe you and I should get hitched.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，只是想，也许你和我应该选择结婚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Breezehome, my house in Whiterun.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，风宅，我在雪漫城的家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lakeview Manor.</Source>
      <Dest>湖景林居。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lakeview Manor.</Source>
      <Dest>湖景林居。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Heljarchen Hall.</Source>
      <Dest>勇士堑山庄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Heljarchen Hall.</Source>
      <Dest>勇士堑山庄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Proudspire Manor, my house in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>傲矛别墅，我在独孤城的家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hjerim, my house in Windhelm.</Source>
      <Dest>霜宅，我在风盔城的房子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have a house in Riften.</Source>
      <Dest>我在裂谷城有栋房子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We could live in my house in Whiterun.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以住在我在雪漫城的房子里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>哈啰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>RelationshipMarriagePostWeddingLoveInterestBlockingTopic</Source>
      <Dest>RelationshipMarriagePostWeddingLoveInterestBlockingTopic</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vlindrel Hall, my house in Markarth.</Source>
      <Dest>林德尔会堂，我在马卡斯城的房子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Windstad Manor.</Source>
      <Dest>文斯塔德庄园</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Windstad Manor.</Source>
      <Dest>文斯塔德庄园</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's probably best we stay friends.</Source>
      <Dest>我们最好还是保持朋友关系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like us to move somewhere else.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我们得去别的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great, I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了，我在那儿等你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great, I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了，我在那儿等你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great, I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了，我在那儿等你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stick and move!  Stick and move!</Source>
      <Dest>坚持住，动起来！坚持住，动起来！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fight!  Fight!</Source>
      <Dest>上啊！上啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Punch 'em like they stole your dinner!</Source>
      <Dest>扁他们！把他们当成偷了你晚餐的贼那样痛扁他们！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The home is great.  Although we probably have to pay a lot of taxes.  Maybe I'll start a store...</Source>
      <Dest>虽然我们可能要付很多的税。但是。。这房子真棒，也许我该开一间商店......</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Drive that snowback to the ground!</Source>
      <Dest>揍翻那个北方佬！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nord ruins. How long do you think they've stood here?</Source>
      <Dest>诺德遗迹。你认为它矗立于此多久了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, you're not exactly what we modest folk call "subtle," are you?  Yes, I'm interested.  What of it?</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，你不正是我们这些谦虚的人称为“狡猾的家伙”的家伙吗？是啊，我挺感兴趣的。这有什么关系呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh!  You're back!  I just want you to know that those rumors are untrue.  I did not lose our fortune playing iron hearts.</Source>
      <Dest>哦！你回来了！我只是想让你知道那些传言是不真的。我们没有丢失那些铁艺的技巧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We're married!  All that's left is deciding on a place to live.  Just don't say my place.   Because that's technically Ulundil's.</Source>
      <Dest>我们结婚啦！现在商量下我们住哪儿吧。但可别说住去我那儿。因为那其实是属于Ulundil的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A Dwarven city. Remarkable.</Source>
      <Dest>一座矮人城市。真是不同寻常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You really know how to let an Elf down gently, don't you?  How about a hint next time, like you think the farmer's handsome or something?</Source>
      <Dest>你真的知道如何让一个精灵变得礼貌吗？打个比方吧，你在讨论一个农民的英俊潇洒或者别的什么类似的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A Nord ruin.  Thousands of years old.</Source>
      <Dest>一个诺德的废墟。已经几千年之久了。但还没人探索过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So...have you spoken to a Priest of Mara yet?  No pressure.</Source>
      <Dest>所以...你跟玛拉的祭司讲了吗？我没催你的意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These masterpieces take time.  Ask me again later.</Source>
      <Dest>杰作当然要花费时间制作。改天再问我吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great. I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。我会在那儿等你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I cooked this and I'm quite proud of it.  I think you might have married a culinary genius.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我煮的，我为此而自豪。我想你可能嫁给了一名天才厨师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great.  I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。我会在那儿跟你汇合。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great.  I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。我会在那儿跟你汇合。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great.  I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。我会在那儿跟你汇合。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great.  I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。我会在那儿跟你汇合。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, my love.</Source>
      <Dest>你好，亲爱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like I close my eyes and picture the fireball coming at me...it's almost here, and now I'm casting my ward and...</Source>
      <Dest>就像我闭上眼睛然后想象火球冲我飞来……它就快到了，现在我就得释放结界然后……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here.  I got this for you.  Just a small token of my gratitude.</Source>
      <Dest>来，这个送给你，只是个表达我心意的小礼物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, I'll just stand right here, and you start hitting the ground with spells and such.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我就站在这儿，然后你就开始用法术之类的撞击地面吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Old ruins. Nordic, by the looks of it.</Source>
      <Dest>从外观上能看出来，这是座古代的诺德遗迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait...hold on.  Maybe you don't have to actually use a spell.  What if...what if I just imagined you were casting them.</Source>
      <Dest>等等，稍等一下。你可能并不需要真正吟唱一个咒语。我可以假装你在吟唱他们</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the Divines, look. A Dwarven city.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵在上。看，一座矮人城市。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Old stonework. Gold, traps, and bones.</Source>
      <Dest>古老石雕制品，金子、陷阱和骨头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Twelve septims on the one who's winning!</Source>
      <Dest>12个金币赌谁赢！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell, my love.</Source>
      <Dest>再见了，亲爱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Legend says Dwarven ruins are haunted. I'd rather not find out.</Source>
      <Dest>传说矮人废墟闹鬼。我情愿没找到这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dwarven ruins. Old cities, old ghosts.</Source>
      <Dest>矮人废墟。老城市，老鬼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye, my love.</Source>
      <Dest>再见，我的宝贝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye, my love.</Source>
      <Dest>再见，我的宝贝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello, my love.  Back from some adventure I bet.</Source>
      <Dest>你好啊，亲爱的。我猜你刚经历了一场冒险回来的吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Need your husband's blade?  I might go mad if I keep staring at the walls.</Source>
      <Dest>需要你丈夫跟你一起冒险吗？让我一直在家盯着墙无所事事我可真要疯了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Business has been...okay.  We're making profits, I think.  Here, have some.</Source>
      <Dest>生意已经……搞定了。我想我们赚了些钱。给，拿着这些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright. I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright. I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright. I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright. I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That amulet...is that what I think it is? Are you?  Are we?   I should just shut up right now and let you speak.</Source>
      <Dest>那个护符...是我想的那样吗？你？我们？我想我该直接闭嘴，该你说了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh?  Where should we move to?</Source>
      <Dest>哦？现在我们该去哪？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's my loving spouse! I bet you didn't expect to see your husband here, you know, outdoors instead of loafing around the house.</Source>
      <Dest>看哪，这是我至爱的妻子！我打赌你一定以为我在外面，而从未想到我会在屋子里晃悠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I assure you, I am acting strictly in the best interests of the family. So what if Thane Larsdon wants to overthrow everything.</Source>
      <Dest>不过我向你保证。我做的一切都是为了家族的利益着想。可要是劳斯登领主想要把一切推倒重来怎么办。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You keep saying that but people at the Four Shields tend to just mope around, drink, and feel miserable. That's not my idea of adventure.</Source>
      <Dest>你只是不停的说“冒险”，然后四面盾牌客栈的人们浑浑噩噩的酗酒，哀叹悲惨的命运。我可不觉得这是我向往的冒险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do the three of you hear something? I thought I heard a woman calling to me...</Source>
      <Dest>你们三个有听到什么吗？我似乎听到一个女人在冲我吼叫...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These towers are impressive, although a bit crooked. Actually, I'm not sure if they are, but try getting that idea out of your head. You can't.</Source>
      <Dest>这些塔真令人印象深刻,尽管有点儿歪。事实上，我不确定它们是不是真的歪了, 但最好忘了我这个想法，你别也这么想啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you're saying I need to work hard and study to achieve my goals...but what if that goes against everything I stand for?</Source>
      <Dest>所以你说我需要努力工作好好学习达到我的目标……但倘若这些违背了我所坚信的一切我该怎么办？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I always make sure to look up and wave at the windows when I pass the Blue Palace. Eventually they might start thinking I'm someone important.</Source>
      <Dest>每当我路过蓝色宫殿的时候我都不忘抬头看看窗户并奋力地在窗前挥舞着我的手。这样总有一天他们会开始把我当成一个重要人物的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right, because the last thing we want to do is walk into a haunted Nord ruin at night.</Source>
      <Dest>对，因为我们要做的最后一件事就是在今晚走进那个闹鬼的诺德遗迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, let's see what we can find here.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，看看我们能从这儿找到些什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're not jealous of him are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你难道是嫉妒他了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think it's time we had a word with the librarian regarding "quality control."</Source>
      <Dest>我想是时候我们得和图书管理员讨论关于“品质控制”的事情了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, now it's actually circling around Masser and hurtling back toward...it looks like that's Rorikstead...oh that poor goat...so much carnage...</Source>
      <Dest>哦，它正围着玛撒尔转圈……然后飞向……看起来像是洛里斯泰德……可怜的羊……好可怕的大屠杀……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I've deflected it, with so much force it seems, the fireball is now shooting off into the sky.  It is literally burning a hole in Aetherius.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我躲过了它，但它太强力了，那火球径直冲向了天空，简直像是要把艾瑟瑞斯烧出一个大洞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look at that! So the farmer was telling the truth about the strange lights! But I don't hear any strange noises. He's obviously hiding something.</Source>
      <Dest>看那边！这么说那农夫说有奇怪的光是真的！不过我没听见什么奇怪的噪音。他肯定还隐瞒了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come on, let's go.  This is obviously not the sort of mage, and I use the term loosely, that can help me.</Source>
      <Dest>来吧，我们走。这显然不是那种法术，我很熟悉他们，我对付他们有经验。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Steepfall Burrow. I like places that have literal names. Imagine how much more motivated we'd be to raid "Lots of Treasure Cave."</Source>
      <Dest>坠崖洞穴。我喜欢这个地方形象的名字。想象一下，如果我们要去劫夺一个叫“宝藏超多洞穴”，那我们该多有干劲儿啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha! Get it? Because they're skeletons. Yeah, I know, worst joke ever.</Source>
      <Dest>哈！明白了吗？因为他们是骨头架子。这是我听过的最糟糕的笑话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, maybe it's a little less ordinary than I thought.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，跟我所想的比起来这或许有点儿奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You mean, besides the fact that they're all wearing matching outfits?</Source>
      <Dest>你是说，除了他们都穿着相配的衣服这事以外还有别的什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These bandits didn't seem to have a problem with it, so why should we? Unless you're implying they're better than us.</Source>
      <Dest>这些强盗都能适应，为什么我们不能呢？除非你在暗示他们比我们强。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh wow, that's a lot of Orichalcum. You're not thinking of mining it all, are you? Oh Gods, you are. </Source>
      <Dest>哦哇哦，这么多的金刚砂。你不会想要全部挖走吧？哦神啊，你还真的有这种打算。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is good place to live. Great views, clean air, and free gold, so long as you can get over the whole "ethics of robbing people" thing.</Source>
      <Dest>这是个居住良所。漂亮的风景，干净的空气，还有些黑钱，只要你能忍受那些抢劫者的道德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This place is called Soljund's Sinkhole, right? Well, here's your sinkhole. And that corpse at the bottom must be Soljund.</Source>
      <Dest>这地方叫索云德的阴沟，对吧？好啦，这儿就是阴沟，而底下那具尸体肯定就是索云德了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Troll's blood! Look at this place!</Source>
      <Dest>巨魔之血！看看这里！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I'm really curious about this bowl of blood. Did the vampire scoop his goblet in there to drink while he reads?</Source>
      <Dest>所以我真的对这碗血很好奇。吸血鬼还会边读书边晃荡着高脚酒杯浅啜啥的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Excuse me...Yes, you, Orc.  Do you have any spell tomes available for..."special" mages?</Source>
      <Dest>对不起……是的，就是你，兽人。你有魔法书籍可供……"特别的" 法师吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that doesn't sound too bad.  Wait a minute...what kind of rodent?</Source>
      <Dest>呃，听起来不是太糟糕。等一下儿……什么样儿的耗子？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ooh, this book has pictures!  It seems easy enough and...it's a children's story on mudcrabs.  What sort of library is this?</Source>
      <Dest>哦~这本书有图片！这似乎很简单，嗯......这是一本有关泥蟹的儿童读物。这到底是什么样的图书馆呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not only are you in charge of the food, you can position the barrels so no one can see you sleeping on the job.</Source>
      <Dest>你不仅仅偷吃食物，你还可以把桶子摆的风骚一点，这样就没有人会看见你上班睡觉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is it just me, or is this place incredibly dark and scary? Maybe if the air wasn't as black as soot, I wouldn't judge it so harshly.</Source>
      <Dest>到底是我的错觉，还是这个地方真的黑乎乎的很可怕？也许如果这里的空气没像烟尘那么黑，我就不会如此苛刻的评价了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, we're here. If Malkoran kills me and turns me into a shade, tell him I don't want to wear a helmet like the others.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我们到了。如果我不幸栽在了莫克然手上而且被变成了一个影鬼， 告诉他我不想像其他影鬼那样戴头盔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I have to ask, as there were a ton of them outside and even more in here. What's with the sheets of leather? Are Forsworn big on tanning racks?</Source>
      <Dest>看着外面这一群甚至更多的弃誓者，我有个问题不得不问。那些和皮革一起穿在身上的是什么东西？弃誓者自身就是个大号制皮架吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I know. I'm just trying to find things I don't like about everyone to lessen the impact if they die.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我知道。我只是试着在找些我不喜欢的事情，是关于如果人们濒死时他们是如何与世界脱离联系的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So Skjarn, if you end up getting your skull split by a Draugr, I'll just try to remember all the women who were spared from meeting you.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧夏尔, 如果你最后落得个脑袋被尸鬼捣得稀巴烂的下场，我会记得有多少女人因此而免于被糟蹋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To use fire, one must ignite the ethereal flint through the synchronistic channeling of...oh rubbish!  This won't do at all!</Source>
      <Dest>要使用火焰的话，首先要通过灵界的渠道同步点燃空灵的燧石…噢去他的，这根本行不通！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh wow, it almost looks like some sort of arena. The crowd looks pretty dead though.</Source>
      <Dest>哇奥，这看上去简直像是个什么竞技场了，不过观众们都是死地挺透的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I were a bandit, I think I'd like a job like this.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我是个强盗，我想我会喜欢这样的工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, that's impressive.</Source>
      <Dest>哇，太好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think you have the wrong person.  I'm just here to learn a spell.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你认错人了。我只是来这儿学魔法的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Will you look at that. I've always said human skulls make for excellent candle holders, and there's your proof right there.</Source>
      <Dest>看那边。我总是说人类的头骨是制作蜡烛台的绝佳材料，那正好就是个证明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I was going to follow you, but not if you're going to spend all day staring at fires and curvy wenches. I could do that at home. Conceivably.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，我得跟紧你，但如果你打算整天盯着身材火辣的妹子，那我宁愿呆在家里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did I hear that adventurer right? Did he say talking spiders? Oh...magic spiders. That's much worse.</Source>
      <Dest>我没听错吧？他刚刚说的是会讲话的蜘蛛？哦……会魔法的蜘蛛。比那个更糟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, it's not like the Thalmor gave us a better offer.</Source>
      <Dest>我是说，这可不比梭莫给我们出的好价。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I fancy myself a fairly decent chef, maybe Falatild can help you with the rest.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我想象自己是个得体而又美丽的厨师，或许会帮你完成剩下的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Absolutely not!</Source>
      <Dest>绝不！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well this looks like an ordinary cave if I ever saw one. And I've seen at least five.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，这看起来就像是我曾见过的普通山洞。我已经看到过至少五个了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or does he dip his finger in there and use it to turn pages? I like to imagine vampires use blood in place of every liquid we normally use.</Source>
      <Dest>还是他把手指往那里蘸蘸好用来翻书？我想吸血鬼们的习惯也许跟我们差不多，只不过他们用的是血。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know what would make these traps more effective? If there were sweetrolls waiting for us at the end of it.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道怎样让陷阱更有效？比如。。放一个甜甜圈在陷阱的另一侧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And here I was going to compliment these bandits on how normal they seem, when we come across a table with somebody's severed hands. Lovely.</Source>
      <Dest>当我们无意发现桌子上的有着某人的断肢时，我不禁想称赞这些强盗，看上去多标准啊。真令人愉快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I love how he just leaves the spider on the shelf with his other things. Middle shelf, gloves. Top shelf, eggs. On top of that, magic spider monster.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢他把蜘蛛和其他自己的东西摆放在架子上的做法。中层的架子上，放手套。顶层架子上，放蜘蛛蛋。最上面，一只蜘蛛魔怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Seems to me that's the best way to avoid ghosts. Well, the imaginary ones anyway. The real ones don't really care what time it is.</Source>
      <Dest>对我而言那是避免见鬼最好的办法。当然，不管怎么说我曾经这么想过。我曾经并不是那么在意时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The dead do seem particular about their treasure.</Source>
      <Dest>这具死尸似乎详细说明了他们的宝藏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The dead do seem particular about their treasure.</Source>
      <Dest>这具死尸似乎详细说明了他们的宝藏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right.  I could do with a more balanced diet.</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的。我需要更均衡的饮食。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right.  I could do with a more balanced diet.</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的。我需要更均衡的饮食。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right.  I could do with a more balanced diet.</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的。我需要更均衡的饮食。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think of our home?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的家怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I would love to hear your horrible store names.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我倒想听听你那糟糕的商店名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I would love to hear your horrible store names.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我倒想听听你那糟糕的商店名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I would love to hear your horrible store names.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我倒想听听你那糟糕的商店名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I would love to hear your horrible store names.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我倒想听听你那糟糕的商店名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're deflecting your fears with humor.  Don't worry, I got this.</Source>
      <Dest>你正在用幽默掩饰你的恐惧，别担心，我已经明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're deflecting your fears with humor.  Don't worry, I got this.</Source>
      <Dest>你正在用幽默掩饰你的恐惧，别担心，我已经明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're deflecting your fears with humor.  Don't worry, I got this.</Source>
      <Dest>你正在用幽默掩饰你的恐惧，别担心，我已经明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're deflecting your fears with humor.  Don't worry, I got this.</Source>
      <Dest>你正在用幽默掩饰你的恐惧，别担心，我已经明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're deflecting your fears with humor.  Don't worry, I got this.</Source>
      <Dest>你正在用幽默掩饰你的恐惧，别担心，我已经明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're deflecting your fears with humor.  Don't worry, I got this.</Source>
      <Dest>你正在用幽默掩饰你的恐惧，别担心，我已经明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're deflecting your fears with humor.  Don't worry, I got this.</Source>
      <Dest>你正在用幽默掩饰你的恐惧，别担心，我已经明白了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This was never about Ancano or revenge.  It was about saving the College.</Source>
      <Dest>这根本不是安卡诺或复仇的问题，而是为了拯救学院。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This was never about Ancano or revenge.  It was about saving the College.</Source>
      <Dest>这根本不是安卡诺或复仇的问题，而是为了拯救学院。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This was never about Ancano or revenge.  It was about saving the College.</Source>
      <Dest>这根本不是安卡诺或复仇的问题，而是为了拯救学院。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then we have to find ourselves a bard.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说咱们得找个吟游诗人入伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by "Sleeping" Giant?</Source>
      <Dest>你说"睡着的"巨人是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by "Sleeping" Giant?</Source>
      <Dest>你说"睡着的"巨人是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by "Sleeping" Giant?</Source>
      <Dest>你说"睡着的"巨人是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I needed to escape Cidhna Mine.  I didn't real care who lived or died.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是想逃离 Cidhna Mine. 我才不在乎谁活着还是死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something tells me this will go horribly wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>我感觉到这件事正在被搞砸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something tells me this will go horribly wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>我感觉到这件事正在被搞砸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something tells me this will go horribly wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>我感觉到这件事正在被搞砸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Giants go to sleep just like the rest of us. How is this one different?</Source>
      <Dest>巨人也是跟我们一样要睡觉的吧。为嘛这只不睡？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Giants go to sleep just like the rest of us. How is this one different?</Source>
      <Dest>巨人也是跟我们一样要睡觉的吧。为嘛这只不睡？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Giants go to sleep just like the rest of us. How is this one different?</Source>
      <Dest>巨人也是跟我们一样要睡觉的吧。为嘛这只不睡？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How should I know? They all look the same to me. And by that I mean "extremely heavy."</Source>
      <Dest>我为什么该知道？而且对我来说他们看起来都一样。我的意思是“非常非常相似“</Dest>
    </String>  
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The spheres wouldn't be functioning, of course, unless you wanted them to be. That's entirely up to you, but don't look at me to clean up the blood.</Source>
      <Dest>除非你想要让那些球体运作，不然它们是不会动的。这完全取决于你，不过别指望我来帮你清理你的血迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Skjarn, think about it for a second. You're a bard, right? What's more precious to a bard than his hands?</Source>
      <Dest>夏尔，再好好考虑一下吧。你是一个吟遊诗人, 不对吗? 还有什么比吟游诗人的双手更加珍贵呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dragonborn says, "Well, Alduin will eat just about anything, but ever since he ate the world, he likes to measure things first."</Source>
      <Dest>龙裔说， "是啊，奥杜因什么都吃。但自从他吃了个世界之后，他就开始喜欢在吃之前先测量东西的大小了。"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The wench, disgusted, asks the Dragonborn what in Oblivion he's doing.</Source>
      <Dest>那年轻的女孩，露出厌恶的神色，责问龙裔在湮灭里都干了些什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We'll need to split up and work on each Companion individually. I'll talk to Ria, and you talk to everyone else.</Source>
      <Dest>我们得分头行动跟战友团的人合作。我去找Ria，你负责其他人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, it's almost rather adorable the way they think they can still spend it. And even if they could, what would they spend it on?</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，他们到了这个地步仍然认为他们能花掉那笔钱还真是令人尊敬。。也许他们能，他们又能花到哪里呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A good name if you're running a museum, a bad name for newly crafted goods and dinnerware.</Source>
      <Dest>要是你开的是博物馆就是个好名字，要是卖的是工艺品和餐具那就不怎么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's the joke.  And since I know you're going to kill that hungry son of a bitch, I might as well tell it now while it's still relevant. Good luck.</Source>
      <Dest>开玩笑而已。从我知道你打算去杀了那个饥饿的狗崽子的时候起，我就想说这其中或许有千丝万缕的关系。祝你好运。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He was dead, of course, but you'd be surprised how many people mistake me for a corpse.</Source>
      <Dest>他死了，当然，但你会惊奇地发现很多人误以为我也是一具尸体。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I kid.  We're adventurers, right?  We need to show people all our spoils lest they think we're lazy!</Source>
      <Dest>不，我的孩子。我们是冒险者，对吗？我们得给人们看看我们的战利品，免得他们以为我们很懒！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha! Well I'm sure wherever Madanach is, he'll be glad to know you didn't put much thought into his death.</Source>
      <Dest>哈！我确定无论迈德纳奇在哪儿，他都会很高兴知道你没把太多心思花在他的死上的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For instance, have I told you the one about the Dragonborn, Alduin, and the High Elf?</Source>
      <Dest>例如，我告诉过你那个关于龙裔，奥杜因，和高精灵的故事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can't have people coming over and the only thing we have to show them is a tuft of Werewolf hair, Mehrunes' drawstring and a slice of moldy cheese.</Source>
      <Dest>别让人们过来，我们能给他们看的东西只有一簇狼人毛，一条梅鲁涅斯的裤带和一片发霉的奶酪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It inevitably will, which is why I propose we bring along some muscle, just in case the whole lullaby thing doesn't work.</Source>
      <Dest>喔，我料到了这点，这也是我坚持带上一名战士的原因，就是为了防着给它唱催眠曲这招不管用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was thinking we could have a couple Dwarven spheres in the corner, and roll them at guests from time to time whenever they annoyed us.</Source>
      <Dest>我在想我们可以在那个角落上放两只矮人球，一旦有来访者打扰了我们，我们就把矮人球扔向他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Exactly! And a bound sword is so much more comfortable in your palm. It's like holding a cloud, if clouds were sharp and made to cut people.</Source>
      <Dest>很好！一把约束之剑在你手中更加合适，就如闪电般杀人于无形之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dragonborn and Alduin walk into a tavern.  The Dragonborn orders a drink, while Alduin orders a High Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>龙裔和奥杜因走进一家客栈，龙裔点了一杯酒，然而奥杜因点了一个高精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, this Breezehome is aptly named.  Everything is just that.  Relaxed.  Easy.  A breeze, so to speak.</Source>
      <Dest>不，风宅这个名字取得很好。一切都是那样。又轻松，又自在。如同微风一般。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Giant and the treasure may very well exist.</Source>
      <Dest>宝藏和守护巨人很可能是存在的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Giant and the treasure may very well exist.</Source>
      <Dest>巨人和宝藏很可能是存在的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The say a hagraven cast a spell on it long ago, and it only wakes when an adventurer comes to plunder the treasure it guards.</Source>
      <Dest>据说有一个乌鸦鬼婆很久以前给它施加了一个咒语，只有当冒险者来夺取它所守护的财宝时，它才会苏醒过来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The say a hagraven cast a spell on it long ago, and it only wakes when an adventurer comes to plunder the treasure it guards.</Source>
      <Dest>据说有一个乌鸦鬼婆很久以前给它施加了一个咒语，只有当冒险者来夺取它所守护的财宝时，它才会苏醒过来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, it's not like the Thalmor gave me a better offer.</Source>
      <Dest>我的意思是，梭默并不能给我更好的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good.  I'm glad we're on the same page.  The problem is getting the others to comply.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。这样我们就说到一块儿了。问题是要把其他人也拉拢才行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It doesn't matter how many of us there are. He's the boss. We have to follow his orders.</Source>
      <Dest>不管我们在这里有多少人，他是老板，我们要听他的指令</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If we can recruit him and the bard, I'd feel a lot more comfortable about our chances.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我们能招募他和那个诗人，我感觉我们会更有把握。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well yes, but to be honest, I would rather not stake my life on the words of this halfwit, regardless of how smart he seems standing next to me.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，但是老实说，我不会因为这个蠢货说的东西就用生命冒险，不管站在我身边的他看起来有多聪明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I tried using a pun.  I set up my goods on benches split by a single walkway.  "The Summerset Aisle," I called it.  As in A-I-S-L-E.</Source>
      <Dest>然后我试着用了个双关语。我把放在长凳上的货物分在两遍，搞出一个单行道出来。我把它叫作“夏暮道。”注意是“道”，不是“岛”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not every High Elf is destined to become a wizard.  Granted, I'm partly to blame for the way people see me.</Source>
      <Dest>不是所有高精灵都一定是巫师。老实说，我对于其他人这么看我有点不爽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good, it just needs more room for display cases.  Just not enough places to display your weapon here.  Well, all except *that* weapon.</Source>
      <Dest>好，我需要给展示柜准备更多空间。这里的地方连装你放在这儿的武器都不够了。好吧，除了“那件”兵器。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you think our party is balanced enough? I mean Falatild is a ranger but it would've been nice to take Valgus along.</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我们的队伍配置好了吗？我是说 Falatild 是不错的射手不过要是有 Valgus 一起就更好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That may seem unfair, but there's no other way.  The rest of them scare me.  </Source>
      <Dest>这并不公平，但是也别无选择。剩下的那些选择都不怎么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I lived with the traveling artists, I once played an Argonian fishmonger with surprising accuracy.</Source>
      <Dest>当我跟一帮在旅行的艺术家住在一起的时候, 我还曾经扮演过亚龙鱼贩子呢，而且演得很像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why, it's absolutely dreadful!  I say that because I want to be the first Elf to ever complain about living in a castle.</Source>
      <Dest>为什么？那太可怕了！我这么说是因为我就要成为第一个抱怨自己城堡生活的精灵了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I suppose I do hold a special kind of loathing for Elves like him.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管我承认我确实对像他这样的精灵有一种特殊的厌恶感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha! Well I'm sure wherever Thonar is, he'll be glad to know you didn't put much thought into his death.</Source>
      <Dest>哈！好吧我很清楚托纳尔在哪,他一定很乐意听说你对他的死不以为意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have some friends in Morthal who told me there's some legendary hero who lives in the marsh and rides a Chaurus.</Source>
      <Dest>我有一些朋友住在墨索尔城，他们告诉我哪里有一些传说中的英雄骑着泥螃蟹生活在沼泽里.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I assure you, I am acting strictly in my own interests. So what if Thane Larsdon wants to overthrow everything.</Source>
      <Dest>但我向你保证，我之所以这么做完全是为了自己的利益。所以要是劳斯登领主想推翻一切该怎么办。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Traps, probably.  I imagine the only thing a skeleton fears are mangy dogs who'd like nothing more than to chew on their bones.</Source>
      <Dest>陷阱，大概吧。我想最让骷髅恐惧的东西是那些最喜欢啃骨头的癞皮狗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hate it.  Well, I would, if I was the sort of person who abhorred being happy.  There are really people like that, you know.</Source>
      <Dest>我讨厌它。如果我是痛恨幸福的那类人，我会那样做。真的有这样的人，你知道的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, really, what is there to say?  We live in a thousand story house in Solitude. </Source>
      <Dest>不，说真的，这简直难以用语言形容！我们住在独孤城。住在一栋充满历史和传奇的房子里！ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So Skjarn, I have to ask. Exactly how many women have you bedded? Approximately. I mean, I don't expect you to have a count.</Source>
      <Dest>那么夏尔，我认真的问你，你到底睡了多少女人？我不指望你还真做了统计，给我个大概数字就行了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you admit I'm funny.  I was starting to wonder if my jokes had any impact.  I was just about to dig deep in my arsenal too.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，你承认我还有点儿意思。我在想，如果我的笑话能够产生什么影响，我也差不多该在我的军械库挖个洞了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I like the fact that this home has a balcony and a fishing boat.  Not that I have any inkling as to how to use either, but I can pretend to.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢这个有着阳台和渔船的家。虽然我完全不会使用，但是我会自认为我会用的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The wench brings over their orders.  The Drago\nborn takes a sip.  Alduin, however, grabs the Elf by the tail and presses him against his bottom.</Source>
      <Dest>村姑带来他们的酒。龙裔抿了一口酒。然而，奥杜因用它的尾巴抓起精灵把他压碎</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's for dinner?</Source>
      <Dest>晚餐是什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's for dinner?</Source>
      <Dest>晚餐是什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's for dinner?</Source>
      <Dest>晚餐是什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's for dinner?</Source>
      <Dest>晚餐是什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's for dinner?</Source>
      <Dest>晚餐是什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where are you headed now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在要前往何处?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where are you headed now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在要前往何处?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where are you headed now?</Source>
      <Dest>你现在要前往何处?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How was your day?</Source>
      <Dest>你今天过得怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How was your day?</Source>
      <Dest>你今天过得怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How was your day?</Source>
      <Dest>你今天过得怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How was your day?</Source>
      <Dest>你今天过得怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How was your day?</Source>
      <Dest>你今天过得怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How was your day?</Source>
      <Dest>你今天过得怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you propose we get past the Giant?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算怎么让我们从那些巨人身边穿过？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you propose we get past the Giant?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算怎么让我们从那些巨人身边穿过？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you propose we get past the Giant?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算怎么让我们从那些巨人身边穿过？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where do you think we should go next?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我們接下來該去哪?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where do you think we should go next?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我們接下來該去哪?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where do you think we should go next?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我們接下來該去哪?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where do you think we should go next?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得我們接下來該去哪?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what do you think is the best way to tap your limitless potential?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得什么是最好的方法来发掘你无限的潜力？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what do you think is the best way to tap your limitless potential?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得什么是最好的方法来发掘你无限的潜力？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Way to pass the blame onto somebody else.</Source>
      <Dest>这样的责任推给别人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Way to pass the blame onto somebody else.</Source>
      <Dest>这样的责任推给别人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any interesting things happen while I was gone?</Source>
      <Dest>我离开的时候发生了什么有趣的事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Stop making excuses.  Spell tomes are so easy a child could figure them out.</Source>
      <Dest>别找理由了，法术书简单的连个小孩都能弄明白。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Stop making excuses.  Spell tomes are so easy a child could figure them out.</Source>
      <Dest>别找理由了，法术书简单的连个小孩都能弄明白。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any questions now that we have time to relax?</Source>
      <Dest>我们现在有时间休息吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any questions now that we have time to relax?</Source>
      <Dest>我们现在有时间休息吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any questions now that we have time to relax?</Source>
      <Dest>我们现在有时间休息吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么心事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么心事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If I listen to your advice, I'm the lowest wit of all.</Source>
      <Dest>若是我听了你的建议，我就是最不风趣的人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If I listen to your advice, I'm the lowest wit of all.</Source>
      <Dest>若是我听了你的建议，我就是最不风趣的人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If I listen to your advice, I'm the lowest wit of all.</Source>
      <Dest>若是我听了你的建议，我就是最不风趣的人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's always some wizard's fault.  They're just bad people in general.</Source>
      <Dest>都是法师们的错。他们大部分都是坏人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's always some wizard's fault.  They're just bad people in general.</Source>
      <Dest>都是法师们的错。他们大部分都是坏人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then we have to find ourselves a bard.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说咱们得找个吟游诗人入伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then we have to find ourselves a bard.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说咱们得找个吟游诗人入伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then we have to find ourselves a bard.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说咱们得找个吟游诗人入伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's the business faring?</Source>
      <Dest>生意还好吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's the business faring?</Source>
      <Dest>生意还好吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How's the business faring?</Source>
      <Dest>生意还好吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sleeping or not, slaying a Giant doesn't sound too difficult.</Source>
      <Dest>不管睡觉与否，杀一个巨人都不会太难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sleeping or not, slaying a Giant doesn't sound too difficult.</Source>
      <Dest>不管睡觉与否，杀一个巨人都不会太难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sleeping or not, slaying a Giant doesn't sound too difficult.</Source>
      <Dest>不管睡觉与否，杀一个巨人都不会太难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I honor the dead, and would never steal from them.</Source>
      <Dest>我尊重死者，从不偷他们的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I honor the dead, and would never steal from them.</Source>
      <Dest>我尊重死者，从不偷他们的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I honor the dead, and would never steal from them.</Source>
      <Dest>我尊重死者，从不偷他们的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, this could be a complete waste of time.</Source>
      <Dest>换句话说这完全就是在浪费时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, this could be a complete waste of time.</Source>
      <Dest>换句话说这完全就是在浪费时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In other words, this could be a complete waste of time.</Source>
      <Dest>换句话说这完全就是在浪费时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree with Olivia. The tomes failed you.</Source>
      <Dest>我跟奥莉薇雅想的一样。那些书辜负了你的期望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In any case, if there's a way to make you better in combat, I'm all for it.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说，只要有办法提高你的战斗力，我都完全赞成。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In any case, if there's a way to make you better in combat, I'm all for it.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说，只要有办法提高你的战斗力，我都完全赞成。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So it's Rumarin's turn to make a decision. Bold move on your part, seeing as I'm half a halfwit.</Source>
      <Dest>现在轮到罗美勒决定了. Bold 挪到你的位置上去, 看看你有没有我一半精明.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, maybe it isn't my fault I can't cast a spell.  Maybe it's the fault of the wizards who write those blasted spell tomes!</Source>
      <Dest>我的意思是, 有可能不是我的原因导致这个法术出错.  有可能是写这些混账法术书的巫师弄错了!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The halfwit told me there's a trick to the spell that lets the hagraven get to her treasure.</Source>
      <Dest>那个傻瓜告诉我这个咒语有个窍门能让乌鸦鬼婆得到她的宝贝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Terrible.  Whose idea was it for me to open a store?  Mine?  Well, that's the last time I'm listening to that fool!</Source>
      <Dest>糟透了。当初到底是谁提出说要我开店的？我吗？哦好吧，这辈子我再也不自己拿主意了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For instance, supposedly the spell has a weakness which allows the Hagraven to access her treasure.</Source>
      <Dest>比如说，那个法术很可能有某种弱点会被乌鸦鬼婆利用来存取她自己的宝藏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If that were true, wouldn't every child from here to Valenwood be casting invisibility spells on our clothes?</Source>
      <Dest>如果这是真的，难道每一个从威木省来这里的孩子都能在我们的衣服上施展无形的法术吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let's see...I counted the amount of lint in my belly button...ten pieces today.  </Source>
      <Dest>看看……我数了数肚脐眼里的线头儿……今天有10根。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I picked up a broom and handed it to our housecarl.  Or maybe it was the mannequin.</Source>
      <Dest>我捡起一把扫帚递给我们的侍卫。或者别的装饰人偶啥的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tonight I think I'm going to make seared slaughterfish with a side of steamed carrots and fried cabbage.</Source>
      <Dest>今晚我打算做以蒸胡萝卜及油炸卷心菜为配菜的碳烤食人鱼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For dinner?  You mean you want me to cook?  Well, that's a fantastic idea, because I happen to be an excellent one.</Source>
      <Dest>做晚餐？你的意思是要我去烧菜吗？哦好吧，这是个绝妙的主意，因为我恰好是个超级棒的厨师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha-ha, have your fun.  But in all honesty, I do think I might be able to learn a spell or two.   I mean, I learned bladebinding easily enough.</Source>
      <Dest>哈哈,有你的.不过说真心话，我觉得我有能力学那么一两个魔法.我是说,我学武器召唤术很轻松.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I mean horrible as in literally inducing "horror."  Would you like to hear them?  No?  Well too bad.</Source>
      <Dest>我的意思是horrible这个词差不多是从"horror" 这个词里诞生的。你想听听吗？不想？真可惜。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Besides, this will be as easy as taking meat from a mudcrab. You see, there's a trick to this spell that the hagraven uses to get to her treasure.</Source>
      <Dest>而且，这会像从泥沼蟹身上得到蟹肉一样容易。你瞧，使用这个魔法有个窍门儿，乌鸦鬼婆就常用它来获取她的宝藏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>According to the halfwit, all we need to do is play it a lullaby and we'll be able to rock the angry giant back to sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>根据那个白痴所说，我们只要哼首摇篮曲就能把愤怒的巨人哄睡着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Naturally, as he was twice as smart as I am, I was intrigued. Supposedly there's an actual Sleeping Giant living somewhere in Falkreath.</Source>
      <Dest>毫无疑问，他比我要聪明两倍，我被耍了。或许在佛克瑞斯还真住着个沉睡巨人呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why yes.  While you were out there slaying dragons and such, I was here agonizing over how to eat in bed without staining the sheets.</Source>
      <Dest>为什么是呢。当你出门去做屠龙之类事情的时候，我只是在这为如何在床上吃东西同时又不弄脏床单而苦恼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So we've reached a consensus then.  I'm not a hapless idiot after all.  Just hapless.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我们已经达成共识了。我不是个倒霉的白痴，只是单纯的倒霉罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unless the children of this generation are far more respectful of their elders than mine.  Such a shame.</Source>
      <Dest>现在的孩子对于长辈的态度远不如我小的时候恭敬，真丢人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was thinking we should also recruit a strong warrior, in the event the giant refuses to take its nap.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我们也应该招募一个强大的战士，如果这个巨人一直不去睡午觉的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I have one. This Olivia Meronin character you met in Winterhold.  Is it true what she says?</Source>
      <Dest>对，我想起来了。那位你在冬堡见到的奥利维亚·马荣尼，她说的是不是真的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I say we scour the halls of the Arcanaeum in Winterhold.  There must be a book there somewhere I can understand.</Source>
      <Dest>我们我们要仔细找找冬堡的秘藏馆，我想一定有一本书，我可以或多或少看懂一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I say we scour the halls of the Arcanaeum in Winterhold.  There must be a book there somewhere I can understand.</Source>
      <Dest>我们我们要仔细找找冬堡的秘藏馆，我想一定有一本书，我可以或多或少看懂一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unless you have some questions you want to ask me first.  You know, to find out if this vessel's seaworthy, so to speak.</Source>
      <Dest>除非你想先问我一些问题。打个比方，问问这艘船的适航能力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't even come up with a decent name.  I was tossing around a few ideas earlier, and they were all horrible.</Source>
      <Dest>我甚至想不出一个体面的名字。我之前扔掉了一些想法，因为它们都太糟糕了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I organized everything in our home alphabetically, then put it all back.</Source>
      <Dest>我把我们家里的所有东西都按字母排列收拾整理了一通，然后把它们恢复一样一样摆放回去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, the bit about students not failing so much as instructors failing to teach them.</Source>
      <Dest>就是那所谓的防止教育者教育失败同时受教者归于堕落的事儿啦，你懂的。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just remember to point the finger elsewhere when things go wrong, otherwise I'm likely to pull it and make some sort of crude noise.</Source>
      <Dest>只需记住，当事情出错了的时候，要责怪别的人，否则我可能会逃走，还会发出些粗杂的噪音。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, okay, it's a loaf of bread and a bowl of cabbage stew.  Sometimes even I get too lazy to cook, and by sometimes I mean six days a week.</Source>
      <Dest>行吧，行吧，就是一条面包和一碗卷心菜汤。有时候连我都懒得下厨，我说“有时”的意思是一个星期有六天都这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么想法吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I took a nap and counted my lint again.  I even gave them names.  The big one is "Belly-marco."   How was your day?</Source>
      <Dest>然后我打了个盹然后又数了数我身上的线头，我甚至给它们起了名字。大点的这个叫“肚子上的马可”。话说回来你今天过得如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thought a learned how to conjure a new sword today, but it turned out it was the same one everyone else is using.</Source>
      <Dest>我正在思考今天刚学的召唤一把新的长剑的魔法，但是事实证明召唤出来的长剑和别人用的没啥区别。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Supposedly the sleep spell has a weakness which allows the Hagraven to access her treasure.</Source>
      <Dest>很可能那个睡眠魔法什么弱点让乌鸦鬼婆有机可乘以便取用她的宝藏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why, a homecooked meal of course!  What's in it?  Would you believe me if I said magic?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么，当然是一顿家常菜！里面有什么？如果我说有魔法你信不信？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If we can recruit him and the bard, I'd feel a lot more comfortable about our chances.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我们能招募他和那个诗人，我感觉我们承担的风险会更小点儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, nothing in life is guaranteed, save the end of it. I should note however that this halfwit was very detailed in his description of the Giant.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，生命里没有什么是有保证的，让我们试试做到最好。我再怎么也该注意到这个笨蛋对巨人的描述太过详细了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll still hate them of course.  I think I'll always be a bladebinder at heart.  But maybe a bladebinder who's one by choice, not by skill.</Source>
      <Dest>我当然还是恨他。我觉得自己会永远发自内心地做一个 bladebinder 。不过这 bladebinder 是一个选择，而不是技能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, but if we were smart, we wouldn't be adventurers. We would be scholars or librarians or some other horrifyingly dull occupation.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，如果我们够聪明的话，我们就不会是冒险者啦。我们可以是学者或是图书馆员或其他听起来高端却无趣的职业。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I digress. I was in Riverwood listening to this halfwit tell me about the story behind the Sleeping Giant Inn.</Source>
      <Dest>可是我开小差了，当时正在河木镇 听着这个弱智跟我讲沉睡巨人旅店的背景故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I never miss an opportunity to attribute my failings to others.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我不会错过任何一个把自己的失败归咎于他人的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I used to think so, but now that I'm thinking about learning more spells, I probably should describe them with a few less expletives.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，我以前也是这样，但现在我我在考虑多学些魔法的事儿，我形容它们应该少些脏话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or we can cook whatever you brought home.  You know, chewy, four-day old mystery meat.</Source>
      <Dest>或者我们能用你带回家的东西做顿饭。像是陈了四天根本嚼不烂的肉什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, if you by chance need a companion to share stories with, and occasionally a back to talk behind, you have mine.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你正好需要一个能与你分享你故事的人，或是想时不时转过身来聊两句，那么我就是那个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just the other day I was questioning my ability to lead when I realized how much easier it is to follow you instead.  See?  All your fault.</Source>
      <Dest>前两天我还挣扎着怀疑我的领导能力，现在我觉得跟着你来得简单多了。。你看，都是你的错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am glad you asked. It means we think on the same level, as that is precisely what I asked our halfwit friend.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴你这样问了。这意味着我们的智商好歹是在同一个水平面上，我就是这样问我们那个蠢货朋友的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have some friends in Morthal who told me there's some legendary hero who lives in the marsh and rides a Chaurus.</Source>
      <Dest>我有一些朋友住在墨索尔城，他们告诉我哪里有一些传说中的英雄骑着泥螃蟹生活在沼泽里.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, priests don't steal from the dead.  They do, however, steal from the living.</Source>
      <Dest>不，牧师才不会从死人那里偷东西。无论如何，他们要偷也是从活人身上偷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must not be a very good adventurer then, but you'd make an excellent priest.</Source>
      <Dest>你不会是个很好的冒险家，但你会成为一个好牧师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>According to him, all we need to do is play it a lullaby and we'll be able to rock the angry giant back to sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>照他的说法，我们只需要对着一个狂怒的巨人演奏摇篮曲就能让他安然入睡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>According to him, all we need to do is play it a lullaby and we'll be able to rock the angry giant back to sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>照他的说法，我们只需要对着一个狂怒的巨人演奏摇篮曲就能让他安然入睡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>According to him, all we need to do is play it a lullaby and we'll be able to rock the angry giant back to sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>照他的说法，我们只需要对着一个狂怒的巨人演奏摇篮曲就能让他安然入睡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which reminds me of an excellent con man I once knew.  All he did was dress in a monk's attire and people simply handed him their money.</Source>
      <Dest>这让我想起了我曾经认识的一个优秀的骗子。只要他一穿上修道士的衣服，人们就会不假思索的给他捐钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I have a friend who works the stables at Windhelm which serves as my unofficial home when I'm not wandering Tamriel.</Source>
      <Dest>Oh, 我有个朋友在风舵城的马厩工作在我不在泰姆瑞尔大陆的时候那就算是我临时的家.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why yes.  Earlier today I almost stepped on a spider, and when I opened the door to let it out some dust in the corner of there moved a bit.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，怎么啦？今天早些时候我差点踩到一只蜘蛛，当我打开门让它出去的时候那边角落的灰尘又挪动了一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright.  I think I know someone who can help teach you a spell.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我想我知道一个可以教你法术的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on Zora?</Source>
      <Dest>你对Zora有什么看法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on Zora?</Source>
      <Dest>你对Zora有什么看法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on Zora?</Source>
      <Dest>你对Zora有什么看法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A fine day is it not?</Source>
      <Dest>很棒的一天，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sentences?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么啦?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Companions Quest) You look like something's troubling you.</Source>
      <Dest>（同伴任务）你看起来有点困扰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Companions Quest) You look like something's troubling you.</Source>
      <Dest>（同伴任务）你看起来有点困扰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Companions Quest) You look like something's troubling you.</Source>
      <Dest>（同伴任务）你看起来有点困扰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Companions Quest) You look like something's troubling you.</Source>
      <Dest>（同伴任务）你看起来有点困扰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there any reason for the war paint?</Source>
      <Dest>这些战痕有什么特别含义吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there any reason for the war paint?</Source>
      <Dest>这些战痕有什么特别含义吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there any reason for the war paint?</Source>
      <Dest>这些战痕有什么特别含义吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Madanach's dead.  Markarth is free of the Forsworn.</Source>
      <Dest>Madanach死了，马卡斯城脱离了Forsworn掌控之下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Madanach's dead.  Markarth is free of the Forsworn.</Source>
      <Dest>Madanach死了，马卡斯城脱离了Forsworn掌控之下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Madanach's dead.  Markarth is free of the Forsworn.</Source>
      <Dest>Madanach死了，马卡斯城脱离了Forsworn掌控之下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I know one more mage that is a bit unorthodox.</Source>
      <Dest>据我所知，可不止一个法师踏上了异端的道路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That sounds incredibly dangerous.  I could kill you.</Source>
      <Dest>这听起来非常危险。我可以杀了你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure, why not.  Sounds like it could be some fun.</Source>
      <Dest>好啊好啊，听起来还真有点意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a wonderful idea.  You are full of great suggestions.</Source>
      <Dest>妙得一逼！你满是好点子啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a wonderful idea.  You are full of great suggestions.</Source>
      <Dest>妙得一逼！你满是好点子啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a wonderful idea.  You are full of great suggestions.</Source>
      <Dest>妙得一逼！你满是好点子啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you haven't lost your sense of humor.</Source>
      <Dest>见你还没丧失你那幽默感，真好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you haven't lost your sense of humor.</Source>
      <Dest>见你还没丧失你那幽默感，真好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you haven't lost your sense of humor.</Source>
      <Dest>见你还没丧失你那幽默感，真好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you haven't lost your sense of humor.</Source>
      <Dest>见你还没丧失你那幽默感，真好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay, there might be another mage that can help you.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，或许别的法师能帮上你的忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you haven't lost your sense of humor, my husband.</Source>
      <Dest>看到你没丧失幽默感这很好，我的丈夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you haven't lost your sense of humor, my husband.</Source>
      <Dest>看到你没丧失幽默感这很好，我的丈夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's good to see you haven't lost your sense of humor, my husband.</Source>
      <Dest>看到你没丧失幽默感这很好，我的丈夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could be right, but we can't take that chance.</Source>
      <Dest>你也许是对的，但是我们不能冒这个险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could be right, but we can't take that chance.</Source>
      <Dest>你也许是对的，但是我们不能冒这个险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could be right, but we can't take that chance.</Source>
      <Dest>你也许是对的，但是我们不能冒这个险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How should I know?  Ask one of the Greybeards.</Source>
      <Dest>要我怎么知道？你得去问灰胡子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How should I know?  Ask one of the Greybeards.</Source>
      <Dest>要我怎么知道？你得去问灰胡子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry, I got it.  Just shoot you in the face, er, feet.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，我懂的。只要击中你的脸，额，脚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't appear as if our strategy is working.</Source>
      <Dest>看上去我们的计划不怎么成功。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't appear as if our strategy is working.</Source>
      <Dest>看上去我们的计划不怎么成功。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't appear as if our strategy is working.</Source>
      <Dest>看上去我们的计划不怎么成功。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't appear as if our strategy is working.</Source>
      <Dest>看上去我们的计划不怎么成功。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>安卡诺死了，冬堡安全了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>安卡诺死了，冬堡安全了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>安卡诺死了，冬堡安全了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about in general? Do you know if there's any significance to war paint?</Source>
      <Dest>那一般而言呢？你知道关于战痕的意义吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about in general? Do you know if there's any significance to war paint?</Source>
      <Dest>那一般而言呢？你知道关于战痕的意义吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I guess that means you're not a Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜那意味着是你不是个梭默.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just concentrate and breathe deeply.</Source>
      <Dest>请集中精力并深呼吸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) There's only room for one on this trip.  But you look relieved.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 这趟旅程只有一个名额了。但你看起来好像松了一口气。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) There's only room for one on this trip.  But you look relieved.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 这趟旅程只有一个名额了。但你看起来好像松了一口气。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) There's only room for one on this trip.  But you look relieved.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 这趟旅程只有一个名额了。但你看起来好像松了一口气。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) There's only room for one on this trip.  But you look relieved.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 这趟旅程只有一个名额了。但你看起来好像松了一口气。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) There's only room for one on this trip.  But you look relieved.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 这趟旅程只有一个名额了。但你看起来好像松了一口气。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) There's only room for one on this trip.  But you look relieved.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 这趟旅程只有一个名额了。但你看起来好像松了一口气。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) There's only room for one on this trip.  But you look relieved.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 这趟旅程只有一个名额了。但你看起来好像松了一口气。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) There's only room for one on this trip.  But you look relieved.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 这趟旅程只有一个名额了。但你看起来好像松了一口气。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which is preposterous.  I'm very good at hidng my disgust.  Just not with this bug.  It was hideous.</Source>
      <Dest>荒唐. 我善于隐藏我的情感. 但对这虫子受不了. 太恶心了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And it's good to see you haven't lost your voice, with all that shouting you were asked to do.</Source>
      <Dest>在你吼完之后你居然还没哑，挺不错的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's a bit heavy on the meat, don't you think?  Last time I checked, the Companions didn't sign a Green Pact.</Source>
      <Dest>硬骨头啊，你不觉得么？上次我检查的时候，战友团还没有签署绿色条约。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She's charming enough, I suppose.  Although I think she's mad at me.  </Source>
      <Dest>她对于我来说已经够迷人的了。尽管我觉得她还在生我的气。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Relieved probably isn't the right word.  More like ecstatic.   You see, we're married, and as my spouse, I'd be obliged to follow you wherever.</Source>
      <Dest>如释重负可能不是个合适的形容，这更像是欣喜若狂。你瞧，我和我的爱人终于结婚了，我会心怀感激的跟着你到任何地方的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And you did just what I would have done.  It's good to have friends in high places, and the Silver-Bloods sit awfully high.</Source>
      <Dest>你只是做了我应该做的。有朋友在高层是很好的，而且银血家族的地位十分的高。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh I get it. You're trying to stir my survival instinct.  Yes, right in the face.  But not really.  You know what I mean.</Source>
      <Dest>哦我明白了。你试着挑起我的求生本能。是啊，全写在脸上了。但不怎么成功，你懂得。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But here I am, escaping on a technicality.  Now what am I going to do with all these excuses?</Source>
      <Dest>我通过一些手段逃脱了那里，但是我该怎么解释这一切呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But here I am, escaping on a technicality.  Now what am I going to do with all these excuses?</Source>
      <Dest>我通过一些手段逃脱了那里，但是我该怎么解释这一切呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, did you read my mind?  Or was it my facial expression?  I call this one, "Bemused."</Source>
      <Dest>喔，你能读懂我的思想?  或者我的面部表情？我把这个叫做”发呆。“</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure, Madanach was a King, but a King in Rags.  That's like being the Prince of Poverty or something.  I'm sure that's why you chose Thonar, right?</Source>
      <Dest>肯定， Madanach是一位国王，但是一位褴褛国王。或者是贫穷王子或者别的什么。我很肯定这就是你为什么选择了托纳尔，是这样么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, we could try one last thing. Otero once said if you want to learn to juggle swords, it does no good to practice with wooden ones.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，我们可以最后试试。奥特罗曾说过如果你想要学会如何驾驭剑，那就不该用木剑来练习。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Exactly.</Source>
      <Dest>就是这样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You should solicit me for advice more often. I have all sorts of opinions on all kinds of topics.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该多问问我的观点。对于任何话题我都有很多要说的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But there's something about mages like Ancano that really pestles my mortar.  They're always looking down on us bladebinders.</Source>
      <Dest>但是有些像安卡诺那样的巫师真烦。他们总是看不起我们召唤武器的法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know what they say, second time's the charm.  Or was it the third time?  Does that mean this next one will be a failure too?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道他们是怎么说，两次。或者，第三次？这是不是意味着下次也会失败？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's rather perceptive of you.  I'm actually an inch shorter than the average High Elf.  Wait, that came out wrong.  Well, you know what I mean.</Source>
      <Dest>你还真是颇有洞察力啊。我的确是比普通的高精灵矮上那么一英寸。等等，那么说貌似有点儿不对。呃，你懂我的意思吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You mean do two things at the same time?  And fashion a ward?  Hmm...it's almost like juggling.  And I'm only half terrible at that.  Let's do this.</Source>
      <Dest>你的意思是在同时做两件事吗？还得制造一个结界？嗯……这几乎像是在玩儿杂耍。我对你的建议感觉不错。让我们来干吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did you plug your ears when you shouted Alduin down?  I have to say there were plenty of times out on the road I wish I had.</Source>
      <Dest>在你把奥杜因吼下来的时候塞上自己的耳朵了吗？我得说在路上有很多次我都希望自己捂上耳朵了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I'm not a real mage.  So what?  At least I'm still alive.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是一个真正的法师，那又怎样？至少我还活着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not that I wouldn't be willing to make it work.  Or that I only care about your body.  Did I mention how much I love you and that I'm glad your home?</Source>
      <Dest>我并不是不希望它能够顺利运作起来，我只是更担心你的身体。我有表达过我对你的爱有多深以及对你平安回来有多么地喜悦么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I don't want you to actually hit me.  I just want you to aim near my feet.   You can do that, right?</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我不是想让你真的对着我打，我只希望你能瞄准我的脚附近。你能做到的，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>None whatsoever, although someone once told me a dash under the eyes blocks the glare from the sun. So does a hood.</Source>
      <Dest>完全不是，虽然有人曾经告诉我，在眼睛下面画道线可以阻挡太阳的光线。兜帽也是一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In the Summerset Isle, paint can serve as a family crest or be worn as a form of art, which I believe led to the development of rouge and blush.</Source>
      <Dest>在夏景群岛省，涂料可以充当一个家徽，或者作为一种行为艺术来穿戴，因此我相信这就是导致口红和腮红发展蒸蒸日上的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The first part being more enjoyable than the last part, I bet.  Not that saving the College isn't important to somebody.</Source>
      <Dest>我打赌，第一部分比最后一部分更为愉快。对某些人来说，拯救学院并非无关紧要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That means sleeping, frolicking, and eating.  Now, I don't mind doing the same, but I'm wondering if we can do something about the menu.</Source>
      <Dest>那意味着吃喝玩乐睡。我现在不介意做同样的事情，但我在想是否能在菜单上做点儿什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure, they've all been altered to mimic whatever you want to hear, but that doesn't make me a lap dog.  It just means I'm attentive.</Source>
      <Dest>的确，他们都受训来模仿任何你想听到的声音，不过这并不意味着我是个爱奉承的家伙。这恰恰说明我比较体贴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am?  I mean, of course I am!  It all comes from having a wealth of experience and an extremely finicky stomach.</Source>
      <Dest>我么？没错,正是本人！这一切都是源于丰富的各类经验还有一副挑剔至极的唇舌。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh?  Who is it?  It's not General Tullius is it? That would be a shocker.</Source>
      <Dest>哎呦?这是谁啊?这不是图留斯将军吗?这太令人震惊了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But really, you don't need me.  I hear Alduin only eats worlds.  You're not a world, are you?  Then you'll be fine.</Source>
      <Dest>但说真的，你用不着我的。我听说奥杜因只会吞噬世界。你又不是”世界“，你会没事的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But really, you don't need me.  I hear Alduin only eats worlds.  You're not a world, are you?  Then you'll be fine.</Source>
      <Dest>但说真的，你用不着我的。我听说奥杜因只会吞噬世界。你又不是”世界“，你会没事的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Relieved probably isn't the right word.  More like ecstatic.   You see, I consider us friends, and as friends, I'd be obliged to follow you wherever.</Source>
      <Dest>用解脱这个词也许不合适，更像是狂喜。你看，我认为我们是朋友了，作为朋友，你让我跟你去哪我都乐意之至。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, I do have a quarrel.  It's just that since you've joined the Companions, I feel like you'll be spending more time here.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说，我确实有些恼怒。这仅仅是因为你已经加入了战友团，我觉得你会在这里花更多的时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, food for thought, in case this horn turns out to be, you know, the kind dremora have on their heads.</Source>
      <Dest>这值得慎重考虑，万一这号角最终被查明是，你知道的，dremora头上的那种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is going to sound crazy, but maybe if you pummeled me with a spell, my survival instinct will kick in and I'll fashion a ward.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来真疯狂，但如果你往我身上扔魔法，我的生存本能就会启动，我会立即躲开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which I already have!  So no harm, no foul.  </Source>
      <Dest>我已经有了！所以不算犯规。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No...it's almost as if I don't have the talent to be anything more than a bladebinder...but that would mean I'm not perfect.</Source>
      <Dest>不……貌似我没有任何超过武器召唤者的天赋……而这意味着我不是完美的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A stunning revelation.  I never saw it coming.</Source>
      <Dest>一个惊人的发现。我真没想过这种事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It took days to get rid of the ringing.  I would've used a potion, but I lost it in a game of iron hearts.  Plus I didn't want to offend you.</Source>
      <Dest>我没有冒犯你的意思。我花了好几天才从耳鸣里解脱出来。我本来想用些药水治疗的，但是我在铁心赌博里把它们都输掉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In some parts of Tamriel, war paint is seen as a tribal mark for warriors. </Source>
      <Dest>在泰姆瑞尔的一些地方，战纹被视作战士们所属部族的标记。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This mage has to be the one.  I mean, it's not as if I'm some one trick bladebinder wearing imitation robes.  That would be a shocking twist.</Source>
      <Dest>这个法师可能就是那个人了。我是说，他不像我，穿着法袍却用召唤剑肉搏。这样的剧本会是一个神转折。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It would just help if you could explain it to me, me being dumber than a snowberry and all.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我需要你和我解释一下。我可比雪浆果之类的笨多啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd probably just get in your way.  And you're strong enough to do this on your own.  See?  That was two of my better ones.  But I've got more.</Source>
      <Dest>我快要赶上你了。而你足够强壮去自己做这事儿。明白了吗？这是两个我最好的人了，但我现在要多有一个了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd probably just get in your way.  And you're strong enough to do this on your own.  See?  That was two of my better ones.  But I've got more.</Source>
      <Dest>我快要赶上你了。而你足够强壮去自己做这事儿。明白了吗？这是两个我最好的人了，但我现在要多有一个了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, there isn't any downside to taking the guard at his word.  Other than maybe building a deep-seeded mistrust of all Nord guards.</Source>
      <Dest>确实用他的话说服守卫再好不过了。 除了可能会使所有的诺德守卫产生不信任.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh know, I'm not falling for that.  You heard what Arngeir said.  I talk to one of them and I'll probably die.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，知道了，我不会上当的。你听到arngeir说。我和其中的任一个交谈就会死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which is a good thing right? It's not like that army of Forsworn you just unleashed is much of a threat, is it?</Source>
      <Dest>你刚解放的那股弃誓者军队没有那么有威胁，不是吗？是个好事呢，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Better than the last.</Source>
      <Dest>比最后一名好点儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, you've convinced me.  There's a dragon out there.  And coincidentally, something warm running down my leg.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我说服我了。外头有头龙，而且更巧的是，我的腿还在流血。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, I don't like your tone.  You do realize I want you to aim at my feet, right?  Suddenly I'm wondering if you got that part.</Source>
      <Dest>等会,我不喜欢你说话的语气。你明白我是想让你瞄着我的脚，对吧？ 这让我开始好奇你是否有脚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They may not have signed the Green Pact, but I have.</Source>
      <Dest>他们可能还没签署那绿色条约，但是我已经签了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They may not have signed the Green Pact, but I have.</Source>
      <Dest>他们可能还没签署那绿色条约，但是我已经签了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He's all but skeever bait now. Any other ideas?</Source>
      <Dest>他现在差不多成了雪鼠的食料了。还有别的主意吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there any reason for the war paint?</Source>
      <Dest>这些战痕有什么特别含义吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is there any reason for the war paint?</Source>
      <Dest>这些战痕有什么特别含义吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Excellent. The bandits will soften him up, and he'll do whatever we ask.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，那些土匪会让他服软的，到时候我们说什么他都得听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you sad to see Honningbrew out of business?</Source>
      <Dest>你看到蜂蜜酒地破产难过吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you sad to see Honningbrew out of business?</Source>
      <Dest>你看到蜂蜜酒地破产难过吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you sad to see Honningbrew out of business?</Source>
      <Dest>你看到蜂蜜酒地破产难过吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you sad to see Honningbrew out of business?</Source>
      <Dest>你看到蜂蜜酒地破产难过吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you sad to see Honningbrew out of business?</Source>
      <Dest>你看到蜂蜜酒地破产难过吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you okay? The skeletons must have surprised you.</Source>
      <Dest>你没事吧？那些骷髅是不是吓了你一跳。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you okay? The skeletons must have surprised you.</Source>
      <Dest>你没事吧？那些骷髅是不是吓了你一跳。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you okay? The skeletons must have surprised you.</Source>
      <Dest>你没事吧？那些骷髅是不是吓了你一跳。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you okay? The skeletons must have surprised you.</Source>
      <Dest>你没事吧？那些骷髅是不是吓了你一跳。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Except Maven hates Honningbrew Mead.  I believe she called it "bile."</Source>
      <Dest>只是玛雯讨厌 Honningbrew Mead. 我确信她叫它 "胆汁"。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Except Maven hates Honningbrew Mead.  I believe she called it "bile."</Source>
      <Dest>只是玛雯讨厌 Honningbrew Mead. 我确信她叫它 "胆汁"。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Except Maven hates Honningbrew Mead.  I believe she called it "bile."</Source>
      <Dest>只是玛雯讨厌 Honningbrew Mead. 我确信她叫它 "胆汁"。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're in denial.   You're trying to cope with your fear.</Source>
      <Dest>你在抗拒。你正在努力掩饰你的恐惧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're in denial.   You're trying to cope with your fear.</Source>
      <Dest>你在抗拒。你正在努力掩饰你的恐惧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're in denial.   You're trying to cope with your fear.</Source>
      <Dest>你在抗拒。你正在努力掩饰你的恐惧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I cringe at Zora all the time.  Have you seen her face?  It's horrifying.</Source>
      <Dest>我一直害怕佐拉。你见过他的脸吗？真是太可怕了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I cringe at Zora all the time.  Have you seen her face?  It's horrifying.</Source>
      <Dest>我一直害怕佐拉。你见过他的脸吗？真是太可怕了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay. My plan is to kill every bandit we see until we find him.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧. 我的计划是干掉每一个强盗 直到我们找到他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not a world, but people think the world of me.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是我的世界，但人们认为这是我的世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not a world, but people think the world of me.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是我的世界，但人们认为这是我的世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not a world, but people think the world of me.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是我的世界，但人们认为这是我的世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not a world, but people think the world of me.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是我的世界，但人们认为这是我的世界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So we're basically going to have to rescue a pile of bones.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我们基本上是去救一堆骨头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't realize you were so sensitive.</Source>
      <Dest>我不理解你为什么如此敏感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't realize you were so sensitive.</Source>
      <Dest>我不理解你为什么如此敏感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't realize you were so sensitive.</Source>
      <Dest>我不理解你为什么如此敏感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about in general? Do you know if there's any significance to war paint?</Source>
      <Dest>那一般而言呢？你知道关于战痕的意义吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about in general? Do you know if there's any significance to war paint?</Source>
      <Dest>那一般而言呢？你知道关于战痕的意义吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't look too concerned about the dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>你好像对龙什么的毫不在意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't look too concerned about the dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>你好像对龙什么的毫不在意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't look too concerned about the dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>你好像对龙什么的毫不在意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't look too concerned about the dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>你好像对龙什么的毫不在意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maybe with a better design it would look fierce.  Yours look like whiskers.</Source>
      <Dest>也许一个更好的化妆会让它看起来更凶残。你这看起来就跟胡子似的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Maybe with a better design it would look fierce.  Yours look like whiskers.</Source>
      <Dest>也许一个更好的化妆会让它看起来更凶残。你这看起来就跟胡子似的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry about it.  Zora's tougher than she looks.</Source>
      <Dest>不用担心。佐拉比她的外表厉害得多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't worry about it.  Zora's tougher than she looks.</Source>
      <Dest>不用担心。佐拉比她的外表厉害得多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thonar locked me up.  But revenge wasn't worth letting Madanach free.</Source>
      <Dest>Thonar害我进了监狱。不过就为报仇也不值得放Madanach出去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a matter of fact, we did.  It was when your back was turned.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我们做了。那是在你转过身去的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a matter of fact, we did.  It was when your back was turned.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我们做了。那是在你转过身去的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a matter of fact, we did.  It was when your back was turned.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我们做了。那是在你转过身去的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you know it's a gimmick, why buy them yourself?</Source>
      <Dest>你要是知道里面有问题，为什么还要自己买下来？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you know it's a gimmick, why buy them yourself?</Source>
      <Dest>你要是知道里面有问题，为什么还要自己买下来？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you know it's a gimmick, why buy them yourself?</Source>
      <Dest>你要是知道里面有问题，为什么还要自己买下来？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have an idea where these bandits took him?</Source>
      <Dest>强盗们把他带到哪儿去，你有线索吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you have an idea where these bandits took him?</Source>
      <Dest>强盗们把他带到哪儿去，你有线索吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well consider the fact that bandits are twice as naive as the average customer looks. Thus one ruse leads to another.</Source>
      <Dest>考虑到事实上那些强盗比一般顾客看上去还要蠢上一倍。要用另一种法子来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I hope this one still has some pages to read.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我还没看够呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Knifepoint Ridge, was the name, over in Falkreath.  If he's alive, we'll find him there.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他还活着，我们能在佛克瑞斯的刀剑山脉中找到他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I may not be able to discuss it, but I can still give you a look of disapproval.   See if you can read this one.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，虽然我能给你意见，不过可以给你一个不赞成的表示。看你能否读得懂我的表情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Honningbrew was that drink.  I just don't get why Maven couldn't keep Sabjorn on her payroll and just re-brand his mead as "Black-Briar Golden."</Source>
      <Dest>那种饮品叫做蜂蜜酒。我只是不明白为什么玛雯不直接雇佣撒布乔恩，而是把他的蜜酒重新打上”Black-Briar Golden“的商标。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay,  you've convinced me.  There's a dragon out there.  And coincidentally, something warm running down my leg.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，你说服我了。外面有一条龙。巧合的是，有一股温热的液体顺着我的腿流下来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, do we really take this guard at his word?  Maybe he wants an excuse to get off his shift.</Source>
      <Dest>我是说，我们真的要怪这个守卫说错话了吗？也许他是想找个接口翘班呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you sure?  Although I suppose that doesn't make her tough.  Ants are tougher than they look, but I can still squish them easily enough.</Source>
      <Dest>你确定？虽然我不认为那会使她变得粗暴。蚂蚁也比外表看起来要更粗暴，可我要捏死它们还是很轻松。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, but I don't think Alduin eats metaphors.  If he did, nobody would give two septims about his diet.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，但我不认为奥杜因会食言。如果他真的破坏了预言，也没人会愿意奖励他的节食的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, the name's Rumarin.  Professional adventurer, bladebinder, and grave robber.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说，我叫罗米勒。专业冒险家，召唤武器家，盗墓专家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sure that was the jealousy talking.  It's like adopting someone else's child.  They're only a brat until they you're own.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢肯定那是出于嫉妒才说的话。就行就像要收养别人的孩子，在孩子成为你自己的之前，他们在你看来只是个乳臭未干的熊孩子一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I guess I'm being too literal.  You're saying she can handle a cringe or two.  Which is precisely the answer I wanted to hear.  No harm done.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我太认真了，你说她会表演滑稽戏剧。我爱听这个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It doesn't come with quite the same prestige as say, a robe from the College of Winterhold.</Source>
      <Dest>冬堡学院来的法师像传闻中那样有威望的嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>More than an idea. I know the exact location of their hideout. I was pretending to be his bodyguard when he made the deal.</Source>
      <Dest>不只是个点子而已。我知道他们藏身之处的准确位置。以前他做生意的时候我是扮作保镖的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh right.  Religion.  One of three topics I love to not discuss, next to politics and Ulundil's unfortunate haircut.</Source>
      <Dest>哦,对了。宗教。我不喜欢讨论的话题之一，就像政治和Ulundil的倒霉发型一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although maybe rags are like coin for savages.  They'll certainly keep you warmer at night.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然说破布头之于我们就像赛普汀于之蛮族一样无价值，但在漫漫寒夜之中它们还是能驱走你的寒意的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not that these robes are only good for conjuring a story.  The enchantment is far from spectacular, but on occasion it does help me conserve magicka.</Source>
      <Dest>这些法袍并不只在编造故事的时候好用。在关键时刻，它们能帮我节省法力值。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, not every High Elf is a wizard, and not every spell is designed for sorcery.  Of course, it's kind of my fault for playing along.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道吗，并不是每个高精灵都是巫师，也并不是每个法术都是为魔法师设计的，当然，好像是我的错，因为我一直执着于此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At least, that's what I'd say if I didn't think whiskers were a compliment.  Which they are.</Source>
      <Dest>至少，如果我不认为“刮胡人”是一种恭维我就会这么说。不过它们其实是一种恭维。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, I'll be with you in spirit, which is another way of saying I'll be at the tavern drinking.  Good luck.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我的精神与你同在，这其实是”我会在酒馆儿喝酒“的另一种说法。祝你好运。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe it's not too late.  I can see it now.  Maven says "Sorry I ruined your business Sabjorn, but your mead was just too tasty!"</Source>
      <Dest>也许还为时不晚。现在我明白了。玛雯说 “抱歉我毁了你的生意撒布乔恩，但你的蜜酒实在是太美味了！”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But no, I suppose I get a bit defensive when someone asks me whether "I know magic."</Source>
      <Dest>不是，当有人问我是否懂得魔法的时候，我会变得有一些抗拒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What are you, my priest?  Because if you are, then who was the lady who cured my witbane?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么人，我的祭祀吗？如果你是，那治好我脑残的那位女士又是谁啊？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe she was just some crazy person.  Maybe I still have witbane.  </Source>
      <Dest>或许她只是疯了而已，又或许只是我的魔障症还没治好。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And the bloodthirsty murderers and savages we unleashed on The Reach?  Just a means to an end.</Source>
      <Dest>在瑞驰把嗜血的凶手跟未开化的野人放了出来？只是达到目的一种手段而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey, I didn't study war paint application for 10 years at the Lythandus school in Cheydinhal to be mocked by an amateur! Good day!</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，我在香丁赫尔的Lythandus学院学了十年战斗迷彩的应用可不是为了被一个外行嘲笑的！日安！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, especially when it comes to my gangly figure and my nirnroot collection.  Mock that and I'm a liable to end up in tears.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，特别是谈到我修长的身材和我收集的奈恩根时。别人嘲笑我这些方面的时候，我的小泪腺实在是把持不住。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, in many parts of the world, excessive makeup is nothing more than an indicator that you will service genitalia for gold.  </Source>
      <Dest>当然了，在很多其他地方，浓妆艳抹不过是表示你愿意提供性交易来的暗示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I guess you've noticed, I'm not so great at goodbyes.  Otero told me it was like the end of a story.  Like closing a book. </Source>
      <Dest>你应该注意到了，我不是那么喜欢分离，奥特罗告诉我分手就好像故事的结尾，好像合上一本书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I'm not disagreeing with you.  I totally get it.  I'd kill all of the townsfolk for personal satisfaction.  That's just the way the Gods made me.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我并不是在反对你。我很理解。我也会为了个人欲望的满足而把镇子里的人杀个干干净净的。我就是为此而生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I had a septim for every time a guard lied to get off work, I'd have like, a hundred septims.  </Source>
      <Dest>如果一枚金币每次都能骗到一个守卫让他下班，我想要一百个金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I'm fine.  Don't worry, that's not blood on my face, it's makeup.  No, I'm sorry, "war paint."</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我没事。不要担心,我脸上没血，这只是化妆，不，我很抱歉，“战痕”.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I'm sure there will be plenty of guts, blood, flesh...and what's the other thing? Oh right, scales!  I almost forgot about the scales.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我敢肯定会有很多的内脏，鲜血，生肉……其他还有什么？哦，该死，鳞片。我总是会忘记那些鳞片。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if we're being completely honest, I'm inclined to agree.  I try and stare at the space between her eyebrows.  That helps.</Source>
      <Dest>坦白说，我比较同意你的说法。我试过，盯着她的眉心看。真的起作用了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am.  I'm a very picky person, and it's very hard to find a Nord beverage that suits my palate.</Source>
      <Dest>是的。我是一个非常挑剔的人，能找到一瓶合乎我口味的诺德饮料真是太难了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, just to say something like, "Look Rumarin, one of the Gods of all creation, Jephre, has come to Jorrvaskr for lunch and tea."</Source>
      <Dest>比如，你只要说说"看那 Rumarin, 创世诸神之一： Jephre, 来到了月瓦斯卡用餐喝茶。“</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unfortunately I'm not familiar with bound armor spells, and I've yet to find a book on the subject in my travels across Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>不幸的是我不会束缚铠甲咒语，并且游遍整个天际我也没能找到记载它的法术书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe that's not a lot of gold, but it's a lot of lies.</Source>
      <Dest>或许这并不是很大一笔钱，但这是用一大堆谎言换来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Keep your voice down!  You do realize she's standing right there, don't you? Although I'm not sure she can hear us.  Too many blows to the head.</Source>
      <Dest>你小点声儿！你明明知道她就站在那儿，不是吗？虽然我不确定她能听见我们。脑袋被打傻了吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are they magical rags?  Well, in that case, I suppose they might be worth something.  Although I still would be cautious in wearing it.</Source>
      <Dest>他们是附魔的麻衫吗？呃，在这种情况下，我想他们可能有些价值。虽然对我来说，穿还是不穿，这是个问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And besides, there wasn't enough room on my skin purse to begin with.  So I decided to paint my face instead.</Source>
      <Dest>更何况，我的皮包上实在是没有足够地方来绘画。所以我决定还是画花我的脸吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know if that's true, by the way, but it sounds like it would be.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道这是不是真的，顺便一提，它听起来跟真的一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Leave it to me to miss out on everything.</Source>
      <Dest>我为了他错过了一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh right.  I suppose you couldn't have just tapped me on the shoulder?</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。但你就能不只拍拍我的肩膀吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We could do that. Or we could go to Knifepoint Ridge. The bandits he was dealing with kind of live there. Your choice though.</Source>
      <Dest>我们能行。或者我们可以去刀尖山脊。强盗们会解决掉所有活着的东西。总之这是你的选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good idea, although he really is only good at forgery. I mean, we could ask him to tell us bad jokes, but then I'd be out of a job.</Source>
      <Dest>好主意, 尽管他只擅长造假. 我是指, 我们能叫他给咱们讲烂笑话, 但那时我或许失业了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And Sabjorn would say, "Is that the reason?  I thought you just didn't like me.  Why didn't you say so sooner!" </Source>
      <Dest>然后撒布乔恩就会说，“这就是一切的原因？我还以为你仅仅是不喜欢我。你怎么不早说！” </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can suggest she bargain with Sabjorn now that he has no leverage.  Just remind her how popular Honningbrew is with the Elves.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以建议她和撒布乔恩讨价还价，既然他现在已经没有利用价值了。记得提醒她蜜酿酒是多么受到精灵的欢迎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I could try forging whatever it is you need myself.  I can do a perfect forgery of an Elven bladebinder. Anything else, we'll need his help.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我能试着给你锻造一些你想要自己用的东西。我能伪造一个完美的精灵剑鞘。至于别的什么的，我们就得找他帮忙了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should do your duty and clear an area of bandit scum.</Source>
      <Dest>尽你的责任，做掉一片区域的强盗人渣吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should do your duty and clear an area of bandit scum.</Source>
      <Dest>尽你的责任，做掉一片区域的强盗人渣吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should do your duty and clear an area of bandit scum.</Source>
      <Dest>尽你的责任，做掉一片区域的强盗人渣吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Given how often we break the law, let's hope we don't run into this zealot.</Source>
      <Dest>想象我们是怎样轻松平常地违反法律, 还是希望我们不要遇到这样的狂热者吧.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is the rightful land of the Forsworn.  I did what I did on principle.</Source>
      <Dest>这是弃誓者的合法土地，我只会按自己的规则办事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is the rightful land of the Forsworn.  I did what I did on principle.</Source>
      <Dest>这是弃誓者的合法土地，我只会按自己的规则办事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It wouldn't hurt to look for him.</Source>
      <Dest>找到他不会伤害他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, that's more than we can say for Ancano.</Source>
      <Dest>关于安卡诺，一言难尽.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, that's more than we can say for Ancano.</Source>
      <Dest>关于安卡诺，一言难尽.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, that's more than we can say for Ancano.</Source>
      <Dest>关于安卡诺，一言难尽.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wonder if his waste was sent to another time.</Source>
      <Dest>我想知道下次他的垃圾会被送到哪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My dear, I think you're more of a snowberry than a banana.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的，我觉得你比起香蕉来更像个雪浆果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My dear, I think you're more of a snowberry than a banana.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的，我觉得你比起香蕉来更像个雪浆果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My dear, I think you're more of a snowberry than a banana.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的，我觉得你比起香蕉来更像个雪浆果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's a musical horn.  It makes music.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一个角笛，可以吹出曲子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's a musical horn.  It makes music.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一个角笛，可以吹出曲子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's a musical horn.  It makes music.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一个角笛，可以吹出曲子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can the Nord who made your robes do handwritten forgeries?</Source>
      <Dest>那个给你做袍子的诺德人能伪造签名吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can the Nord who made your robes do handwritten forgeries?</Source>
      <Dest>那个给你做袍子的诺德人能伪造签名吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can the Nord who made your robes do handwritten forgeries?</Source>
      <Dest>那个给你做袍子的诺德人能伪造签名吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can the Nord who made your robes do handwritten forgeries?</Source>
      <Dest>那个给你做袍子的诺德人能伪造签名吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can the Nord who made your robes do handwritten forgeries?</Source>
      <Dest>那个给你做袍子的诺德人能伪造签名吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You wear the robes of a college mage.</Source>
      <Dest>你穿着一所魔法学院的衣服。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You wear the robes of a college mage.</Source>
      <Dest>你穿着一所魔法学院的衣服。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There must have been leaves. You always have to have a plan.</Source>
      <Dest>就像树上一定有叶子一样。你总是必须有一个计划。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There must have been leaves. You always have to have a plan.</Source>
      <Dest>就像树上一定有叶子一样。你总是必须有一个计划。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Elder Knowledge) It looks as if we have to retrieve an Elder Scroll.</Source>
      <Dest>（上古知识）看来我们得拿回上古卷轴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Elder Knowledge) It looks as if we have to retrieve an Elder Scroll.</Source>
      <Dest>（上古知识）看来我们得拿回上古卷轴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like to hear these excuses.</Source>
      <Dest>我倒想听听这些借口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like to hear these excuses.</Source>
      <Dest>我倒想听听这些借口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like to hear these excuses.</Source>
      <Dest>我倒想听听这些借口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like to hear these excuses.</Source>
      <Dest>我倒想听听这些借口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a shame.  I enjoy tongue jousting.</Source>
      <Dest>真丢人。我喜欢口舌之战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a shame.  I enjoy tongue jousting.</Source>
      <Dest>真丢人。我喜欢口舌之战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Forsworn are a blight on the Reach. Madanach got what he deserved.</Source>
      <Dest>弃誓者是邊塞領的毒瘤。Madanach得到了他应得的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Forsworn are a blight on the Reach. Madanach got what he deserved.</Source>
      <Dest>弃誓者是邊塞領的毒瘤。Madanach得到了他应得的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And you were his understudy? Remind me never to hand you an Elder Scroll.</Source>
      <Dest>以及你是他的候补？哦我不会把上古卷轴交给你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And you were his understudy? Remind me never to hand you an Elder Scroll.</Source>
      <Dest>以及你是他的候补？哦我不会把上古卷轴交给你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And you were his understudy? Remind me never to hand you an Elder Scroll.</Source>
      <Dest>以及你是他的候补？哦我不会把上古卷轴交给你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That story couldn't possibly be true.</Source>
      <Dest>那个故事不可能是真的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That story couldn't possibly be true.</Source>
      <Dest>那个故事不可能是真的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This mad dark Elf. Is his name Raynes?</Source>
      <Dest>这个发疯的黑暗精灵。他的名字是不是瑞纳斯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're not exactly a serious Elf, are you.</Source>
      <Dest>你不真的是个严肃的精灵吧，不是么.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Horn of Jurgen Windcaller) Looks like we have some fetching to do.</Source>
      <Dest>(约根唤风者的号角) 看样子我们得取些东西了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Horn of Jurgen Windcaller) Looks like we have some fetching to do.</Source>
      <Dest>(约根唤风者的号角) 看样子我们得取些东西了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I defeated Alduin.  Sovngarde is safe.  The world is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>我打败了奥杜因。松加德安全了，全世界得救了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I defeated Alduin.  Sovngarde is safe.  The world is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>我打败了奥杜因。松加德安全了，全世界得救了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I defeated Alduin.  Sovngarde is safe.  The world is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>我打败了奥杜因。松加德安全了，全世界得救了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I defeated Alduin.  Sovngarde is safe.  The world is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>我打败了奥杜因。松加德安全了，全世界得救了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I defeated Alduin.  Sovngarde is safe.  The world is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>我打败了奥杜因。松加德安全了，全世界得救了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I defeated Alduin.  Sovngarde is safe.  The world is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>我打败了奥杜因。松加德安全了，全世界得救了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I defeated Alduin.  Sovngarde is safe.  The world is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>我打败了奥杜因。松加德安全了，全世界得救了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I defeated Alduin.  Sovngarde is safe.  The world is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>我打败了奥杜因。松加德安全了，全世界得救了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think you're more of a snowberry than a banana.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得比起香蕉来，你更像个雪浆果。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think you're more of a snowberry than a banana.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得比起香蕉来，你更像个雪浆果。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I think you're more of a snowberry than a banana.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得比起香蕉来，你更像个雪浆果。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>See, you can say that because we're friends.  And because you're the Dragonborn.  And because I have a sense of humor about myself.</Source>
      <Dest>瞧,你可以说那是因为我们是朋友，还可以说因为你是龙裔，还能说因为我很有幽默感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As is Alduin's stomach.  You did him a favor as far as I'm concerned, because from what I hear this world is rotten to the core.</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因的胃啊，你实在帮了他一个大忙，因为据我所知这世界已经烂到根子上了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, so I made some of those up.  Maybe all of them, but the point is, you didn't give me any time to make up some good ones.</Source>
      <Dest>好，我搞定了一部分，或者全部。但重点是，你没给我足够的时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, here's a question.  If Jurgen Windcaller was the first Greybeard, that means he had a pretty powerful voice, right?</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，现在有个问题：如果Jurgen Windcaller是史上首位灰胡子，那也就是说他的龙吼应该很强，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if he also lied about the night he bedded seven wenches and a Countess because they were fond of his cartwheels.</Source>
      <Dest>我很怀疑他是否在他那个和七个女孩还有伯爵夫人上床的故事里面也说谎了。他说她们为了他的优雅炫目而着迷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What if he got carried away during a rendition of Ragnar the Red?  I've seen it happen before.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他在演奏红衣拉格纳的时候被带走怎么办？我见过这种事发生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why I leave the tough moral quandaries to you.  It saves me from all the thinking and absolves me of all the blame.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我把难缠的道德难题留给了你解决，那样我才摆脱了一切思考和责任。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, here's a few more.  "I'll be with you in spirit."  "Bound weapons don't work in Sovngarde."  "I slept with Odahviing's sister."</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，这里还有几句：“我的心与你同在。”“召唤武器在松加德用不了。”“我跟奥达威英的妹妹睡过。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh I agree. The Forsworn are a wicked bunch. All that murdering and pillaging and stuff. And having a Silver-Blood on your side is never a bad thing.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，我同意。弃誓者是一群邪恶的人。他们烧杀抢掠无恶不作。另外，和银血家族站在一边准没错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My theory is the horn isn't the kind you blow, but you know, the kind a dremora wears on his head.  Just some food for thought.</Source>
      <Dest>我的理解是那个号角不是你吹的那种，应该是，你见过的魔人头上顶的那种角吗，像那样的。这是个耐人寻味的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I totally agree.  An Elf is nothing without his scruples.  Although having a purse full of rubies would be nice too.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我完全同意。虽然一个精灵总能够无所顾虑。但是有一个装满红宝石的钱包总比口袋空空好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which makes you the spouse of a crazy person.  Now you'll think twice before scolding me for sticking gold coins up my nose.</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让你如此疯狂？ 在你把金币朝我鼻子扔前，你应再三考虑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look, I think it's obvious I want you to succeed.  And if it came down to it, I'd be willing to fight by your side.  No, I'd be honored to.</Source>
      <Dest>听着，很显然我是想让你成功的。如果你有需要，我很愿意成为你的左膀右臂。说真的，我很渴望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do know an Argonian who does excellent forgeries. I once asked him to make a Jarl's decree that pies were a type of vegetable.</Source>
      <Dest>我倒是认识一个擅长偷龙换凤的亚龙人。有一回我还让他给我弄了一张领主令呢，上面说的是“馅饼是一种蔬菜”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Never pick up anything that isn't worth at least 10 times its weight.  It's a rule all good adventurers should live by.</Source>
      <Dest>永远不要捡起任何价值低于它重量十倍的物品。这是每个优秀的冒险家的座右铭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why we work well together.  We think on the same level.  Always finishing each other's...finishing each other's...</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我们为什么一起工作。我们总是想到一起。总是互帮互助…总能互帮互助…</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>See, you can say that because we're married.  And because you're the Dragonborn.  And because I have a sense of humor about myself.</Source>
      <Dest>看吧，你可以说这是因为我们结婚了。或者因为你是龙裔。或者是因为我有一种自嘲的幽默感。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, don't say his name out loud. If you say it three times, he'll visit you in your nightmares and stick a dagger up your nose or something.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，别那么大声说他的名字。如果你说了三遍，他就会进到你的噩梦里，再用匕首割掉你的鼻子啥的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I would visit the apothecary to treat my blindness.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我会去请药剂师医治我的失明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Needless to say I never liked him.  He reminds me of every mage who ever looked down on me for being a bladebinder.</Source>
      <Dest>不用说，我从没喜欢过他。他让我想起了一个因为我是个束刃者就瞧不起我的法师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If that's the case, why does he need a horn?</Source>
      <Dest>如果是这样的话，他为什么需要一个号角？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not that I don't mind cleaning for you.  Did I mention how much I love you and that I'm glad your home?</Source>
      <Dest>不，我不介意帮你打扫屋子。我有没有提到过我是多么的爱你。。。还有我多么很高兴你终于回家了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I don't even own a horse, so there's that.</Source>
      <Dest>我甚至没有自己的马，所以就是这样了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So he was a bard of some sort?  That's a dangerous profession for someone who can shout you to death.</Source>
      <Dest>那他是个吟游诗人啥的喽？让一个唱歌唱得听众哭爹喊娘的人当吟游诗人还真是难为他啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anyway, good to have you back.  I imagine you'll want to rest for a bit, but I'll be here if you need someone for your adventures.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说，你能回来真是太好了。我想你可能需要休息一段时间，不过如果你需要一个一同冒险的人的话，我随时在这等着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I'll have to settle for having been with you until now.  That alone should fetch me a free drink or two at the tavern.  Good luck.</Source>
      <Dest>但一直跟你到现在，已经令我满足了。这件事情本身就值得在酒馆换取一杯，两杯免费的酒水。祝你好运。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As is Alduin's stomach.  My love, you did him a favor as far as I'm concerned, because from what I hear this world is rotten to the core.</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因的胃啊，亲爱的，你实在帮了他一个大忙，因为据我所知这世界已经烂到根子上了。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, although there might be a significant bounty in it for us. Do bandits put out bounties? Like on guards they don't like? It would only be fair.</Source>
      <Dest>强盗知道城里在通缉他们，但是强盗不会因为惧怕赏金就不惹事，就如同守卫不会因为盗贼不惹事就不会贴悬赏，这样才公平。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But would that make the world a fruit?  People always say the world can be eaten but I'm not so sure.</Source>
      <Dest>但是那会使世界变成水果吗？人们总是说世界可以被吃掉但是我不怎么确定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But would that make the world a fruit?  People always say the world can be eaten but I'm not so sure.</Source>
      <Dest>但是那会使世界变成水果吗？人们总是说世界可以被吃掉但是我不怎么确定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wouldn't that be something. It's like "Hey, there's Ysgramor! And wow, is that a Snow Elf? And look over there, it's Otero's droppings!"</Source>
      <Dest>真是不可思议。这就像是 "嘿，伊斯格拉谟！哇哦，那是只雪精灵吗？看那边，奥特罗拉出的粑粑！"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow. An Elder Scroll. Otero used to tell me a story about how he found one while out in the woods.</Source>
      <Dest>哇噢，上古卷轴。Otero 经常跟我讲他是怎么在野外发现这么个玩意的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which makes you the friend of a crazy person.  Now you'll think twice before scolding me for sticking gold coins up my nose.</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让你如此疯狂？下次你骂我财迷之前我希望你可以多考虑一下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He also does a bit of crafting.  Of course, I heard he ran into a bit of trouble stitching together guard uniforms for a group of bandits.</Source>
      <Dest>他也做一点手艺的。当然，我听说他在为一群强盗裁缝守卫制服时遇到了一点麻烦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And while some see bandits as walking trunks of loot, the loot they carry is heavy, and goes against my personal code.</Source>
      <Dest>人们把强盗看成是会走路的赃物口袋，那些赃物重得很，而且跟我的个人品味差太远了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, my skin is a golden yellow, and I'm fairly skinny. I could tell you I'm a banana, but that doesn't mean it's true.  I could just be insane.</Source>
      <Dest>我是说，我的皮肤是耀眼的金黄，我的身材也一级棒。告诉你其实我是根香蕉，那也不一定是真的。也许只是我疯了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, my skin is a golden yellow, and I'm fairly skinny. I could tell you I'm a banana, but that doesn't mean it's true.  I could just be insane.</Source>
      <Dest>我是说，我的皮肤是耀眼的金黄，我的身材也一级棒。告诉你其实我是根香蕉，那也不一定是真的。也许只是我疯了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The point is to convince naive patrons the enchantments were performed by a master.  They are not.</Source>
      <Dest>关键是要说服那帮天真的老主顾们，那附魔是来自于一位大师。而事实上根本不是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What did he do with it? Well, he used it to wipe his arse. There really wasn't any other choice, being so far away from the stream.</Source>
      <Dest>他拿这干什么? 嗯~, 他拿它擦屁股. 还真没那么多其他可能, 在离河流那么远的地方.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not that it doesn't form an appealing visual, but if we actually did joust with our tongues, we'd likely crack our skulls.</Source>
      <Dest>这一点也不有趣，如果我们真的用舌头来决斗的话，我们的脑袋估计得碎掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Him? Oh no, he's a bit daft when it comes to writing. Besides, he's too busy making curved swords.</Source>
      <Dest>他？哦不，在谈及写作的时候，他是有那么一丁点儿蠢。此外，他太忙于打造弧形的剑了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I didn't adopt everything Otero taught me.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，看来我没能吸纳奥特罗教给我的所有东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only duty I have is to myself, and he would rather be healthy and alive.  </Source>
      <Dest>我只对自己负有责任，他也许会健康地活下去的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Apparently they weren't good enough to trick some mad Dark Elf who hunts lawbreakers.</Source>
      <Dest>显然他们还不足以哄骗那些疯狂的黑暗精灵偷猎者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not quite.  These are actually a cheap imitation, woven and enchanted to look like their more esteemed counterpart.</Source>
      <Dest>不完全正确。这些实际上是廉价的仿造品和编织物，被人施加了魔法所以看上去很像真品。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not Otero. He was the type to scamper off into the woods and figure things out later.</Source>
      <Dest>不是奥特罗。他是那种先逃进森林然后再想到底是怎么回事儿的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Besides, regardless of where you are, you can always find something to wipe your unmentionables. And he did. It just happened to be an Elder Scroll.</Source>
      <Dest>另外，不管你在哪儿，你永远都能找到方法弄干你的内衣。他也那么做了。只不过这次弄干的是一个上古卷轴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I imagine it's going to hurt either way. At least, for him. Bandits aren't the gentlest of forest creatures.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我觉得两条路线都会受伤，至少就他而言如此。强盗可不是森林里最绅士的生物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if the body's lying around somewhere.  I wouldn't mind raising him from the dead and having him fetch our flagons.</Source>
      <Dest>我在想，那尸体就该躺在附近吧。我不介意复活他然后得到他的酒壶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know what? It does sound suspiciously like a lie.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道么？那听起来很可疑就跟个瞎话一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And here I thought you were the type who fancies males.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾认为你是那种中意男性的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And here I thought you were the type who fancies males.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾认为你是那种中意男性的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You picked up conjuring weapons just like that?</Source>
      <Dest>你就是这样拿魔法武器的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You picked up conjuring weapons just like that?</Source>
      <Dest>你就是这样拿魔法武器的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's not what I meant.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是那个意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's not what I meant.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是那个意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's not what I meant.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是那个意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good.  Now you don't have to pretend bladebinders actually exist.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，你现在不用再假装bladebinders真的存在了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think you'll be able to learn other spells this way?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为你能这样学其他的法术？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think you'll be able to learn other spells this way?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为你能这样学其他的法术？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think you'll be able to learn other spells this way?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为你能这样学其他的法术？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think you'll be able to learn other spells this way?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为你能这样学其他的法术？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think you'll be able to learn other spells this way?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为你能这样学其他的法术？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is that a jest?  Or do you fancy other males?</Source>
      <Dest>是个玩笑吗？还是你真的喜欢男人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is that a jest?  Or do you fancy other males?</Source>
      <Dest>是个玩笑吗？还是你真的喜欢男人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, and once your friends are there to hold you back, you charge ahead.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，并且一旦你的朋友让你回去，你会义无反顾地回去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, and once your friends are there to hold you back, you charge ahead.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，并且一旦你的朋友让你回去，你会义无反顾地回去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A High Elf with a sense of humor. I like you.</Source>
      <Dest>有着幽默感的高精灵。我喜欢你。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sabjorn's in prison.  If he got out, he'd just start making more mead.</Source>
      <Dest>Sabjorn在牢里。如果他出去的话，肯定已经着手酿更多的蜜酒了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sabjorn's in prison.  If he got out, he'd just start making more mead.</Source>
      <Dest>Sabjorn在牢里。如果他出去的话，肯定已经着手酿更多的蜜酒了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sabjorn's in prison.  If he got out, he'd just start making more mead.</Source>
      <Dest>Sabjorn在牢里。如果他出去的话，肯定已经着手酿更多的蜜酒了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh stop complaining you bloody thumb-drinker.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，别抱怨你的伤了，你这吮指头的货。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh stop complaining you bloody thumb-drinker.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，别抱怨你的伤了，你这吮指头的货。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh stop complaining you bloody thumb-drinker.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，别抱怨你的伤了，你这吮指头的货。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We're on Maven's good side.  Now's not the time to start making demands.</Source>
      <Dest>我们都收了玛雯的好处，现在不是向她提要求的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We're on Maven's good side.  Now's not the time to start making demands.</Source>
      <Dest>我们都收了玛雯的好处，现在不是向她提要求的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We're on Maven's good side.  Now's not the time to start making demands.</Source>
      <Dest>我们都收了玛雯的好处，现在不是向她提要求的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, Thalmor invasions are always on time.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，梭默入侵总是很准时。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, Thalmor invasions are always on time.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，梭默入侵总是很准时。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hope not.  I would love the chance to gut a dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>但愿不是这样，我更乐意得到摧毁一条龙的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hope not.  I would love the chance to gut a dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>但愿不是这样，我更乐意得到摧毁一条龙的机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you had any strength, your weapons would never be a burden.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你有力量，你的武器永远不会成为你的负担。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you had any strength, your weapons would never be a burden.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你有力量，你的武器永远不会成为你的负担。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An excellent idea.  Well, except for the fact Sabjorn would die first.</Source>
      <Dest>好主意。好吧，除了Sabjorn会先死的那部分事实以外。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An excellent idea.  Well, except for the fact Sabjorn would die first.</Source>
      <Dest>好主意。好吧，除了Sabjorn会先死的那部分事实以外。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An excellent idea.  Well, except for the fact Sabjorn would die first.</Source>
      <Dest>好主意。好吧，除了Sabjorn会先死的那部分事实以外。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you know any other magic besides conjuring weapons?</Source>
      <Dest>除了召唤出武器你还会什么魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you know any other magic besides conjuring weapons?</Source>
      <Dest>除了召唤出武器你还会什么魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you know any other magic besides conjuring weapons?</Source>
      <Dest>除了召唤出武器你还会什么魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Excellent.  Hopefully you will last longer in battle now.</Source>
      <Dest>好极了，希望你在战斗中能坚持更久。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Excellent.  Hopefully you will last longer in battle now.</Source>
      <Dest>好极了，希望你在战斗中能坚持更久。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Conjured weapons are noisy, take too long to draw, and can't be enchanted.</Source>
      <Dest>召唤武器的声音很刺耳，准备的时间又长，又不能附魔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Conjured weapons are noisy, take too long to draw, and can't be enchanted.</Source>
      <Dest>召唤武器的声音很刺耳，准备的时间又长，又不能附魔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bandits are an excellent form of exercise.  You should be luring them.</Source>
      <Dest>强盗们是多好的陪练呐。你应该主动勾引他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bandits are an excellent form of exercise.  You should be luring them.</Source>
      <Dest>强盗们是多好的陪练呐。你应该主动勾引他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bandits are an excellent form of exercise.  You should be luring them.</Source>
      <Dest>强盗们是多好的陪练呐。你应该主动勾引他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bandits are an excellent form of exercise.  You should be luring them.</Source>
      <Dest>强盗们是多好的陪练呐。你应该主动勾引他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't be foolish.  Nord guards are paragons of integrity.</Source>
      <Dest>别傻了。诺德人的卫兵都是正直诚实的模范。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't be foolish.  Nord guards are paragons of integrity.</Source>
      <Dest>别傻了。诺德人的卫兵都是正直诚实的模范。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't be foolish.  Nord guards are paragons of integrity.</Source>
      <Dest>别傻了。诺德人的卫兵都是正直诚实的模范。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Don't be foolish.  Nord guards are paragons of integrity.</Source>
      <Dest>别傻了。诺德人的卫兵都是正直诚实的模范。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Congratulations.  You are officially a mage.</Source>
      <Dest>恭喜恭喜，你正式成为一个法师了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good.  It isn't healthy for adventurers to get too close to each other.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。冒险者之间靠得太近的话不利于健康。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good.  It isn't healthy for adventurers to get too close to each other.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。冒险者之间靠得太近的话不利于健康。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Size isn't everything.  A lesser than lesser ward is good enough.</Source>
      <Dest>大小不能决定一切。越小的结界防御力越强。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Size isn't everything.  A lesser than lesser ward is good enough.</Source>
      <Dest>大小不能决定一切。越小的结界防御力越强。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So it's not the gift so much as the thought.  Keep that in mind when I give you this paltry reward.</Source>
      <Dest>所以说，这与其说是礼物，不如说是思考。在我给你这微不足道的奖励的同时，把它铭记在心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's always been my strategy for brawls.  Although it doesn't work too well when you travel alone.</Source>
      <Dest>这一直是我打架的策略，尽管当你独自旅行时它不是那么顶用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So that explains your getup, I suppose?  Or rather, it doesn't.  Unless that's how wealthy nobles dress in this part of Tamriel.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这就解释了你的装束？然而确切的说，这是不行的。除非是有钱的贵族在泰姆瑞尔大陆穿着它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>More importantly, we both learned a lesson.  Leave the spellcasting to real mages, and the invisible swords to me.   </Source>
      <Dest>更重要的是，这事给我们都上了一课。把魔法留给真正的法师去用，把无形的剑留给我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I do not fancy myself a conjurer, I fancy myself a bladebinder.  </Source>
      <Dest>不，我一点都不喜欢自己是个巫师。我更喜欢幻想自己是一名束刃武士。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean look at me.  Do I look like a mule to you?  No wait, don't answer that.  I'm rather sensitive about my figure.</Source>
      <Dest>我说你好好看着我，我长得像驮行李用的骡子吗？哦别说，不用回答啦。我对自己身材的问题可是很敏感的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ooh, that came out wrong.  Saying "I fancy myself" sounds like I want to be alone in a room with nothing but a mirror.</Source>
      <Dest>哦……不是这样的。说什么”我为自己代言“，弄得好像我想在一间只有镜子的房间里顾影自怜一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe now, while the wound is fresh.  But give him some time behind bars, and he'll come around.</Source>
      <Dest>或许是现在，在那创伤尚未平复的时候。不过还是给他一点时间吧，他会自己过来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, it's not just a preference.  There's a practical aspect to it.  Meat makes me feel sluggish.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，那不只是一种偏好。而是有原因的。吃肉让我感觉反应迟钝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yes, it's perfect for an ice spike.  All I have to do is line it up right at the needle point.  Shouldn't be too hard for someone of my skill.</Source>
      <Dest>噢是的，对于一个冰棘来说刚刚好。我所需要做的就是把那些顶点连起来。对我这样的天才来说应该不是什么问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's kind of scary.  I'm not really into that sort of blood and guts stuff, but maybe if I vomit constantly you'll see that I'm trying to do my part.</Source>
      <Dest>这太可怕了。 我并没有真的沉浸到那些血液和内脏中去，但也许如果我经常呕吐话，那就是你发现我在做我份内之事的时候.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, but I do.  Males, females, beasts, goats, the list goes on and on.  I'm not a particularly picky Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>哦不，我是认真的。男性，女性，野兽，山羊，还有很多其他的。我不是一个挑剔的精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look, I'm grateful for everything you've done.  Not many people would've gone this far to help a friend.</Source>
      <Dest>看着。我很感激你做过的任何事情。不是所有人都会千里迢迢来帮助一个朋友的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But honestly, the size of the ward is really only enough to protect one nipple.  Which begs the question...left or right?</Source>
      <Dest>但说实话，结节的大小真的仅仅只够保护一个乳头，这就引出一个问题了。是保护左边的……还是右边？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?  You don't want to slay it, or just chase it away, but gut its belly?  That's a rather visceral description. </Source>
      <Dest>是吗？你不想杀掉它，或是仅仅把它赶走，却还能把它的内脏挖出来？这真是一个发自肺腑的想法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm following you in order to increase my chances of survival.  I'm perfectly capable of dying on my own.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在跟着你来增加我活下去的可能。如果我是独自一人的话肯定已经死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What I'm trying to say is that High Elves are born with an affinity for magic.  A head start, if you will, in the skill of hand waggling.</Source>
      <Dest>我要说到的是高精灵生来就具有对魔法的亲和力。比其他种族在操纵手指的技巧方面出色一些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, but suppose Maven decided to strike a bargain with him.  She could pin the crime on Mallus and free Sabjorn in exchange for his service.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，假如玛雯想和他计较。她会把罪名栽赃给马鲁斯，然后把萨布乔恩放出来作为他为她跑腿的回报。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>See, we can't disagree on the weather, and unlike politics, when it comes to cuisine nobody is forcing anything down each other's mouth.</Source>
      <Dest>看见了吗，我们不能就天气问题达成一致，但说到美食，这可不同于政治，谁也不能强人所好呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I confess I don't like billies.  You're not a billie, are you?  Well, if you are, I'll still do it, but it's going to cost extra.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然我承认我不喜欢守卫。你不会是守卫吧？你是么？算了，如果你是我照样会做，但那就不止这点钱了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I confess I don't like billies.  You're not a billie, are you?  Well, if you are, I'll still do it, but it's going to cost extra.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然我承认我不喜欢守卫。你不会是守卫吧？你是么？算了，如果你是我照样会做，但那就不止这点钱了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Remember, I'm a bladebinder.  I conjure weapons because I don't want to carry them.  The same is true for a bulging stomach.</Source>
      <Dest>记住，我是束刃者。我之所以召唤武器是因为我不想带着他们。对于鼓起来的肚子来说也同样正确。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only loser would be Mallus, but he creeps me out anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>唯一的失败者只会是莫鲁斯，但是他依然让我毛骨悚然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That, I'm afraid, requires more than being born with your ears pointed skyward.  That requires...ugh...studying.</Source>
      <Dest>这个，我恐怕，需要的不仅是天赋。这个需要的是....额.....学习。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh no, I'm going to stay in my fantasy land with the other delusional folk.  You should come over. It's much warmer and there's mermaid and unicorns.</Source>
      <Dest>哦不，我要和其他妄想之人生活在我幻想的国度。你应该过来。这儿很温暖，还有人鱼和独角兽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll just evade the question thank you and focus on more agreeable questions, like the weather, the temperature, and the local food.</Source>
      <Dest>多谢你我刚刚回避了那个问题以讨论更让人惬意的话题，比如天气，冷暖，以及本地小吃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You forgot impermanent, magicka draining, and the fact that they only come in one color.  Still, you don't have to carry them.</Source>
      <Dest>你还漏了它们是非永久的，消耗魔法的，而且只有一种颜色。不过好处是你不需要携带它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know about you, but the idea of slogging from town to town with a weapon rack strapped to my back is not my idea of an adventure.</Source>
      <Dest>我不了解你，但这种把武器架绑到我的背上，苦哈哈的从一个城镇走到另一个城镇的主意，可不符合我对冒险家的美好印象。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As a result, the other day I was caught in the embarrassing predicament of confusing a hunter with a noble, and vice versa.</Source>
      <Dest>结果，在不久前的某天我陷入了分不清猎人和贵族或是贵族和猎人的令人尴尬的窘境。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh wait, is it?  I don't even know when I'm being sarcastic anymore.   I forget which dead animals exemplify status in this province.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，等等，是吗？我都不知道什么时候我说话又带上了嘲讽的语气。我差点忘了那些死去的动物就是这个省现状的例证。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Next time I get any bright ideas, just ignore me.  But thanks for listening this one time.</Source>
      <Dest>我要感谢你这次能听我的.但是下次我再有主意得话，就请直接无视我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, there's the problem.  I have skill, not strength.  I have speed, but no stamina.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，问题就在这儿。我有技巧，但缺少力量。我有速度，但是缺乏耐力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, you've convinced me.  There's a dragon out there.  And coincidentally, something warm running down my leg.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么说，你说服我了。外面有条龙，巧合的是，我觉得我尿裤子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But only if you think it's a good plan.  That's why I'm running it by you first.  I wouldn't know a good idea if it urinated on my leg.</Source>
      <Dest>但是除非你认为那是个好计划。这就是为什么我让你先从头捋一遍，如果这货尿到我腿上我可没什么好点子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, let's not get carried away.  I'm still a bladebinder first.  I'm just a wardbinder on my days off.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，我还是别得意忘形了。我首先是个武器召唤师。至于防护召唤我只是个业余的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look, two minutes is a perfectly acceptable amount of time for someone of my age and stature.  Besides, I was distracted the last time.</Source>
      <Dest>喂，两分钟的时间对于我这样的年龄和身份而言可是完全合理的。另外，上次我被分神了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever seen an Elf juggle three axes while conjuring a fourth?  Tie a cherry stem into a knot with their tongue?  Now that's magic.</Source>
      <Dest>见过一个精灵在耍着三把斧头的同时还召唤了第四把吗？见过他们会把一根樱桃木跟舌头打个结吗？那就是魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps. The real question is, do I want to? After what we went through to learn this one, I'd say the answer is a resounding no.</Source>
      <Dest>也许吧。真正的问题是，我是不是想要？为了得到这个答案我们经历了这么多，我想最终的回答是个坚定的不。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I assume you are referring to the schools of magic traditionally taught in places like the College of Winterhold.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，我认为你是指传统上的魔法学校，就像冬堡学院这样的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I guess you have a point.  Admittedly, I am sort of biased by all the inane banter they make.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你是对的.对于他们那些无聊空洞的玩笑，我并不感冒.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I was thinking you could float it out there.  Like "I can't believe there's actually wealthy nobles who swear by Honningbrew.  What fools!"</Source>
      <Dest>不，我在想其实你现在就可以说出来。比如说“我才不相信那些权贵会以Honningbrew起誓。太蠢了！”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just throw in a word with the cook if you can.  Blame it on the "stupid Elf," and then point at me and I'll wave or something.</Source>
      <Dest>可以的话你去和厨师唠两句。把事情怪罪给“愚蠢的精灵”，然后指指我，我会挥挥手什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I wasn't suggesting we demand it.  I like not having the Dark Brotherhood on my back.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我希望我们不用那样做。我可没有黑暗兄弟会来做后盾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh I know, but I learned that discussing politics and religion is an exercise in futility.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，我知道的，但据我所知，讨论政治和宗教是件很没意义的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know if that's true, by the way, but it sounds like it would be.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道这是不是真的，但是它听起来跟真的一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, what were we talking about again?</Source>
      <Dest>等下。刚才我们说什么来着？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The folks here really ought to carry signs so I know who to be courteous to.</Source>
      <Dest>这里的人们真该带着标识好让我知道我该对谁表示礼貌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, but so is the Empire. The Stormcloaks are the only ones who come late to the party.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，但是帝国也是如此。风暴斗篷是聚会上唯一迟到的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But what they lack in punctuality they make up for with surliness.</Source>
      <Dest>但他们用粗暴弥补了他们的不守时。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Males, females, beasts, goats, the list goes on and on.  I'm not a particularly picky Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>雄的，雌的，野兽，山羊，清单没完没了。我可不是个特别挑剔的精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Because...we're all going to die?  That doesn't really motivate us, now does it? </Source>
      <Dest>因为……我们都会死？那可没激励我们，是吧？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you become an adventurer?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么成为一个冒险者的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you become an adventurer?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么成为一个冒险者的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you become an adventurer?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么成为一个冒险者的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you become an adventurer?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么成为一个冒险者的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you become an adventurer?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么成为一个冒险者的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We could just buy you some scrolls.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以给你买点卷轴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We could just buy you some scrolls.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以给你买点卷轴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He wore it as a hat.</Source>
      <Dest>他把它当帽子来戴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Valgus should be able to help you.</Source>
      <Dest>威尔格斯应该能帮你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, there's one mage who happens to live in a sewer.  Dagri'lon.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，碰巧有位法师住在下水道里。叫Dagri'lon.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did that relationship develop?</Source>
      <Dest>你们是如何认识的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did that relationship develop?</Source>
      <Dest>你们是如何认识的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did that relationship develop?</Source>
      <Dest>你们是如何认识的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did that relationship develop?</Source>
      <Dest>你们是如何认识的的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did that relationship develop?</Source>
      <Dest>你们是如何认识的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're different than most High Elves I've met.</Source>
      <Dest>你和我见过的大部分高精灵很不同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're different than most High Elves I've met.</Source>
      <Dest>你和我见过的大部分高精灵很不同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're different than most High Elves I've met.</Source>
      <Dest>你和我见过的大部分高精灵很不同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's just crazy enough to be the stupidest idea ever.</Source>
      <Dest>那是一个疯狂至极且愚蠢到爆的主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's just crazy enough to be the stupidest idea ever.</Source>
      <Dest>那是一个疯狂至极且愚蠢到爆的主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I haven't met anyone that fits your description.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我没见到任何一个符合你描述的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I haven't met anyone that fits your description.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我没见到任何一个符合你描述的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Mugnor's a college mage, but she's crazy.</Source>
      <Dest>玛格抐是个学院法师，不过她不怎么正常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Mugnor's a college mage, but she's crazy.</Source>
      <Dest>玛格抐是个学院法师，不过她不怎么正常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bound armor spells are very 3rd Era.  Now mages prefer alteration shields.</Source>
      <Dest>绑定护甲法术已经过时了，如今法师们更喜欢变换系的护盾法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bound armor spells are very 3rd Era.  Now mages prefer alteration shields.</Source>
      <Dest>绑定护甲法术已经过时了，如今法师们更喜欢变换系的护盾法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bound armor spells are very 3rd Era.  Now mages prefer alteration shields.</Source>
      <Dest>绑定护甲法术已经过时了，如今法师们更喜欢变换系的护盾法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How about an underground guild full of gutter wizards?  Not informal enough?</Source>
      <Dest>一个到处都是低劣的巫师的地下公会怎么样？过于非正式了么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How about an underground guild full of gutter wizards?  Not informal enough?</Source>
      <Dest>一个到处都是低劣的巫师的地下公会怎么样？过于非正式了么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Meals?</Source>
      <Dest>开饭了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Imitation robes?  Is it some sort of black market operation?</Source>
      <Dest>冒牌法袍？这是什么黑市的路子吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Imitation robes?  Is it some sort of black market operation?</Source>
      <Dest>冒牌法袍？这是什么黑市的路子吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Imitation robes?  Is it some sort of black market operation?</Source>
      <Dest>冒牌法袍？这是什么黑市的路子吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Imitation robes?  Is it some sort of black market operation?</Source>
      <Dest>冒牌法袍？这是什么黑市的路子吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Imitation robes?  Is it some sort of black market operation?</Source>
      <Dest>冒牌法袍？这是什么黑市的路子吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not everyone can do both conjuration and alteration.  Most can't do either.</Source>
      <Dest>并不是所有人都会召唤和变换。大部分人只会其中一种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, tomes tell us how to cast magic, but does anyone really know how it works?</Source>
      <Dest>我是说，法术书能教会我们如何施放法术，但是有人真正知道其中的原理么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Admit it, you love my childish antics.  Can you imagine how dreadful life would be if you had to wake up every morning next to a humorless sod?</Source>
      <Dest>承认吧，你喜欢我的风格。你能想象每天早上醒来面对着一个毫无幽默感的世界是多么可怕的人生么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Admit it, you love my childish antics.  Can you imagine how dreadful life would be if you had to wake up every morning next to a humorless sod?</Source>
      <Dest>承认吧，你喜欢我的风格。你能想象每天早上醒来面对着一个毫无幽默感的世界是多么可怕的人生么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that went about as poorly as one could expect.  I need to make a mental note:  Orcs are surly.</Source>
      <Dest>唉，勉勉强强就那么回事儿吧。让我们铭记一条真理：兽人无比残暴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I'd say it's more like taking a sabrecat pelt, washing it with an oil and salt mixture, then using an enchantment to make the coat Khajiit soft.</Source>
      <Dest>不，要我说更像是取一张剑齿虎皮，用油盐混合剂洗过之后，通过附魔让它柔软得像虎人的皮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I guess what I'm saying is, no mages were hurt in the sewing of this robe.  Although maybe the college's reputation gets taken down a notch.</Source>
      <Dest>我想说的是，没有法师会因袍子上的缝纫物而受伤，但或许学院的名誉就因此而蒙上一层阴影了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As to where I bought them, that's a bit of a secret.  I used to know a Nord man who was blessed with the gift of forgery.</Source>
      <Dest>我就是在那儿买的，这是个小秘密。我曾经认识一个诺德男人，他有上天赋予的铸造天赋</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yes, your egomaniacal corpse friend.  Somehow I don't think this is going to be entirely painless.</Source>
      <Dest>哦是的，你这极端利己的僵尸小伙伴。我并不认为这将是完全无痛的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Admit it, you love my childish antics.  Can you imagine how dreadful life would be if your adventuring companion was some mindless atronach?</Source>
      <Dest>认了吧，你喜欢我的幼稚的举动。 你能想象如果和你冒险的同伴只是一些愚蠢的石像，那会是多么可怕的生活吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you're curious, you can ask me, because I know.  I'm married to one.  </Source>
      <Dest>如果你好奇的话，其实可以问我，因为我对婚姻很了解。我已经结婚了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you're curious, you can ask me, because I know.  I'm married to one.  </Source>
      <Dest>如果你好奇的话，其实可以问我，因为我对婚姻很了解。我已经结婚了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Naturally I was terrified.  But Otero rose up, looking fat and half drunk, and warned the bandits to leave, or die.</Source>
      <Dest>我当然害怕了。但Otero站了起来，看起来酒意半酣又满腹油脂，他警告强盗要么离开这里，要么死在这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wouldn't have it been better to see her first?  Not that I'd ever question you.  Well, back to Winterhold then.</Source>
      <Dest>先去看她难道不是更好么？我并不是在质询你。好的，那么返回冬堡吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We need to find a place that's the opposite of that.  Like a college built by sewer mages.</Source>
      <Dest>我们需要找到的是一个与此相反的地方。比如被下水道的法师们修建的学院。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And be a paper mage?  Oh Gods no, I still have my pride.  </Source>
      <Dest>成为一个学术法师可不是一个好选择，九圣灵啊，我还是有作为战士的骄傲的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?  Here I thought you knew everyone.  Or was that Ulundil?  I get you two confused sometimes, because I have poor eyesight.</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗?我以为你知道在这儿的每一个人。还是乌伦迪尔 ？有时我分不清你们两个。因为我的视力不好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He knew my favorite book was Withershins, and he would often converse with me in the order of the alphabet, much to our company's chagrin.</Source>
      <Dest>他知道我最喜欢的书是《逆时针》，所以他老是跟我讨论类似的话题。这让我们的同伴十分窝火。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is probably not the best place for me to learn anyway.   Winterhold is a traditional institution.</Source>
      <Dest>这里也许不是我进行研习的好选择，冬堡是一个传统而古板的学院。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What I meant is, mages who had sort of an unorthodox education.  Do you know anyone like that?</Source>
      <Dest>我所说的是，没有受过一系列非传统教育的法师，你知不知道有谁是这样的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All kidding aside, I'm sure that person is out there.  We'll find them eventually.</Source>
      <Dest>说真的，我很确定有人在那边。我们最终会找到他们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They never saw the blade appear in his hand. I never saw a fat man act so swift. That's when I learned how truly disarming laughter really was. </Source>
      <Dest>他们从未见他手中有剑。而我从未见过有哪个胖子能如此敏捷。正是从那时起我才知道“无敌意”的微笑的意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We just need to find a mage who's a little more unorthodox than the ones here.  Do you know anyone like that?</Source>
      <Dest>我们只需要找一个不那么因循守旧的魔法师。你认识那样的人吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was a series of stories, each more uproarious than the last.</Source>
      <Dest>那是一系列笑话，一个比一个好笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say there's a book on conjuration so abstruse that only two scholars can understand it and both disagree on the meaning.  Vehemently.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说，有一本召唤书极其深奥，只有两个学者能看懂，而且两人理解出来的意思还不一致......那可是相当地不一致。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Otero wasn't like other jesters who got cheap laughs from doing somersaults and wearing a hat with bells.</Source>
      <Dest>奥特罗跟其他那些依靠翻筋斗和带铃铛帽子惹人发笑的小丑不一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although granted it would make opening urns a lot more harrowing.</Source>
      <Dest>不过我想掀开骨灰罐的感觉确实会更痛苦一些吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That makes it sound so sinister, like some place you buy fur coats made from Khajiit pelts.</Source>
      <Dest>这让它听起来很邪恶的样子，好像某个卖虎人毛皮做成皮衣的黑市。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think it was a lesser ward!  Although you can't really call it that. Maybe a lesser than lesser ward.  Or the least ward.  But still, a ward.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得这是一个小防护魔法。尽管你不会这么认为。或许比小防护魔法还要小，但是即便是最小的防护魔法，它也仍然是防护魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course he can.  And if he can't well, it'll be his fault.  I like Olivia's way of thinking.</Source>
      <Dest>他当然能。要是他做得不好，那就是他的错。奥莉薇雅这种思路我喜欢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No really, you're wonderful, savior of Skyrim and all that.  You might want to stop with the insults though.  Not everyone finds them attractive.</Source>
      <Dest>那不是真的，你很棒，你拯救了天际和所有的一切。虽然你可能想要制止侮辱。不是每个人都能发现他们有吸引力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No really, you're wonderful, savior of Skyrim and all that.  You might want to stop with the insults though.  Not everyone finds them attractive.</Source>
      <Dest>那不是真的，你很棒，你拯救了天际和所有的一切。虽然你可能想要制止侮辱。不是每个人都能发现他们有吸引力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, that was a frightening experience.  The Nords should really consider burning their dead.</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，那经历太可怕了。诺德人真应该好好考虑一下实行火葬的可行性。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I know one person who's willing to suffer this fool.  And she's standing right in front of me.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我知道有人乐意和这蠢材打交道。她就站在我面前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I know one person who's willing to suffer this fool.  And she's standing right in front of me.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我知道有人乐意和这蠢材打交道。她就站在我面前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, you're getting warmer.  I was thinking it was a Dremora horn.  That's right Jurgen Windcaller was a dremora.  It's just a theory, anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，你看起来暖和些了.  我认为那是个Dremora 的号角.  也许 Jurgen Windcaller 是一个 dremora. 这仅仅是我的猜想罢了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, but now that you mention it, you did eat one of the sweet rolls I was saving.  I wasn't going to say anything, but you brought it up.</Source>
      <Dest>不,说起来, 你把我存起来的甜卷吃了. 我之前没有追究你, 但是你现在又让我回忆起来了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, at least we won't have to go very far.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，至少我们不用走太远。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Robes from Winterhold, fake scimitars from Hammerfell, there is nothing this craftsman could not build.  Well, except a personality.</Source>
      <Dest>从冬堡的长袍，到打造落锤省的弯刀，这个铁匠没什么不能造的。嗯，除了定制产品的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The bandits took one look at the sweaty, rotund Nord and roared.   "Shut up and empty your coin sack, jester," one of them cried.</Source>
      <Dest>强盗们看一眼就乐弯了腰，圆滚滚的诺德人哈哈笑。“闭嘴吧小丑，破财免灾了，”其中的一个高声叫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He often talked of his homeland, how it was the most humorless place in all of Tamriel.</Source>
      <Dest>他经常会提及他的家乡，那儿绝壁上整个泰姆瑞尔大陆最没幽默感的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Probably not, I mean, they're still a guild. That would make them organized.</Source>
      <Dest>也许不是，我是说，他们仍然是一个公会。这会让他们团结起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was the jester to whom I gravitated to, a Nord man named Otero.  </Source>
      <Dest>那是一个我喜欢的小丑，是个诺德人，叫奥特罗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He talked of how it needed laughter.  How laughter was the essence of joy, how it could disarm even the most guarded of men.  </Source>
      <Dest>他说大笑的重要性。说大笑是快乐的核心，即使最戒备的守卫也会因大笑而放松警惕。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The road is a hard place. I learned that the day Otero took me aside to test his new act.</Source>
      <Dest>此路难于登天。I learned that the day Otero took me aside to test his new act.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, maybe not mages that actually live in sewers. That would mean we'd have to actually go in one, and I just washed this robe.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，也许不是那些下水道的法师。但那意味着我们得亲自到那些下水道里找吧，我才把我的长袍洗了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think...I think I did it!  I mean, it was smaller than a juniper berry but I actually felt the ward coming out of my hand!  It worked!</Source>
      <Dest>我想……我想我做到了！我是说，它比杜松果还小但是事实上我觉得结界正在从我的手中产生！成功了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I know one person who's willing to suffer this fool.  And he's standing right in front of me.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我知道谁能忍受这个傻逼了。他就站在我面前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's a bladebinder?</Source>
      <Dest>bladebinder是什么</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's a bladebinder?</Source>
      <Dest>bladebinder是什么</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's a bladebinder?</Source>
      <Dest>bladebinder是什么</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's a bladebinder?</Source>
      <Dest>bladebinder是什么</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's a bladebinder?</Source>
      <Dest>bladebinder是什么</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you don't like grave robbers, don't put gold in your coffin.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你不喜欢盗墓贼，那就别在棺材里放金子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would you classify yourself as a witchblade or spellsword then?</Source>
      <Dest>你会把自己归结为一名女巫剑士呢还是个魔法剑士呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would you classify yourself as a witchblade or spellsword then?</Source>
      <Dest>你会把自己归结为一名女巫剑士呢还是个魔法剑士呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would you classify yourself as a witchblade or spellsword then?</Source>
      <Dest>你会把自己归结为一名女巫剑士呢还是个魔法剑士呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good news!  I'm completely mad as well.</Source>
      <Dest>好消息！我也一起疯透了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good news!  I'm completely mad as well.</Source>
      <Dest>好消息！我也一起疯透了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good news!  I'm completely mad as well.</Source>
      <Dest>好消息！我也一起疯透了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good news!  I'm completely mad as well.</Source>
      <Dest>好消息！我也一起疯透了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good news!  I'm completely mad as well.</Source>
      <Dest>好消息！我也一起疯透了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yeah, it's a good day.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，天气是不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good news husband!  I'm completely mad as well.</Source>
      <Dest>我的丈夫，有一个好消息，我觉得我也完全疯掉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good news husband!  I'm completely mad as well.</Source>
      <Dest>我的丈夫，有一个好消息，我觉得我也完全疯掉了。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good news husband!  I'm completely mad as well.</Source>
      <Dest>我的丈夫，有一个好消息，我觉得我也完全疯掉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good news husband!  I'm completely mad as well.</Source>
      <Dest>我的丈夫，有一个好消息，我觉得我也完全疯掉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a High Elf, you must have an opinion on the Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>作为一个高精灵，你必须对梭默有所表态。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I killed both of them.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，我把他们两个都杀了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, I killed both of them.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，我把他们两个都杀了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We could just go to the Bannered Mare.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以去母马横幅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We could just go to the Bannered Mare.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以去母马横幅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We could just go to the Bannered Mare.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以去母马横幅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We could just go to the Bannered Mare.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以去母马横幅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Gold coins up your nose? So that's why you're an insufferable mouth breather.</Source>
      <Dest>你把金币塞进鼻子里面了吧？这就是为什么你是一个连用鼻子呼吸也不会的，讨厌的傻瓜。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I love you too, husband.</Source>
      <Dest>我也爱你，亲爱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I love you too, husband.</Source>
      <Dest>我也爱你，亲爱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I love you too, husband.</Source>
      <Dest>我也爱你，亲爱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Um...I think I dropped something or other outside.  You keep at it.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯……我想我把什么东西落在外面了。你先顶住。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Um...I think I dropped something or other outside.  You keep at it.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯……我想我把什么东西落在外面了。你先顶住。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You nitwit.  You should apologize to her.</Source>
      <Dest>傻孩子，你得像她道歉才行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You nitwit.  You should apologize to her.</Source>
      <Dest>傻孩子，你得像她道歉才行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, don't make me feel guilty.  You know I'm not the most romantic person in the world.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，别让我有罪恶感.  你知道我并不是这个世界上最浪漫的人.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did I also mention how much I love you and that I'm glad your home?</Source>
      <Dest>我有提到过我是多么爱你以及我很喜欢你的家吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Should I introduce you to those apothecaries?  Get them to vouch for me?  Although that would be difficult, seeing as I made them up.</Source>
      <Dest>要我把你介绍给那些药剂师吗？让他们帮我担保吗？虽然鉴于我对他们的所作所为，这可能有点儿困难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Admit it, you love my childish antics.  Can you imagine how dreadful life would be if your adventuring companion was some mindless atronach?</Source>
      <Dest>认了吧，你爱我这幼稚的举动。 你能想象如果和你冒险的同伴只是一些愚蠢的石像，那会是多么可怕的生活吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why I leave the tough moral quandaries to you.  It saves me from all the thinking and absolves me of all the blame.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我把难缠的道德难题留给了你解决，那样我才摆脱了一切思考和责任。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why I leave the tough moral quandaries to you.  It saves me from all the thinking and absolves me of all the blame.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我把难缠的道德难题留给了你解决，那样我才摆脱了一切思考和责任。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when you find yourself in situations hairier than a troll's backside, traveling light makes it all the more easier to flee.</Source>
      <Dest>当你发现你处于一个比趴在巨魔的背部更让人恐惧的局面时，轻装上阵，会让逃跑变得更容易。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The third?  Well, let's not talk about that one.  Let's just say he won't be treating any more cases of dementia anytime soon.  Because I killed him.</Source>
      <Dest>已经第三个了？呃，咱们不聊那个了。这么说吧，很快他就不能再治愈任何一个痴呆患者了。因为我会杀了他的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The third?  Well, let's not talk about that one.  Let's just say he won't be treating any more cases of dementia anytime soon.  Because I killed him.</Source>
      <Dest>已经第三个了？呃，咱们不聊那个了。这么说吧，很快他就不能再治愈任何一个痴呆患者了。因为我会杀了他的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that's the thing.  I don't know for a fact that she saw me cringe.  And if I tell her about the bug, there's no way she'll believe me.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，就是这样。我确实不知道她看到我畏惧了。就算我告诉她那个问题，她也不会相信。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, those folks are far more adept at magic than I.  Unless by illusion you mean hiding a dagger in my sleeve.</Source>
      <Dest>不，那些家伙们对魔法远比我在行得多。除非你把袖子里藏匕首也叫幻术系法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And pay for our food?  Oh no, that probably isn't a good idea.  In that case, we're better off shopping at Carlotta's for fresh ingredients.</Source>
      <Dest>还得给我们的食物付钱？哦不，在这种情况下这可不是个好主意，我们最好到Carlotta那儿买一些新鲜食材。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My theory is the horn isn't the kind you blow, but you know, the kind a dremora wears on his head.  Just some food for thought.</Source>
      <Dest>我的理解是那个号角不是你吹的那种，应该是，你见过的魔人头上顶的那种角吗，像那样的。只是一点点建议。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If not, then I am no more a spellsword than a massage is restoration.  I am more of a blacksmith. Oblivion is my forge, and conjuration my hammer.</Source>
      <Dest>如果不是的话，那我就不再是个魔剑士，也不是个按摩恢复师。我更多是作为一名铁匠。湮灭是我的熔炉，并召唤着我的锤子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or don't.  I really have no opinion one way or the other.</Source>
      <Dest>或者不。不管怎样，我真的没什么意见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They told her not to worry.  Rumarin the mage would come to the rescue.  Looking into their eyes, I couldn't say no.</Source>
      <Dest>他们让她别担心。法师罗勒美会把她的母亲给救出来。看着他们那样期盼的眼神，我怎么能忍心拒绝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm not saying the horn isn't real, just that it might not be the kind of horn you think it is.</Source>
      <Dest>我并不是说那支号角不是真的，只是也许它不是你所想的那种号角。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, to be honest, I don't do anything to discourage the fact that I'm not a real mage.  Sometimes I even use it to boost my own ego.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，说实话，我并没有因为我不是一个真正的法师而气馁。有时我甚至用这个事实来激励自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was a spell tome for a bound sword.  And, I've relied on it ever since.</Source>
      <Dest>这是约束之剑的魔法书。并且，我从那时起就一直依赖它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you're curious, you can ask me, because I know. I'm good friends with one.</Source>
      <Dest>如果如果你感到好奇，你可以问我，因为我知道，你是我的好朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you're curious, you can ask me, because I know. I'm good friends with one.</Source>
      <Dest>如果如果你感到好奇，你可以问我，因为我知道，你是我的好朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, how about this.  It would be a shame if you didn't come back.  I'm too young to be a widow.</Source>
      <Dest>好，这么说吧。要是你回不来的话就太可惜了。我可不想这么年轻就当寡妇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, you were just making small talk?  I thought we were playing the Withershins game.</Source>
      <Dest>等等，你只是在闲聊天儿吗？我还以为我们在玩儿逆时针游戏呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was always good with a sword and a bow, and always too lazy to carry them.  Learning how to conjure the weapons I need solved that dilemma.</Source>
      <Dest>我向来擅长弓和剑，只不过太懒了不想带着它们而已。要学习如何召唤武器我需要先从这个围城里走出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That was another joke by the way. Just making sure you know that grin on my face was a smile and not a creepy stare.</Source>
      <Dest>顺便一说，那只是另一个玩笑。只是为了让你知道我刚刚裂开嘴是在微笑，而并不是什么惊悚的凝视。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That was another joke by the way. Just making sure you know that grin on my face was a smile and not a creepy stare.</Source>
      <Dest>顺便一说，那只是另一个玩笑。只是为了让你知道我刚刚裂开嘴是在微笑，而并不是什么惊悚的凝视。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm tearing up already.  Seriously though, please come back, I have no idea where we're supposed to put our trash.</Source>
      <Dest>我早已泪水盈眶。说真的，请一定要回来。如果你不回来了，我要如何处置你带回的那些垃圾呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's right there in the word.  I summon and bind blades and weapons from Oblivion.</Source>
      <Dest>就在这个词里！我自湮灭召唤并束缚我的武器！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Summoning weapons allows you to travel light.  Your blade never rusts, your quiver never runs out of arrows.</Source>
      <Dest>召唤的武器能使你轻装旅行。你的刀片不会生锈，你的箭袋也不会消耗箭矢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unless by alteration you mean covering my nose in the presence of beggars, or by destruction you mean what time does to love.</Source>
      <Dest>除非你的“变换”的意思是当有乞丐存在的时候捂住我的鼻子，“毁灭”的意思就像是时间对爱情所做的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh really?  I hope you mean madly in love with me, because I wasn't being serious earlier.  Two out three apothecaries say I'm completely sane.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，是吗？我真希望你的意思是已经无法自拔地爱上了我，因为我先前并不是太认真。现在，我确信自己是清醒的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The other children comforted her, while I stood there dreading what would come next.</Source>
      <Dest>另外一群孩纸在安慰她，而我站在一旁，忧虑着接下来要发生的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But toward the bottom of the sack, I found something I never knew was there.  A gift from Otero.  One last jester's trick.</Source>
      <Dest>但在袋子的最底下，我找到了一件出乎我意料的东西。那是由奥特罗所送的一件礼物。这是那个小丑的最后一个玩笑了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No really, you're wonderful, savior of Skyrim and all that.  You might want to stop with the insults though.  Not everyone finds them attractive.</Source>
      <Dest>那不是真的，你很棒，你拯救了天际和所有的一切。虽然你可能想要制止他们侮辱。但是要知道你不能要求每个人都欣赏你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No really, you're wonderful, savior of Skyrim and all that.  You might want to stop with the insults though.  Not everyone finds them attractive.</Source>
      <Dest>那不是真的，你很棒，你拯救了天际和所有的一切。虽然你可能想要制止他们侮辱。但是要知道你不能要求每个人都欣赏你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd pull a septim from behind their ear, or a flower from my sleeve.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以从他们的耳朵里掏出一枚金币，或是从我的袖口变出一朵花。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I returned to the inn that night, and in a fit of rage, I started throwing away my belongings. They were as useless as I was.</Source>
      <Dest>我那晚回到了旅馆，满腔怒火，我狠劲摔打我的东西。他们现在就如我当时那样无助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just throw in a word with the cook if you can.  Blame it on the "stupid Elf," and then point at me and I'll wave or something.</Source>
      <Dest>可以的话你去和厨师唠两句。把事情怪罪给“蠢货精灵”，然后指指我，我会挥挥手什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bringing it up would just make things awkward.  Better to just let the guilt eat at my insides.</Source>
      <Dest>再抖出这件事只会让人尴尬。还是让我一个人受良心的折磨吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh really?  I hope you mean mad about adventuring, because I wasn't being serious earlier.  Two out three apothecaries say I'm completely sane.</Source>
      <Dest>哦是吗？我希望你是为冒险而痴狂，因为我一开始并不是认真的。三个药剂师里有两个都说我是完全正常的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, the markets in Sovngarde must be awfully expensive given how desperate they are to take their possessions with them.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，鉴于松加德的人们是在多么铤而走险的情况下才能把自己的财产带在身边，那里市场的物价一定贵的吓人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The problem is, that would also require more work.  It would be easier if we could just get them to prepare better meals.</Source>
      <Dest>问题是，那也要布置更多。如果我们只是让他们准备更好的饭菜，那会事情会变得相当简单。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I know one person who's willing to suffer this fool.  And he's standing right in front of me.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我知道谁能忍受这个傻逼了。他就站在我面前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here for a moment.</Source>
      <Dest>在这儿等一下.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's nothing. Never mind.</Source>
      <Dest>没什么事，不用担心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can't say I disagree.</Source>
      <Dest>就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need you to do something for me.</Source>
      <Dest>我需要你为我做件事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes. Let me show you.</Source>
      <Dest>不错，你看看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here.</Source>
      <Dest>在这里等着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes.  All the way to the ledge, but not over it.  Even I have my limits.</Source>
      <Dest>对，一直走到壁架 ，但不要越过去。我的忍耐是有限度的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, one of these days I'd like to be able to explore a cave without finding a corpse on a slab.</Source>
      <Dest>你要知道, 这些天我想去探索一个山洞而不是去找一具尸体.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, this arena looks familiar. I think I lost 100 septims betting on one of these bandits. Now I don't feel so bad for killing them. </Source>
      <Dest>知道吗，这个竞技场看起来还挺眼熟的。我想我浪费了100个金币的赌注在这群强盗中的某人身上。现在杀了他们我也不会觉得难受了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Doubtful any day has been as good as this one.  Okay, that was fun, but I really don't have the stamina or patience to go all the way to Z.</Source>
      <Dest>恐怕从没有哪天像今天这么愉快了。好啦，真开心，不过我确实没有那个耐力或者耐心坚持到底啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sorry, can't be done.</Source>
      <Dest>对不起，我做不到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that it?</Source>
      <Dest>就是这个？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Already?  We haven't even told each other are deepest darkest fears yet!  Mine's centaurs.  There.  Now we can go our separate ways.</Source>
      <Dest>我们还没有告诉彼此最深的黑暗的恐惧呢！啊，我的半人马在那里。现在我们可以分道扬镳了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, let's trade.</Source>
      <Dest>那好，我们交换点东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now and forever. Just kidding.  Marriage joke.  I'll be going home now.</Source>
      <Dest>从现在开始，直到永远。只是个玩笑，婚姻的玩笑。我现在得回家了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, Gathrik's tomb, huh. The famous Gathrik from the battle of what's-his-name. You know, that Gathrik. Feel free to fill in the blanks at any time.</Source>
      <Dest>哇，Gathrik的坟墓。 哈，Gathrik之战中大名鼎鼎的Gathrik。你懂得，就是那个 Gathrik，什么时候都可以拿来当话题的那个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, let's be serious. If a bunch of smelly savages want your land, how valuable can it be?</Source>
      <Dest>好了，大家认真一点。如果一坨野蛮人要占据你的土地，那土地还能值钱？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, they really should put up a sign outside this camp. On one side it'd say, "Warning: Bandits." On the other it'd say "Beware: Adventurers."</Source>
      <Dest>你瞧，他们真应该在这个营地外立个牌子。一半儿写着“警告：此处有强盗”，另一半儿刻上“冒险者出没注意”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, this Sybil seems awfully mature. Which is probably why I like her. Neither of us want to act our age.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道吗，那个女预言家真的非常成熟。这就是我喜欢她的原因。我们中没有一个人想表现得与自己的年龄相符。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Departs}</Source>
      <Dest>{离开 }</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look, I realize bandits aren't the sharpest tools in the shed, but if I'm a sentry, the last place I'd be standing is in front of a giant target.</Source>
      <Dest>你瞧，我意识到强盗们在小屋里可不是什么敏捷的家伙，但如果我是个放哨的，我最不想站的地方估计是在一个巨型目标前面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you need?</Source>
      <Dest>你想要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Zzzzz...</Source>
      <Dest>Zzzzz……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, the Dainty Sload! I know these pirates! The first mate is an Orc. I say we kill him before he remembers I owe him money.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，小蛞蝓号！我知道这些海盗！他们的大副是个兽人。我得说，我们得在他记起我欠还他钱之前杀死他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Somehow I knew this was coming.</Source>
      <Dest>反正我知道这要来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not that I want to question our Khajiit friend who in no way looks like a thief, but how do you make incense out of a flawless ruby?</Source>
      <Dest>我并非想怀疑我们这位怎么看也不是小偷的虎人朋友，不过你是怎么用无瑕的红宝石做出熏香的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say broken towers are usually filled with broken people. This tower's lopsided as well. And yet, I feel a strange compulsion to move in...</Source>
      <Dest>他们说破旧的塔楼里一定盘踞着一群乌合之众。这座塔楼也有点斜了。而且，我还感到似乎有一种力量隐隐约约在吸引我进去...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you need me to take?</Source>
      <Dest>你需要多长时间?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think Danica has a point. This sapling won't bring nearly as much glory to her pockets...I mean, Kynareth as the old tree.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得Danica有道理。种子不会带来和她匹敌往日的荣耀。我的意思是，无论是对吉娜莱丝还是那颗老树。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Huzzah! The Draugr is dead and now the miners can go back to a life of dangerous labor for menial pay! We did it!</Source>
      <Dest>乌拉！尸鬼已经死完了，而矿场又重回正轨。现在危险的日子一去不回！我们做到了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, I can't believe the Gildergreen's restored. And all it took was sap from the Eldergleam. It's like some kind of strange tree incest.</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，我简直无法相信翠苒树复活了，所需的只是古藤圣所的树液。像是树之间的通亲之类的奇怪的事情一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure, I'll manage.  Somehow.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，我会处理的。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We're incredibly far east for a Forsworn camp. Just how much of Skyrim do they think is there's anyway? Not that I blame them for fudging the maps.</Source>
      <Dest>为了找一个弃誓者营地我们已经向东走得太远了吧。我不是在责怪他们捏造地图。但是他们到底认为天际有多少土地需要我们去探寻？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not to talk ill of the dead, but "The Bear will lead the way?" Agna could've just told you about the pull chain.</Source>
      <Dest>不是我要非议死者，但是“熊会带路？”AGNA就应该告诉你关于链环的事的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've heard there are some incredibly stupid people who think this place is full of gold. But it's not. It's full of something called "Guld."</Source>
      <Dest>我听说有些蠢到家了的家伙相信这地方到处是金子。但才不是那样呢。这鬼地方是有带金字开头的东西，不过那玩意叫金盏花。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Silver-Bloods are willing to offer gold for this pile of dirt that is the target of constant Forsworn raids...and Ainethach said "No?" </Source>
      <Dest>就算这烂泥坑里装满了弃誓者，银血家族也很乐意为它付上一笔钱买下它……但艾尼塔克那家伙的回答居然是"不"？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure.  Just leave me a honey nut treat and a bottle of beer or something to pass the time.</Source>
      <Dest>好嘞。记得给我留串蜜果宴或者留罐啤酒，或者其他打发时间的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like, say you have an embarrassing social disease you want to hide from the others, and you need a potion. Just send them in the back way.</Source>
      <Dest>比如你得了什么……见不得人的病，要买药就叫他们从这后门进。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm not sure who to trust here. Saadia seems rather shady, but so do these Alik'r. I say we help the highest bidder. Gold would never lie.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道在这里该信任谁了。萨蒂亚似乎相当可疑，但那些阿利克尔人也没好到哪儿去。我得说我们还是去帮出价最高的人吧。金子不会说谎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This cove is a great way to smuggle things in and out of camp.</Source>
      <Dest>这个山凹真是带货出入营地的好路子啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll be home if you need me.  But who's to say I'll need you? We shall see, we shall see.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你需要我，我就在家。谁说我会需要你啦？哼哼，我们走着瞧，走着瞧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If only we could conjure everything.   Keys, food, junk.</Source>
      <Dest>要是我们有变戏法的本事那该多好，变出些钥匙、食物、垃圾什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This always happens.  Dump the goods on the Elf who carries nothing.</Source>
      <Dest>总会发生向什么也没带的精灵倾倒商品这样的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You do realize that's impossible, don't you?</Source>
      <Dest>你明白这是不可能的，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that escalated rather quickly. But maybe Christer won't mind that we took his one true love and spilled her brains on the floor.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，升级相当迅速嘛。也许克里斯特不会介意我们拿走他的挚爱并让他脑浆四溅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This poor, sweet old hag. All she wants is to get her tower back so she can go back to turning men into monsters. Is that too much to ask?</Source>
      <Dest>这个可怜又可爱的女巫. 她只求要回她的塔楼继续回去进行把人变成怪物的勾当。难道她要求过分么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's a good thing Christer didn't follow us. Can you imagine if he walked in right when Fjola gave us the ring? That would've been awkward.</Source>
      <Dest>克里斯没跟着我们真是好事。你能想象当菲欧拉给我们戒指的时候他正好走过来回事什么样子吗？那就糗大了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I like how the bandit announced his plans to kill us instead of just stabbing us in the back. I wish more of them shared his candor.</Source>
      <Dest>比起背后暗害的强盗们我更喜欢他这种光明正大挑明的和我们正面冲突的方式，我希望更多的强盗能学到他的坦率。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Make your request, and it shall be done.  Eventually.</Source>
      <Dest>提出你的要求，你终将会被满足。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't get me wrong, I feel bad for this couple having to die, but I'm also very impressed by whoever killed them, hitting a moving target and such.</Source>
      <Dest>别把我想得太糟，我对这对夫妻必须死感到很不好，但是我对杀死他们的人一样印象深刻，竟然能击中移动中的目标。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Small caves like this are a great place to catch Bone Break Fever.</Source>
      <Dest>像這樣的小洞窟最容易得骨熱病了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, if I lived in the Ratways, I'd be predicting dragons would return too.  I'd also be wearing my pants on my head.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道, 如果我呆在鼠道里, 也能预感到龙会回归的话. 我也会把裤子穿在脑袋上.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Skeevers?  That's weird.  You'd think he'd start with an army of trolls.  Or mammoths. Even birds could be useful.  I wonder if he tried those first.</Source>
      <Dest>雪鼠？真奇怪。你会以为他应该从一群巨魔开始。或者是长毛象。就算是鸟也有点用。不知他有没有先试过那些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The ghosts of the original Companions.  To think, if it weren't for them, Skyrim would be full of Elves.  Does that make them heroes or murderers?</Source>
      <Dest>那些是战友团前辈的幽灵。想想吧，要不是他们，天际省就全被精灵占了。这样说的话他们到底是英雄呢还是凶手呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why bother translating Gallus' journal?  It won't be in his writing.  Wouldn't it make more sense to hire a forger?</Source>
      <Dest>Gallus的日记有什么好翻译的？那又不会是他自己写的。还不如找个专业的造假师呢吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, what just happened?  You and Aela were swinging at nothing, and then talking to nothing, and now you're Harbinger?  I'm confused.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，刚才发生了什么事儿？你和艾拉突然晃来晃去，然后对着空气说了半天话，而现在你就成了预言者了？我有点儿糊涂了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I...I can't believe the old wolf is dead.</Source>
      <Dest>我……我不敢相信这只老狼已经死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh look what's for dinner, a canis root and a boiled chaurus egg.  I'm going to have to have a word with the chef. </Source>
      <Dest>噢，看看晚饭都有些什么，一个犬型根和一个水煮查鲁斯卵。我得找主厨谈谈了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who do you think told Kodlak about what you and Aela were up to? My gold's on Skjor. Sure, he's dead, but wouldn't that make for the perfect alibi?</Source>
      <Dest>你以为是谁告诉了科拉克关于你和艾拉的打算？我赌思科月。当然，他是死了，不过这样就成了更完美的不在场证明，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is an impressive kitchen for an old Nord fort.  I wonder if we have time to cook something up.  You can kill more bandits with stew than swords.</Source>
      <Dest>这厨房在诺德古堡里面太奇特了。我觉得我们有时间多做点好吃的。你用汤杀死的强盗能比用剑还多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So this Meridia speaks to you, but curiously not to your faithful companion. Wouldn't it better to call a meeting so we can coordinate our movements?</Source>
      <Dest>所以美瑞蒂亚跟你说话了，但却莫名其妙的不理会你忠诚的伙伴。如果我们能开一个小会，然后协调我们的行动不是更好吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, we made it. Ivarstead. It looks like a nice enough village. I don't know why anyone would want to live atop a mountain when they can live here.</Source>
      <Dest>恩，我们成功了。紫杉镇。它看起来真是个不错的村庄。我不明白为什么有人在他们可以住在这里的时候却非想住在山上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Redoran's Retreat. Is that like House Redoran? I didn't know there was a clan in Morrowind completely devoted to banditry.</Source>
      <Dest>瑞多然的休息处。这就像是瑞多然的家？我还真不知道这个晨风省的氏族已经完全致力于强盗事业了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Greybeards get free food and water delivered to them?  Well, if you call salted meats food.  Here's a hint.  It isn't.</Source>
      <Dest>有人免费为灰胡子们送去食物和水？好吧，要是你把那种咸肉也称为食物的话。我个人觉得那不算是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was master of a guild once.  Only it wasn't so much of a guild as it was people around a campfire, and by master I mean gathered the kindling.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾经一度是公会的头领。尽管那时的公会不过是人们聚在火堆旁烤火，而作为公会头领的任务则是把人们聚在一起并点燃火。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ooh!  A mystery friend in Riverwood!  I love mysteries!  Who do you think it is?  I bet it's this fifth Greybeard the others were talking about.  </Source>
      <Dest>哦！一个神秘的朋友在河木镇！我爱神秘的感觉！你感觉那会是谁呢？我打赌连那五个灰胡子都在谈论这件事。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, sometimes I think the Dwarves are trying to send us a message from wherever they are. Most days, that message is "I want to kill you."</Source>
      <Dest>你知道的，有时候我觉得矮人试图传递给我们一个消息，无论他们身在何处。大多数情况下，这个消息是“我想杀了你。” </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So now we take the scroll to the "time-wound?" Does that mean someone stabbed it? Will it fester? Suddenly I'm concerned. But not really.</Source>
      <Dest>所以现在我们要用这张卷轴来对付 "时间伤口" 了吗？它会被刺伤吗？伤口会恶化吗? 我突然觉得很担心。这不是真的对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm glad Jarl Elisif takes the time to listen to crazy farmers from Gods know where. It's not like there's other things she needs to address.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴艾丽西弗领主还有时间去倾听那帮不知道从哪个鬼地方滚出来的脑子坏掉的农民的情愿。看起来似乎她也没别的事情需要去关心了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, extortion.  And then say there are no good careers for childhood bullies.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，勒索。然后就该说这里没什么能欺负孩子的好职业了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here's a question.  These witches are half-birds, right?  Do you think they lay eggs?  Or would it be half an egg for half a bird?</Source>
      <Dest>我有一个疑问。这些女巫是半人半鸟对吗？那你知道他们生蛋吗？或者跟进一步说，她们会生下半人半鸟的幼崽吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think some of these Greybeards rather enjoyed getting hit with your thu'um. Don't be surprised if you find some whips and chains in the back room.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉着这些灰胡子更喜欢被你的吐目射中的感觉。如果你在后面的房子找到了些鞭子和锁链，可千万别惊讶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright I get the part about Septimus needing an Elder Scroll, what I don't understand is everything else he said.</Source>
      <Dest>对于赛普汀默示的话，我除了他想找到上古卷轴那一部分话之外，别的我是一个字儿都听不懂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Drinking blood isn't my thing, but if it was, I probably would try and put more of it down my throat instead of on the walls.</Source>
      <Dest>我不喜欢喝血，如果我喜欢的话，我应该会把血更多的吞进喉咙而不是洒在墙上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you mind if maybe, when this all over, if a friend of mine can borrow your Nightingale Armor?  You know, to make replicas and sell them for gold.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你不介意的话，等这一切结束了，我的一个朋友可以借你的夜莺铠甲一用吗？你懂的，做做复制版啦。。然后换点小钱什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The mead bottle Esbern, don't forget the mead bottle.  Unless it's Black Briar mead.   Then you can forget it.</Source>
      <Dest>还有蜜酒啊，伊斯本，别忘了拿上蜜酒。除非它是黑荆棘蜜酒，那你就可以忘了这件事儿了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Remember when we met? There were skeletons there too. This is kind of like that time, only now my toes are frozen.</Source>
      <Dest>还记得我们相遇的时候吗？当时那儿也有些骷髅。现在就跟那时一样，只不过现在我的脚趾头都冻僵了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look, this poor sod died trying to reach his ale. He would've gotten to it too, if he wasn't stuck inside a bushel of hay.</Source>
      <Dest>瞧，这个可怜虫多么拼命想够到他的啤酒啊。如果不是被这堆干草困住的话，他肯定就能得手了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you sure that's Nettlebane? Shouldn't it be, I don't know, an axe or something? Unless the Eldergleam is smaller than I remember.</Source>
      <Dest>你确定那是草木灾星？不觉得应该是把斧头什么的吗？除非古老闪光比我记忆中的要小。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A Thalmor party?  I bet they throw great ones.  It's always the people you least expect.</Source>
      <Dest>一个梭默的宴会? 我打赌他们邀请了些重量级人物。那里肯定有你意想不到的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alduin's Wall.  I'm not sure what the law says, but doesn't that mean it's technically his property?  I mean, it's his wall.</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因之墙。我不知道法律上该怎么说，但从严格意义上来说，这不是他的财产吗？我的意思是，这是他的墙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So this puzzle has pillars, but no clues.  It's almost as if they don't want us to solve it.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这个谜题只有本体而几乎无线索. 好像他们不想让我们解决它，所以才设计的无迹可寻.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did you read that note?  "M" is for Mercer.  Who do you think "R" stands for?  Do we know anyone whose first name starts with the letter "R?"</Source>
      <Dest>你读了那个纸条吗？“M”是指墨瑟。你觉得"R"指的是谁呢？咱们认识哪个人名字开头字母是“R”的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We just stopped a plot to overthrow the Thieves Guild! Sure it was being carried out by two mad beggars, but Brynjolf doesn't have to know that part.</Source>
      <Dest>我们阻止了一个推翻盗贼工会的阴谋！可以肯定的是这是两个疯乞丐搞的鬼，但布林乔夫不需要知道这一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So now that you have the skeleton key, we can open a lot of doors. Any door, for that matter. Which door should we open first? I'm drawing a blank.</Source>
      <Dest>既然现在你有万能钥匙了，你就可以打开很多扇门了。事实上，是个门你就能开。你想先开哪扇门？我列张表出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So the secret code was renting the attic room?  I would've went with a weird menu item like the potage, or the name of a childhood toy or something.</Source>
      <Dest>所以说密码就在顶楼？我应该一张古怪的名单上去吗？例如浓汤料或者童年玩具的名称什么的？.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Was that really a crimson nirnroot over there? And is that really a cooking pot? Are you thinking what I'm thinking?</Source>
      <Dest>那边的真的是猩红奈恩根？那玩意确定是煮饭锅？你和我在想一样的事情么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I were a Falmer slave, I would give all my masters names and paint them on their chests. How else am I supposed to know who's water I'm fetching?</Source>
      <Dest>如果我是一个雪精灵奴隶的话，我会给我的每一个主人都起名字并且把它写在他们的胸脯上。不这样的话我怎么知道自己是在给谁取水呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, Maven Black-Briar.  I've never met a famous person before.  Do we have to dress up?  I don't know any spells for conjuring fine robes.</Source>
      <Dest>哇噢。Maven Black-Briar。我以前从没见过名人啊。得穿一身正装才行吧？可我不会什么召唤礼服的法术啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bees, bears, blood, bones, and bandits. All this cave needs now is baubles. I'm sure they're in that chest, I mean, box.</Source>
      <Dest>死蜜蜂，死狗熊，死人血，死人骨，死强盗。现在这洞窟只差死人的财宝了。我很确定在那个箱子里，我是说，死盒子里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, did you see Arngeir's face curl up when he starting talking about the Blades? You'd think Esbern slept with his sister.</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，你有没有注意到，每次谈到刀锋的时候，艾恩盖尔的脸都拧巴得苦瓜一样? 你会觉得伊思本真的有和他姐姐私通.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did you hear that?  Brynjolf sells an elixir that gives you "god-like" powers!  I wonder if he gives discounts for buying in bulk.</Source>
      <Dest>你听到了吗？布林乔夫卖的药能给你神一样的力量！我不知道从他那儿批发有没有折扣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So are you going to make the joke or am I?  You know, about the poison being Black-Briar mead.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这个笑话是由你还是由我来讲？就是那个关于毒药和黑荆棘蜜酒的笑话，你知道的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I wanted to split up Maven and the Thieves Guild, I would've just hired you to do it.  But I'm sure this Gulum-Ei is a capable turncoat.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我要把玛雯和盗贼工会分离开，我就不止会雇你一个来干了。但是我相信这个Gulum-Ei是个叛徒坯子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were 3 Blades standing behind you in that relief...Delphine, Esbern, and a mystery third person?  Lucky for me, that sword isn't conjured.</Source>
      <Dest>有3个强大的力量会在背后为你撑腰当你后援...戴尔菲娜, Esbern, 和神秘的第三个人?  我真幸运，这些高手都不是幻觉.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good to see you on your feet.  For a second there I thought was going to have to avenge you.  But now you can avenge yourself.  With my help.</Source>
      <Dest>很高兴看到你还活着.  上一秒我还认为可能需要去为你报仇.但是现在你可以在我的帮助下进行复仇了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is what I don't get.  Delvin and Brynjolf never noticed things were missing?  I think one of them is colluding with Mercer.</Source>
      <Dest>我就是不明白这个。戴尔文和布林乔夫从没注意过丢东西了吗？我觉着他们中的某人是墨瑟的同伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know how I know a cave is weird? The mushrooms. Without them, this place is just peculiar. But add a giant glowing mushroom, and you have weird.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道我是怎么知道一个洞穴很诡异的吗？蘑菇。如果没有蘑菇，这个地方只不过有些奇怪。但当一个巨大的蘑菇长在这儿，就变得诡异了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Liar's Retreat. Did I ever tell you this tavern was named after me? Well, that's the joke, anyway. It doesn't seem so funny now.</Source>
      <Dest>Liar's Retreat。我告诉过你这个酒馆是以我命名的么？好吧，这是个玩笑。虽然现在听起来不怎么好笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder why some of the bandits sleep on the shipwreck? It must be their version of Cidhna Mine.</Source>
      <Dest>我在想为什么一些土匪喜欢在船骸上睡觉。 他们一定是这样诠释Cidhna Mine的.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever notice the skulls on these enchanting tables?  They have horns yes, but they also have three eyes.  Three!</Source>
      <Dest>留意到放在漂亮桌子上的那些骷髅了吗?  他们的确有角, 但它们也有三只眼睛.  三只!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Synod?  Here?  In Skyrim?  Well, there's a lot of people here in Skyrim I suppose.  By the way, what's a Synod?</Source>
      <Dest>希诺人？这里？在天际省？  好吧，我想在天际省的人略有点多。顺带问一下，什么是希诺人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I bet murderers love taverns with an apprentice.  You can kill the innkeep and still be confident the mead will flow.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得杀人犯们一般比较喜欢那种有学徒的酒馆。即使杀了老板，也不影响营业。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, I'm starting to miss those old Nord puzzles.  This Dwarven one doesn't even have pictures.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道，我开始想念那些诺德人的老式谜题了。这些矮人的玩意连图画都没有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This one reminds me a lot of myself.  The drunken lout, not the Elf in college robes.</Source>
      <Dest>这个人让我想起了自己。一个醉鬼，而不是一名学院里的长袍精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Radiant Raiment.  I would have gone with "Argent Armor" myself, but that's just splitting hairs.</Source>
      <Dest>是锦衣，如果是‘银色盔甲’我早都带着它跑路了，但是这只是鸡蛋里挑骨头的玩笑罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't you think Stalleo should have lent us one of his bodyguards?  I don't want to say he's a coward, but I'm heavily implying it.</Source>
      <Dest>你不觉得Stalleo保镖太多了以至于应该把他的保镖借个给我们么？我不想说他是个胆小鬼，不过我就是这么个意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, is it dead?  I mean, I know it's already dead, it's a bone dragon, but is it dead dead?</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，它死了吗？我是说我知道骨龙本来就是死的，不过现在是不是已经死的不能再死了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I love tours as much as the next Elf, but when do we get to blow stuff up?  Notice how I said we?  I hope no one notices I'm not a real student.</Source>
      <Dest>我跟之后那个精灵一样喜欢旅行，但什么时候我们才能做完这些事儿？ 注意到了吗我说的是“我们”？希望没人发现我不是真的学生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't understand what all the debate is about.  Quicksilver ore is obviously more valuable than iron.</Source>
      <Dest>我不明白还要吵些什么。水银矿明显比铁矿有价值。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Step 1: Kill the disembodied voice. Step 2: Retrieve the Staff of Magnus. Step 3: Shove it down Ancano's throat.</Source>
      <Dest>第一步：除掉不切实际的声音。第二步：取回玛格努斯之杖。第三步: 把玛格努斯之杖塞进安卡诺的喉咙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What in Oblivion were these things?  Damn that Ancano.  He gives us Elves a bad name.</Source>
      <Dest>这特么都是些什么玩意儿？该死的安卡诺。他是我们精灵的耻辱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is it me, or are those coffins a bit on the small side?  Maybe these conjurers have a thing for female Bretons.</Source>
      <Dest>是我的问题吗，还是那些棺材的有点短小小？也许这些巫师有适合布莱顿人女人的棺材。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of all the things you can do with horkers, mounting them on a wall would be last on my list.  Birna seems nice though for a crazy person.</Source>
      <Dest>在海象的所有用途里面，我最不可能把它当装饰挂在墙上。不过比尔娜弄的还行吧，从疯子的角度而言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This mage didn't kill as many Draugr as I hoped.  I guess it would've been asking too much for a leisurely walk to the treasure.  </Source>
      <Dest>这法师干掉的尸鬼不如我想象的多。我猜一次轻松的寻宝之旅不会要价太高。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do we tell Grosta the truth? Because it's so ridiculous, him being lured here and murdered, that it sounds like we're just covering for his whoring.</Source>
      <Dest>我们该告诉格罗斯塔真相吗？因为这……太荒唐了。他被诱骗到这儿，然后就被干掉了。听起来就像是我们在为他的寻花问柳做掩饰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do we have a cure disease potion?  I think this Haelga could use one.  Or twelve.</Source>
      <Dest>我们还有祛病药剂吗？我觉得哈尔嘉可能会用掉一个。或是一打。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Funny, I think this fort would've been easier to defend if they actually used all these potions and armor instead of decorating the tables with them.</Source>
      <Dest>真有趣。我想如果他们把那些药剂和护甲投入使用而不是当做装饰品的话，这个要塞会更容易防守。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This vampire finished two plates of humans but didn't touch his apple.  I'm going to need to have a word with his mother.</Source>
      <Dest>这个吸血鬼吃掉了两盘人肉但却不去碰他的苹果，看来我得和他的老妈谈谈了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tolfdir's right. The Arch-Mage must be told of this discovery! A copy of the Lusty Argonian Maid, right here in Saarthal! And the orb too I suppose.</Source>
      <Dest>托夫迪尔是对的。必须向首席法师汇报这一发现！一本《元气满满的亚龙人女仆》，在萨瑟尔城里！我想。。也许还有那个球？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is it me, or are the ceilings here really low?  If I bump my head on a support beam and this place collapses, don't blame me.  Blame short people.</Source>
      <Dest>到底是因为我太高呢还是这地方的天花板就那么矮？如果我不相信把我的脑袋撞在横梁上导致这地方坍塌的话，那别怪我，去怪那些矮个子吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh look, another beautiful grove and another dead alchemist.  I'm beginning to think the Spriggans grow all these ingredients to bait them.</Source>
      <Dest>噢看啊，又一片美丽的林地和又一个死去的炼金术师。我开始认为是树精故意种下所有这些草药来引诱他们了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh, you're not thinking of taking this mangy dog with us, are you?  Well, I'm not sleeping in the same room.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你不会真的想带这只肮脏的狗一起走吧，不会吧？好吧，我可不会和他睡在一个房间。    </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So we're not following the crazy dream priest, are we?  Well, at least he's taking us to a place where no one will hear us, I mean him, scream.</Source>
      <Dest>那么我们没有在跟随疯神的脚步，是吗？好吧，至少他把我们带到了一个没人能听到我们说话的地方，我指他，那个尖叫的疯子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright...Snake-Fish-Bird, Snake-Fish-Bird, Snake-Fish...wait.  What if it's Bird-Fish-Snake?  Do you read them right to left, or left to right?</Source>
      <Dest>好吧……蛇-鱼-鸟，蛇-鱼-鸟，蛇-鱼……等等，如果是鸟-鱼-蛇咋整？你是从左往右看的还是从右往左瞅的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ancano should relax. Hasn't he heard of a Psijic Order? You walk into a tavern, order 400 sweet rolls, and when the maid brings them over, you run. </Source>
      <Dest>安卡诺应该休息下。 他没有听说过一个Psijic点菜的故事么？你走进一个酒店，点了400个甜甜圈，等待者把它们端上来的时候，你就跑了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you understand what he's saying?  Because I haven't the faintest idea.</Source>
      <Dest>你懂他在说啥吗？我可是听懵了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh look, a hole in the roof.  I wonder if people just drop in from time to time.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，看，房顶上有个洞。我在想从那上面是不是经常会掉下个人来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, that's a little better.  Still needs to work on his diction though.</Source>
      <Dest>喔，好点了。不过还是要注意措辞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you really think it was wise to split up?  Does Tolfdir care at all about the welfare of his students?  Sure, we can handle ourselves, but still.</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得在这儿分头行动对劲吗？Tolfdir 在乎学生们的人身安全吗？ 当然我们是能自保的，不过还是小心为妙……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I rather like this room.  When you're done shooting things, you can sit down, have a drink, and read a good burned book.</Source>
      <Dest>我挺喜欢这间屋子呢。当你练习完射箭，就可以随便坐下，喝点东西，捧一本烧焦的书来读读。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vampires and conjurers.  Oh, I'm all for letting them kill each other. Yes, I conjure weapons, but I'm not a mage. I trust they know the difference.</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼和召唤师。哦，我致力于让他们自相残杀。对，没错，我召唤武器，但是我不是法师。我相信他们能分辨出个中差异。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mining for soul gems, huh.  Well that's new.</Source>
      <Dest>这是打算挖出灵魂石来么。好吧这可挺新鲜的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Frozen Hearth?  That doesn't sound very inviting.  Although mages might appreciate the paradox.</Source>
      <Dest>冰封熔炉？那听起来不咋地。虽然法师们也许会欣赏这种悖论。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, I was a bit intimidated by this lot at first.  But the Companions have mercs, green thumbs, and even a drunk!  We fit right in!</Source>
      <Dest>你懂的，我先被这一大帮子人吓着了。但仔细一瞅，他们里边有雇佣兵，有花匠，甚至还有个醉鬼！正合我意！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is it too late to take bets?  Good, because I was about to put it all on the Elf, and now...well, forget I said anything.</Source>
      <Dest>现在下注太晚了吗？好吧，因为我想把全身家当压在那个精灵身上，现在……呃，忘了我刚说的话吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh...the "Augur" of Dunlain.  Now it makes sense.  Here I was excited about meeting a magical Ogre, and instead it's some talking ball of light.</Source>
      <Dest>哦……是“预言师”杜兰。这就有些道理了。我本为能见到一些会魔法的食人魔而感到兴奋，现在却因为看见了一个会说话的光球。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This answers two questions for me. Yes, vampires do sleep in coffins.  No, they don't sleep standing up. Or upside down. At least, this one doesn't.</Source>
      <Dest>这同时解答了我两个疑问。第一个，吸血鬼是睡在棺材里的。 第二个，但他们不是站着睡或倒吊着睡的。至少这只不是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great!  We retrieved the books, and nobody had to die.  Well, nobody we care about anyway.  If only all evil warlocks were this accommodating.</Source>
      <Dest>好极了！我们把书复原了，谁都不用死了。额，反正我们根本不在乎有谁会挂掉。要是所有的邪恶术士这么肯通融该好啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I were Bryling, I would name this mine something like "Sunshine and Butterflies."  It would cut down on a considerable amount of wallowing.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我是布莱琳，我就会把这个矿场命名为“阳光小蝴蝶”什么的。这能大大减少这里的忧郁气氛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Temple of the Divines.  Wouldn't it be funny if the Gods spoke a different language?  Then all our prayers would just sound like nonsense.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵神庙。如果圣灵们说的是另一种语言会不会很有趣？那样的话，我们所有的祈祷在他们听上去都会像是呓语。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Finally, a puzzle worthy of someone of my intellect!  And by that I mean a puzzle designed for a self-educated peasant.</Source>
      <Dest>终于有个能配得上我的智商的谜题了。 我是说一个为自学成才的精灵设计的谜题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fort Snowhawk.  Named after the nocturnal bird that I just made up.</Source>
      <Dest>雪鹰要塞。  是以一种我编造的夜鸟的名字命名的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey, one of those ghosts looked familiar.   I know, don't tell me, it was Tolfdir, right?  Oh Gods, does that mean he's dead too?</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，那些鬼魂里有一个很眼熟。我知道了，先别告诉我，那是托夫迪尔，是吧？噢神啊，那是不是意味着他也死了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why do they call these men "Spectres?"  They don't look like ghosts.</Source>
      <Dest>他们为什么会把这些人称作“幽灵”？他们看起来并不像鬼魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great!  We retrieved the books, and all we had to do was find a stupid Elf and kill a dangerous one.  It was a lot of work, is what I'm saying.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了！我们重新取回了书，并且我们现在要做的就是找到那个蠢精灵，然后宰了那个危险的家伙。我说的这些，可有好多活要干呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh good, a killing circle made of mushrooms and a random skull.   There's something you see every day.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，真好，一个由蘑菇和随便一个头骨组成的杀戮之环。这都是你每天都能看见的东西啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Murder plots, secret notes, duplicitous strangers.  I think I'm going to like this town.</Source>
      <Dest>谋杀的阴谋，秘密的便条，奸诈的陌生人。我想我会喜欢这个城市的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hag's Cure. Does that mean cures for Hags, or made by them?  I suppose either way, they're of little use to me.</Source>
      <Dest>鬼婆药剂…这意思是说给鬼婆治病的药呢还是由鬼婆亲手做的药？我看两种都有吧，反正我用不着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What in Oblivion was that?  I thought it was an earthquake, but it sounded like it came from above us.</Source>
      <Dest>湮灭在上，这他喵的是个啥？我还以为是地震,但它听起来像来自我们上方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sure if they told the Jarl, he'll send his men to Kolskeggr any day now.  There's really no need for us to get involved.  Yes, any day now.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢肯定一旦他们告诉了领主，那领主随时都会派人前往科斯凯格。我们真的没必要卷入这些事情中。是的，随时。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So many bodies.  So much death.  And to think, it could have all been avoided if they didn't insist on learning ice magic.</Source>
      <Dest>这么多的死尸，这么多的死人。仔细想想的话，如果他们不坚持学习冰系魔法，所有这一切也许可以避免。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That waterfall looks clean enough to bathe in!  The Draugr agree with me, half of them are already naked.  </Source>
      <Dest>这个瀑布看起来干净的足够洗澡了！看来尸鬼们跟我想得一样，他们中的一大半已经赤裸裸的了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Would it be weird if I said the innkeeper here is more attractive than the tavern wench?  She's a bit too...forward.</Source>
      <Dest>要是我说这里的店主比女仆更有魅力会不会很奇怪。她有点过于性感了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So we're helping a maniac, repair an evil dagger, from the Daedric Prince who caused the Oblivion Crisis. Okay! I just follow whatever you do anyway.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我们在帮助一名法师，去修复一把从引发湮灭危机的魔族君主那儿得来的邪恶的匕首。好吧！无论你干什么我都跟着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This cabin has holes in the roof. Where does she sleep when it rains?</Source>
      <Dest>这小屋屋顶有洞，下雨时她睡哪？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So...the Jarl's Steward and the Stallion's Potion.  I don't even have joke here.</Source>
      <Dest>所以…… 领主管家和这种马药剂。我是认真的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When Nepos said we weren't leaving his home alive, I got a chill up my spine.  Not that I doubted you, but he was rather convincing.</Source>
      <Dest>当尼普斯说我们不能活着走出他家的时候，我的脊梁骨一阵发冷。不是我不相信你，只是他说话真的很有威慑力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How did they get that man in the cage? And do they drop him for the wolves? Wouldn't he die from the fall? I'm all sorts of confused.</Source>
      <Dest>他们是怎样把他们抓进笼里的？他们把他扔下去喂狼了吗？他有没有摔死？我充满疑惑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow, you managed to escape Cidhna Mine?  Well, I guess I owe Yngvar 10 septims then.</Source>
      <Dest>哇哦，你真的成功从希讷矿坑逃出来啦？呃，那我就欠英格瓦10金币了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ooh, a wreath of snowberries.  I thought being called a snowberry meant you were a squishy little coward.  I wonder if we'll also find milk.</Source>
      <Dest>啊。。雪浆果花丛。我想被称为雪浆果一定是你又蠢又懦弱吧，来，看看我们能不能在你身上发现牛奶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If the Dwarves made these puzzles, the heads would speak the answers.  They would say "Spider, Sphere, Centurion!"  and spit oil if you got it wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>如果那些谜题是由矮人们所制的，那这些脑袋应该会吐出答案来的。它们会说"蜘蛛，矮人球，百夫长！"，而一旦你弄错了的话它们就会喷出油来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I-I don't know how to react at funerals.  People always say the dead are off to a better place, but then why is everyone so sad?</Source>
      <Dest>我。。。我在葬礼上有点儿不知所措。人们总说死了的人正在去往一个更好的地方，但如果是那样，为何每个人都这么伤心呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dead, dead, and dead.  Here's something I don't understand.  Why keep them in cages if you're just going to kill them?</Source>
      <Dest>死人，死人，还是死人。我就是有那么点儿不明白。既然要杀他们那干嘛还得把他们关笼子里呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Agh!  Sorry, I thought that Centurion flinched.  But it was just me.</Source>
      <Dest>诶呀！真对不起，我还以为是百夫长吓的往后退了呢。但那其实是我在后退。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I want to find their Sybil.  I'm not looking for any special reward or anything. Really.  Those priestesses are diseased.</Source>
      <Dest>我想找到她们的先知。说真的，我可不是为了奖赏或者其他什么东西才去找的。那帮女祭司都不大正常了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Great, look at this mess.  You know the owners are going to blame us, and not the creepy tenant they keep in the basement.</Source>
      <Dest>太好了，看看这烂摊子。你知道主人会责怪我们，而不是去责怪那些在地下室里呆着的令人毛骨悚然的占有者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Gods gave you two hands and you use them both for your weapon.  The Gods gave me ten fingers, but I never seem to use more than one.</Source>
      <Dest>众神给了你两只手，你都用来拿武器了。众神给了我十根手指，不过我似乎从没用过一根儿以上的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeack.  Spriggans.  And alchemists wonder why we chop down forests.  I bet that dead one is re-thinking his stance.</Source>
      <Dest>Yeack.  树精. 还有炼金术师都想知道我们为什么要砍伐森林。我敢打赌那个死人会重新考虑他自己的立场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the Eight that was exhilarating!  A dragon, and we killed it!   I'm going to tell everyone at the Bannered Mare tonight that I know you.</Source>
      <Dest>八圣灵在上，这真爽翻了！龙，我们干翻了一头龙！跟你说吧，我今晚得把这事儿告诉母马横幅的每一个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that a bound weapon?  I always knew there was something I liked about you.</Source>
      <Dest>你那是召唤武器吗？我就知道你总能拿出点我喜欢的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How in Cloudrest can 1 person own so many boots? Or maybe he just sniffs them. I knew someone like that. And no, I'm not referring to me this time.</Source>
      <Dest>在云区的人是如何能拥有那么多双鞋的？或者也许他只是根据气味判断的。我认识一个像那样的人。不，这次我说的不是我自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's a lot of cheese on this table.  More cheese than blood.  Are you sure Movarth was a vampire?  Maybe he was a really powerful goat herder.</Source>
      <Dest>这桌子上有许多奶酪，甚至比血都多。你确定莫瓦斯是个吸血鬼？也许他只是个非常强大的牧羊人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So the Forsworn are raiding shipments, but instead of taking weapons or supplies they steal a statue?  No wonder they lost Markarth.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，弃誓者抢了货物，不是为了抢武器或者是补给而是为了抢一个雕像？怪不得他们丢了马卡斯城。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That bow's nice, but with a bound one, you never run out of arrows and they don't cost a septim.  Otherwise I would owe Oblivion a fortune.</Source>
      <Dest>那把弓蛮不错的，可惜一端粘牢了；你不可能逃出弓箭的射程，而且射箭不花钱。否则，我真的欠下这湮灭世界一大笔钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Looks like the people are out for blood.  Does that make them vampires too?</Source>
      <Dest>看起来那些人也是为鲜血而来的。那他们也算是吸血鬼吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now that we've helped these Dibellan priests, they don't have to commune anymore, right?  Someone better tell the local apothecary.</Source>
      <Dest>既然我们都已经帮了这些迪贝拉的祭司了，那她们应该不用再把自个儿锁密室里嘀嘀咕咕了吧？最好找个人跟当地的医生知会一声，就说不用麻烦他们过来治了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you think Skjor will let me inside? I mean, I'm already here. Might as well show me your secret. Not that I'd tell. Really. Please don't kill me.</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得斯科月会让我进去吗？我是说，我已经在这儿了。也许我会瞧见你的秘密。我不会说出去的。真的。请不要杀我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Working for the Thalmor, hm?  Finally come around to the winning side?  Oh, I have no opinion either way.  Your politics are my politics.</Source>
      <Dest>替梭默工作，哼？终于站在胜利者这方了？噢，我怎么都行。你的政治观点就是我的政治观点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You want things forged? Find an Orc. You need a slave-driving foreman? Find an Orc. No offense, but your people are a bit cranky.</Source>
      <Dest>你想要打造东西吗？找个兽人吧。你想要监管奴隶的监工吗？找个兽人吧。无意冒犯，但你们这些人貌似有点儿脾气暴躁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thane of Whiterun.  Better than being, uh, White of Thanerun.  Really, I'm still in shock from the dragon, I'll come up with a better joke next time.</Source>
      <Dest>雪漫城的男爵。嗯，比男漫城的雪爵好点儿。说真的，我还没从对龙的震惊中恢复过来，下次我会想出个更好的笑话的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, since we've been in here I've been wondering.  What in Lorkhan's breath is a Thaumaturgist?</Source>
      <Dest>所以，从我们到这里开始我就一直觉得奇怪。看在洛克汗的份上奇术到底是什么玩意儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You want things forged? Find an Orc. You need a iron-fisted foreman that will work his miners to death? Find an Orc. Never fails.</Source>
      <Dest>你想要锻造？找兽人。你需要一个铁拳领班把他的矿工们工作到死？找兽人。保准让你满意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fresh food, clean house, and nobody seen coming or going.  Maybe there's a a back entrance.  Sometimes the simple answer is the most comforting.</Source>
      <Dest>新鲜的食物，干净的房子，没看到任何人进出。也许这儿有个后门。有时候直线思维是最容易找到答案的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whatever killed these men was particularly vicious. Are you sure we want to stick around here?</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎样杀了这些人是极其恶毒的。你确定我们还要呆在这么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe if we chop wood for them, the Hunter's will give us some of their venison.  You know how to chop wood, right?  Because I don't.</Source>
      <Dest>也许如果我们帮他们砍木头，猎人会愿意给我们一些他们的鹿肉。你知道如何砍柴，对不对？但我不知道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are those...Daedric boots you're wearing?  Otero once told me people who wear daedric artifacts are very promiscuous, but I assumed he made it up.</Source>
      <Dest>你穿的是。。。魔族的靴子吗?  Otero 曾告诉过我带上魔族神器的人会变得很反常, but I assumed he made it up.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow!  Did she just disappear?  Oh no wait, I see her.  I think.  Damn invisibility spells, they get me every time.</Source>
      <Dest>哇噢！她刚才消失了吗？噢不等等，我想我看到她了。他妈的隐形咒语，每次都能耍到我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, Nimhe is kind of cute when she isn't trying to bite your head off.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道吗，尼姆赫没试着咬掉你的头还真有点可爱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They call this place Bannermist Tower.  I see the banner.  Where do you think the mist went off too?</Source>
      <Dest>他们把这里叫做旗霭塔。我看到了旗子，你觉得雾霭跑到哪里去了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>About "Nepos the Nose."  You'd think he would've chosen a name that made him sound less like a criminal, like Nepos the Necromancer or something.</Source>
      <Dest>说说“大鼻子内波斯。” 你想想他总得给自己选一个听上去不像是罪犯的名字, 像是亡灵术士内波斯或者别的啥的肯定不行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This house has some impressive mounts.  I think that Elk is bigger than a dragon.  At least, the one I saw.  Maybe it was a baby dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>这间屋子里有一些令人印象深刻的装饰。我想那头麋鹿应该比龙还大。至少，我看见的那头是这样的。也许是一只小龙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Does this Nimriel ever talk to you?  She doesn't talk to me. And I have cabbages to sell.</Source>
      <Dest>那这位尼姆瑞尔以前跟你聊过么？她倒是没跟我说过话。 并且我还得接着卖我的洋白菜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did you see all those dead skeevers back there?  I just hope that's all of them.  I don't want another case of the ataxia.</Source>
      <Dest>你想回去看看那些被干掉的雪鼠么？我希望那就是全部了。我可不愿意再被麻痹了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bandits.  Maybe if we ask them nicely they'll leave us alone.</Source>
      <Dest>强盗.  如果跟他们好好说下，说不定他们会放过我们.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A vampire lair.  Well, people have always said I think the sun shine's out of my bottom.  So we know they won't come up from behind us.</Source>
      <Dest>有个吸血鬼巢穴。对了，人们总说什么太阳晒屁股了。那他们怕太阳就应该不会出现在我们屁股后面吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At what moment does someone point out that Dawnstar itself is a living nightmare?  I would, but I don't want to be that guy.</Source>
      <Dest>在什么时候，才会有人指出晨星城本身就是一个活生生的梦魇？我是这么想的，但我才不愿成为那个人呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You think with all this technology the Dwemer would have a mechanical carriage or something so we wouldn't have to walk through this infernal ruin.</Source>
      <Dest>你认为以锻莫所掌握的技术而言，可以造一个机械马车或是别的东西，让我们可以不用徒步通这地狱般的遗迹吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's nothing quite like a good adventure, but I'd say relieving oneself comes awfully close.</Source>
      <Dest>没有什么比得过一场冒险了，但我想说这和自我抚慰的感觉非常接近。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know what's the hardest word to say in the entire Tamrielic language?  Orrery.  Of course, the Dwarves are the ones who make them.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道在泰姆瑞尔大陆语言中最难说的那个单词是什么吗？星象仪。当然，矮人是他们的制造者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I were a cave I would fill myself with flowers and benches and liquor.  Why couldn't this cave be more like me?  Stupid cave.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我是个洞穴我就把自己装满鲜花长椅和酒水。为什么这些洞穴不学学我？傻瓜洞穴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's always fun to go traipsing through caves.  Or is it more accurate to say we caper?  Gambol?  Skip?  Frolic?   Help me out here.</Source>
      <Dest>在整个洞穴游荡总是很有趣。或者更确切的说我们是在？嬉戏？跳跃？ 嬉闹？我又在发疯了，赶紧唤醒我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Question.  If we both die, who gets to keep our stuff?</Source>
      <Dest>有个问题。如果我们都死了，我们的遗嘱该怎么写？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whiterun is a city after my own heart.  Too lazy to pick a side.</Source>
      <Dest>白漫城正合我意。我懒得挑了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So Morthal hasn't turned into a bubbling cesspool.  Yet.</Source>
      <Dest>所以墨索尔城没有变为一个冒着热气的粪池。至少现在还没。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hope you're aware there's a clause in my adventurer contract that says I should be treated to at least one meal a day plus dessert.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望你知道，我的冒险家契约的一项条款上明明白白的写着，我应该每天至少有一顿饭后加甜点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is it time to play match the pictures?  I love playing match the pictures. So good to turn off the mind every once and awhile.</Source>
      <Dest>是到了玩儿匹配图片的时间了吗？我爱玩儿匹配图片。每隔一段时间就放松一阵大脑的感觉真爽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know what I expected to find in a place called Embershard mine?  Miners.  And Minstrels.  I'm funny that way.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道我想找个叫煤块矿场的地方吗？矿工，和吟游诗人。我就喜欢这个调调。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've heard people say that wolves can smell fear.  I wonder what it smells like? Probably cheese.</Source>
      <Dest>我听别人说狼能够嗅出恐惧，我在想那闻起来是什麽味道？或许会跟乳酪很像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I once knew a conjurer who kept scamps as pets.  Falmer look like scamps, so it's hard for me to take them seriously.</Source>
      <Dest>我记得有个召唤师把当雪精灵当宠物养。雪精灵看起来挺萌的，哎呀！看来我很难认真对待它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever try sleeping tree sap? I have a friend, yes, a friend who swears by the stuff.  Makes time stand still.  His words, not mine.</Source>
      <Dest>尝试过安眠树脂么? 我有一个朋友，呃，我那朋友指着安眠树脂发誓来着，说是它能让时间静止。这是他说的，可不是我啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Never thought I'd see a dragon in my lifetime...all that's left now is a dancing bear and a humble Jarl and my life will be complete.</Source>
      <Dest>我从没想到我这辈子能看见龙...等我有朝一日再看到一头会跳舞的熊或者一个低声下气的领主的时候那我的人生就圆满啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fair warning.  Friendly fire is not uncommon with me.  It's not that I forgot how to aim.  It's just that I never really knew how.</Source>
      <Dest>这警告对我来说很合理。误伤对我来说并不少见。不是说我忘了怎么瞄准，而是我真的不知道该如何去瞄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These bedrolls are bunched awfully close together.  I guess even Orcs get lonely.</Source>
      <Dest>这些铺盖卷也摆得太近了吧。我猜大概是因为兽人也会寂寞吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As an adventurer, I've experienced some of the most intense wounds you can imagine, but nothing comes close to biting the inside of your lip.</Source>
      <Dest>作为一个冒险者，我经受过你所能想象到的最严重的伤的折磨，但这些都比不上你嘴里冒出来的那些所给我带来的痛苦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I haven't conjured a dagger in ages.  I hope they haven't changed the spell.</Source>
      <Dest>我好久没召唤过匕首了。希望他们还没改过咒语。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you think the water here's safe to drink?  It's looks so clean, but we're in a mine.</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得这里的水能喝吗？它看起来是很干净，但我们可是在矿坑里啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if any of the mages here would even recognize my robes weren't genuine.  No one pays any attention to the novices.</Source>
      <Dest>我甚至怀疑这里的法师根本不会认出我的法袍是假冒的。完全没有人关注新人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some say I'm one part of Elves Ear and two parts nightshade.  What does that make me?  A terrible alchemist.</Source>
      <Dest>有人说我的成分就是三分之一的精灵耳加三分之二的夜茄。而我究竟从何而来呢？一个可怕的炼金术士创造了我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say Polydor and Eloisa were doomed because of the cruel nature of the world.  Maybe Eloisa just got fat.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说佩拉吉奥和埃洛伊萨注定失败是因为世界的残酷。也许埃洛伊萨只是太胖了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever heard of the Arena?  If they ever made a competition out of eating Elsweyr Fondue, I'd be Grand Champion.  And a skooma addict.</Source>
      <Dest>听说过竞技场么？他们要是办一场吃艾斯维尔乳酪大赛,我肯定是冠军。然后我就会用奖金去做个斯库玛瘾君子。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So is there where we meet Halldir?  Should we have brought wine?  We are guests in his home, after all.</Source>
      <Dest>那我们在哪儿跟霍迪尔见面？我们该带瓶酒当见面礼吗？毕竟，在他家的话我们都是客人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What if trolls weren't trying to slap you, but shake your hand?  Beasts are so misunderstood.</Source>
      <Dest>如果那帮巨人不是想杀你，而只是想跟你握个手呢？野兽的想法经常会被误解的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've never been to an Orc Stronghold. But I've never tried to swallow a live rodent either.  Some things just never cross your mind, until they do.</Source>
      <Dest>我从未去过兽人要塞，也从未尝试过生吞一只活鼠。这些想法头一次穿过我的脑壳。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I bet oakflesh was invented so we wouldn't have to wear clothes, and by the world's foremost pervert.</Source>
      <Dest>我敢打赌，树皮术一定是被一个世界顶尖的绅士发明出来的，目的是让我们不用穿衣服了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It must be tough being married to an illusionist.  It'd just be so hard to have a real conversation.</Source>
      <Dest>跟一个幻术师结婚肯定很蛋疼。每一次对话都讲得人云里雾里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Funny.  When they said their king wore rags, I assumed the Forsworn were an army of beggars.</Source>
      <Dest>真有趣。当他们说到他们自己的褴褛国王的时候，我还以为弃誓者是一支乞丐组成的军队呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Snow?  In Skyrim? Surprising, that.</Source>
      <Dest>雪？在天际省？恩，真让人惊讶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At the risk of sounding a bit whiny, my feet are tired.  I know we're in a dangerous Nord ruin and can't stop, but I just wanted to put it out there.</Source>
      <Dest>也许你会觉得我爱发牢骚，但我的脚实在是累了。我知道我们身处一座危机四伏的诺德遗迹中，不容许片刻停留。但我就是想休息一下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So we raid a simple Nord ruin and it's crawling with Draugr.  Total coincidence, I'm sure.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我们洗劫了一个简陋的诺德遗迹，里面爬满了尸鬼。完完全全的巧合，我确定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How do they live on this rock with so little fertile land?  I suppose they trade cabbages for ore.  But you can never run out of cabbages.</Source>
      <Dest>他们是在这片有着如此贫瘠的石头地上是怎么生活的？我猜他们用卷心菜换矿石。卷心菜是永远不会枯竭的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Otero once told me, "You can grab a Khajiit by the tail but not by the whiskers.  Unless he's a warlock, at which point run like hell."</Source>
      <Dest>奥特罗曾经告诉我，"你可以随便抓虎人的尾巴，但千万别薅他们的须子，除非他是个术士，他会尖叫着逃跑的。"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Markarth is one of the prettier cities in all of Skyrim.  Coincidentally, the Nords had nothing to do with it.  Just an observation.</Source>
      <Dest>马卡斯城是天际省最漂亮的城市之一。巧合的是，马斯卡城正好不是诺德人的作品。这只是一个外来人的看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, if you really wanted to give Nurelion a quick death, you should've just told him his apprentice and I were in love. </Source>
      <Dest>你知道的，如果你真的想给Nurelion一个痛快，你就应该直接告诉他，他的徒弟和我正在谈恋爱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If this is a Hagraven nest,  I think you should take the lead.  A bigger lead than usual.  No, I insist.</Source>
      <Dest>如果这就是乌鸦鬼婆的巢穴的话,我想应该由你来做指挥官。比通常权利更大的指挥官。不对，我是确信应该如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, just in time for dinner! What's on the menu?  Ugh, people again? Alright, but I'm not eating anything from below the waist.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，晚饭时间到！菜谱上都有什么？啊呸，又是人类？好吧，但人下水什么的我可不吃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Does the college pay taxes to the Jarl of Winterhold?  I'm struggling to see what the economy here is based on.</Source>
      <Dest>这学院给冬堡的领主交税了吗？我特别想看看这里的经济基础是什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Isn't it strange to have a day when you haven't killed a bear?</Source>
      <Dest>要是哪天你没干掉一头熊，你不会觉得不爽吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So how did this bandit become chief anyway?  I hope it wasn't for brains, because I don't think standing in a pool of oil is a smart idea.</Source>
      <Dest>总之这个强盗是怎么改行小偷的？我看不是因为变聪明了，因为站在一汪油里面可不是明智之举。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I did carry a sword, I wouldn't learn how to use it.  I'd just get an Akaviri one and call it a day.</Source>
      <Dest>就算我有一把剑，我也不会去学着使用它。哪怕我拿到手的是阿卡维尔剑，我也会把它束之高阁的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, I am so tired of being mistaken for Ulfric Stormcloak. </Source>
      <Dest>你知道，我已经对被误认为是乌佛瑞克·暴风斗篷感到厌烦了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if the Dwarves made airships.  We could use it to fly over the Jerall Mountains, then come back when we realized we were in Cyrodiil.</Source>
      <Dest>我好奇矮人是否做出了飞船。当我们真的到了赛瑞迪尔，我们可以通过它飞越杰洛山脉然后返回。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They call this place Mazin...Mmm-zoon...Blast, is it me or do Dwarves have something against vowels?</Source>
      <Dest>他们管这里叫 Mazin...Mmm-zoon...Blast, 是我还是矮人发元音有问题?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are those mammoth tusks?  What are mammoths doing in a place like this?</Source>
      <Dest>这是长毛象的牙齿?  长毛象在这里做什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did I ever tell you I was allergic to animals?  That's right, all of them.</Source>
      <Dest>我有没有告诉过你，我对动物过敏？是的，对所有动物都过敏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What if these ruins were built not to keep adventurers out, but to keep Draugr in?  No, that's just the skooma talking.</Source>
      <Dest>假使这些废墟不是为了阻止冒险者进来，而是为了阻止什么危险的东西出来会怎么样呢？。得了吧，这话说得就像刚嗑完斯库玛之后一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Damn you!</Source>
      <Dest>混蛋！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're nothing!</Source>
      <Dest>你这无名小卒！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't wait to see who Ahtar will execute next.  It's really the only entertainment this city has.</Source>
      <Dest>真等不及要看看下一个被 阿塔处决的是谁。这真是这城里唯一的乐趣所在了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Aaaaayyargh!</Source>
      <Dest>啊～～咿呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This inn looks tidy enough.  Maybe only half the beds are infested with fleas.</Source>
      <Dest>这家客栈是人住的地方吗？也许床上有一半儿的地方都被跳蚤霸占了啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever dress like a priest so people would trust you with their darkest secrets?  Um...me neither.</Source>
      <Dest>穿的像个女祭司人们就会向你倾吐最黑暗的秘密么？唔……反正我不会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do your worst!</Source>
      <Dest>你还是做好最坏的打算吧！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Victory is yours!  I yield!  See me yielding?</Source>
      <Dest>胜利是属于你的！我投降了！嘿！我在向你投降你看到了吗？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Agh! Enough! This ends now!</Source>
      <Dest>嘿！够了！已经结束了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I love small towns.  None of that cooked garbage smell you get in the cities.  Although I guess that's more of a Cyrodiil problem.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢小镇。那里没有你在城市里闻到的黑暗料理的味道。虽然我猜这更多的是赛瑞迪尔的问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Spare me!  I'm too pretty to die!</Source>
      <Dest>饶了我吧！我很漂亮，我还不想死！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You can't win this!</Source>
      <Dest>就你这两下子还想获胜？！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hyargh!</Source>
      <Dest>嘿呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You need to do better than that!</Source>
      <Dest>你需要做得更好！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Agh!  Bastard!</Source>
      <Dest>啊！混蛋！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take that, you fiend!</Source>
      <Dest>接招吧，你个魔鬼！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Die, damn you!</Source>
      <Dest>去死吧，混蛋！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Go back to where you came from, dragon!</Source>
      <Dest>巨龙，滚回你来的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, don't kill me!  I-I have gold, I swear!</Source>
      <Dest>等等，别杀我！我，我有钱，我发誓！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Draugr always make me think of pirates with scurvy.  I wonder why that is.</Source>
      <Dest>尸鬼总让我想起得了坏血病的海盗。不知道为什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is this what you want?</Source>
      <Dest>这就是你想要的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like the bite of a flea!</Source>
      <Dest>就被跳蚤咬了一口！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've had enough of you!</Source>
      <Dest>我受够你了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm in the mood for some red meat.  And a flagon of something so strong it makes the goats look like wenches.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在特别要一个娘们儿. 刚那壶酒好烈，究竟什么东西，我现在看着羊长得都娘们一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll kill you, beastman!</Source>
      <Dest>我非杀你不可，畜生！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just...stand still!</Source>
      <Dest>站住…别动！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That the best you can do?</Source>
      <Dest>这就是你的极限了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some legend you are!</Source>
      <Dest>你只不过会夸夸其谈而已！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the Gods that hurt!</Source>
      <Dest>卧槽好疼！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ist that it? Is that your best?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？这就是你的极限吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I used to know this Dunmer mage.  Very heroic.  Every now and then though, he'd wear a thief's costume.   I wonder what your vice is.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾知道这个暗精灵。很英勇。不过常常穿盗贼的衣服。我在想你的癖好是啥。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Agh!</Source>
      <Dest>啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Agh!</Source>
      <Dest>啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh, you fiend!</Source>
      <Dest>呃，你这魔鬼！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You want Esbern?  I'll teach you to pick on old men!</Source>
      <Dest>你要伊斯本？我要教教你找老人的茬的代价！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, I discovered the other day that shopkeepers will still buy your goods even if you treat them poorly.  Good to know.</Source>
      <Dest>我发现即使有你对待那些小店主很糟糕，他们仍然会买你的货物。可是条好消息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can take you!</Source>
      <Dest>你完了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll have your head!</Source>
      <Dest>我要剁你的脑袋！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Does this inn have a bard?  I'm feeling nostalgic, and my ears are thirsty for song.</Source>
      <Dest>这旅馆里有没有吟游诗人？我有点想家了，而且我很想听歌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You picked the wrong dinner, animal!</Source>
      <Dest>你选错晚餐了，畜生！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I want to ask people who only drink wine, do you enjoy being an arrogant sod?</Source>
      <Dest>我想问问那些只喝葡萄酒的家伙，你愿不愿意变成一个傲慢的大草包？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A wise alchemist once told me the two ingredients a person should never, ever mix together are nirnroot and...I forget the rest.</Source>
      <Dest>一个很有才的炼金术士曾经告诉过我，一个人永远永远也不能把那两种材料混在一起，这两种材料分别是奈恩根和……额，后面那个我给忘了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The joke's on us. There's no treasure save this ring. Still, I had fun.</Source>
      <Dest>这是个玩笑。这个指环不会带来任何宝藏，不过，我还是挺开心的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As for the bard, do you want to go to the College in Solitude?</Source>
      <Dest>至于成为诗人，你想去独孤城的学院吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As for the bard, do you want to go to the College in Solitude?</Source>
      <Dest>至于成为诗人，你想去独孤城的学院吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As for the bard, do you want to go to the College in Solitude?</Source>
      <Dest>至于成为诗人，你想去独孤城的学院吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As for the bard, do you want to go to the College in Solitude?</Source>
      <Dest>至于成为诗人，你想去独孤城的学院吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll cut right through your scales, monster!</Source>
      <Dest>我会连你的鳞片一刀切的，怪物！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You won't get away!</Source>
      <Dest>你跑不了！ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I get that he's a necromancer, but what do you mean you never saw eye to eye?</Source>
      <Dest>我知道他是个亡灵法师啊，不过你说你们从来没见过是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, fought any good Giants lately? Or deranged princesses?</Source>
      <Dest>所以，最近和那个巨人搏斗了？　或是看上了哪一個无知的少女？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if any of the Companions know how to sing? We should stop by Jorrvaskr find out before we go asking a bard if he can swing a mace.</Source>
      <Dest>战友团里有人会唱歌吗？我们应该在前往月瓦斯卡寻找那个可能会唱歌的人之前，随便去问哪个吟游诗人是否能挥舞得起狼牙棒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you think of this idea, Karras? An entire regiment using bound weapons.</Source>
      <Dest>让全团的人都使用统一的武器。你觉得这个主意怎么样， 卡拉斯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't stand a chance!</Source>
      <Dest>你一点机会也没有！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A ring? Hold on, is that what I think it is? A sapphire ring that lets you...(gulp)...breathe underwater? Oh no..we've made a horrible mistake!</Source>
      <Dest>一个戒指？等一下，是不是我想的那样？一个蓝宝石戒指能让你……（喘气）……在水下呼吸？哦不……我犯了一个大错误！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know, it sounds to me like the only difference is I have to pay you money. </Source>
      <Dest>我不知道，似乎唯一的区别就是我不得不向你掏钱了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now you'll pay!</Source>
      <Dest>为你悲惨的生活求饶吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I won't die today, not against you!</Source>
      <Dest>我今天是不会死的，至少是不会死在你的面前的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Drink someone else's blood, vampire!</Source>
      <Dest>离我远点，吸血鬼！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That would probably be a bad idea. We want someone who can handle themselves in a fight.</Source>
      <Dest>那可能是个坏主意。我们想要个能够在战斗自保的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're going to look good mounted on my wall!</Source>
      <Dest>你会变成我墙上挂的战利品！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll tear you to pieces!</Source>
      <Dest>我要把你撕碎！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Say hello to Ysmir for me, Nord!</Source>
      <Dest>帮我向伊斯米尔问个好，诺德佬！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why don't you stay dead this time!</Source>
      <Dest>这个时候你应该在死人堆里！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Damn rebels!</Source>
      <Dest>该死的叛军。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come on, is that all you've got!</Source>
      <Dest>得了吧，你就这点本事？！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yield or die!</Source>
      <Dest>投降或者死！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've had enough of you!</Source>
      <Dest>我受够你了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With three beers down, the Orc did frown and bid the Elf goodbye, for none could know twas not for show, and someone had to die!</Source>
      <Dest>三杯啤酒穿肠走，兽人跟精灵要分手。这不是一次表演秀，而是有某人要死咯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come on, I can take you!</Source>
      <Dest>来吧，我可以对付你！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why won't you die already?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么还不去死？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That was a bottle of imitation skooma. I carry it around sometimes because it makes me look more dangerous.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一瓶仿制的斯库玛。我有时候带着它到处转，因为这让我看起来更不好惹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're outmatched!</Source>
      <Dest>你输了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I had a conscience, and I'm beginning to suspect I might, it would weigh heavily on it if I got some poor lutist killed.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我还心存良知，我可能会开始怀疑自己。如果我杀了一些可怜的琵琶弹奏者，这会有很大影响吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's ridiculous. I don't even like skooma.</Source>
      <Dest>真是荒谬。 我根本就不喜欢skooma.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's an odd question, coming from blacksmith of Kvatch. Don't your weapons practically come from Oblivion?</Source>
      <Dest>这是个奇怪的问题，科瓦奇来的铁匠铸造的武器。你的武器难道不是从从湮灭弄来的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just filthy. This treasure of yours lets you breathe underwater, but that's it.</Source>
      <Dest>这真是个糟糕玩意儿。你的这个宝物可以让你在水下呼吸，但也仅此而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Century old Giant Broth would make for a great soup.</Source>
      <Dest>百年巨人肉汤一定会成为一道美味的汤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Century old Giant Broth would make for a great soup.</Source>
      <Dest>百年巨人肉汤一定会成为一道美味的汤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There was a body down there, and a ring.</Source>
      <Dest>那里有一具戴着指环的尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I still prefer to kill the Giant rather than put him to sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>我依旧愿意杀掉巨人，胜过哄他睡觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I still prefer to kill the Giant rather than put him to sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>我依旧愿意杀掉巨人，胜过哄他睡觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I still prefer to kill the Giant rather than put him to sleep.</Source>
      <Dest>我依旧愿意杀掉巨人，胜过哄他睡觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm soaking wet and tired, and all for a ring and some dead Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>我泡在水里，全身湿透，筋疲力竭。还全是为了那枚戒指和一些死去的精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm soaking wet and tired, and all for a ring and some dead Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>我泡在水里，全身湿透，筋疲力竭。还全是为了那枚戒指和一些死去的精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't like the idea of putting Fjona in danger.</Source>
      <Dest>我不喜欢这个让费欧娜去冒险的主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't like the idea of putting Fjona in danger.</Source>
      <Dest>我不喜欢这个让费欧娜去冒险的主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't like the idea of putting Fjona in danger.</Source>
      <Dest>我不喜欢这个让费欧娜去冒险的主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you saying this Giant sleeps underwater?</Source>
      <Dest>你的意思是那个巨人沉睡在水下？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you saying this Giant sleeps underwater?</Source>
      <Dest>你的意思是那个巨人沉睡在水下？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you saying this Giant sleeps underwater?</Source>
      <Dest>你的意思是那个巨人沉睡在水下？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And, seeing how well sound travels in a cave, that Giant will be able to hear her play from there as well.</Source>
      <Dest>并且，以声音在洞穴中传播的效果来看，那个巨人从那边也能听见她的演奏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Probably because it tastes like century old Giant broth.</Source>
      <Dest>可能是因为它的味道像是搁了有些年头儿的巨人肉汤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm hoping bringing the others will help us avoid that scenario, or at least give us ample time to run away.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望带来的其他人能帮助我们避免这种情况，或者至少留给我们留足时间逃跑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm hoping bringing the others will help us avoid that scenario, or at least give us ample time to run away.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望带来的其他人能帮助我们避免这种情况，或者至少留给我们留足时间逃跑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Actually, I forgot to mention one other part. The song will put him to sleep, but he won't stay that way.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，我忘记提另一点了。这首歌会让他入睡，不过他不会一直那样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is it dead, or just sleeping?</Source>
      <Dest>它死了吗？还是只是在睡觉？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, the dead ones are proof enough. Also the footprints those bodies are lying in.</Source>
      <Dest>当然,死人还不足以为证。还有这些留下的脚印。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did you find anything? Are we filthy rich, or just filthy?</Source>
      <Dest>你找到什么了吗？我们能走狗屎运吗，还是只有狗屎？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And before you ask, don't worry, I'm not a total idiot. The first thing I did was secure a bottle from one of the local traders.</Source>
      <Dest>你不用问，别担心，我没那么白痴。我当时做的第一件事就是从一个当地小贩那里保住了一个瓶子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, maybe I should explain. You see, this Giant isn't a normal Giant. Well, it used to be, but then an old Hagraven cast a spell on it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，也许我应该解释一下。你看，这不是一个正常的巨人。嗯，它曾经是，但那个老乌鸦鬼婆曾对它施了个法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hopefully you're not talking about me being the dead Elf. Wait, what do you mean by a ring? It doesn't let you breathe underwater, does it?</Source>
      <Dest>但愿你不是在说让我成为那个死的精灵。等等，你说的是什么意思，一个戒指？不会是能让你在水下呼吸的那个吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>On the other hand, I'm half a halfwit. Who's to say anything I say is logical?</Source>
      <Dest>另一方面，我是半个笨蛋。谁说我说得都是符合逻辑的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just don't ask from who. Although if you want a hint, it rhymes with "Ybolda."</Source>
      <Dest>别问是谁。要是你想要个提示，发音是“伊博尔达”的韵脚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, there's a catch. Legend has it that the spell is activated not with magic, but with a song.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，是有个窍门。传说那个法术不是用魔力来施展，而是用一首歌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, I think we better get going. I hear someone calling me somewhere over there. Away from the crazy person.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我认为我们最好离开这儿。我听见那里的某个地方有人在喊我。我们得离疯子远点儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Underwater? Wait, that ring wasn't attached to some beautiful princess, was it? Don't tell me that halfwit was telling the truth!</Source>
      <Dest>在水底下？等等，这个戒指该不会是属于某个漂亮的公主的吧？别告诉我那个蠢货说的是真的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I just assumed he was being a romantic.</Source>
      <Dest>但我只是以为他在幻想。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I really like the looks of this Jonas fellow. But the wench doesn't seem too impressed, and I trust my wenches. I guess it's off to the marsh then.</Source>
      <Dest>我确实喜欢乔纳斯这小子的模样。不过我家女招待看不上，而且我相信姑娘们的眼光。我猜之后是去了沼泽地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although granted, I rather be a short Elf than a dead one. We're far more likely to end the day six feet under as opposed to five feet tall.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管你做了保证，我还是宁愿去当一个矮精灵而不是死精灵。我觉得我当一个5英尺的矮精灵活下来的概率比一个6英尺的死精灵高多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not unless we add a little something extra to his blood. Like say, via a sword coated in sleeping tree sap?</Source>
      <Dest>除非我们在他的血里添点儿额外的料。比如说，把剑涂上一层沉睡之树的液汁如何？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You called me a mage. I don't know whether to be flattered or disgusted.</Source>
      <Dest>你说我是……一个法师？我真是不知该笑还是该哭了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, and I prefer to remain the height I am now as opposed to being clubbed so hard I wake up a Wood Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，并且相对于被木棒狠狠地砸扁，我更乐意保持现在的身高，所以我叫醒了一个木精灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, we're here. If the legend is true, then this Giant should be waking up as soon as I began this sentence five seconds ago.</Source>
      <Dest>得，我们已经到这儿了。如果传言不虚，那大块头在我五秒钟前开始念咒的时候就该醒了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nonsense! Why would...oh Gods...</Source>
      <Dest>废话！为什么会……哦上帝啊……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not everything in life has a point, Fjona. Like this adventure. It just is. That's what I'm taking away from all this.</Source>
      <Dest>生活中不是每件事都有明确方向的，费欧娜。就如同这场冒险一样。正因如此，我才要远离这一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean seriously, those muscles were bigger than her entire head! All three of our heads put together!</Source>
      <Dest>我说真的，那些肌肉比她整个脑袋还大！比我们三个脑袋加在一起还大！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although it could've been all the mead he was drinking.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然这有可能是他所喝下的所有蜂蜜酒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So they say. Problem is, half the hunters who go into that cave end up dead, and the other half see nothing at all.</Source>
      <Dest>他们是这样讲的。问题是，一半进这个洞穴的猎人死了，另一半却什么都没看见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the way, in all seriousness, you should never leave soup stock out overnight. Sure, you can boil away the toxins, but it'll also lose flavor.</Source>
      <Dest>顺带说一句，永远都不要把汤放过夜。当然你可以将其再次煮沸消毒，但是这样也会失去原有的鲜美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, hold on. Fjona has to coax it to sleep first. I know when I get out of bed the first thing I want to do is hop back in.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，坚持住。费欧娜得先哄它睡觉。我就知道我起床后第一件想干的事儿就是希望再蹦回被子里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I would do it myself, but I use bound weapons, and I'm not a hundred percent sure it would work.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我自己干好了，不过我要用的是武器缠绕召唤术，我不能百分百地保证法术能生效。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't see how it could hurt. Maybe I should sing as well.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得没什么不好的。或许我也该唱两嗓子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wow. That's amazing. I taught myself how to shuffle a deck of cards once. It's even less impressive when you consider I was a grown Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>哇。太不可思议。我曾经自学过怎么洗扑克牌。作为一个成年精灵，我这方面太逊色了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And Anum-La, a bound sword never dulls. Of course, I don't want to brag, but you do need a bit of magical talent to wield both. </Source>
      <Dest>而且，阿努姆拉,好剑永远不会钝.我也不想吹牛，但是掌握召唤武器和正确的吹嘘都需要天赋的. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think you said "soup" when you meant to say "poison."  It was an honest mistake, I'm sure.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为你说“汤”的时候你其实是在说“毒药”。这是真诚的错误，我敢肯定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, did that body belong to a princess? Don't tell me that halfwit was right! Which means that ring...</Source>
      <Dest>等会，那是公主？别告诉我那个蠢蛋是对的！这意味着那戒指…</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, that's one down, and one to go.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，那就是一个走了一个死了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not a clue.</Source>
      <Dest>毫无头绪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was him! He did it! You marry him!</Source>
      <Dest>是了！他做到了！你终于嫁给了他！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Supposedly it's been asleep for centuries at the bottom of a lake, cradling an old treasure left by the witch.</Source>
      <Dest>据说它已经在湖底沉睡了几百年，怀中抱着一个女巫留下的陈旧宝藏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, maybe he is a milk-drinker. But what if he's not? All I'm saying is, we just put him in front of a Giant, and see what happens.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，也许他是一个懦夫。但如果他不是呢？我想说的是，我们就把他放在一个巨人面前，看看会发生什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was her! She did it! You marry her!</Source>
      <Dest>那是她！她做到了！你娶了她！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was her! She did it! You marry her!</Source>
      <Dest>那是她！她做到了！你娶了她！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For instance, Fjona, think of how much time and energy you can save by not having to loot corpses for stray arrows.</Source>
      <Dest>举个例子，费欧娜，要是不必再从尸体上寻回箭矢，想想你能节省多少时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh no, here it comes...</Source>
      <Dest>哦不，又来了……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And risk that Giant waking up and biting my head off? Besides, that water looks cold.</Source>
      <Dest>这风险可略大啊。要是巨人醒来咬掉我的头怎么办？而且，这水看上去好冷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He seemed to fall asleep whenever Karita stopped singing and played those soft instrumentals. You know, the same one all you bards play.</Source>
      <Dest>貌似只要Karita 不唱歌只弹那些乐器他就会睡着. 你懂的，就是中你们吟遊诗人都用的那些乐器.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, then let's go. If that's okay with you, being the leader and everything.</Source>
      <Dest>好的, 我们上路吧. 如果你准备好了, 所有东西都由你说了算.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Apparently, a lot of hunters like to frequent this cave, and there's even a small lake toward the rear, but no one ever drinks from it.</Source>
      <Dest>很明显，许多猎人喜欢频繁光顾这个洞穴，后面往前走一段甚至还有个小湖，但是没人从那里喝过水。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, we have our bard and our Giant slayer. All that's left to do now is find our Giant.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，吟游诗人和巨人杀手都已经具备了，只欠巨人了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As I matter of fact, I've met a Giant before. Well, a puny one, but a Giant nonetheless.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我以前遇到过巨人。好吧，一只小巨人，尽管如此那仍然是个巨人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh trust me, if this Giant really does wake up, we'll be able to see it from the other side of the cavern.</Source>
      <Dest>相信我,如果这个巨人被唤醒了, 我们就会在洞穴的另一边见到它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Let's go.</Source>
      <Dest>走吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me. I need your help.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着我。我需要你的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me. I need your help.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着我。我需要你的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you're enjoying the festivities.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你喜欢这个节日。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you're enjoying the festivities.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你喜欢这个节日。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, everything is perfect. I'm just glad you're here.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，一切都很完美。我只庆幸你也在这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, everything is perfect. I'm just glad you're here.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，一切都很完美。我只庆幸你也在这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We need to escape this reality. Are you with me or not?</Source>
      <Dest>我们必须逃离这份现实，你会和我一起吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't worry about me, I'm in the best shape of Sload's life.</Source>
      <Dest>别为我担心,我在蛤蟆人当中算混得不错的了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, you already have someone.  I don't want to be a third wheel.</Source>
      <Dest>你已经有人陪着你了，我可不想当电灯泡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What does it look like?  Saving your scaley tail.</Source>
      <Dest>它看起来像什么?除了你的鳞片尾巴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right now it's saying something so beautiful, my tongue is jealous it didn't think of it first. But it loves you all the same.</Source>
      <Dest>现在它在说如此优美的话语，实在令我的舌头感到嫉妒老天没有宠爱它。但它依旧喜欢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course. I'm not big on debauchery and wild parties. These sort of simple gatherings between friends is precisely where I excel.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。我可不热衷于花天酒地和狂野派对。这样朋友间的简单聚会才是我想去的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So is it true what they say, that you ride an armored chaurus? Please tell me it's true.</Source>
      <Dest>那么他们说你骑了一头披甲的查鲁斯是真的喽?？请告诉我那是真的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now I don't want to sound like a Bound Weapon peddler, if such a thing even exists, but you two really ought to consider using them.</Source>
      <Dest>我不想像个小贩似的给你们推销召唤武器，要是有人卖这个的话，不过你们真的应该用用看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am too. I know I'm not good at romantic overtures, so I'll just let my smile do the talking.</Source>
      <Dest>我也是，我知道我不擅长浪漫的提议，所以我只会在说话的时候带上微笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I die, I want you to bury me in a coffin.  Made of pie.</Source>
      <Dest>要是我挂了，希望给我订制个棺材——用馅饼做的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did I ever tell you what my name means in the old Aldmeri?  That's because I have no idea.</Source>
      <Dest>我有没有告诉过你我的名字在古语的意义？ 这是因为我也不知道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I...I can't believe the old wolf is dead.</Source>
      <Dest>我……我不敢相信这只老狼已经死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We heading out?  Let me just conjure up the energy.</Source>
      <Dest>出发么？补充点能量吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Should we get moving?</Source>
      <Dest>我们该动身了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whose side are you on?</Source>
      <Dest>你站在哪一边？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let's go.</Source>
      <Dest>走吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You lead, I'll follow.</Source>
      <Dest>你带路，我跟着你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some say Rumarin is a feminine name.  But I'm not a girl, I just fight like one.</Source>
      <Dest>有些人说罗美勒是个女性的名字。但人家才不是女生，人家只是在打架的时候像。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, I heard there was a legendary knight living in this town.</Source>
      <Dest>等等，我听说这座小镇里住着个传奇骑士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That guard saw a dragon?  I'll believe it when I see it.  I'll stop believing when I wake up, but for that moment I'll believe.</Source>
      <Dest>那个守卫看见了一条龙？我亲眼看见就会相信。不过我一醒来就又不信了，但就在那一刻我会相信的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that should tie everything up in a neat little bow. You got your forgery, I got my debt erased, and Sunken-Roots got his life back.</Source>
      <Dest> 好了，这样我们就皆大欢喜了。你得到了你的伪造物，我清除了我的债务，而且桑肯‧树根也救了他的命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you sure you don't have some buyer's remorse? I mean Anum-La is great, but did you see the size of that Jonas fellow?</Source>
      <Dest>你确定你真的一点不后悔？我是说，阿努姆拉确实很棒，但你看到那个乔纳斯的体格没有？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ready to get moving?</Source>
      <Dest>准备好出发了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For Kodlak!  I just want to feel included.</Source>
      <Dest>为了克拉科！我只是也想出把力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My mother always said, "Never Thu'um with your mouth full."</Source>
      <Dest>我妈妈总说，“不要张口闭口就吐目的。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fine, if you're going to be such a sod about it, we'll just let you rot in here.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。如果你对这这么依赖，我们就让你腐烂在这里算了。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's your classical happy ending. Unless you're a bandit, then it went about as badly as one could expect.</Source>
      <Dest>你将会获得一个典型的美好结局。除非你是个强盗，真是那样的话，你的下场将会惨得出人意料的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah!  You hit me!  I can't believe it!  The pain!  So much pain!  And...wait a minute...I felt something else as well....in my hand...</Source>
      <Dest>啊！你打我！我不相信！好疼啊！真的好疼啊！而且……等等……我觉得其他东西……在我的手里……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You did say she plays primarily in Old Hroldan, right? And this journal is from a bard in Markarth. Sounds like a cheap, neighborly bard to me.</Source>
      <Dest>你确定你说过她一般在老霍尔丹表演，是吗？这次旅途是由一个在马卡斯的诗人发起的。听起来还真是个俭吝友善的诗人，对我来说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that was fast.  I didn't even finish counting down half of the 99 barrels of Elves off the wall.</Source>
      <Dest>哇，这可真快。  我还没把99数到一半呢，一圈精灵就从墙上下来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May your road lead to other followers you wouldn't possibly consider replacing me with.  Also, warm sands.  I've always wanted to say that.</Source>
      <Dest>愿在你的前方尽是一些你不是想到取代我的追随者等着你。当然，还有温暖的沙地。我一直想这么说啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright, that's one down, and one to go.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，那就是一个走了一个死了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What's the matter with you!</Source>
      <Dest>你有毛病啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh come on, Sunken-Roots, you would break the moment they threatened to pluck a feather.</Source>
      <Dest>噢得了，桑肯-树根，你会毁了他们威胁着要拔毛的这一刻的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Has this Dibellan amulet been properly washed? I'm just saying, we have no idea where it's been. </Source>
      <Dest>这件迪贝拉挂件有被清洗过吗?我只是问问，现在我们找不到它究竟被放在了哪里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Married to adventure and each other.  I've always wanted multiple spouses.</Source>
      <Dest>要是能和冒险结婚的话。我估计就忍不住得犯重婚罪了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, love. Just tell me which wizard I need to kill, or what magical artifact I need to shatter, or how many times I should click my heels.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，亲爱的。告诉我我应该杀掉哪个巫师，或者应该毁掉哪些魔器，或者我应该用脚跟互磕几次。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I have one bone to pick with Zora, it's the location. If she wanted to have the party here, she could have at least asked me to cook.</Source>
      <Dest>硬要我在佐拉那儿鸡蛋里挑骨头，我觉得是选址。如果她想在这里开场聚会，她至少应该让我为聚会掌勺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's comforting to know.</Source>
      <Dest>得知这些我很欣慰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure, that works for me.</Source>
      <Dest>没问题，这对我来说蛮有用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm right behind you.</Source>
      <Dest>我紧随在后。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh right.  I still haven't paid you for that, have I.</Source>
      <Dest>哦对了。我还没有把它付给你，对吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, what's the plan?</Source>
      <Dest>计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So Fjona, is it true that you're self-taught?</Source>
      <Dest>所以费欧娜，你真的是自学成才的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, so I need a saddle and...oh...you're being sarcastic! You know, I don't like it so much when other people do it to me.</Source>
      <Dest>等下, 那么我需要一副鞍具和...噢...你这是在指桑骂槐！你懂的，我不喜欢别人这么对干。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey, be careful!</Source>
      <Dest>嘿，小心点！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My invisible, magic sword is yours.</Source>
      <Dest>我将我那无形之魔法剑授予你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you. I'd hate to think I was slipping.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你。我讨厌迷路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wait, so you're the Argonian who braves the marsh? I was expecting some...burlier.</Source>
      <Dest>等等，这么说你就是那些勇敢面对沼泽的亚龙人？我还以为会……更强壮些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're someone I confide in. I need to talk about the events of the past month.</Source>
      <Dest>你是我信任的人，我想谈谈过去一个月的事件</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've been having a lot of dreams, and I'm not sure what's real.</Source>
      <Dest>我有很多梦想，但是不知道可不可以实现。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've been having a lot of dreams, and I'm not sure what's real.</Source>
      <Dest>我有很多梦想，但是不知道可不可以实现。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've been having a lot of dreams, and I'm not sure what's real.</Source>
      <Dest>我有很多梦想，但是不知道可不可以实现。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I know what everyone did, but I wasn't there. My mind was in another place.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道别人都怎么想，但是我当时并不算是在那里。我当时在琢磨其他的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I know what everyone did, but I wasn't there. My mind was in another place.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道别人都怎么想，但是我当时并不算是在那里。我当时在琢磨其他的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I know what everyone did, but I wasn't there. My mind was in another place.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道别人都怎么想，但是我当时并不算是在那里。我当时在琢磨其他的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So, fought any good Giants lately? Or deranged princesses?</Source>
      <Dest>所以，最近和巨人們搏斗了嗎？　或是看上了哪一個无知的少女？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you remember that cemetery at Orphan Rock? When I die, just make sure my pie coffin is out in the sun.</Source>
      <Dest>你还记得那个孤儿岩的坟墓吗? 当我死了只要确保我的馅饼做的棺材处在阳光的照耀下，就行了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know, it sounds to me like the only difference is I have to pay you money. </Source>
      <Dest>我不知道，似乎唯一的区别就是我不得不向你掏钱了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs)</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you think about this idea, Karras? An entire regiment using bound weapons.</Source>
      <Dest>让全团的人都使用统一的武器。你觉得这个主意怎么样，卡拉斯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll bet you 100 septims I can hit the bulls-eye twenty times in a row.</Source>
      <Dest>我跟你赌100 金币，我能连续击中靶心二十次。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you mean our victory or our friendship, because I can't imagine you would want to end the party.</Source>
      <Dest>你是指我们的胜利和友谊吗？因为我无法想象你会结束这个组合。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I still can't believe Gren beat us to the axe. Of course, we were just trying to defend Riverwood. We had no idea there was even an axe to fetch.</Source>
      <Dest>我仍无法相信格伦用斧子攻击了我们。没错，我们只是想保卫河木镇.。我们不知道这里甚至可以拿到斧子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Huzzah!</Source>
      <Dest>好啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, sorry! I was talking about another Skjarn. A man so ugly he couldn't possibly be you.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，抱歉！我说的是另一个夏尔。那男的丑得要死，你怎么可能会是他呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, don't mind us. I'm just trying to figure out ways to take Skjarn's money.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，别理我们。我正在想办法套走 史卡盎 的钱呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anyways love, my advice is to just enjoy the day. Whether it's here or in our heads or anywhere else.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，亲爱的，我建议咱们去享受一天。无论是在这里，还是在我们的头上，亦或是在其他地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That was a bottle of imitation skooma. I carry it around sometimes because it makes me look more dangerous.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一瓶仿制的斯库玛。我有时候带着它到处转，因为这让我看起来更不好惹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But you have nothing to apologize for, my love. In fact, it's better if you don't let people think it was all an accident.</Source>
      <Dest>但是亲爱的，你没什么好感到抱歉的。实际上，如果你能让人们认为这并不完全是个事故的话会更好一些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Speech!</Source>
      <Dest>说话!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Damn, there's a joke here, but Skjarn isn't really haughty enough to sit on a high horse. Arrogant and contemptuous yes, but not haughty.</Source>
      <Dest>该死的，这就是个笑话，但夏尔真的没有足够傲慢到去骑一只高头大马。他是对谁都挺不屑一顾的，但并不傲慢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did I tell you how great this party is? The Jarl must be so jealous.</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉过你这个聚会有多好吗？连领主都嫉妒了呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's ridiculous. I don't even like skooma.</Source>
      <Dest>真是荒谬。 我根本就不喜欢skooma.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hear, hear!</Source>
      <Dest>你听，你听！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Arrows? Who said anything about arrows?</Source>
      <Dest>箭头? 有人提起过箭头吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm all ears, my love. Pointy ones, at that.</Source>
      <Dest>洗耳恭听，我的宝贝儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's an odd question, coming from blacksmith of Kvatch. Don't your weapons practically come from Oblivion?</Source>
      <Dest>这是个奇怪的问题，科瓦奇来的铁匠铸造的武器。你的武器难道不是从从湮灭弄来的？</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
