<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to go back to my other questions.</Source>
      <Dest>我想回到我其他的问题上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you wish to learn more of our history, I suggest you walk the path and talk with those who lived it.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你想要更多关于我们的历史，我建议你沿着小径去和住在那的人讨论讨论。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How old is this order?</Source>
      <Dest>教团成立多长时间了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It goes back as far as the days of Pelagius. Times of war and madness tend to bring out the best and worst of us.</Source>
      <Dest>如同昔年那黑暗的佩拉吉奥斯时代啊。在那个充斥着癫狂暴政与战火的年代，人性的善恶被成倍放大开来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How old is this order?</Source>
      <Dest>教团成立多长时间了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The story of our brotherhood is proof of both.</Source>
      <Dest>我们的兄弟情谊的故事是一生的证明。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about this brotherhood.</Source>
      <Dest>多给我讲点有关这个兄弟会的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say we began as thieves and assassins. Nightblades, they called us. But in the beginning there were only two. Deneris, and his chosen.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说我们原来是小偷和刺客。他们叫我们夜刃。但最开始夜刃组织只有两个人，丹尼勒斯和他选中的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about this brotherhood.</Source>
      <Dest>多给我讲点有关这个兄弟会的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Over time the order grew, each chosen learning how to master the art of shadow and illusion.</Source>
      <Dest>随着时间的推移，规则也在成长，其中每个被选择的在学习如何掌握阴影和幻术的艺术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about this brotherhood.</Source>
      <Dest>多给我讲点有关这个兄弟会的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But Deneris wanted more. He spent his days secluded, praying to dark forces, sending his brothers to death for relics without a name. </Source>
      <Dest>但丹尼勒斯想要的更多。他每天独自呆在家里，向黑暗仪式祈祷，祈求能把他的兄弟们送归死亡，只为那无名的神器。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about this brotherhood.</Source>
      <Dest>多给我讲点有关这个兄弟会的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As his obsession deepened, he sought Nocturnal's favor, and commanded his chosen to steal Azura's Star. </Source>
      <Dest>随着他逐渐痴迷于此，他开始寻求诺克图娜尔的帮助，并且命令他挑选出来的手下去偷阿祖拉之星。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about this brotherhood.</Source>
      <Dest>多给我讲点有关这个兄弟会的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But Azura was the God of the first chosen, and so on the 21st of First Seed, he led a coup against his master.</Source>
      <Dest>但阿祖拉是第一选择，因此在初种（3月）的21日，他领导完成了反抗自己主人的壮举。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about this brotherhood.</Source>
      <Dest>多给我讲点有关这个兄弟会的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is from that betrayal and Azura's gratitude that our brotherhood was born.</Source>
      <Dest>我们的兄弟会因背叛和阿祖拉的感激而诞生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So your brotherhood was originally a mercenary group?</Source>
      <Dest>所以你的兄弟会原本是个雇佣兵组织？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes. The founder, Deneris, wanted to make a guild that would bridge the gap between the Thieves Guild and the Dark Brotherhood.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，创始人丹尼勒斯想通过一个公会，来弥合盗贼工会和黑暗兄弟会之间的间隙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So your brotherhood was originally a mercenary group?</Source>
      <Dest>所以你的兄弟会原本是个雇佣兵组织？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The first mortal he chose was a nine-fingered man named Varyan. A common thief, but the most skilled of all the chosen.</Source>
      <Dest>第一个被他选中的人是个缺一只手指的人名叫瓦里安。是个普通的贼，只是所有选择中技术最好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So your brotherhood was originally a mercenary group?</Source>
      <Dest>所以你的兄弟会原本是个雇佣兵组织？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So when he sought Azura's Star, he trusted Varyan and Varyan alone with stealing it.</Source>
      <Dest>所以当他寻找阿祖拉之星的时候，他信任瓦里安，还和他一起偷了阿祖拉之星。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So your brotherhood was originally a mercenary group?</Source>
      <Dest>所以你的兄弟会原本是个雇佣兵组织？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He had never chosen more wisely.</Source>
      <Dest>他明智地没有选择更多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened to Deneris?</Source>
      <Dest>丹尼勒斯出什么事了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know. Some say the first chosen took pity on the founder. Others say he refused to curse himself as a kinslayer.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道。有的人说第一个门徒对丹尼勒斯产生了恻隐之心。其他人说他不想背负弑亲者的骂名。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened to Deneris?</Source>
      <Dest>丹尼勒斯出什么事了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But to let Deneris go was to defy Azura, so he and two of his pupils sacrificed their own lives as a measure of atonement.</Source>
      <Dest>但是放走丹尼勒斯是对阿祖拉的忤逆，因而他与他的两个学生选择了牺牲自己来平息阿祖拉的怒火。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened to Deneris?</Source>
      <Dest>丹尼勒斯出什么事了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When it was done, they were reborn as spirits in this Temple. Whether her boon was meant as a blessing or a curse, only she knows.</Source>
      <Dest>当尘埃落定之时，他们在神殿中作为精神重生。她的恩惠究竟是祝福还是诅咒，只有她自己知道了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened to Deneris?</Source>
      <Dest>丹尼勒斯出什么事了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But in the centuries since, each member of our brotherhood has undergone the same rites to join them. For us, it is truly an honor.</Source>
      <Dest>但是几个世纪以来，我们每个成员都是通过这个仪式来加入的我们的。那对我们来说就是荣誉的象征。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's that large fire for?</Source>
      <Dest>那次火灾的原因是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When a body is burned, the watcher sees it in the fire below, and opens the way. That is how you entered this temple.</Source>
      <Dest>当一副躯体被燃烧，守卫会注意到这火焰，然后打开通路。你就是这么进入这座神庙的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's that large fire for?</Source>
      <Dest>那次火灾的原因是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But your role as bearer is not yet finished. You must still guide the spirit to the main hall, where it is reborn as a guardian warrior.</Source>
      <Dest>但是你作为跑腿者这个角色的使命还没完。你仍然必须指引自己的心灵前往主厅，那个它重生为勇士守护的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should probably keep the dagger, lest it end up in some general goods store.</Source>
      <Dest>你还是自己留着这把匕首吧，免得它最后沦落到某个小卖部的货架上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you aim to sell it, I doubt you will receive what it's worth. But perhaps that's the point of giving it to you. </Source>
      <Dest>如果你就是想卖掉它，我都怀疑你收不收得回本儿来。但或许这也是把它给你的意义所在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You should probably keep the dagger, lest it end up in some general goods store.</Source>
      <Dest>你还是自己留着这把匕首吧，免得它最后沦落到某个小卖部的货架上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Think of it as a test of faith. Not of the Gods, but my faith in you. So with that said, I bid you goodbye. Safe travels to you both.</Source>
      <Dest>把它当作对信念的测试吧。不是对神的信仰，而是我对你的信任。那就这样了，我向你道别。一路平安。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I prefer to hunt alone. You'll only get in my way.</Source>
      <Dest>我习惯一个人打猎。你来只会碍我的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your current companion must be the exception then. And perhaps the one that died is the rule.</Source>
      <Dest>你现在的同伴一定是个例外，以及或许那条规则已经被破坏了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I prefer to hunt alone. You'll only get in my way.</Source>
      <Dest>我习惯一个人打猎。你来只会碍我的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I understand your trepidation, but perhaps you will reconsider when the time comes. Until then, safe travels.</Source>
      <Dest>我理解你的忧虑，但是你应该在时机到来的时候再考虑下。一路平安。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Take your time. Your brothers deserve no less.</Source>
      <Dest>不用急，你的兄弟不会消失的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you for understanding. Redemption awaits the both of us, friend. Safe travels.</Source>
      <Dest>我感谢你的理解。我们都等待着救赎，朋友。一路平安。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would be honored to fight by your side.</Source>
      <Dest>我非常荣幸能与你并肩作战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You bestow honor upon me, but you haven't actually seen me fight.</Source>
      <Dest>您授予我荣誉，但您并未亲眼见证我的战斗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would be honored to fight by your side.</Source>
      <Dest>我非常荣幸能与你并肩作战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps when I have recovered, I will find a way to do your words justice. For now, safe travels.</Source>
      <Dest>等我恢复了，我说不定会按照你对正义的定义来生活。但是现在，一路小心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what now?</Source>
      <Dest>那么现在呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what now?</Source>
      <Dest>那现在该怎么做？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was wrong to judge you harshly friend. It seems you are just another victim of Deneris' wickedness. </Source>
      <Dest>我错怪你了，朋友。看来你只是丹尼勒斯恶行之下的另一个受害者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what now?</Source>
      <Dest>那么现在呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what now?</Source>
      <Dest>那现在该怎么做？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My blood yearns to boil, but right now, I know only grief. I thought I had brought my brothers peace, only to find their souls in turmoil once more.</Source>
      <Dest>我的鲜血渴望沸腾，但现在，我只知道悲伤。我以为我已经给我的兄弟们带来了安宁，没想到会发现他们的灵魂会再次动荡不安。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what now?</Source>
      <Dest>那么现在呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what now?</Source>
      <Dest>那现在该怎么做？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here. Take this dagger. When I have finished mourning, I will return for it.</Source>
      <Dest>拿着这把匕首。等我服丧期结束之后，我会来问你拿的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what now?</Source>
      <Dest>那么现在呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what now?</Source>
      <Dest>那现在该怎么做？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And on that day, if somehow Deneris still lives, then I will join your ranks, and we will hunt him together.</Source>
      <Dest>那天，如果丹尼勒斯还活着, 那么我会加入你，我们一起追杀他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did it ever occur to you that Deneris would find a nightblade to recruit him?</Source>
      <Dest>你有没有想丹尼勒斯会招募一个夜刃？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Troll's blood! That would explain how he received the mark! The ink is scarce, but there are those in the brotherhood who still know how to make it.</Source>
      <Dest>巨魔之血啊！那解释了他如何取回了标志！墨水短缺，不过兄弟会里有人知道怎么制作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did it ever occur to you that Deneris would find a nightblade to recruit him?</Source>
      <Dest>你有没有想丹尼勒斯会招募一个夜刃？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Given the watcher sees all, they could not have performed the ritual out in the open, or even while Deneris still lived. But it is possible.</Source>
      <Dest>鉴于观察者们的见解，就算丹尼勒斯还活着，他们也不可能公开的执行仪式。但那还是有可能的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did it ever occur to you that Deneris would find a nightblade to recruit him?</Source>
      <Dest>你有没有想丹尼勒斯会招募一个夜刃？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We can only hope that his spirit is trapped in that cave with the others.</Source>
      <Dest>我们只能寄希望于他的灵魂和其他人一样被困在这山洞里了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He claimed to have been chosen by another nightblade.</Source>
      <Dest>他声称已经被另一个夜刃选中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is it possible that Deneris' vassals wormed their way into the order? Or was one of my brothers blinded by his skill?</Source>
      <Dest>难道是丹尼勒斯的奴仆混进了教团？亦或是我的一位兄弟被自己的本事而蒙蔽了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He claimed to have been chosen by another nightblade.</Source>
      <Dest>他声称已经被另一个夜刃选中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whoever it is, he was too much of a coward to bear the corpse himself. The only question is whether his gambit succeeded.</Source>
      <Dest>不管是谁，都又废又蠢又懦弱。唯一的悬念在于他们能不能先发制人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He claimed to have been chosen by another nightblade.</Source>
      <Dest>他声称已经被另一个夜刃选中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If Deneris underwent the right of passage, he would be reborn...we can only hope that existence is forever trapped inside the temple.</Source>
      <Dest>如果丹尼勒斯经受住了那正确旅程的考验，他将重生……我们唯一能希望的就是那个存在会永远被困在神殿之内。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We were fooled. The corpse we delivered was Deneris.</Source>
      <Dest>我们被耍了。我们交出了丹尼勒斯的尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Deneris? But his corpse bears no mark! How is that even possible?</Source>
      <Dest>丹尼勒斯？但它的尸体上没有标记啊！这怎么可能？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Trial by combat.</Source>
      <Dest>来试试我的格斗技巧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then the Gods truly smile upon me. For when our battle ends, I will join my brothers, or enact their vengeance.</Source>
      <Dest>那么诸神看来真的对我微笑了，战斗结束之后，我会和我的兄弟团聚，或者我会为他们报仇雪恨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A brother who died of old age and was buried in Windhelm.</Source>
      <Dest>一个老死后葬在风盔城的兄弟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But you found him, and that's what's important. I weep for those still out there, who have outlived their chosen. I too may share the same fate.</Source>
      <Dest>但你找到了他，这才是最重要的。我为那些仍在那里，却已遗忘了当初的选择的人们而感到悲哀。我也可能遭受同样的命运。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I bear the corpse of one your brothers, but he is a stranger to me.</Source>
      <Dest>我把你这位兄弟的尸体运来了，可我不认识他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's not often outsiders are allowed in this place, but as long as the way opens, then you are welcome.</Source>
      <Dest>外人不是那么容易进入这里的。但如果道路打开，那你就会被欢迎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were four of us, all told, sailing on that ship. When one of my brothers died, we vowed to deliver him here.</Source>
      <Dest>我们有四个人，总之，都在这条船上航行。我的一个兄弟死了的时候，我们发誓把他送回这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But when the Sea of Ghosts took our ship and the winter claimed our bodies, that promise was nearly broken.</Source>
      <Dest>但当幽灵之海夺走了我们的船只，寒冬吞没了我们的躯体，那承诺几乎支离破碎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, I am all that's left.  And I must bury three, instead of one.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，我就剩下这些了。还有我必须要埋三个，而不是一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And what is your story? Whose spirit will you lay to rest?</Source>
      <Dest>那么说说你的故事吧？哪个神明可以让你无忧而眠？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We made it! Just barely, by the sound of it. But I believe you have some explaining to do.</Source>
      <Dest>我们做到了！从声音来判断，真是千钧一发。但是我相信你需要做些解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My brothers were sworn to defend that temple, but as spirits, they often do not distinguish between the victims and the guilty.</Source>
      <Dest>我的兄弟们发誓保护那座神庙，可是作为灵魂，他们通常分不清牺牲者与罪人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I, on the other hand, will allow you the chance for a trial. Choose your defense, blade or tongue.</Source>
      <Dest>另一方面，我将允许你有试验的机会。你可以选择防御，攻击或者龙语。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does one join this brotherhood?</Source>
      <Dest>一个人要怎样加入这个兄弟会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>None of us joined. We were chosen. My mentor Azarek recruited me when I was but a pup. And as his chosen, it was my responsibility to bring him here.</Source>
      <Dest>我们不是加入的，我们是被选上了。我的导师阿扎瑞克在我还是个臭小子的时候带上了我。因为他的选择，我有责任把他带到这儿来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does one join this brotherhood?</Source>
      <Dest>一个人要怎样加入这个兄弟会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My other companions, Fram and Lorgren, they were too young to have chosen a brother. But as witness to their deaths, I must deliver them as well.</Source>
      <Dest>我其他的战友，法姆和洛格瑞，他们还太年轻所以还不能选择自己的搭档。但是作为他们死亡的见证人，我也必须去给他们送行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What becomes of the spirits here?</Source>
      <Dest>这里的灵魂变成了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You need only walk the path and see for yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>你需要的只是行走在道路上，亲自去看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What becomes of the spirits here?</Source>
      <Dest>这里的灵魂变成了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You may watch the ceremony, but be careful not to step onto the dais.  The brothers will not allow you to approach the first chosen.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以观看仪式举行，但小心别走上讲台。那些大块头可不会让你在他们眼皮底下大摇大摆地走过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What becomes of the spirits here?</Source>
      <Dest>这里的灵魂变成了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To do so is considered an open threat to the sanctity of this temple, which Azura herself is said to have provided us.</Source>
      <Dest>正如阿祖拉所承诺的那样，这么做可是对这一神庙的神圣性的公开亵渎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And you frightened a poor bandit, from what he says in his journal.</Source>
      <Dest>以及根据某个强盗的日记里所说的，你吓走了那个可怜的混蛋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I reckon he was downright spooked. But we were alive and well, thanks to our training. Sorcery and stamina is what saw us back to land.</Source>
      <Dest>我估计他吓傻了。可我们就是活的好好的，多亏了平时勤加训练。法术和耐力能够帮我们回到陆地上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And you frightened a poor bandit, from what he says in his journal.</Source>
      <Dest>以及根据某个强盗的日记里所说的，你吓走了那个可怜的混蛋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But even though we outfoxed Kynareth, old man winter still had his say.</Source>
      <Dest>但即使我们智取了凯纳瑞斯，寒冬老人仍然能发出属于他的冰冷咆哮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It would require a lot of constitution to travel such a distance.</Source>
      <Dest>如果要进行这样远距离的长途旅行，我们得事先进行大量的准备。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True. It helped that Lorgren was a skilled enchanter, and we all wore necklaces that boosted our stamina.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊。它帮助劳格伦成为了一名熟练的法师，我们都把项链戴在脖子上以增强我们的耐力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It would require a lot of constitution to travel such a distance.</Source>
      <Dest>如果要进行这样远距离的长途旅行，我们得事先进行大量的准备。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But even though we outfoxed Kynareth, old man winter still had his say. Now that I must bury my kin, I wonder if he spared me out of pity or spite.</Source>
      <Dest>但是尽管我们用计谋战胜了凯娜瑞斯，自由冬天那个老家伙还是坚持他的看法。现在我必须葬了我的族人，我不知道他宽恕我是出于怨恨还是怜悯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How in Oblivion did you hold your breath?</Source>
      <Dest>你究竟是怎么屏住呼吸的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We didn't. We used alteration magic. Waterbreathing, to be specific. A sailor's best friend.</Source>
      <Dest>我们没有。我们常常使用变换系魔法。具体来说，是水下呼吸。它可真是水手的好朋友啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How in Oblivion did you hold your breath?</Source>
      <Dest>你究竟是怎么屏住呼吸的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But even though we outfoxed Kynareth, old man winter still had his say.</Source>
      <Dest>但即使我们智取了凯纳瑞斯，寒冬老人仍然能发出属于他的冰冷咆哮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you by chance wash up at Orphan's Tear?</Source>
      <Dest>你曾在孤儿泪洗过什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I did indeed. The sky promised steady winds that day, but Kynareth was in a bad mood, and she always has the last word.</Source>
      <Dest>的确。天空承诺过今天应该风和日丽，但凯娜瑞斯的心情不是太好，而她总有最后的决定权。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you by chance wash up at Orphan's Tear?</Source>
      <Dest>你曾在孤儿泪洗过什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The ship was about to capsize when Fram got the idea to put on the heavy plate armor that we had retrieved from a group of pirates.</Source>
      <Dest>就在船快要倾覆的那一瞬间，艾弗朗突然想出了一个主意，他要我们穿上我们从海盗那儿缴获的重型板甲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you by chance wash up at Orphan's Tear?</Source>
      <Dest>你曾在孤儿泪洗过什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Because while the sea raged on above, the waters below were as quiet as a shadow.</Source>
      <Dest>因为当上层的海水激烈的翻涌之时，水底却如同阴影一般的安静。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you by chance wash up at Orphan's Tear?</Source>
      <Dest>你曾在孤儿泪洗过什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We walked what must have been a thousand yards and came rising out of the shore, with the corpse of our brother draped over our shoulders.</Source>
      <Dest>我们一定已经背着我们的兄弟走了数千码，直至看到海岸线。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The corpse I found had a blackened finger.</Source>
      <Dest>我发现的那具尸体有一只黑化的手指。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A mark granted to all those who join the brotherhood, and a tribute to the first chosen who painted their fingers black in a show of solidarity.</Source>
      <Dest>所有加入兄弟会的人都会被授予一个标志，兄弟会会向那些被选中的人送出一封印着黑手印的信，作为团结的证明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The corpse I found had a blackened finger.</Source>
      <Dest>我发现的那具尸体有一只黑化的手指。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say the ink itself holds a magical property, taken from the sap of an Eldergleam and boiled over the ceremonial brazier below.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说那墨水经由古藤的树汁影响并在下面的仪式用水盆里煮沸后，其自身有了魔力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The corpse I found had a blackened finger.</Source>
      <Dest>我发现的那具尸体有一只黑化的手指。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As the ink is scarce, most like myself have had the mark branded by that very fire. Supposedly it sears the very bone. It certainly felt that way.</Source>
      <Dest>As the ink is scarce, most like myself have had the mark branded by that very fire. Supposedly it sears the very bone. It certainly felt that way.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come on! We've got to get out of here before the place collapses!</Source>
      <Dest>来吧！我们得在这个地方倒塌前离开这里！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The spirit you burned walks among you, lighting the path ahead, but it cannot stray from the bearer. </Source>
      <Dest>被你所焚烧的灵魂在你周围游走，照亮前面的路，但是它却不能自传递者处偏离。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Once it reaches the throne room, the spirit will renew its oath with the first chosen, and be reborn.</Source>
      <Dest>一旦它到达了正殿，这个灵魂会首先恢复它自己的誓言，然后重获新生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must be careful not to disturb this process.</Source>
      <Dest>You must be careful not to disturb this process.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So many brothers were lost that day. I only hope they find their way home.</Source>
      <Dest>那天我们失散了很多兄弟。我只希望他们回了家才好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Sea of Ghosts is so calm. Not at all like that day.</Source>
      <Dest>幽灵之海看起来如此平静，和它奔腾汹涌吞噬一切的那一天截然不同。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
