<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's in charge of this operation?</Source>
      <Dest>这个行动的负责人是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laugh) I'm sorry, but there ain't enough coin in your pocket to make me answer that.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑）我很抱歉，但想让我回答这个问题，你还差点儿钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You may be fair, madame, but a proper lady does not speak like a ruffian.</Source>
      <Dest>您也许很文雅，女士，不过正经的女人不会像个恶棍一样说话吧.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Didn't figure you for a posh one, but we get all types in here. The lady part ain't a title. It's because I got lady parts.</Source>
      <Dest>没看出来您是个有品味的，不过我们这儿什么类型都有。"夫人（Lady）"这个词倒不是头衔，而是因为我本身非常淑女。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There has to be something unfair about it, or else you wouldn't make a profit.</Source>
      <Dest>这其中确实有点不公平，否则你也不会有利润了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ain't nothing unfair about charging for a service. You just try and make a wager with some of these lowlifes, and see how many are good for it.</Source>
      <Dest>服务费而已，没什么不公平的。你就试试，和这些坏蛋打赌，看看付多少好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There has to be something unfair about it, or else you wouldn't make a profit.</Source>
      <Dest>这其中确实有点不公平，否则你也不会有利润了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The nobles are even worse.</Source>
      <Dest>贵族更糟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There has to be something unfair about it, or else you wouldn't make a profit.</Source>
      <Dest>这其中确实有点不公平，否则你也不会有利润了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We keep the books, same as any business, so there ain't no confusion about who owes what.</Source>
      <Dest>就像任何一次交易一样，我们留下了书面文件，所以无关谁欠谁什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does anyone try any rough stuff?</Source>
      <Dest>有人试过打打架什么的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If they do, Thorn will make sure every part of them gets crooked.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他们这样做，索恩会确保每个部分都被扭曲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought it was due to your overwhelming beauty.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这是因为你倾国倾城的容颜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're a decent lass to say so, but you'll have more luck working the fans. I'm too old to play anyone's Fjori.</Source>
      <Dest>你还真是个正派的姑娘，不过如果你将你的（奉承）对象选择为你的粉丝的话那效果会更好的。我已经不年轻了，无法当某个人的佛里乔了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I thought it was due to your overwhelming beauty.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这是因为你倾国倾城的容颜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I ain't one to say no to flattery, but you'll have more luck working the fans, Holgeir. I'm too old to play anyone's Fjori.</Source>
      <Dest>我倒不是那种听不得奉承的人，但如果你将你的（奉承）对象选择为你的粉丝的话那效果会更好，霍吉尔。我已经不年轻了，无法当某个人的佛里乔了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do they call you "The Fair Lady?"</Source>
      <Dest>为啥他们叫你"窈窕淑女?"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Because I handle the gold. When you win I pay, and when you lose I don't. Fair's fair.</Source>
      <Dest>因为我拿着钱。你赢了我就给钱，你输了我就不给。很公平。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No thanks.</Source>
      <Dest>不用，谢谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fine. But remember, 50 gold is a piddling sum compared to what you'll get if you win, and what you'll lose if you don't.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，但记住了，50金币与你赢了所能获得的，以及输了就要失去的东西相比，实在是太微不足道了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here. 50 gold.</Source>
      <Dest>拿着。50金币。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A pleasure doing business, stranger.</Source>
      <Dest>和你做生意很愉快，陌生人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here. 50 gold.</Source>
      <Dest>拿着。50金币。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for what I know, your previous opponents were a tough draw. At least, I could tell as much by the way J'Sharr's ears cringed.</Source>
      <Dest>至于我知道的事情嘛，你之前的对手们艰难战平了。最后，我可以顺便多告诉你一点儿，洁莎怂了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here. 50 gold.</Source>
      <Dest>拿着。50金币。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This new pair though, nobody knows what to make of them.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一对新人，但没人知道是什么使他们在一起的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here. 50 gold.</Source>
      <Dest>拿着。50金币。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Two foreigners from Hammerfell. You know, the ones with that got them funny swords and even funnier robes.</Source>
      <Dest>两个从落锤省来的老外。你知道，就是那些拿着奇怪的剑穿着更奇怪的长袍的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here. 50 gold.</Source>
      <Dest>拿着。50金币。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If nothing else, it'll make for a good show.</Source>
      <Dest>如果没有其他的事，让我们欣赏表演吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any information on the next fight?</Source>
      <Dest>有没有下一场比赛的消息？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fifty gold ought to do it. Don't look surprised now, information costs money. Fair's fair.</Source>
      <Dest>给我50个金币就告诉你。别看起来太惊讶，消息可都是要点花费的，这可是很公道的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No thanks, I'll ask elsewhere.</Source>
      <Dest>不了，谢谢。我会去其他地方问问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fine.</Source>
      <Dest>好嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here. 200 gold pieces.</Source>
      <Dest>给，200金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, that wasn't so hard, was it? Alright, I'll tell you what I know, fair's fair.</Source>
      <Dest>现在看看，这并不难，不是吗？好吧，我会把我所知道的告诉你，公正公平。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here. 200 gold pieces.</Source>
      <Dest>给，200金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was a name written on the back of one of his betting slips. Now I don't know if he let me see it on purpose, but it's all I know.</Source>
      <Dest>有一个名字写在他那张投注单的后面。现在我不知道是不是他故意让我看到它的，但这是我所知道的一切。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Here. 200 gold pieces.</Source>
      <Dest>给，200金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The name was Orotheim. Some cave over in Hjaalmarch. I'd look for him there.</Source>
      <Dest>那地方叫奥瑟姆。就在希雅陲领里的某个山洞。我会在那儿找他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Khajiit is manipulating matches and making your job harder. Give him up.</Source>
      <Dest> 虎人操纵着这场比赛并让你更难做，放弃他们吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, having him out of the way would make my life easier. On the other hand, so would 200 septims.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，他直接消失掉的话我的生活会轻松一些。另一方面，（这）需要花费200金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If it's worthless, you ought to lower your price. It would only be fair.</Source>
      <Dest>如果它是无用的，你应该把价格降低。这才是公平。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, aren't you the cute one.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，你真是不可爱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If it's worthless, you ought to lower your price. It would only be fair.</Source>
      <Dest>如果它是无用的，你应该把价格降低。这才是公平。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Two hundred septims.</Source>
      <Dest>两百金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Any idea where J'Sharr might be?</Source>
      <Dest>知道杰夏尔有可能在哪吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, the information I've got may not be worth a wooden septim. But that doesn't mean I'll sell it for less than 200 gold ones.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我所得到的信息恐怕连个木制赛普汀都不值。不过这并不意味着我就不会把这条信息以200金的价格来出售。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you're one of J'Sharr's friends? Or should I say friend, seeing as you'd be the first.</Source>
      <Dest>那么你是杰夏尔的一个朋友？或许我该说“杰夏尔的朋友”，看样子你是她第一个朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They call me the Fair Lady. What can I do for you?</Source>
      <Dest>他们都叫我窈窕淑女。我能为你做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nice work. The crowd took a liking to you. Won't help your odds much, but there's more than one way to make coin here.</Source>
      <Dest>干得好。那群人挺喜欢你的。不想多帮一下你的老伙伴们吗！而且在这儿，赚钱的法子很多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>J'Sharr mentioned other locations.</Source>
      <Dest>杰夏尔提到了其他地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's right. It's the best way to operate outside the law. You stay in one place, and one day even a drunken lout will stumble upon it.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，这是在法律以外运作的最好方法，你只要一直呆在同一个地方，有朝一日哪怕一个醉酒的蠢货都会发现它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>J'Sharr mentioned other locations.</Source>
      <Dest>杰夏尔提到了其他地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Jarl's men ain't much smarter than that, but that makes them smart enough.</Source>
      <Dest>The Jarl's men ain't much smarter than that, but that makes them smart enough.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>J'Sharr mentioned other locations.</Source>
      <Dest>杰夏尔提到了其他地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why we rarely use this place, save for special matches like with your friend there.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我们很少用这里的原因，我们一直在等一个绝好的对手——比如你的朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>J'Sharr mentioned other locations.</Source>
      <Dest>杰夏尔提到了其他地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Most days I'm working in some dirty cellar, sitting on a stool with more splinters than hairs on me head.</Source>
      <Dest>大多数时候我都在肮脏的地下室里工作，坐在一个木渣比我头上的头发还多的椅子上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>J'Sharr mentioned other locations.</Source>
      <Dest>杰夏尔提到了其他地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I'll take a few needles in the rear if it keeps us out of trouble. Fair's fair.</Source>
      <Dest>不过如果可以避免麻烦的话我会在后面放一些针的。公平至上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's all the questions I have. I'm ready for the cage.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我全部的问题。我准备好进牢笼了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you're in luck. It looks like our friends from Hammerfell have arrived.</Source>
      <Dest>那你还真走运，看来我们那来自于落锤省的朋友已经抵达了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have to ask, did J'Sharr bet on us to win?</Source>
      <Dest>我得问一下，洁莎在我们身上下注了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) It would be just like him to bet against himself, but aye, he did put it on the both of you to win.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)那正是他的风格，喜欢跟自己对赌；但是确实如此，他在你们双方身上都有押注。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you get into this business?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么混进这一行的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Same as any chambermaid, tavern wench, or Jarl. You grow up in it.</Source>
      <Dest>就和家庭女仆一样，酒馆侍女，或者领主。你在这里成长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you get into this business?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么混进这一行的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My dad was gambler. He liked to bet on wolves, not men. Different animals, same rules. Some win, some lose. Fair's fair.</Source>
      <Dest>My dad was gambler. He liked to bet on wolves, not men. Different animals, same rules. Some win, some lose. Fair's fair.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Walk me through how you set the odds for our fight.</Source>
      <Dest>在比斗间击败我，通过你寻求任何的可能机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know much about you, but J'Sharr's got a reputation. I'd wager it's all a sham, but it ain't my business if the patrons want to believe it.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是很了解你，但是杰夏尔得到了她的名誉。我敢打赌，那全是胡扯的，但是要是赞助人想要去相信那些鬼话的话也和我没关系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Walk me through how you set the odds for our fight.</Source>
      <Dest>在比斗间击败我，通过你寻求任何的可能机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He's always doing some sort of grooming exercise, like licking his fur or straightening his whiskers.</Source>
      <Dest>他总在做一些梳理练习。像是舔自己的毛儿啊，或是把自己的胡须捋直什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Walk me through how you set the odds for our fight.</Source>
      <Dest>在比斗间击败我，通过你寻求任何的可能机会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People see that, and they see a milk-drinker. They'll risk 100 gold to win 30 because that's how little they think of him.</Source>
      <Dest>人们看见了，他们看见了一个小屁孩。他们会冒着失去100金的风险去赢那30金，因为他们认为他就值这些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So if we win, a portion goes to the house?</Source>
      <Dest>因此如果我们赢了，一部分人就要滚回家了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We don't take a cut from the fighters. It don't make much sense, seeing as the two of you can wager against each other.</Source>
      <Dest>我们不会从斗士的薪水中提成。这不合情理，看上去就像你们当中的两个可以互相赌博一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So if we win, a portion goes to the house?</Source>
      <Dest>因此如果我们赢了，一部分人就要滚回家了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, you might not get the same odds. That's why we handle the wagers. Fair's fair.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，你可能无法得到相同的赔率。这就是为什么我们要管理赌注。对所有人都要公平。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you handle the wagers?</Source>
      <Dest>只是你能操纵这赌博吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do more than handle them. I set the odds. Now you might be thinking, what's this old hag know about fighters?</Source>
      <Dest>我并不仅仅操纵它们，我还控制着赔率。现在你可能会思索，这个老巫婆对那些斗士们了解多少？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you handle the wagers?</Source>
      <Dest>只是你能操纵这赌博吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not a sodding thing. But it ain't my job to pick the winners. It's to set the odds. </Source>
      <Dest>答案是，你想多了。我的工作是设定几率而非挑选出胜者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you handle the wagers?</Source>
      <Dest>只是你能操纵这赌博吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And to do that, you have to know the bettors, not the overgrown oafs they're betting on.</Source>
      <Dest>And to do that, you have to know the bettors, not the overgrown oafs they're betting on.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you handle the wagers?</Source>
      <Dest>只是你能操纵这赌博吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every fight's got their bride and their groom. If I set the odds right, then you got an equal number of folks on both sides of the aisle.</Source>
      <Dest>好了每场竞技都有自己的人选了，只要我把赔率定好，就能保证两边下注的人数相等。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you handle the wagers?</Source>
      <Dest>只是你能操纵这赌博吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You got too many on one side, you change the odds so the rest of the patrons sit on the other.</Source>
      <Dest>别总是盯着这边，你去招呼下坐在那边的主顾们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I take it you handle the wagers?</Source>
      <Dest>只是你能操纵这赌博吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's the only way to guarantee we come out ahead. It doesn't matter which fighter wins, because we get a piece of every winning bet.</Source>
      <Dest>那是确保我们占上风的唯一方法。那个斗士的输赢无所谓，因为我们总会赢得一份赌注。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you live to see another day, cat.</Source>
      <Dest>So you live to see another day, cat.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Last call for bets! 3 to 1 for J'Sharr and the new blood! 2 to 7 for the warriors from Hammerfell!</Source>
      <Dest>最后一次下注！杰夏尔和新来的家伙这一方的赔率是3赔1！来自于落锤省的战士们这一方的赔率是2赔7！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ain't that right, Thorn?</Source>
      <Dest>Ain't that right, Thorn?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You've got Nocturnal's luck, cat. Different pair, but the same odds. The crowd doesn't think much of your chances.</Source>
      <Dest>你得到了诺克图娜尔的青睐，小猫咪。不同类型，但效果一样。大家并不看好你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, not a single patron has come to complain. Seems like they weren't betting on them so much as they're betting against you.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，不止一个顾客来抱怨了。看起来由于在你身上下了大头，顾客们没在他们身上下注太多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>J'Sharr! It looks like your match has gotten pushed back. Your dance partner got a case of the brain rot and fled.</Source>
      <Dest>杰夏尔！看来你的比赛得推后了。你的搭档得了脑残病然后跑掉了。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
