<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Argis contracts me out for mercernary work. He pointed me to you.</Source>
      <Dest>阿格斯联系了我让我当一当雇佣兵，他让我来找你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmph. Funny story, on may way to recruit the others, I got a letter from Argis saying his sellsword couldn't take the job.</Source>
      <Dest>哼。有趣的故事，或许可以招点儿其他人，我收到了封阿格斯的来信，他说他的佣兵干不来这活儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Argis contracts me out for mercernary work. He pointed me to you.</Source>
      <Dest>阿格斯联系了我让我当一当雇佣兵，他让我来找你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know who sent you, but either way, you can't be trusted. Now, you're going to die!</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道谁把你送来的，但是无论如何你是不值得信任的。现在，我要宰了你！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Argis is my cousin's wife's uncle's nephew.</Source>
      <Dest>阿格斯是我表弟的妻子的叔叔的侄子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You think you're funny? We'll see who's laughing when you're knee deep in your entrails!</Source>
      <Dest>你认为你很有趣吗？让我们看看等你的膝盖绞进你肠子里的时候你还能不能笑得出来！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does it matter who I am? I helped you, and now I'm leaving.</Source>
      <Dest>我的身份是啥并不重要，我帮了你，现在我要走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmph. You got a point, stranger. Hell, it probably was a good thing you showed up instead whatever lousy sod Argis got.</Source>
      <Dest>Hmph. You got a point, stranger. Hell, it probably was a good thing you showed up instead whatever lousy sod Argis got.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does it matter who I am? I helped you, and now I'm leaving.</Source>
      <Dest>我的身份是啥并不重要，我帮了你，现在我要走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here. Take this gold and get lost. I never want to see you here again.</Source>
      <Dest>过来。拿上这些钱然后滚。我这辈子再也不想在这儿看到你了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hold on. I can explain myself. This is all a misunderstanding.</Source>
      <Dest>等等。我可以解释这事。这全都是一个误会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Too late. You should have come clean back at the inn. I don't know who sent you, but either way, you can't be trusted. Now, you're going to die!</Source>
      <Dest>太迟了。你本应该回到这家客栈老实交代的。我不知道是谁派你来的，但无论如何你已经不值得信任了。现在，死吧！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've never met Argis. I don't care who he is. I just came along for the spoils.</Source>
      <Dest>我从来没有遇到过。我不在乎他是谁，我是为了战利品才来这里的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Now that's how a bandit should think! Blood and boon. And here are thought you were one of Javid's dogs.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 真是强盗逻辑! 满脑子除了钱就是暴力。这里的人都知道你只是贾菲的一条狗而已.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've never met Argis. I don't care who he is. I just came along for the spoils.</Source>
      <Dest>我从来没有遇到过。我不在乎他是谁，我是为了战利品才来这里的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here. Take your spoils then. But fair warning, unless you're one of the crew, you won't be welcome here again.</Source>
      <Dest>Here. Take your spoils then. But fair warning, unless you're one of the crew, you won't be welcome here again.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't know Argis, to be honest. You insisted I did.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认识阿吉斯，真不认识！是你非说我认识的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And yet you played along. Seems to me you could've just came clean then.</Source>
      <Dest>但你也参与其中。在我看来,你完全可以实话实说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't know Argis, to be honest. You insisted I did.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认识阿吉斯，真不认识！是你非说我认识的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know who sent you, but either way, you can't be trusted. Now, you're going to die!</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道谁把你送来的，但是无论如何你是不值得信任的。现在，我要宰了你！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't say.</Source>
      <Dest>我可没说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, you didn't. Funny story, on may way to recruit the others, I got a letter from Argis saying his sellsword couldn't take the job.</Source>
      <Dest>No, you didn't. Funny story, on may way to recruit the others, I got a letter from Argis saying his sellsword couldn't take the job.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't say.</Source>
      <Dest>我可没说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know who sent you, but either way, you can't be trusted. Now, you're going to die!</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道谁把你送来的，但是无论如何你是不值得信任的。现在，我要宰了你！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You managed to escape with your life. Now you want to go on a suicide mission.</Source>
      <Dest>你好不容易活着逃出来了，现在又想去做个自杀任务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Suicide mission? Argis told me you were good. The best. But I suppose his word ain't worth the bucket I piss in!</Source>
      <Dest>自杀性任务？阿格斯告诉我说你人挺不错。是最棒的那个。不过我不觉得就凭他动动嘴皮子我就能去赴汤蹈火！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You managed to escape with your life. Now you want to go on a suicide mission.</Source>
      <Dest>你好不容易活着逃出来了，现在又想去做个自杀任务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't worry. It ain't just us. I've got a couple more stops to make. You head on over to Redoran's Retreat, but don't go in until I get there.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心。不光是我们。我这边还有几个人。你先前往瑞多然的休息处，但是我们的人到齐之前别进去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what you're saying is you're a terrible leader.</Source>
      <Dest>你是说自己这个头儿当得糟透了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You got a lip on you, dontcha? Argis said as much. Probably sent you as payback for all the times I looted him at Iron Hearts.</Source>
      <Dest>You got a lip on you, dontcha? Argis said as much. Probably sent you as payback for all the times I looted him at Iron Hearts.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So what you're saying is you're a terrible leader.</Source>
      <Dest>你是说自己这个头儿当得糟透了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I don't mind, so long as you get the job done. Head on over to Redoran's Retreat, but don't go in until I get there.</Source>
      <Dest>不过我无所谓，只要你能把活儿干好。一会就去瑞多然的休息处门口等我吧，在我到之前别进去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't help bandits. I kill them.</Source>
      <Dest>我不会帮强盗，我只会杀了他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know. That's why Argis recommended you. You'll be killing a whole clan of them, and getting a share of the spoils.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白。这就是阿格斯推荐你的原因。你会杀了他们家族的所有人，并得到一份战利品。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't help bandits. I kill them.</Source>
      <Dest>我不会帮强盗，我只会杀了他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Can't let you have all the fun though. I got a couple more men I need to recruit. You meet us over at Redoran's Retreat.</Source>
      <Dest>不能让你一个人享乐子。我还有几个帮手要去集合一下。到时候你跟我们在瑞多然的休息处见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So now you want revenge.</Source>
      <Dest>所以现在你想报仇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For starters, yeah. But getting the hideout back is just as important.</Source>
      <Dest>对初期而言，没错。不过夺回那个据点也很重要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So now you want revenge.</Source>
      <Dest>所以现在你想报仇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's an old mining shaft. Redoran's Retreat is what they call it, though I can't say why. Just meet me outside the entrance when you're ready.</Source>
      <Dest>是一个老旧的矿井。 他们把它叫做瑞多然的休息处，虽然我不知道为啥起这名字。准备好了就到入口处跟我汇合。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't know, but it's pretty damn ugly.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道，但这也太特么丑了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) You're Argis' kid then, I take it? He said you had some stones, but maybe he was selling you short.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑声）那么我估计，你就是阿格斯的孩子？他说你有一些石头，但也许他是投机赚了你一笔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't know, but it's pretty damn ugly.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道，但这也太特么丑了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose your old boss didn't bother to tell you what the job's about either. Don't worry, it ain't a long story. Follow me.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜你以前的老板没告诉过你工作相关的事儿。别担心，这不是个很长的故事。跟我来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Apparently I'm supposed to come here and ask you about a job.</Source>
      <Dest>显然，有人让我来这儿向你找活干。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Huh? You got worms in your skull? That don't make a lick of sense. Which means you're probably the one Argis sent over.</Source>
      <Dest>哈？ 你脑袋生蛆了吧？ 那根本就不合理， 这意味着你是阿格斯派来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Apparently I'm supposed to come here and ask you about a job.</Source>
      <Dest>显然，有人让我来这儿向你找活干。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose the snowback didn't bother to tell you what the job's about either. Don't worry, it ain't a long story. Follow me.</Source>
      <Dest>我想那个弱逼也没有费心告诉你这个任务究竟是关于什么的。别着急，这并不是一个很长的故事。跟我来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your name's Theron, I take it. I'm here about the job.</Source>
      <Dest>你的名字是塞隆，我知道了。我是来这里工作的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yeah? You're a bit scrawnier than the way Argis described ya. But I'll be a Riekling's uncle the day he tells it true.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，是吗？比起阿格斯的描述，你本人看起来更瘦一点儿。要是哪天他告诉我这是真的，我就是一个雪地精的叔叔了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your name's Theron, I take it. I'm here about the job.</Source>
      <Dest>你的名字是塞隆，我知道了。我是来这里工作的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose the snowback didn't bother to tell you what the job's about either. Don't worry, it ain't a long story. Follow me.</Source>
      <Dest>我想那个弱逼也没有费心告诉你这个任务究竟是关于什么的。别着急，这并不是一个很长的故事。跟我来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What are you looking at?</Source>
      <Dest>你在看什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was them beasts that gave me enough time to figure out what was going on, and slip out the back way. </Source>
      <Dest>是那群野兽给了我足够的时间来弄清到底发生了什么事，并且使我得以从后面悄悄溜走。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Funny part is, I'd been nagging the boys to kill those things for weeks.</Source>
      <Dest>其实最哏的是，为了这帮小子“滥杀无辜”的事儿我已经唠叨他们好几个星期了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, I blame Argis. If he was half the fence he claimed to be, he could sell the thing for twice what it was worth.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，都是阿格斯的错。作为销赃者，如果他真的有他所声称的一半厉害，那他应该能够把东西的价格提高两倍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not that I need to tell you, seeing as you used to work for him.  Where did you say you two met, anyway?</Source>
      <Dest>看来我没必要告诉你，因为你似乎曾经为他工作过。话说回来，你们俩以前是在哪见过面？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anyway, the funny part is I couldn't pawn it, with the bloody inscription on the back.  "To my Darling Cassandra."</Source>
      <Dest>总之，搞笑的就是，这东西我可典当不了，背面还刻着血字“给我亲爱的卡珊卓”...这怎么行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why couldn't he have just married a girl named Helga?</Source>
      <Dest>他为什么不干脆娶个叫哈尔嘉的姑娘呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now this is more like it. Every one of these things has a story.</Source>
      <Dest>现在这就更像它了。这些东西中的每一样都有故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take this pendant for example. Got it off a carriage moving a noble's family to Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>以这个吊坠为例，我从一个要搬家到独孤城的贵族家庭的马车上得到了它.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was locked in a safe, you see, and try as we might nobody could crack it. </Source>
      <Dest>It was locked in a safe, you see, and try as we might nobody could crack it. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This noble, he tried to bargain with me, saying he'd open the safe if I spared his blushing bride.</Source>
      <Dest>这个贵族，想要跟我讨价还价，说只要我放过他美貌的新娘就给我打开保险柜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I said sure, 'A deal's a deal. Open the safe and I won't lay a hand on your girl.' Of course, I never said anything about my men! (Laughs)</Source>
      <Dest>我说话算数，交易就是交易。只要打开保险箱我就不会动你女人一根手指头。不过当然，我可不保证我的手下不会动手动脚！（笑声）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Talos' beard! I hardly recognize the place. Is that a sodding book on the table?</Source>
      <Dest>塔洛斯的胡子在上！我简直认不出这地方了。那儿是不是有本已经长草的书放在桌子上？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm confused as well. You say kill everything on two legs, but don't that include us?</Source>
      <Dest>我也很困惑。你说杀了一切两条腿走路的，但那不也包括我们了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You idiots. Just kill everything in the cave, except the four of us. Got it?</Source>
      <Dest>You idiots. Just kill everything in the cave, except the four of us. Got it?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah boss, I got a question. What if they have dogs? Wouldn't they be on four legs instead of two?</Source>
      <Dest>老大，我有一个问题，如果他们有狗呢？那不就是四条腿而不是两条？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or do you want us to spare them seeing as they ain't but stupid mutts?</Source>
      <Dest>还是你想让我们看在他们不过是傻瓜的份儿上放了他们？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Good. You're all here. The plan's simple. We go in and kill everything on two legs. Except for the chief. I'll have him crawling on all fours.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。你们都到齐了。我们的计划很简单。我们杀进去，灭了所有两条腿儿的生物。那头子除外，因为我要看着他满地乱爬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Any questions?</Source>
      <Dest>还有问题吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, about the job. I doubt Argis told you this, but I used to be a bandit. Had a crew that numbered two dozen not a month ago.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，关于工作。我估摸着阿格斯已经告诉你了，但我以前是个强盗。不到一个月前我手下的小喽啰多得用双手双脚都数不过来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We were making good coin, raiding caravans and the occasional mine, until one of them decides he wants a bigger slice of the pie. My slice.</Source>
      <Dest>我们当时借由袭击商队，偶尔打劫一下矿坑赚了不少钱，直到其中一人不满于现状，也想要我的那份。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't know how he convinced the others, but about six of them made rounds around camp, cutting throats. All my men, dead as dog meat.</Source>
      <Dest>不清楚他是如何让别人信服的，但是他们中的六个包围了营地，割断了那些人的喉咙。我所有的手下，就像狗那样死去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wolves outside must've smelled it too, because they started howling.</Source>
      <Dest>外面的狼群肯定也嗅到了它，它们已经开始嚎叫了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, that's better. You got to love that fresh winter air. </Source>
      <Dest>啊，好多了。你一定会爱死冬天的新鲜空气的。 </Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
