<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am no one's servant. I decide who lives and dies. Be thankful I spared you.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是任何人的奴仆。所有人的生死大权都在我的手里。你要感谢我留你一命！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your response is typical. Servants of the champion often get drunk with power, and attempt to betray him at the final hour.</Source>
      <Dest>你的反应真特别。勇士的仆从们总是醉心于力量，并且在最后的紧要关头背叛他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am no one's servant. I decide who lives and dies. Be thankful I spared you.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是任何人的奴仆。所有人的生死大权都在我的手里。你要感谢我留你一命！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The same thing happened with the sellswords I hired. They assumed their ability to pull levers made them better than the Dwarvenborn.</Source>
      <Dest>同样的事情也发生在了我雇的佣兵身上。他们以为有能力拉动杠杆使得他们比锻莫后裔更棒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am no one's servant. I decide who lives and dies. Be thankful I spared you.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是任何人的奴仆。所有人的生死大权都在我的手里。你要感谢我留你一命！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To teach them a lesson, I decided to sheathe my machine hand, and let Mzanauch's spiders overrun them.</Source>
      <Dest>必须给他们一个教训,我决定不使用我的机械手, 让他们好好享受马瑟诺迟的蜘蛛们.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why Servant-Made? Why not Servantborn? Why the distinction?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么是创世者的仆从？为什么不是第一仆从？有什么区别吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Because, some people are born servants. Others are made. Sometimes by force, but usually by crippling poverty.</Source>
      <Dest>因为有些人生来就是奴仆，其他人则是被迫如此。有时是因为被权力胁迫，但是通常是因为无法忍受的贫穷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why Servant-Made? Why not Servantborn? Why the distinction?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么是创世者的仆从？为什么不是第一仆从？有什么区别吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But sometimes, a servant is made by the Divines, to help the one true hero fight off the mechanical forces of evil. This is one of those times.</Source>
      <Dest>但有些时候，仆从是受圣灵感召而来的，为的是帮助那个真英雄与邪恶相对抗。这次就是如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you just call me a maid?</Source>
      <Dest>你刚才是不是叫我女佣来着？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, not "Servant-Maid."  Servant-Made. Your version would just be redundant. The Champion of Mundus would never make such a clumsy mistake.</Source>
      <Dest>不，不是 "少女仆从"而是“创始者的仆从”。你可真是想多了。梦达思的勇士绝不可能犯这种低级错误。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's an honor. How may I serve you, my champion?</Source>
      <Dest>这是我的荣幸。有什么我可以为你服务的,我的勇士?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, the first thing you will need to do is dress like a servant. You will need an apron and a broom and a compulsion to clean that borders on sick.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，首先你得穿得像个佣人。你需要有围裙、扫把和保证没有病毒入侵的义务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had a feeling it would be you. At the tower, there was something about your knobby left thumb that reminded me of the egg I was hatched from.</Source>
      <Dest>我就感觉会是你。 在那座塔的时候，你左手的拇指上的东西让我想起了把我孵出来的那颗蛋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It marked you as my vassal, for just as there must be a Dwarvenborn, there also must be one to open his doors and pull the occasional lever.</Source>
      <Dest>那意味着你便是我的仆从，就如同必须要有一个锻莫后裔一样，必须要有人负责开门和解决不时碰到的机关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And at times, when Mzanauch in his cowardice uses his meat slaves to counter the Dwarvenborn's machine hand, you must fight alongside the champion.</Source>
      <Dest>但有时候，马瑟诺迟这懦夫会妄图用他的肉奴来抵抗矮人裔的机械之手，这时你只能与勇者一同战斗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And with your actions today, you have helped me land a great blow to the God Eater. You have truly earned the title "Servant-Made."</Source>
      <Dest>你今天的行为帮我战胜了世界吞噬者。现在，你才真正赢得了“创世者的仆人”的称号。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You spoke of three heralds of the apocalypse.</Source>
      <Dest>你谈到了天启的三个先驱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes. Raldbthar, half Dwarf, half machine, three quarters insane. He has crossbows for feet and when he walks, they fire.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，劳德布塔。一半是矮人, 一半是机械，四分之三是疯子。他被弩瞄着脚，一旦他抬腿想走就会被他们射击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You spoke of three heralds of the apocalypse.</Source>
      <Dest>你谈到了天启的三个先驱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then there's Mzinchaleft. A master strategist who thinks only in numbers, and Mzanauch's most trusted adviser.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是津查遗址。一个运筹帷幄的战略大师，也是马瑟诺迟最信任的导师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You spoke of three heralds of the apocalypse.</Source>
      <Dest>你谈到了天启的三个先驱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As he long ago abandoned his body, he now takes the form of a giant head on a stick, carried around by a Centurion slave.</Source>
      <Dest>很久以前，他就放弃了自己的身体。现在，他是以一颗插在棍子上的巨人头颅的形式存在，被一名百夫长奴隶随身携带。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You spoke of three heralds of the apocalypse.</Source>
      <Dest>你谈到了天启的三个先驱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then there is this temple's namesake, Alftand. Little is known about him, but there are rumors that Mzanauch blessed him with the Meat Hand.</Source>
      <Dest>Then there is this temple's namesake, Alftand. Little is known about him, but there are rumors that Mzanauch blessed him with the Meat Hand.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What now, Dwarvenborn? What does Mzanauch have planned next?</Source>
      <Dest>现在呢，锻莫后裔？马瑟诺迟的下一步计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will return to Reachwind Eyrie, to stand watch as I always have, and await the day of reckoning.</Source>
      <Dest>我会回临风鹰巢，一如既往地站岗，等待那一天的到来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What now, Dwarvenborn? What does Mzanauch have planned next?</Source>
      <Dest>现在呢，锻莫后裔？马瑟诺迟的下一步计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As for you, I wish to reward you for your services. Here. Take this spoon I disabled.</Source>
      <Dest>至于你，我希望能奖赏你的所作所为。过来这里。拿着这个我用坏的勺子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What now, Dwarvenborn? What does Mzanauch have planned next?</Source>
      <Dest>现在呢，锻莫后裔？马瑟诺迟的下一步计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dwarves use spoons like this to consume deities, or if need be, jump into the throats of their enemies.</Source>
      <Dest>矮人用这种像勺子一样的东西来对抗神灵，或者如果真的需要的话，插入到他们敌人的喉咙里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What now, Dwarvenborn? What does Mzanauch have planned next?</Source>
      <Dest>现在呢，锻莫后裔？马瑟诺迟的下一步计划是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Keep it as a reminder that Mzanauch's appetite is insatiable, and that our work is far from over.</Source>
      <Dest>留着它让我们记得，马瑟诺迟的欲望是无穷的，而我们还有很长的路要走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do with the sphere and the Lexicon?</Source>
      <Dest>你对这球和方典做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Isn't it obvious? I ate them.</Source>
      <Dest>这不很明显吗？我把它们吃了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not stuck. Deactivated. Permanently disabled by my Machine Hand. As will all the devices in this temple of evil.</Source>
      <Dest>不是卡住，是被关掉了。由我这只机械手将其永远地废除了。还有这个邪恶神殿里的所有装置都等着我来干掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All that's left is to deactivate you. </Source>
      <Dest>All that's left is to deactivate you. </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't play coy with me, servant of the God-Eater. </Source>
      <Dest>别跟我绕弯子，噬神者的仆从。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know as well as you that this teleportation device was designed specifically to bring Mzanauch's generals into Skyrim. </Source>
      <Dest>我和你一样清楚这个传送设备是专门设计用来把马瑟诺迟的邪恶军团传送至天际省的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Raldbthar. Mzinchaleft. And Alftand.  They are not places, but names.  The names of the three machine heralds of the Apocalypse.</Source>
      <Dest>劳德布塔。津查遗址。还有精灵之牙。这些都不是地名，而是名字。这三个机器的名字预示着大灾变。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I have disabled your device with my Machine Hand.  Watch as I press this button and nothing happens!</Source>
      <Dest>但是你的装备已经被我这只机械手废除了。看，我按了这个按钮，没用！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Scotti? There is no Scotti. He was a figment of my imagination, until I made him a reality of yours.</Source>
      <Dest>斯科蒂？这里没有斯科蒂。在我梦想成真之前，他只是我臆想的产物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, you speak to the first hero of the 4th era, Champion of Mundus.  Two-Tails, the Dwarvenborn!</Source>
      <Dest>No, you speak to the first hero of the 4th era, Champion of Mundus.  Two-Tails, the Dwarvenborn!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No.  I am not yours to command. Nor will you fool these people any longer, servant of Mzanauch!</Source>
      <Dest>不，我不会再遵从你的命令。你也不必再去愚弄这些人了。马瑟诺迟的仆从！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No one is going anywhere!</Source>
      <Dest>你们哪儿也不许去！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I tell you, I tell you the Dwarvenborn comes!</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉你！我告诉你锻莫后裔来了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Our hero, our hero, claims a warrior's heart!</Source>
      <Dest>英雄，英雄，勇者无惧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, the correct term is "Dwemerborn."  But I get your meaning.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，正确的术语应该是“锻莫后裔”，但我明白你的意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, you're one of those pedantic types.  Can't stand it if a lizard ain't drank no speechcraft potion before he opens his mouth.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，你可真是迂腐至极。一个没喝口才药水的亚龙人都能把你搞定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Actually, the correct term is "Dwemerborn."  But I get your meaning.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，正确的术语应该是“锻莫后裔”，但我明白你的意思。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well you Speech Thalmor can suck on the business end of my tail.  Both the Gold and Purple Dwarves anointed me Dwarvenborn, so that's who I am.</Source>
      <Dest>噢你这打官腔的梭莫非要让我搬出商务态度来。金矮人和紫矮人都给我施了祭礼，承认我为矮人裔，所以我就是矮人裔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've been to Mzinchaleft.  That Centurion was walking just fine.</Source>
      <Dest>我去过津查遗址。只要百夫长一走就万事大吉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What you saw was an illusion, some sort of metal ghost, or a lie.  Each of those three explanations is far less ridiculous than the alternative.</Source>
      <Dest>你看到的要么是一个幻象，要么是某种金属的幽灵，要么就是你在撒谎。这三个解释都比你说那个靠谱得多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So if I visit Mzinchaleft, the ruins will be completely free of hostiles?</Source>
      <Dest>那就是说，如果我前往津查遗址将不会遇到任何有敌意的行为啰？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not all of them.  Unfortunately, my machine hand doesn't work on bandits, unless they have dwarven metal in their teeth.</Source>
      <Dest>Not all of them.  Unfortunately, my machine hand doesn't work on bandits, unless they have dwarven metal in their teeth.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What in Oblivion is a steam mammoth?</Source>
      <Dest>那头发怒的猛犸是特么的怎么了？！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A metal mammoth, powered by Dwarven pistons and steam.  What else could it possibly be?</Source>
      <Dest>一头金属猛犸，由矮人活塞和蒸汽驱动。还可能是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Two-Tails? I am honored to meet you.</Source>
      <Dest>The Two-Tails? I am honored to meet you.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you should be.  It's not everyday you get to meet the first hero of the 4th Era, and Champion of Tamriel.</Source>
      <Dest>你本该如此。不是每天都能见到这位第四纪元的第一英雄、泰姆瑞尔大陆的勇士的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Two-Tails? I am honored to meet you.</Source>
      <Dest>The Two-Tails? I am honored to meet you.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With the Divines' blessing, I've been granted a great gift, a weapon to conquer an ancient evil that has awoken from centuries of slumber.</Source>
      <Dest>在圣灵的祝福下，我得到了一件宝贵的礼物，一件曾经击败过上古恶魔的武器从数百年的沉睡中苏醒过来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Two-Tails? I am honored to meet you.</Source>
      <Dest>The Two-Tails? I am honored to meet you.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why the bards sing my name from mead halls to ship decks, in castles and colleges and sometimes in your head.</Source>
      <Dest>这也就是为什么从酒馆到渡船，从城堡到学院直至到你的耳边，都能听到吟游诗人传唱着我的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Two-Tails? I am honored to meet you.</Source>
      <Dest>The Two-Tails? I am honored to meet you.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Our hero, our hero, claims a warrior's heart.  I tell you, I tell you, the Dwarvenborn comes.</Source>
      <Dest>Our hero, our hero, claims a warrior's heart.  I tell you, I tell you, the Dwarvenborn comes.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you keep saying.</Source>
      <Dest>你继续说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm not saying.  The Gold and Purple Dwarves, both of them is who said it.  I'm just repeating words that have already been said.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是我说的.  金矮人和紫矮人, 他们都被人提起过.  我只是复述出来而已.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If the Divines are soup, how do they influence events?</Source>
      <Dest>如果圣灵是汤,他们是怎么发挥影响力的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The same way a beast of the wild attracts a mate.  Musk.  Smell.  Aroma.  The kind that will drive mortals to action.</Source>
      <Dest>野兽采取相同的方式在野外吸引配偶。麝香。臭味。香气。而这也将驱使人类采取行动。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If the Divines are soup, how do they influence events?</Source>
      <Dest>如果圣灵是汤,他们是怎么发挥影响力的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not all of those actions are necessarily good.  Some of them are great.  And some are pretty much perfect.  I'm that some.</Source>
      <Dest>那些行为并不一定都是好的。有些是极好的。而有些堪称完美。我就是那一类。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm having trouble following you.  Either I'm drunk or you're mad.  Maybe both.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着你混可真不容易啊！一会是我喝多了，一会是你生气了，或者一起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fear not, visitor.  It's easy to lose one's head when in the presence of greatness.  But remember, I was once a humble citizen like yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>别害怕，旅行者。在一个伟大的存在面前是很容易手足无措的，但是你要记住，曾经我也如你现在这般卑微。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm having trouble following you.  Either I'm drunk or you're mad.  Maybe both.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着你混可真不容易啊！一会是我喝多了，一会是你生气了，或者一起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then the earth shook, a forgotten evil made its return, and the world as we knew it was thrust into turmoil. </Source>
      <Dest>后来大地颤抖，被人忘却的邪恶重现人世，正如我们所知，世界陷入了动乱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm having trouble following you.  Either I'm drunk or you're mad.  Maybe both.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着你混可真不容易啊！一会是我喝多了，一会是你生气了，或者一起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The people cried out for a hero.   A savior.  The Divines answered their prayers by bestowing a single mortal with a gift.  </Source>
      <Dest>人们呼唤着英雄的诞生，一位救世主。圣灵们回应了他们的祷告，赐予凡人一位英雄。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm having trouble following you.  Either I'm drunk or you're mad.  Maybe both.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着你混可真不容易啊！一会是我喝多了，一会是你生气了，或者一起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That mortal was me.  For but a season ago I was a humble fisherman.  Now I am Two-Tails, first hero of the 4th Era.  Dwarvenborn!</Source>
      <Dest>那个凡人就是我。 不久之前我不过是个卑微的渔夫。  现在我是双尾, 第四纪元的第一英雄。 锻莫后裔!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you mean the legend of the Dragonborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是指龙裔传奇？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dragonborn? Do I look like I have wings?  No, I have horns and feathers and walk on three feet.  Just like Dwarves.</Source>
      <Dest>龙裔? 我看起来像是有翅膀的样子么？不，我长着角和羽毛，用三只脚行走，就像矮人一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you mean the legend of the Dragonborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是指龙裔传奇？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Besides, in war, fire is best fought with fire, and you don't bring a dragon to a Dwarf fight.  Not unless it's Dwarvenborn.</Source>
      <Dest>另外,战争中, 两边最好旗鼓相当, 你不能把一条龙拉到一场矮人对决中.  除非是龙裔.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you mean the legend of the Dragonborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是指龙裔传奇？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nothing else can combat the infinite armies of Mzanauch, the God-Eater.</Source>
      <Dest>没有什么能与噬神者马瑟诺迟的无尽军团作战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm pretty good with a forge.  Perhaps I could repair a machine too.</Source>
      <Dest>对锻造我很在行。也许我也能修一台机器。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You do realize every machine you raise from its slumber is another garrison for the armies of Mzanauch, don't you?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道你唤醒的所有机器都是马瑟诺迟守军中的一员，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm pretty good with a forge.  Perhaps I could repair a machine too.</Source>
      <Dest>对锻造我很在行。也许我也能修一台机器。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every innocent that dies as a result is someone you've killed.  Which makes you a murderer.  Not the good kind either.</Source>
      <Dest>每个最终死去的无辜者都是因你而被杀的。所以，你也算是凶手。也不是什么好人嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm pretty good with a forge.  Perhaps I could repair a machine too.</Source>
      <Dest>对锻造我很在行。也许我也能修一台机器。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, the kind of murderer that's rich and attractive and has their own Thanes.  In Skyrim, they call these murderers "Jarls."</Source>
      <Dest>你知道么, 某些杀人犯很有钱也很有魅力，并且拥有自己的领地.在天际省,这些杀人犯被称作“领主”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm pretty good with a forge.  Perhaps I could repair a machine too.</Source>
      <Dest>对锻造我很在行。也许我也能修一台机器。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You, on the other hand, would be just another killer.</Source>
      <Dest>另一方面，你不过只是个杀手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Lie) I'm pretty good with a forge.  Perhaps I could repair a machine too.</Source>
      <Dest>(撒谎)我打铁是一把好手,或许我也能帮你修好机器.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You do realize every machine you raise from its slumber is another garrison for the armies of Mzanauch, don't you?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道你唤醒的所有机器都是马瑟诺迟守军中的一员，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Lie) I'm pretty good with a forge.  Perhaps I could repair a machine too.</Source>
      <Dest>(撒谎)我打铁是一把好手,或许我也能帮你修好机器.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every innocent that dies as a result is someone you've killed.  Which makes you a murderer.  Not the good kind either.</Source>
      <Dest>每个最终死去的无辜者都是因你而被杀的。所以，你也算是凶手。也不是什么好人嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Lie) I'm pretty good with a forge.  Perhaps I could repair a machine too.</Source>
      <Dest>(撒谎)我打铁是一把好手,或许我也能帮你修好机器.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, the kind of murderer that's rich and attractive and has their own Thanes.  In Skyrim, they call these murderers "Jarls."</Source>
      <Dest>你知道么, 某些杀人犯很有钱也很有魅力，并且拥有自己的领地.在天际省,这些杀人犯被称作“领主”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Lie) I'm pretty good with a forge.  Perhaps I could repair a machine too.</Source>
      <Dest>(撒谎)我打铁是一把好手,或许我也能帮你修好机器.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You, on the other hand, would be just another killer.</Source>
      <Dest>另一方面，你不过只是个杀手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Mzanauch?</Source>
      <Dest>马瑟诺迟是谁?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your worst enemy and your best friend.  As you are nothing but a dog to him.</Source>
      <Dest>你最好的朋友或者最坏的敌人.而对他来说，你只不过是狗一样的存在.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Mzanauch?</Source>
      <Dest>马瑟诺迟是谁?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And like a good doggie, he's going to make you fetch dirt, then bring it to the surface while his army of Centurions flog you with brass whips.</Source>
      <Dest>And like a good doggie, he's going to make you fetch dirt, then bring it to the surface while his army of Centurions flog you with brass whips.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Mzanauch?</Source>
      <Dest>马瑟诺迟是谁?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mzanauch aims to devour the Gods, at least, the ones that live underground, and in doing so propel our world into chaos.  </Source>
      <Dest>马瑟诺迟想要吃掉神灵，至少是，深居地下的那些，以此把我们的世界推向混乱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Mzanauch?</Source>
      <Dest>马瑟诺迟是谁?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But as it is written in the hist bark, and inscribed in the assortment of spoons I keep in my pocket, all is not lost.</Source>
      <Dest>但因为已经在树皮历史书上有所记载，而且我兜里那些各式各样的勺子都有刻录，一切都未失传。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Mzanauch?</Source>
      <Dest>马瑟诺迟是谁?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For there is one that even the mad Dwarf and his legion of machines fear.  In their tongue, I am known as "Thuamerdhezin."  Dwarvenborn!</Source>
      <Dest>因为故事中有个即便疯癫的矮人和他的机械军团都惧怕的存在。在他们口中，我被称作"梭莫行刑官."锻莫后裔！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything special about the armor?</Source>
      <Dest>这装备有什么特别之处吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes.  It's as useless as a wet tunic against steel or iron, but it's impervious to attacks from machines.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。面对钢铁，它就像湿长袍一样毫无防护力，但是却能够有效抵御机械的攻击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything special about the armor?</Source>
      <Dest>这装备有什么特别之处吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's also immune to the call of Mzanauch's voice, as well his machine magic, despite being comprised of Dwarven metal.</Source>
      <Dest>它也对马瑟诺迟的呼唤免疫，以及他的机械魔法，尽管它是由矮人金属组成。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Anything special about the armor?</Source>
      <Dest>这装备有什么特别之处吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Truly an armor designed for a purpose, and fit for a champion.</Source>
      <Dest>老实说，盔甲总是为特定目的而设计，并且与勇士相配。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dwarven armor isn't made by Dwarves.</Source>
      <Dest>矮人护甲不是矮人做的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Correct.  But what I don is the Armor of the Animunculi, crafted for the one true Dwarvenborn and impenetrable to Mzanauch's magic.</Source>
      <Dest>正确。但我穿的可是阿尼姆恩古里之铠，由一名真正的锻莫后裔打造，马瑟诺迟的魔法可是无法穿透的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dwarven armor isn't made by Dwarves.</Source>
      <Dest>矮人护甲不是矮人做的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Their similar appearances is merely a coincidence.  No doubt one weaved by the Divines in order to allow me to move about freely.</Source>
      <Dest>他们类似的外表只是一个巧合，毫无疑问，这个圣灵创造的巧合是为了让我能够自由活动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You killed him?</Source>
      <Dest>你杀了他？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Didn't have a choice.  He fired first.  He just made an island come out of the bay. Now he was winking at me.  </Source>
      <Dest>我别无选择，是他先动手的。先是凭空从海岸召唤出一座岛来，现在又冲我眨眼。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You killed him?</Source>
      <Dest>你杀了他？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For all I knew he was going to waggle his fingers, cross his eyes and pull my heart out of my throat.</Source>
      <Dest>据我所知，他会来回晃动手指，眯着眼睛，把我的心脏从嗓子眼儿里拽出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I won't dignify your nonsense with a response.</Source>
      <Dest>介于你的荒谬无知，我可以选择不作回应</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then there's no need for me to respond with dignity, you overgrown guttersnipe.</Source>
      <Dest>那我就没有必要假模假式地客套了，你这早熟的贫民窟贱种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I tried repairing a Dwarven spider once.  The results were...unexpected.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾经尝试着去修复一只矮人蜘蛛。结果真是…出人意料。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You...tried to repair a Dwarven relic?  Fool!  Why not simply hand Mzanauch all of Nirn on a metal plate!</Source>
      <Dest>你……试图修复一个矮人遗迹？傻瓜！为什么不直接把整个奈恩河域装在金属盘子里端给马瑟诺迟呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does one eat a God?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么才能吃掉一个神？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not with a fork apparently, as that was my first guess.  Turns out the Gods are a soup-based life form.</Source>
      <Dest>显然不能用叉子，我初步估计是这样的。事实证明神灵这种生命形式是跟一碗浓汤差不太多的存在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, a visitor.  Word travels fast it seems, as fast as time flies.  Which makes sense, given that they're both a type of bird.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，是旅行者。现在这消息传得可快啊，跟时间过得一样飞快。确实这样，反正他们都跟飞鸟是差不多的存在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No doubt you come for the Argonian known as Two-Tails.  I am he.</Source>
      <Dest>毫无疑问你到这儿来是要找那个叫双尾的亚龙人的。我就是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Broom Floor Sweep.  If only that worked on people.</Source>
      <Dest>Broom Floor Sweep.  If only that worked on people.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must be one of those happily married folk.  They always like to complain about how happy they are.</Source>
      <Dest>你肯定已经是已婚了。这些可恨的小夫妻们总是喜欢秀恩爱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This fishing staff...did it happen to be a Wabbajack?</Source>
      <Dest>这个鱼竿……是瓦巴杰克？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wabba...what?  It's a fishing staff.  It had a hole in the end with which to catch salmon.</Source>
      <Dest>瓦巴……啥子？这是一只鱼竿。它底部的有个洞用来勾起大马哈鱼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This fishing staff...did it happen to be a Wabbajack?</Source>
      <Dest>这个鱼竿……是瓦巴杰克？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, I could've used the staff to catch twice as many fish, if I were a fisherman and not the one true savior of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，如果我是一个渔夫而不是天际省的救主，我本可以用这东西抓到比这多一倍的鱼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This fishing staff...did it happen to be a Wabbajack?</Source>
      <Dest>这个鱼竿……是瓦巴杰克？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But first I needed to step through that portal.  Which I had no problem doing.  I didn't kill a man and three beggars to catch more salmon.</Source>
      <Dest>但首先我必须跨进大门。这对我来说不是问题。我杀掉三个乞丐和一个行人可不是为了抓几条鲑鱼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A tale worthy of the bards.</Source>
      <Dest>一个值得被传颂的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you're here to document my heroism, you're welcome to do it.  </Source>
      <Dest>If you're here to document my heroism, you're welcome to do it.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A tale worthy of the bards.</Source>
      <Dest>一个值得被传颂的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have a few pieces of scrap metal here that I can reactivate and disable right now, which you should be able to spin into at least a dozen poems.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我这里刚好有几片零碎的金属可供再次激活或者废弃。至少应该足够你吟诵出一打的诗歌了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is that when you woke up?</Source>
      <Dest>你正是在那时候醒来的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why yes.  Sacred Dwarven rituals are always performed in the dream world.  </Source>
      <Dest>为什么醒来.  矮人族的神圣典礼都是在梦里举行的.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is that when you woke up?</Source>
      <Dest>你正是在那时候醒来的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Luckily, the dream also told me where the Armor of the Animunculi would materialize in the real world.</Source>
      <Dest>幸运的是，那个梦还告诉了我阿尼姆恩古里之铠在真实世界中出现的位置。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I merely had to travel to Skyrim and retrieve it from a chest in Ironbind Barrow.</Source>
      <Dest>我要做的只是前往天际省然后到铁岩石冢的一个箱子里把它取回来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is that when you woke up?</Source>
      <Dest>你正是在那时候醒来的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I couldn't chance it.  Portals like that don't stay open forever.  Just long enough for a hero to pass through them.</Source>
      <Dest>我冒不起那险。那样的入口不会一直敞开。时间刚刚容许让一位英雄从中穿过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Rock cheese sounds delicious.  You should've stopped and had a picnic.</Source>
      <Dest>巨岩奶酪，听起来很是可口的样子。你应该马上停下来，大吃一顿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I didn't kill a man and three beggars to let fate pass me by while I was busy eating pieces of curdled stone.</Source>
      <Dest>我杀了一个男人和三个乞丐，不是为忙着吃石头却让宿命从我身边溜走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Rock cheese sounds delicious.  You should've stopped and had a picnic.</Source>
      <Dest>巨岩奶酪，听起来很是可口的样子。你应该马上停下来，大吃一顿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was fishing near the coast of Niben Bay in Cyrodiil, when I saw a bearded mage standing by the bank.</Source>
      <Dest>我在赛瑞迪尔沙滩的小浅滩附近钓鱼,当时我看见有个大胡子的法师站在岸上.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you discover you were Dwarvenborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么发现自己是锻莫后裔的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In his hand was the ugliest fishing staff I had ever seen, but when he raised it to the sky, a massive island rose right out of the water.</Source>
      <Dest>他手中握着的是我平生见过最丑的鱼竿，但是当他将其举向天空的时候，一座巨大的岛屿突然从水面上探出头来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you discover you were Dwarvenborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么发现自己是锻莫后裔的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>On it were rocks chiseled into the shape of Dwarven heads, only they weren't rocks, but cheese.</Source>
      <Dest>在上面的是被雕刻成矮人头部的石头，只不过那些不是真正的石头，是奶酪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you discover you were Dwarvenborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么发现自己是锻莫后裔的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then, waving the staff around some more, he conjured three beggars to eat away at the cheese rocks from its mustache down to its chin.</Source>
      <Dest>然后在相对较密集的一处，他挥动竿子、施了个咒召唤出三个乞丐来，让他们对着巨岩奶酪一顿猛啃，从石像的胡子啃到下巴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you discover you were Dwarvenborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么发现自己是锻莫后裔的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Their efforts revealed a secret portal.  A gateway to the Dwemer homeworld.</Source>
      <Dest>他们的努力换来了一个秘密入口。一座通往矮人家园的大门。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you discover you were Dwarvenborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么发现自己是锻莫后裔的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Curious, I followed him into the bay.  I swam.  He walked.   I trailed him to edge of the shoreline, just as he was about to enter the portal.</Source>
      <Dest>好奇心驱使，我跟在他后面进入海湾，他在岸上走，我在水中潜伏，我跟随他直到到达海岸线的边缘，那一刻他正要进入大门。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you discover you were Dwarvenborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么发现自己是锻莫后裔的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do after the portal was revealed?</Source>
      <Dest>那个传送门打开之后，你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then he stopped, and turned in my direction.  I was hiding behind some brush, but I could've sworn he winked at me.</Source>
      <Dest>然后他站住了，转向我的方向。我当时正藏在灌木丛后，可我敢说他确实是有朝我眨了眨眼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you discover you were Dwarvenborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么发现自己是锻莫后裔的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do after the portal was revealed?</Source>
      <Dest>那个传送门打开之后，你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Turns out there was just something in his eye.  Specifically, the arrow that I shot in his face for winking at me.</Source>
      <Dest>原来这些就是在他所眼见的东西。具体而言，那支我因为他冲我眨眼而射到他脸上的箭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you discover you were Dwarvenborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎么发现自己是锻莫后裔的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do after the portal was revealed?</Source>
      <Dest>那个传送门打开之后，你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then one day, while renovating an old cave, he came across a magic scroll, written inside a tube of fungus.</Source>
      <Dest>然后有一天，在搜寻一个古洞时，他找到了一卷法术书，就写在一支蘑菇管茎之上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Inside was a 100,000 year old prophecy, one that foretold what already happened 75,000 years ago, at the Dawn of Time.</Source>
      <Dest>藏在里面的是一本有十万年历史的古老预言书，书中预言了距今七万五千年前黎明时代的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It told of the age of the soup people, who flowed through the underground rivers of Nirn like hot creamy magma, and were extremely delicious.</Source>
      <Dest>讲述的是汤羹民族时代的故事，他们在奈恩地下河中像热奶油浆一般流淌，而且相当的美味。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It warned of a day in the distant past when the soup would turn cold. So cold it congealed.</Source>
      <Dest>It warned of a day in the distant past when the soup would turn cold. So cold it congealed.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These jelly blobs and their scabs would be what they've become. The early beginnings of man and beast.</Source>
      <Dest>These jelly blobs and their scabs would be what they've become. The early beginnings of man and beast.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay.</Source>
      <Dest>好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say he was a gifted Dwarf, blessed with the ability to craft, repair, and if need be, marry machines simply by touching them.</Source>
      <Dest>人们说他是个矮人天才，天赋异禀，能制造、修理机器。如果需要的话，他碰一下就能让机器们结婚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like to know more about this God-Eater.</Source>
      <Dest>我想知道更多关于这个噬神者的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some even say he learned the Way of the Voice. That he could direct his spiders to sweep the floors by issuing a simple three word command.</Source>
      <Dest>有些人甚至说他学会了龙吼之道。他可以通过发出三个简单词汇的命令他的蜘蛛去扫地板。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like to know more about this God-Eater.</Source>
      <Dest>我想知道更多关于这个噬神者的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something like "Broom Floor Sweep" or "Beep Boop Bop" or "Insert tube here."  You know, common phrases of the machine tongue.</Source>
      <Dest>你要知道，像“去扫地”或者“哔啵啵"再或者”插管道“之类的，是机器人的通用语言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like to know more about this God-Eater.</Source>
      <Dest>我想知道更多关于这个噬神者的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm Dwarvenborn, aren't I?</Source>
      <Dest>我就是锻莫后裔，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you enter the portal?</Source>
      <Dest>你去过阳台？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As Dwarvenborn, I possess what is known as the machine hand.  Simply by placing my palms on a device, I can disable it permanently.</Source>
      <Dest>作为矮人裔，我拥一只机械之手。我只要把手掌放在一个机器上，就能让它永远停止工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting. What sort of powers does the Dwarvenborn possess?</Source>
      <Dest>真有意思！锻莫后裔拥有什么样子的力量呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am now on a great quest to place my hands upon as many Dwarven machinations as possible, so that I may render the God-Eater's army inert.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在正在干操作尽可能多矮人机器这样重要的大事，或许就能减缓噬神者的部队的动作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting. What sort of powers does the Dwarvenborn possess?</Source>
      <Dest>真有意思！锻莫后裔拥有什么样子的力量呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It doesn't matter if it's a broken spider or a fully operational Centurion, one touch from my machine hand and no smith can repair it.</Source>
      <Dest>不管那是一个已经坏掉的矮人蜘蛛还是一个运转良好的百夫长，一旦我用我的机械手轻轻地碰一下，就再没哪个铁匠能把它们修好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interesting. What sort of powers does the Dwarvenborn possess?</Source>
      <Dest>真有意思！锻莫后裔拥有什么样子的力量呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unfathomable!  I am a hero, the Champion of Mundus.  You dare insult me by suggesting I raid Dwarven ruins like a common bandit?</Source>
      <Dest>真是不可理喻！我是个英雄，是梦达思的扞卫者。你却胆敢让我像个普通强盗那样洗劫矮人遗迹，以此来羞辱我？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Someone like you would be handy when plundering a Dwarven ruin.</Source>
      <Dest>像你这样的人搜刮起矮人废墟来总是得心应手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll raid them like an uncommon bandit.</Source>
      <Dest>I'll raid them like an uncommon bandit.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Someone like you would be handy when plundering a Dwarven ruin.</Source>
      <Dest>像你这样的人搜刮起矮人废墟来总是得心应手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know, the kind that says "Please" and "Thank you" and hates the predicament an unfair society has placed him in.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道的，满口“请”、“谢谢”，却总是怨恨社会不公的，可都是这种人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Someone like you would be handy when plundering a Dwarven ruin.</Source>
      <Dest>像你这样的人搜刮起矮人废墟来总是得心应手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was my fishing bow.  How else are you supposed to catch slaughterfish without a proper bow?  Or staff, for that matter.  Now I had both.</Source>
      <Dest>那是我的捕鱼弓。你要是没有把好弓还怎么去捉食人鱼呢？或者法杖也行。现在我都有了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait.  I thought you were fishing.  What were you doing with a bow?</Source>
      <Dest>慢着！我还以为你在钓鱼。拿把弓是要做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, I could've used the staff to catch twice as many fish, if I were a fisherman and not the one true savior of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，如果我是一个渔夫而不是天际省的救主，我本可以用这东西抓到比这多一倍的鱼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait.  I thought you were fishing.  What were you doing with a bow?</Source>
      <Dest>慢着！我还以为你在钓鱼。拿把弓是要做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But first I needed to step through that portal.  Which I had no problem doing.  I didn't kill a man and three beggars to catch more salmon.</Source>
      <Dest>但首先我必须跨进大门。这对我来说不是问题。我杀掉三个乞丐和一个行人可不是为了抓几条鲑鱼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait.  I thought you were fishing.  What were you doing with a bow?</Source>
      <Dest>慢着！我还以为你在钓鱼。拿把弓是要做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I told you they were delicious, didn't I?  Seems that's reason enough.</Source>
      <Dest>我跟你说过那东西很好吃，对嘛？那理由应该足够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That doesn't explain why Mzanauch wants to eat them.</Source>
      <Dest>这无法为什么马瑟诺迟想吃掉他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't say this is unexpected.  Heroes are known to have their share of devotees.  But I require no donation of arms or armor, mead or gold.</Source>
      <Dest>对我来说，这一点儿也不意外。众所周知，英雄都有他们各自的迷恋者。但我不需要别人赠送的武器或防具，蜜酒或黄金。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're fun. I like you.</Source>
      <Dest>你真有趣，我很中意你。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For all that I require to stand against the armies before me is this magical armor and my machine hand.</Source>
      <Dest>我用来对抗在我面前那些军团仅仅需要这件魔法护甲和这只机械手而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're fun. I like you.</Source>
      <Dest>你真有趣，我很中意你。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Indisputably so.  I tried to dispute it once, although I was just pretending to be humble.  Females seem to like that.</Source>
      <Dest>Indisputably so.  I tried to dispute it once, although I was just pretending to be humble.  Females seem to like that.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. My mistake.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，我弄错了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only both the Purple and Gold Dwarves I met in the Isles, they preferred me arrogant.  They wanted me to claim my title as Dwarvenborn.</Source>
      <Dest>Only both the Purple and Gold Dwarves I met in the Isles, they preferred me arrogant.  They wanted me to claim my title as Dwarvenborn.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. My mistake.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，我弄错了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I did.  I couldn't refuse a lady.  Well, I could, but only if she wanted me to pay for dinner.  You eat it, you buy it.</Source>
      <Dest>我也是，我怎能拒绝一名女士。好吧，如果她想要我为她的晚饭买单的话，我也是会拒绝的。因为既然你吃了它，那你总得付钱吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Of course. My mistake.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，我弄错了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only what the Gods foretold. They say Mzanauch will come from the west, charging down a mountain led by an avalanche of metal boulders.  Spheres.</Source>
      <Dest>仅仅只有神灵的预言。马瑟诺迟自西方破山而来，统帅金属巨石洪流。自山顶滚落。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know of Mzanauch's plans?</Source>
      <Dest>你对马瑟诺迟的计划知道多少？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Behind them will be the Mad Dwarf himself, riding in a steam-powered war carriage pulled along by Dwarven mammoths.</Source>
      <Dest>紧随其后便是那个疯矮人，他会乘坐一个由矮人猛犸拉着的蒸汽战车。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know of Mzanauch's plans?</Source>
      <Dest>你对马瑟诺迟的计划知道多少？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say when Mzanauch makes his charge, the ore veins across Skyrim will melt, and the rivers will run bright with metal.  </Source>
      <Dest>他们说，当马瑟诺迟掌管一切的时候，整个天际省的矿脉会融化，而波光粼粼的河流混杂着金属奔淌。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know of Mzanauch's plans?</Source>
      <Dest>你对马瑟诺迟的计划知道多少？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only the Dwarvenborn possesses the power to stop him.</Source>
      <Dest>只有锻莫后裔拥有阻止他的力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know of Mzanauch's plans?</Source>
      <Dest>你对马瑟诺迟的计划知道多少？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>From here in the Eyrie, I can watch for his descent, as well as create a strategic barrier to protect myself from his spies.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以把这作为一个堡垒，躲避他的侵袭和监视。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know of Mzanauch's plans?</Source>
      <Dest>你对马瑟诺迟的计划知道多少？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What you speak of is a temporary solution.  Pointless when you consider that Mzanauch can resurrect his machines with his hands or his voice.</Source>
      <Dest>你说的是一个临时的解决方案。 但考虑到马瑟诺迟可以用手或者声音把机器重新启动什么的，这建议毫无意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Isn't it easier just to destroy them from afar?  Those things are dangerous.</Source>
      <Dest>从远处摧毁他们不是更简单么？这些东西很危险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only the touch of my machine hand can render them ineffective.  Every wire, every gear, every part becomes as immaterial as the void.</Source>
      <Dest>只有经过我这只机械手的触碰之后才能让它们无效。每一根电线，每一只齿轮，每一个部分都像虚空一样化为无形。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Isn't it easier just to destroy them from afar?  Those things are dangerous.</Source>
      <Dest>从远处摧毁他们不是更简单么？这些东西很危险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only a single Centurion was left intact, at the tail end of the cavernous ruin. Before it could rise, I ambushed it with my sacred palm.</Source>
      <Dest>在这洞穴废墟之末，只有一个百夫长完好无损。在它复苏之前，我就一记如来神掌把它干掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Was there anything left to disable?</Source>
      <Dest>这儿还有什么需要关闭的东西？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I laid it right on its thigh, but it's dynamo core seemed to be protected by some sort of magical force field.  Mzanauch's work, no doubt.</Source>
      <Dest>我把它摆成盘坐在大腿上的姿势，，但它的动力核心似乎被某种魔法盾保护着。毫无疑问，是马瑟诺迟的杰作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Was there anything left to disable?</Source>
      <Dest>这儿还有什么需要关闭的东西？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We had to disable the field first, immobilize it manually. I left the mercs to deal with such menial work.</Source>
      <Dest>我们必须先关掉那片区域，手动停止它。我留下一些佣兵处理这些小事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Was there anything left to disable?</Source>
      <Dest>这儿还有什么需要关闭的东西？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Once the mercs finished paralyzing it, I blessed it with my machine hand.</Source>
      <Dest>一旦佣兵把它瘫痪了，我就用我的这只机械手为它赐福。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Was there anything left to disable?</Source>
      <Dest>这儿还有什么需要关闭的东西？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I solved this quandary by hiring mercs to open doors for me. Then we went northeast to Mzinchaleft.</Source>
      <Dest>为了解开困惑，我雇了一些佣兵帮我打开门。然后我们向东北进发，前往津查遗址。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you get inside then?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎样进去的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet it seems most of the machines were already destroyed by some horker of a woman.</Source>
      <Dest>Yet it seems most of the machines were already destroyed by some horker of a woman.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you get inside then?</Source>
      <Dest>你是怎样进去的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Everything in this tower, for one. Notice how still the chair and pieces of scrap metal are?  </Source>
      <Dest>在这塔里的所有东西，只是一击而已。有注意到这些椅子和废金属有多牢固？  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just curious.  How many Dwarven devices have you successfully disabled?</Source>
      <Dest>随便问下.  你已经顺利关掉几个矮人装置了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Dwemer Museum in Markath has also received my blessing.  Not a single device in there is operational.</Source>
      <Dest>马卡斯城的锻莫博物馆也有收到过我的“祝福”。现在那里连一台能用的设备都没有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just curious.  How many Dwarven devices have you successfully disabled?</Source>
      <Dest>随便问下.  你已经顺利关掉几个矮人装置了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Other than that, I tried entering a ruin northwest of here, but I accidentally disabled the door, permanently locking it.</Source>
      <Dest>除那之外，我试图进入西北方向的一个废墟，但我不小心把门给废了，完全打不开了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just curious.  How many Dwarven devices have you successfully disabled?</Source>
      <Dest>随便问下.  你已经顺利关掉几个矮人装置了?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's the only place that's completely safe.  Mzanauch has his spiders everywhere.  Hiding in the dirt like eight-legged mudcrabs.</Source>
      <Dest>这是唯一一处绝对安全的地方。马瑟诺迟的蜘蛛到处都是。它们像八爪泥沼蟹一样躲在泥土里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you staying in this tower?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么待在这座塔里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're out there right now, burrowed in the mud not forty paces from where we stand, using the grass and the weeds like an insect's antenna.</Source>
      <Dest>他们正在距我们这里不到四十步的地方的挖掘地洞。那边的草就像昆虫的触须一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you staying in this tower?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么待在这座塔里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Only these antenna aren't like the kind you find on a bug. No, attached at the end are magical listening spheres, painted white to look like flowers.</Source>
      <Dest>只是这些触角不像是你从臭虫身上看到的那样。不对，这末梢上的是魔法聆听之球，涂成白色是为了看起来像花。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you staying in this tower?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么待在这座塔里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Cotton balls, fungal pods, tulips...his eyes and ears are everywhere, searching for the one they call Dwarvenborn.</Source>
      <Dest>棉花球，真菌孢子，郁金香...他眼观六路耳听八方，在寻找一个被叫做锻莫后裔的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you staying in this tower?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么待在这座塔里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Conversely, there isn't a section of wall or piece of Dwarven metal that I haven't blessed with my machine hand.  It's completely quarantined.</Source>
      <Dest>相反地, 这里的没有一面墙哪怕是一块金属不被我的机械手赐福过。这是完全隔离的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why are you staying in this tower?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么待在这座塔里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The third and final test was to don the Armor of the Animunculi. For legend stated only a true hero could claim it.</Source>
      <Dest>第三个也是最后的考验是穿上阿尼姆恩古里之铠。因为相传只有真正的英雄穿得上它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And the third?</Source>
      <Dest>那么，第三？?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The armor was encased in columns of gold and purple light. Two Dwarves stood guard before it, but opened the path to reveal my prize.</Source>
      <Dest>盔甲放在紫金光华照耀的石柱上. 两个矮人站在前面守护着它, 但他们挪开让出小道让我取得奖励.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And the third?</Source>
      <Dest>那么，第三？?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I put it on, a chant began to swell, one that would echo across the Isles. For I was Dwarvenborn.</Source>
      <Dest>当我穿上它的时候，歌声开始响起、扩散,传遍整个群岛。因为我是锻莫后裔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And the third?</Source>
      <Dest>那么，第三？?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The second test came with a twist. I was asked to repair an Orrery, so I could learn to touch devices without damaging the mechanism.</Source>
      <Dest>第二个测试有点新颖。我被要求去修理一台星象仪，这样一来我就可以在不破坏现有机制的情况下学着去用那个装置了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the second test?</Source>
      <Dest>第二个测试又怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I managed to suppress my power as I connected the cylinders, cogs, and coherers to their respective wheels, which were powered by rodents.</Source>
      <Dest>当我把这些汽缸，齿轮，检波器和它们对应的用老鼠驱动的轮子连接起来的时候，我努力压制着自己的力量.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the second test?</Source>
      <Dest>第二个测试又怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It did. But not before having me undergo 3 tests in 3 nights to see if I my machine hand was true.</Source>
      <Dest>恩啊。但在此之前，让我在三天三夜里接受三次测试来验证是否我的机械手是真的 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were saying a steam mammoth anointed you Dwarvenborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是说一头蒸汽猛犸把你奉为锻莫后裔？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The first test was simple. Touch the chassis of a Dwarven Sphere and return it to its shell. That's when I first learned the nature of my power.</Source>
      <Dest>第一个测试非常简单。去碰一下那个矮人球体的底座然后放回原位。那是我第一次发现自己真正能力的本质。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were saying a steam mammoth anointed you Dwarvenborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是说一头蒸汽猛犸把你奉为锻莫后裔？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Through my palm, I could channel into the matrix of gears and wires and shatter the soul crackers that powered them.</Source>
      <Dest>我的手能感知到这些神奇机械的每一条线路以及驱动它们的灵魂碎片所在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You were saying a steam mammoth anointed you Dwarvenborn?</Source>
      <Dest>你是说一头蒸汽猛犸把你奉为锻莫后裔？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Let's revisit this topic later.</Source>
      <Dest>我们稍后重谈这个话题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unconscionable.  What's a Werecroc but a mortal and a crocodile.  That's easy.  Like mixing an agility potion.  Even a rapist could do it.</Source>
      <Dest>说的太过火了。鳄人什么的不就是人和鳄鱼的结合体嘛。没什么大不了。就像是混合一瓶敏捷药水一样。强奸犯都办得到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, but that's still not as impressive as say, a Werecroc.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，但鳄人并不像所宣称的那样令人印象深刻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I saw one do it with a mortar, a pestle, an alembic, and some Aster bloom.  But mostly I just watched him rape things.</Source>
      <Dest>我看见过有个强奸犯用研钵、杵、蒸馏器和紫苑根茎制作敏捷药剂。但是大多时候都是看见他正在犯罪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, but that's still not as impressive as say, a Werecroc.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，但鳄人并不像所宣称的那样令人印象深刻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Me, on the other hand, I'm an Argonian with the power of a Dwarf.  That's hard.  That's impressive.</Source>
      <Dest>我，换言之，不过是个拥有矮人力量的亚龙人。这挺难的，也挺令人吃惊的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, but that's still not as impressive as say, a Werecroc.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，但鳄人并不像所宣称的那样令人印象深刻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why the Purple and Gold Dwarves both named me Dwarvenborn.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是为什么紫矮人和金矮人称呼我为锻莫后裔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, but that's still not as impressive as say, a Werecroc.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，但鳄人并不像所宣称的那样令人印象深刻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell that to the people who called me "featherbrain."  There's quite a few of them.  Which is precisely why I pluck my feathers.</Source>
      <Dest>把这件事去告诉那些嘲弄我轻浮笨蛋的家伙——那样的人还真是不少。这也是我拔掉身上羽毛的直接原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't see any feathers.</Source>
      <Dest>连毛都没有.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For some reason you smiled when you said that, and the reason's a good one.  Who wouldn't smile when hearing the tale of a true hero?</Source>
      <Dest>不知为何你说这些的时候微笑了，而且这是个不错的理由。有谁不会为一个真英雄的故事而动容呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A likely story.</Source>
      <Dest>真实的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dragons?  Unthinkable.  The dragons have been extinct for centuries.  What is dead can never be revived.</Source>
      <Dest>龙？不可能吧。早在几个世纪前它们就灭绝了。死掉的东西怎么可能复生呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see. The dragons have risen and you have been chosen to stop them.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了。龙族已经崛起，而你被选中去阻止它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, the ancient evil I speak of is Dwarves.  Returned from the land that time forgot, to enslave mortals to work in their underground mines.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我说的那个远古恶魔是指矮人。他们会从早已被遗忘了的大陆回到这儿，重新把人们拖进他们的地下矿场进行奴役。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see. The dragons have risen and you have been chosen to stop them.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了。龙族已经崛起，而你被选中去阻止它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or more specifically, a dwarf.  Mzanauch, the God-Eater.  He returns with his army of mechanical spiders and Centurions, to end the day itself.</Source>
      <Dest>或者更具体一点, 是个矮人，叫做马瑟诺迟，一个噬神者。他带着机械蜘蛛与百夫长回来，终结这个世界.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see. The dragons have risen and you have been chosen to stop them.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了。龙族已经崛起，而你被选中去阻止它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People blame Ulfric. Call him power hungry and arrogant.  Looks to me like we got two Ulfrics in Skyrim, only one of them calls himself Elisif.</Source>
      <Dest>人们责难乌弗瑞克渴望权力、目中无人。我觉得天际省有两个乌弗瑞克，只是其中有一个管自己叫艾利西弗.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think that is?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会那样想？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Same with the Dwarves.  One of their own, the God-Eater himself was on the loose, and they were too busy griping to care.</Source>
      <Dest>矮人也是这样。他们中的一人，噬神者本人曾经异常暴虐，而他们忙着抱怨现状顾不上他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think that is?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会那样想？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Luckily, a chamberlain by the name of Haskill led me down a Yellow Road, where I was granted an audience with a steam mammoth.</Source>
      <Dest>Luckily, a chamberlain by the name of Haskill led me down a Yellow Road, where I was granted an audience with a steam mammoth.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think that is?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会那样想？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The mammoth told of how it betrayed Mzanauch, and how his former master sought the nature of the Divines so that he could know how to eat them.</Source>
      <Dest>猛犸描述了它是如何背叛马瑟诺迟的，以及他的前任主人又是如何探寻着圣灵的本质并由此明白要如何吃掉他们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think that is?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会那样想？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not purple and gold.  Purple "and" Gold.  Two separate factions.  The Gold Dwarves are the rich ones, on account of all the gold they wear.</Source>
      <Dest>不是什么紫金。是“紫矮人”与“金矮人”。两伙势力。金矮人族是有钱人，以他们大肆佩戴金质首饰而闻名。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about these purple and gold Dwarves.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我更多关于这些紫金矮人的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The purple ones are the smart ones.  They paint their gold purple so no one will steal it.</Source>
      <Dest>紫矮人是最聪明的。他们把黄金涂上一层紫色所以没有人会去偷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about these purple and gold Dwarves.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我更多关于这些紫金矮人的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Both of them don't take kindly to men, except the purple ones are less unkind.  Only thing they hate more is each other. </Source>
      <Dest>他们两族对别人都不怎么地，紫矮人似乎还好点。唯一他们最恨的估计就是彼此了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about these purple and gold Dwarves.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我更多关于这些紫金矮人的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They remind me of the Imperials and the Stormcloaks.  Hacking away at each while the real threat grows strong.</Source>
      <Dest>他们让我想到帝国和风暴斗篷。他们相互斫杀，却任由真正的威胁发展壮大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me more about these purple and gold Dwarves.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我更多关于这些紫金矮人的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who, the Centurion?  It's not wise to give them names, or get attached to them.  They may look like people, but they aren't.</Source>
      <Dest>谁，那个百夫长？赐予他们名字是不明智的行为，与他们走得太近也一样。他们可能看起来是人，但事实上并非如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Her name is Mjoll, you insensitive boot.</Source>
      <Dest>她的名字叫穆月尔, 你这反应迟钝的家伙.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're mindless, godless slavers, and their hordes of spiders and steam carriages will threaten your family, your wives, and even your livestock.</Source>
      <Dest>他们是愚蠢而又没有信仰的奴隶贩子，他们的那些蜘蛛群、蒸汽马车会威胁到你的家人，你的妻子，甚至你的家畜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Her name is Mjoll, you insensitive boot.</Source>
      <Dest>她的名字叫穆月尔, 你这反应迟钝的家伙.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Impossible.  You speak to the first hero of the 4th Era, blessed by the Divines with a great and ancient power.</Source>
      <Dest>不可能的。你与第四纪元的首位英雄交流，被圣灵祝福给予强大的上古之力的那位。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Never heard of you.</Source>
      <Dest>从来没听说过你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With it, I will vanquish a great evil that has returned from centuries of slumber, and now threatens the very fabric of our world. </Source>
      <Dest>我会用它打败一个沉睡了几个世纪，而今苏醒过来危害我们的世界秩序的极度邪恶的存在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Never heard of you.</Source>
      <Dest>从来没听说过你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's right, you would've guessed it, had I not told you two seconds from now.  I...am Dwarvenborn.</Source>
      <Dest>说得对，你会猜得到的……不过我有没有在几秒钟前告诉过你，我其实是……锻莫后裔？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Never heard of you.</Source>
      <Dest>从来没听说过你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nonsense! They're Dwarves. You can tell by their horns and feathers. Which they shed as babies, just like tails.</Source>
      <Dest>胡说！他们是矮人。你可以靠他们的角和羽毛分辨。那些东西在他们婴儿时期脱落，就像尾巴一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like Saints and Seducers to me. Residents of the Shivering Isles.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来像是那些战栗孤岛的居民——圣徒们以及诱惑者们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had feathers once too.  The tips were as blue as Niben Bay in the summer.  That is, until the locals started calling me a featherbrain.</Source>
      <Dest>我以前有过羽毛，它们的尖端就像夏季的尼本湾河水一样蔚蓝。嗯，不过都是当地人都把喊我轻浮笨蛋之前的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like Saints and Seducers to me. Residents of the Shivering Isles.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来像是那些战栗孤岛的居民——圣徒们以及诱惑者们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Others said that was an insult to feathers.  The jokes on them, I plucked my feathers, cut them open, and they had no brains to speak of.</Source>
      <Dest>有人说这是对羽毛的侮辱。真是笑话，我把我的羽毛扯下来，把它们切开，你猜怎么着？它们根本没有大脑去提抗议。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sounds like Saints and Seducers to me. Residents of the Shivering Isles.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来像是那些战栗孤岛的居民——圣徒们以及诱惑者们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, it may be your servant now, but when Mzanauch sounds the clarion call through his steam horn, all of Tamriel will be overrun by spider hordes.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，那它现在大概已经是你的仆人了，但一旦马瑟诺迟吹响他那蒸汽号角，那泰姆瑞尔大陆上就会挤满蜘蛛群了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I repaired a Dwarven spider.  It called me "Master" and seemed docile.</Source>
      <Dest>我修好了一只矮人蜘蛛。它恭敬地称呼我主人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Spiders you repaired because you thought they would make nice pets.</Source>
      <Dest>你修好了那些蜘蛛是因为你觉得他们会成为很好的宠物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I repaired a Dwarven spider.  It called me "Master" and seemed docile.</Source>
      <Dest>我修好了一只矮人蜘蛛。它恭敬地称呼我主人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha!  You are not Dwarvenborn.  Goblinborn, maybe.  But the plague that sweeps over this land is not pale and squishy.</Source>
      <Dest>哈哈！你不是锻莫后裔！也许是什么哥布林裔。但横扫过这片土地的瘟疫可不是绵软无力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're no hero. But you're looking at one.</Source>
      <Dest>你们这儿没英雄。但你们正面对着一个英雄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, it clanks and it whistles and it's made of metal.  I speak of Dwarves, and their army of walking ingots.</Source>
      <Dest>不不，那货会发出咣当咣当声还会鸣汽笛，而且是金属做成的。我说的是矮人，还有他们那些会动的铁疙瘩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're no hero. But you're looking at one.</Source>
      <Dest>你们这儿没英雄。但你们正面对着一个英雄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They are led by the traitor Mzanauch.  The outcast who seeks to eat the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>他们由背叛者马瑟诺迟带领。就是那个因为妄图噬神而被驱逐的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're no hero. But you're looking at one.</Source>
      <Dest>你们这儿没英雄。但你们正面对着一个英雄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As the Khajiit say, may your sand lead to road warmth...or something.</Source>
      <Dest>如那虎人所说，愿你的前路是温暖的沙地……或是别的什么东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until next time.</Source>
      <Dest>下回见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>哈啰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tidings.</Source>
      <Dest>怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something...on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>你是在想…什么呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How can I...help you?</Source>
      <Dest>我...我怎么帮助你?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
