<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just three of thousands of people who want a certain housecat dead.</Source>
      <Dest>只是有成千上万的人想要某只家猫死掉而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thousands? Are you sure you aren't underselling it? </Source>
      <Dest>成“千”上“万”？这价钱低得太离谱了吧？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Just three of thousands of people who want a certain housecat dead.</Source>
      <Dest>只是有成千上万的人想要某只家猫死掉而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here's my advice. You go chasing after that cat, you'll end up chasing your own tail. Let it go. He ain't worth the effort.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我的建议。如果你跑去跟踪那只猫，你最后只会徒劳无获。让他去吧。他不值得你去费心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We're looking for J'Sharr. I want to cut a deal with him.</Source>
      <Dest>我们在找杰夏尔。我想和他做笔买卖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You really are a glutton for punishment, aren't you? But alright. It just so happens that I work for J'Sharr.</Source>
      <Dest>你对于惩罚真的是贪得无厌，是不是？不过，也罢。我当年为杰夏尔工作时就是这个样子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We're looking for J'Sharr. I want to cut a deal with him.</Source>
      <Dest>我们在找杰夏尔。我想和他做笔买卖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He pays me to say bad things about him, and I must say it's a job I rather enjoy.</Source>
      <Dest>他花钱雇我说他的坏话，这活儿对我可真有乐子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We're looking for J'Sharr. I want to cut a deal with him.</Source>
      <Dest>我们在找杰夏尔。我想和他做笔买卖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I also pass the word on if anyone wants to do business. He has a place in Hjaalmarch near that old Crabber's Shanty where he makes his deals.</Source>
      <Dest>如果有人想做生意的话，我也会把这句话带到。他就在希雅陲领的旧捕蟹人棚屋附近交易。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We're looking for J'Sharr. I want to cut a deal with him.</Source>
      <Dest>我们在找杰夏尔。我想和他做笔买卖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll have to let him know it's you and your friend who's asking though. You understand.</Source>
      <Dest>我会让他知道这是你和你朋友的要求。你懂的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My friends and I just stopped by to say hello to J'Sharr.</Source>
      <Dest>我和朋友们只是顺路跟杰夏尔打个招呼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Just a friendly stroll through the pits, is it? Ah, well, you won't find him here. Your companion didn't give him much reason to stay.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 大老远跑到斗兽场来散个步吗？啊，好吧，不过估计你在这儿是找不到他的。你的伙伴可是会撵跑他的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My friends and I just stopped by to say hello to J'Sharr.</Source>
      <Dest>我和朋友们只是顺路跟杰夏尔打个招呼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As to where he's run off to, I haven't the slightest idea. But he's probably too busy stepping on his own tail to have made it very far.</Source>
      <Dest>As to where he's run off to, I haven't the slightest idea. But he's probably too busy stepping on his own tail to have made it very far.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you know where J'Sharr might have run off to?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道洁莎可能逃哪儿去了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah yes, the cat. Everyone wants to know where the cat is. But not everybody is willing to pay the toll.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，那只猫。每个人都想知道那只猫到底在哪儿。但并不是每个人都愿意支付这消息的代价。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you know where J'Sharr might have run off to?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道洁莎可能逃哪儿去了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, as much as I despise the cat, I ain't the sort to go squealing on a  pit mate.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，正如我鄙视那只猫一样，我不是那种会在矿坑里大喊大叫的伙伴儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you know where J'Sharr might have run off to?</Source>
      <Dest>你知道洁莎可能逃哪儿去了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At least, not for anything less than a 1000 gold. You're better off asking the Lady. She'll give you a fair deal.</Source>
      <Dest>至少，不少于1000金币吧。你最好问问那位女士，她开出的价码会很公平的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Honestly, I'm pretty much a coward and I'll be lucky to survive this.</Source>
      <Dest>坦白讲，我基本上就是个懦夫，能活过这关算我命大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) In that case, I hope you don't mind if I put a large wager on your opponent.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 既然如此，我希望你别介意我在你的对手身上下个大注。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Honestly, I'm pretty much a coward and I'll be lucky to survive this.</Source>
      <Dest>坦白讲，我基本上就是个懦夫，能活过这关算我命大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, if you told the Fair Lady what you just told me, I probably won't get very good odds.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，如果你把刚对我说过的话也告诉了窈窕淑女，我估计没有多大胜算。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not just good. I'm the best.</Source>
      <Dest>我不只是好，而是最好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You took the words right out of everyone's mouth. Because pretty much everyone thinks they're the best.</Source>
      <Dest>You took the words right out of everyone's mouth. Because pretty much everyone thinks they're the best.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not just good. I'm the best.</Source>
      <Dest>我不只是好，而是最好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right up until the point it's their blood that's splattered on the wall.</Source>
      <Dest>等到他们的血飞溅三尺了他们就不会那样说了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not very good, but I am quite slippery.</Source>
      <Dest>我不是非常优秀，但我很油滑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then the two of you together will be like mudcrabs in the rain. And I mean that as a compliment.</Source>
      <Dest>你们两个在一起真是如泥沼蟹得雨。呃，我这么说是恭维的意思啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You obviously don't know me very well.</Source>
      <Dest>你显然非常不了解我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know you at all. But I've been watching him, and that Khajiit is what my friends in Elsweyr call a housecat.</Source>
      <Dest>我根本不认识你。但我一直看着他，那虎人是我的朋友们在艾斯维尔叫做家猫的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you're the poor sod they paired up with J'Sharr, huh. I almost feel sorry for you.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你肯定是那个和杰夏尔一块儿来的杂碎。哼，我差不多为你感到伤感了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That cat's got nine lives, and he's going to need them all in the pit.</Source>
      <Dest>那只猫有九条命，可到了这儿他恐怕全都得用掉啦！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, if you're the kind of cat who only has one, you better be damn good or damn slippery if you want to survive.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，如果你是那种落单的猫咪，你最好在优秀或狡猾里占一样儿，如果你想活下去的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you're the poor sod they paired up with J'Sharr, huh. I almost feel sorry for you.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你肯定是那个和杰夏尔一块儿来的杂碎。哼，我差不多为你感到伤感了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That cat's got nine lives, and he's going to need them all in the pit.</Source>
      <Dest>那只猫有九条命，可到了这儿他恐怕全都得用掉啦！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, seeing as you only got one, you better be damn good or damn slippery if you want to survive.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，看来你已经收了他一条命了，如果你想要活下来你最好他妈的圆滑聪明着点儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not bad. Now I see why J'Sharr chose you to be his partner. Too bad that information cost most of us a small fortune.</Source>
      <Dest>不错。现在我知道为什么杰夏尔选你做他的合作伙伴了。只可惜为了明白这一点，耗掉的可是我们的运气啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Didn't expect to see you two back here. Or is it three now?</Source>
      <Dest>Didn't expect to see you two back here. Or is it three now?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you a pit fighter or one of the guards?</Source>
      <Dest>你是一个斗士还是一名守卫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A fighter like you, although I've been known to do some recruiting, if the price is right.</Source>
      <Dest>我是个和你一样的战士，并且如果价钱合适的话，我还会变身成为一个小有名气的雇佣兵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you a pit fighter or one of the guards?</Source>
      <Dest>你是一个斗士还是一名守卫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>See, in every arena you got your wolves, and you got your dogs. The wolves are like your Redguard friend. They draw the crowd.</Source>
      <Dest>瞧，每一个竞技场里你都能遇见狼，也能遇见狗。说狼就是像你们红卫人，成帮结伙地上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you a pit fighter or one of the guards?</Source>
      <Dest>你是一个斗士还是一名守卫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now the dogs, they're different. They don't have the sharpest fangs, or the thickest hides, but they make up for it with grit.</Source>
      <Dest>这些狗，它们是不同的。它们没有尖锐的牙齿，也没有厚实的皮毛，但它们用勇气弥补了这些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you a pit fighter or one of the guards?</Source>
      <Dest>你是一个斗士还是一名守卫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When a wolf takes a bite off you, it rips off a chunk of your flesh. When a dog sinks its teeth into you, it never lets go. </Source>
      <Dest>当狼一口咬住你，它会扯下你的一块儿肉。而当狗咬住你的时候，它就再也不松口。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you a pit fighter or one of the guards?</Source>
      <Dest>你是一个斗士还是一名守卫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In the pit, that's what makes for a good show. And I got a keen eye for dogs.</Source>
      <Dest>在斗兽场里，那会让表演更为精彩。我爱死那些斗犬啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you considered J'Sharr is putting on an act to swing the odds?</Source>
      <Dest>你确定杰夏尔做了什么操纵胜率的事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure. It crossed my mind. But you haven't seen him fight. I'd say half the blood in that cage is his.</Source>
      <Dest>Sure. It crossed my mind. But you haven't seen him fight. I'd say half the blood in that cage is his.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you considered J'Sharr is putting on an act to swing the odds?</Source>
      <Dest>你确定杰夏尔做了什么操纵胜率的事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, that's how he managed to survive. There was so much blood on the ground the Nord he was fighting slipped, fell, and broke his back.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，这就是他如何设法活下来的。这个诺德人在战斗时不慎跌倒，摔伤了后背，血流了一地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you considered J'Sharr is putting on an act to swing the odds?</Source>
      <Dest>你确定杰夏尔做了什么操纵胜率的事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, he may try and get and edge, but as the lady says, in the cage, "Fair's fair."</Source>
      <Dest>不，没准他会竭尽全力在地上爬行呢，不过正如那位女士所言，身陷囹圄，“要一碗水端平啊”。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a shame. As a vampire, I could use more thralls.</Source>
      <Dest>真丢脸. 作为一个吸血鬼, 我可以支配更多奴隶.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't think J'Sharr's the type who takes his partner's opinions into account. Don't think he won't hesitate to use you as a shield either.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认为杰夏尔是会听他伙伴劝的那种类型。别以为他就不会拿你来当挡箭牌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a shame. As a vampire, I could use more thralls.</Source>
      <Dest>真丢脸. 作为一个吸血鬼, 我可以支配更多奴隶.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But, on the other hand, maybe you're more useful to him alive. The cat's got connections. Knows all the right people to snuff out all the bad fires.</Source>
      <Dest>但是，这样看来，让他活着说不定对你更有利。那只猫已经接上头了。他可是对那些扑灭了那严重火灾的关键人物们知道得一清二楚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a shame. As a vampire, I could use more thralls.</Source>
      <Dest>真丢脸. 作为一个吸血鬼, 我可以支配更多奴隶.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, there was an Argonian here the day before the bloodsuckers vanished. Stuck out like a glowing mushroom. J'Sharr's work, no doubt.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，在那帮吸血虫消失之前这儿曾有一只亚龙人，像只蓬勃生长的蘑菇似的杵在这儿。毫无疑问就是杰夏尔干的嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a shame. Vampire hunting is a favorite pastime of mine.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一个耻辱。狩猎吸血鬼是我最喜欢的消遣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't think J'Sharr's the type who takes his partner's opinions into account. Don't think he won't hesitate to use you as a shield either.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认为杰夏尔是会听他伙伴劝的那种类型。别以为他就不会拿你来当挡箭牌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a shame. Vampire hunting is a favorite pastime of mine.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一个耻辱。狩猎吸血鬼是我最喜欢的消遣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But, on the other hand, maybe you're more useful to him alive. The cat's got connections. Knows all the right people to snuff out all the bad fires.</Source>
      <Dest>但是，这样看来，让他活着说不定对你更有利。那只猫已经接上头了。他可是对那些扑灭了那严重火灾的关键人物们知道得一清二楚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a shame. Vampire hunting is a favorite pastime of mine.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一个耻辱。狩猎吸血鬼是我最喜欢的消遣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, there was an Argonian here the day before the bloodsuckers vanished. Stuck out like a glowing mushroom. J'Sharr's work, no doubt.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，在那帮吸血虫消失之前这儿曾有一只亚龙人，像只蓬勃生长的蘑菇似的杵在这儿。毫无疑问就是杰夏尔干的嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would vampires be a tactical disadvantage?</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼战斗力不行吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know, you'd have to ask him. Could be the chance of infection was high, and this ain't the type of place to find a potion or a priest.</Source>
      <Dest>I don't know, you'd have to ask him. Could be the chance of infection was high, and this ain't the type of place to find a potion or a priest.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would vampires be a tactical disadvantage?</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼战斗力不行吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The point is, he wanted things changed, so he changed them. Must have had something to do with that Argonian that was here the other day.</Source>
      <Dest>重点是，他想要什么就动手去做。在那时，肯定有什么事儿必须得对那只曾在这儿的蜥蜴做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would vampires be a tactical disadvantage?</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼战斗力不行吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This one was as stiff as a poker and clearly out of his element. We would've made him for a Jarl's man if he weren't a bloody lizard.</Source>
      <Dest>那个家伙就像拨火棍一样僵硬并且连手和脚都不知道该往哪放。如果他不是一只血淋淋的蜥蜴的话我们早就让他去为领主服务了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would vampires be a tactical disadvantage?</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼战斗力不行吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But as soon as he vanished, so did our bloodsucking friends. Not a coincidence if you ask me.</Source>
      <Dest>但是他一消失，我们的吸血朋友也跟着一起没了。依我说这不是什么巧合。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>J'Sharr is a fool then. The blood on the wall would probably distract them.</Source>
      <Dest>洁莎是个白痴，墙上的血或许可以转移他们的注意力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or drive them into a frenzy. Are you willing to risk that chance? J'Sharr wasn't.</Source>
      <Dest>或者使他们陷入疯狂。如果是你的话你会冒一下险吗？杰夏尔就不会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>J'Sharr is a fool then. The blood on the wall would probably distract them.</Source>
      <Dest>洁莎是个白痴，墙上的血或许可以转移他们的注意力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The rumor is the cat's got connections. Knows all the right people to snuff out all the bad fires.</Source>
      <Dest>The rumor is the cat's got connections. Knows all the right people to snuff out all the bad fires.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>J'Sharr is a fool then. The blood on the wall would probably distract them.</Source>
      <Dest>洁莎是个白痴，墙上的血或许可以转移他们的注意力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, there was an Argonian here the day before the bloodsuckers vanished. Stuck out like a glowing mushroom. J'Sharr's work, no doubt.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，在那帮吸血虫消失之前这儿曾有一只亚龙人，像只蓬勃生长的蘑菇似的杵在这儿。毫无疑问就是杰夏尔干的嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't seem as if you respect J'Sharr as a fighter.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来你没把杰夏尔当成一个战士来尊敬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nobody does, least of all him. I'm guessing that's why he worked so hard to get his opponent replaced.</Source>
      <Dest>没人会，尤其是他。我猜这就是为什么他努力工作来取代竞争对手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't seem as if you respect J'Sharr as a fighter.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来你没把杰夏尔当成一个战士来尊敬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Fair Lady will tell you they lost their backbone, but what she won't tell you is how.</Source>
      <Dest>窈窕淑女会告诉你他们失去了自己的决心和毅力，但是她不会告诉你原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't seem as if you respect J'Sharr as a fighter.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来你没把杰夏尔当成一个战士来尊敬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You see, when we found out the fight was going to be here, I overheard J'Sharr muttering to himself about the blood on the walls of the cage.</Source>
      <Dest>You see, when we found out the fight was going to be here, I overheard J'Sharr muttering to himself about the blood on the walls of the cage.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't seem as if you respect J'Sharr as a fighter.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来你没把杰夏尔当成一个战士来尊敬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I paid the Fair Lady for some information, and it turns out your previous cage partners were vampires.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我告诉了窈窕淑女一些信息，这些都可以证明你以前笼子里的那位伙伴是吸血鬼。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
