<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What spell was that?  I don't feel any different.</Source>
      <Dest>那是什么咒语？我没看出来有什么不同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I feel invigorated.  Brave.  Like a soldier once more.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得精神焕发。勇敢无畏。就好像再一次上了战场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you're a healer as well.  Excellent.   Some priests would feel otherwise, but this is not a competition.  I welcome your aid.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说你也是个治疗者，太好了。有的祭司可能好强争胜，但是我知道现在可不是竞赛的时候。感谢你的援助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My wounds are closing.  I thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>我的伤口正在愈合。很感谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's no reason for us to continue fighting.</Source>
      <Dest>我们已经没有继续战斗的理由了吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of all the schools of magic, Alteration is by far the most imaginative. But I'd rather you not turn me invisible.</Source>
      <Dest>目前为止，变化系是所有魔法派系中最令人叹为观止的一种。不过我还是希望你别把我变成隐形的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So the light moves from room to room by reflecting off these mirrors. We just have to point them the right way.</Source>
      <Dest>所以说那光随着那些镜子的反射而在房间与房间之间移动。我们只需要以正确的方式将它们给找出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Enchanted or not, the same rules apply. Ranged attacks and using the narrow doorways are critical against an opponent this size. </Source>
      <Dest>附魔或不附魔，规则同样适用。范围攻击和利用好这狭窄的门廊是对抗敌人的关键。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vampires. It's not a surprise this dog and its master are worshipped by such vile creatures.</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼。也难怪这只狗与它的主人会被这样的邪恶生物顶礼膜拜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So that's why the Greybeards taught you Whirlwind Sprint.  It was essentially a key to those gates behind us.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这就是灰胡子教你旋风精力的原因。它毫无疑问就是打开我们身后那些大门的钥匙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A Glenmoril witch. We only need one head, but I would advise that we eliminate the coven.  Mercy does not apply to abominations.</Source>
      <Dest>一个格仑摩里女巫。我们只需要一个人头，但我建议我们把来聚会的女巫全给结果掉。邪恶之物可配不上怜悯这个词。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This cave is blessed by the Shadow. It must be popular with smugglers and traffickers.  Mortals who have no idea how many lives they ruin.</Source>
      <Dest>这个洞穴受到阴影的庇护。这儿肯定特受走私贩子的欢迎。凡人们对他们糟蹋掉的生命一无所知。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These blades are old but sharp. The one who goes first should pull the chain so the other can follow.  I will heal our wounds if necessary.</Source>
      <Dest>这些刀片虽旧但还锋利。总得先有人牺牲一下去关上机关，后人才能前行吧。必要的时候我会为你疗伤的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>From the looks of this deer, I'd say it was felled by a blade, not by beasts.</Source>
      <Dest>从这只鹿的尸体来看，我打赌它是被人用利刃杀死的，而不是被野兽咬死的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vampires usually have their thralls stand guard.  They are fairly weak, but we should be cautious.</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼一般让他们的家畜站岗。他们比较弱，但我们还是得小心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Castle undercrofts are often used for storage.  These conjurers use it to store the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>城堡地窖通常是用来贮藏的。这些巫师用它来存放尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Up here, you get a sense of how big the world is. As high as we are, we're still far beneath the Throat of the World. And it's far beneath the stars.</Source>
      <Dest>在这里，你能感受到天地的广阔。无论我们站得多高，抬头望去，在我们之上总还是有着那世界之喉以及漫天繁星的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Souls of Aetherius!  This must be where the horn is kept.  Somewhere over by the altar.  Maybe...behind it or something.</Source>
      <Dest>这些都是艾瑟瑞斯的灵魂！一定有什么东西把它们给召唤进来了，那玩意说不定就在祭坛旁边。或者……是在祭坛背后或是别的什么地方？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Amazing. Those gears must have been spinning for thousands of years, and they will continue to spin for thousands more.</Source>
      <Dest>真令人惊讶。这些齿轮准是运转了数千年了，并且它们还将继续运行下去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the Shadow...Nightingale Hall.</Source>
      <Dest>阴影女士在上……这是夜莺大厅！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Calcelmo's stubbornness may put these guards' lives in danger.  We would do well to avoid any conflict.</Source>
      <Dest>卡赛默的固执也许会害那些守卫丢了性命的。我们最好是尽量避免起冲突。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By Aetherius...this machine can trap starlight? I know not whether to praise the Dwemer for their ingenuity, or condemn them for their blasphemy.</Source>
      <Dest>By Aetherius...this machine can trap starlight? I know not whether to praise the Dwemer for their ingenuity, or condemn them for their blasphemy.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say the breath of the Volkihar tribe could freeze the blood in your veins.  This place is cold and these vampires strong, but we should be safe.</Source>
      <Dest>人们都说瓦奇哈氏族之息可以让你血管中的血液都结成冰。这地方很冷，那些吸血鬼很强大，但我们会平安无事的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The ancient Nords must have built cathedrals like this in reverence of the sky, whose watchful eye brings light to this cavern.</Source>
      <Dest>先古的诺德人一定是满怀着对天空的敬意才修筑了这样的圣堂，那一先见之明给这个洞穴带来了光明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That must be where Mikrul lies.  According to Valen's notes, he fought for 3 days and 3 nights.  Be prepared for a long battle.</Source>
      <Dest>米拉克一定就在那儿。根据瓦伦的笔记，他打了三天三夜，一看就是对长期作战早有准备。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A thousand drops become one.  The White River pours life into this cavern, and from this natural wonder, the Spriggans have made a home, and a lure.</Source>
      <Dest>自然之力，巧夺天工。白河为这洞穴注入了生命，而树精则在这个自然奇观中建造了居住地，也设置了诱饵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Calcelmo did an amazing job reassembling these devices. Books are fine, but for children it's the sculptures that will capture their sense of wonder.</Source>
      <Dest>卡塞默居然把这些装置重新组装起来了。书是个好东西，但是对于孩子们来说，能吸引他们的注意的可能还是雕刻吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By Aetherius, a Dragon Wall.  Look at that script.  It's as if it were carved into the rock by a dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>艾瑟瑞斯在上，居然是一座龙墙。看看那些字迹。它仿佛是被一条龙雕刻在岩石上的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wonderful. I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。我会在那儿与你见面的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Heljarchen Hall.</Source>
      <Dest>勇士堑山庄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wonderful. I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。我会在那儿与你见面的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Windstad Manor.</Source>
      <Dest>文斯塔德庄园</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wonderful. I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。我会在那儿与你见面的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lakeview Manor.</Source>
      <Dest>湖景林居。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Let's live in my house in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>让我们住在我在独孤城的房子里吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wonderful.  I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>太棒了。我们不见不散。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How about my house in Windhelm?</Source>
      <Dest>我在风盔城的房子怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wonderful. I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。我会在那儿与你见面的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My house in Markarth would be perfect.</Source>
      <Dest>我在马卡斯城的房子将会很完美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wonderful.  I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>太棒了。我们不见不散。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wonderful. I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。我会在那儿与你见面的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have a house in Riften.</Source>
      <Dest>我在裂谷城有栋房子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>We could live in my house in Whiterun.</Source>
      <Dest>我们可以住在我在雪漫城的房子里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wonderful.  I'll meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>太棒了。我们不见不散。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>RelationshipMarriagePostWeddingLoveInterestBlockingTopic</Source>
      <Dest>RelationshipMarriagePostWeddingLoveInterestBlockingTopic</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My love, as a wanderer, I have no home.  But if you would like me to settle down somewhere, I am willing.</Source>
      <Dest>我的宝贝，作为一个浪迹天涯的旅人，我没有家。但是，如果你想让我找个地方安顿下来，我也愿意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Has the store made any money?</Source>
      <Dest>商店有赚钱吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I tend to keep prices low, but I've found that helps both the customer and our profits.  Here is your share.</Source>
      <Dest>我试着低价出售，然后我发现对我们和顾客来说是双赢。这是属于你的分红。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Has the store made any money?</Source>
      <Dest>商店有赚钱吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here's your share.</Source>
      <Dest>这是你的那份。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright. I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Heljarchen Hall.</Source>
      <Dest>勇士堑山庄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright. I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Windstad Manor.</Source>
      <Dest>文斯塔德庄园</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright. I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lakeview Manor.</Source>
      <Dest>湖景林居。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'd like us to move somewhere else.</Source>
      <Dest>我想我们得移动到别的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gladly.  Where should we move to?</Source>
      <Dest>非常乐意。我们应该搬到哪里去?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Proudspire Manor, my house in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>傲矛别墅，我在独孤城的家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hjerim, my house in Windhelm.</Source>
      <Dest>霜宅，我在风盔城的房子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright. I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Vlindrel Hall, my house in Markarth.</Source>
      <Dest>林德尔会堂，我在马卡斯城的房子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Honeyside, my house in Riften.</Source>
      <Dest>甜蜜湾，我在裂谷城的房子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright. I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Breezehome, my house in Whiterun.</Source>
      <Dest>风宅，我在雪漫城的房子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your old place would suit us just fine.</Source>
      <Dest>你的老地方会很适合我们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I'll get everything packed and meet you there.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我会打包所有行李跟你在那边见面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would you mind cooking something for me?</Source>
      <Dest>你介意帮我煮点吃的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course.  This meal should help restore your strength.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了。这顿饭应该能帮你恢复体力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Would you mind cooking something for me?</Source>
      <Dest>你介意帮我煮点吃的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I apologize my love, I don't have one prepared yet.  </Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉，亲爱的，我还没准备好。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye, my love.</Source>
      <Dest>再见，我的宝贝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell, my dear.</Source>
      <Dest>再见了，亲爱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think it's a good idea for us to get involved.</Source>
      <Dest>我不认为我们的参与是一个好主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I understand.  It is foolish for a man to think the stars would bless him twice in one lifetime.</Source>
      <Dest>我懂。只有蠢货才会相信星辰在庇佑过他一次之后，还会光顾第二次。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interested in me, are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你对我有兴趣，没错吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hope I'm not being too forward, but are you interested in me?</Source>
      <Dest>希望我进度不会太快，但是你对我没有兴趣吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was not sure, given my past, it would be something I desired.  But now, after being with you, and knowing you, I feel as if I'm ready.</Source>
      <Dest>我不确定，若是以前的我，那这或许就是我所想要的了。但现如今有你陪伴身旁，与你交心之后，我觉得我似乎已经准备好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interested in me, are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你对我有兴趣，没错吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have always been a bit of a romantic, and that is where I am conflicted.  Part of me believes that true love comes once in a lifetime.</Source>
      <Dest>我一向是个浪漫主义者，这也是我矛盾的地方。一方面我相信真爱一生只有一次。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on remarrying?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么看待再婚的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interested in me, are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你对我有兴趣，没错吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on remarrying?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么看待再婚的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is another part of me, however, that believes love is more than childish fancy. That real love is built over time, and time spent together.</Source>
      <Dest>在我内心深处，一定还有一部分仍然相信着，相爱并不是如童话中那样一见钟情。唯有时间，唯有漫长的时间才能铸就真爱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interested in me, are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你对我有兴趣，没错吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on remarrying?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么看待再婚的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lenora was my first love, and in truth, it was a love that had yet to reach full bloom.</Source>
      <Dest>莱诺拉是我的初恋。然而实际上，这份爱从来就没能结出过果实。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We were married so quickly as it was the Nord's way, and as a young and compulsive man, I was in no mood to dissent.</Source>
      <Dest>我们是像诺德人一样玩了个闪婚，我这样急躁的年轻人可没什么心情多费口舌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interested in me, are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你对我有兴趣，没错吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think that is?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会那样想？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interested in me, are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你对我有兴趣，没错吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think that is?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会那样想？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes I wonder if it is the manner which we parted that is the cause of my attachment, and not the time we spent before.</Source>
      <Dest>有时候我会怀疑是不是我们这种分手的方式而不是我们之前度过的时光影响了我的情感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interested in me, are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你对我有兴趣，没错吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But when I try to recall those memories, those days when we were happy, it all seems to blend together like a forgotten dream.</Source>
      <Dest>但当我试图去回想时，那些我们一起开心过的日子，那过往的种种都混杂在了一起，就像一个醒来时就会被遗忘的梦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think that is?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会那样想？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Interested in me, are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你对我有兴趣，没错吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wear an Amulet of Mara.  I'm sure you've noticed.  Everyone does.</Source>
      <Dest>我戴着个玛拉护身符呢，你肯定注意到了，人人看得到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Marriage is an important institution.  See that you choose wisely, and remain faithful to your heart.</Source>
      <Dest>Marriage is an important institution.  See that you choose wisely, and remain faithful to your heart.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I love you.  I think we should get married.</Source>
      <Dest>我爱你。我想我们应该要结婚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I love you as well.  Then it's settled.  We should meet in the chapel of Riften.</Source>
      <Dest>我也爱你。那么就这么定了。我们就在裂谷城的教堂相见吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Amulet of Mara.  You seek marriage then.  It is a noble endeavor.</Source>
      <Dest>是玛拉护符。这么说你在找人结婚呢。这种努力可是很崇高的哟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I found this, I thought of you.  An odd gift to be sure, coming from me, but take it as a token of my gratitude.</Source>
      <Dest>When I found this, I thought of you.  An odd gift to be sure, coming from me, but take it as a token of my gratitude.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>哈啰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Keep your hands up!</Source>
      <Dest>不要把双手放下！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've uncovered some information that may be of some use.</Source>
      <Dest>我发现了一些有用的信息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you should relay that to Karras, my love. With the Thane gone, it would be best to defer to him.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的，那你最好把它交给卡拉斯。既然男爵不在，那交给他是最好的选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you should relay that to Karras, Dragonborn. With the Thane gone, it would be best to defer to him.</Source>
      <Dest>Then you should relay that to Karras, Dragonborn. With the Thane gone, it would be best to defer to him.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've uncovered some information that may be of some use.</Source>
      <Dest>我发现了一些有用的信息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry. I imagine the two of you grew close while traveling together.</Source>
      <Dest>对不起，我还以为你俩在旅行途中变得更亲近了呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We didn't have much in common. Much like the Steed, he was impatient, but he was also straightforward, and I respected that.</Source>
      <Dest>我们没有很多共同语言。他没什么耐性，跟烈马一样，不过他也很直爽，我佩服这点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry. I imagine the two of you grew close while traveling together.</Source>
      <Dest>对不起，我还以为你俩在旅行途中变得更亲近了呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I just pray the stars guide him to safety, in this life or the next one.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是祈祷星辰可以保佑他的安全，永生永世。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If they wanted him dead, they would have left the body there as a message.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他们想要他死，那他们应该把他的尸体留在那里作为信息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not exactly. They might want discover what he knows. At which point, death might have been the merciful end.</Source>
      <Dest>不尽然。他们或许是想了解他究竟知道些什么。从这个角度上来看，死亡对他来说可能是一种仁慈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If they wanted him dead, they would have left the body there as a message.</Source>
      <Dest>如果他们想要他死，那他们应该把他的尸体留在那里作为信息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May the stars watch over him and give him strength.</Source>
      <Dest>愿星光守望着他，并赐予他力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>He's probably dead. You can mourn him after this is over.</Source>
      <Dest>他可能已经死了。在此结束後你可以悼念他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mourn him now. Even if he's alive, a piece of him will die in those shackles. May the stars watch over him and give him strength.</Source>
      <Dest>我现在为他而悼念。即使他还活着，他也永远无法完全挣脱那些束缚。愿星辰庇佑着他，给予他力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So let's hear it. Try to exaggerate their numbers to make it more believable.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我们听听看。试着把他们的数量鼓吹到更可信的水平。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To be honest, there weren't more than half a dozen. They didn't need numbers. Just the element of surprise.</Source>
      <Dest>老实说，并没有超过半打之数。他们并不需要过分夸大的数字。只是想来点刺激的剧情罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So let's hear it. Try to exaggerate their numbers to make it more believable.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我们听听看。试着把他们的数量鼓吹到更可信的水平。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was dangerous gambit. They cut themselves on purpose, knowing I would check their wounds.</Source>
      <Dest>这是危险的赌博。他们故意割伤自己，是因为知道我会去检查他们的伤口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So let's hear it. Try to exaggerate their numbers to make it more believable.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我们听听看。试着把他们的数量鼓吹到更可信的水平。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The amount of discipline required...these men were well trained. I had just finished healing the last of them when the mace hit my skull.</Source>
      <Dest>这么多的规则……这些人一定都经过严格训练。我刚把最后一个人治好就被一钉锤敲晕了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I lost consciousness, but by the Atronach's blessing, I managed to survive. Unfortunately, when I awoke, both the Thane and the soldiers were gone.</Source>
      <Dest>I lost consciousness, but by the Atronach's blessing, I managed to survive. Unfortunately, when I awoke, both the Thane and the soldiers were gone.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So let's hear it. Try to exaggerate their numbers to make it more believable.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我们听听看。试着把他们的数量鼓吹到更可信的水平。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They were posing as wounded soldiers. No, not posing. They were wounded. Such was their discipline and commitment to their trap.</Source>
      <Dest>他们冒充受伤的士兵。不，不是冒充。他们确实受伤了。这就是他们为这个圈套而做出的牺牲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what happened. How did you get ambushed?</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我发生了什么，你是怎么中的埋伏？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As soldiers, it wasn't unusual for them to be carrying weapons. One of them knocked me over the head just as I was healing the last of them.</Source>
      <Dest>就像那些士兵，对他们来说随身带着武器是很平常的事儿。他们中的一个在我治疗完他们最后一个伤员的时候在我身后敲了我的脑袋。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what happened. How did you get ambushed?</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我发生了什么，你是怎么中的埋伏？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I lost consciousness, but by the Atronach's blessing, I managed to survive. Unfortunately, when I awoke, both the Thane and the soldiers were gone.</Source>
      <Dest>I lost consciousness, but by the Atronach's blessing, I managed to survive. Unfortunately, when I awoke, both the Thane and the soldiers were gone.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me what happened. How did you get ambushed?</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我发生了什么，你是怎么中的埋伏？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And yet somehow you managed to survive. Falathil's right. This is suspicious.</Source>
      <Dest>不管怎么样，你撑过来了。 菲拉罗是对的。这里有问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If this were my doing, the last place I would be is here.</Source>
      <Dest>如果这是我所为，那我根本不可能来这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My love, I'm sure you did everything you could.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的，我确信你已经尽力了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know my dear. As I tried to tell Falatild, in life, there's so many things we deserve blame for.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道，亲爱的。就像我试着告诉菲菈缇儿的那样, 别将一切不顺利归咎于自己，有时这就是天命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It makes little sense to take responsibility for the things we are not.</Source>
      <Dest>为那些我们未曾做过的事情而承担责任是毫无意义的。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My love, I'm sure you did everything you could.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的，我确信你已经尽力了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know. As I tried to tell Falatild, in life, there's so many things we deserve blame for.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道。就像我试着告诉菲菈缇儿的那样, 别将一切不顺利归咎于自己，有时这就是天命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's alright. I'm sure you did everything you could.</Source>
      <Dest>没事没事，我十分确定你已经尽力而为了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It makes little sense to take responsibility for the things we are not.</Source>
      <Dest>为那些我们未曾做过的事情而承担责任是毫无意义的。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's alright. I'm sure you did everything you could.</Source>
      <Dest>没事没事，我十分确定你已经尽力而为了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Hooded men in red cuirasses, I'm guessing.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜，那些穿着红色胸甲的蒙面人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, likely the same group that attacked you at Riverwood. The Blood of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>对，在河木镇袭击你的可能是同一拨人，天际之血。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, the important thing is you survived. I never liked the other guy.</Source>
      <Dest>重要的是你活下来了。我一直都不喜欢另一个家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This isn't the time for levity. Not when the Thane meant so much to the people in this room.</Source>
      <Dest>如果对于这个房间里的大家来说这位领主如此地重要，那就不能如此轻率地下结论了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So the letter arrived...just not in time. We were ambushed.</Source>
      <Dest>这封信确实送到了...只是来得太迟了。我们中了埋伏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes...that was surprising. Still, it doesn't change anything. The ritual is perilous, regardless of the person's age or constitution.</Source>
      <Dest>Yes...that was surprising. Still, it doesn't change anything. The ritual is perilous, regardless of the person's age or constitution.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I overheard your conversation with Falatild. Are you still going to help them?</Source>
      <Dest>我听到你和菲菈缇儿的对话。你还是要去帮助他们？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I overheard your conversation with Falatild. Are you still going to help them?</Source>
      <Dest>我听到你和菲菈缇儿的对话。你还是要去帮助他们？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't agree with the idea of risking anyone's life. Nor do I believe the Thane's claim to the throne is particularly strong.</Source>
      <Dest>我既不想用任何人的生命为代价去冒险，也不觉得男爵有足够资格获得王位。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I overheard your conversation with Falatild. Are you still going to help them?</Source>
      <Dest>我听到你和菲菈缇儿的对话。你还是要去帮助他们？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I cannot stand idly by and let him perish. If we find him, and he still wants to go through with it, I'll heal him.</Source>
      <Dest>但我不能眼睁睁地看着他走向毁灭而无动于衷。如果我们找到了他，而他依旧执迷不悟，那我会让他清醒过来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let's go. Hopefully someone at their camp will betray the Thane's whereabouts.</Source>
      <Dest>那走吧。但愿他们的营地里会有人会吐露出男爵的行踪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And if you die?</Source>
      <Dest>如果你死了呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She's right. Even with the most powerful of spells, I can only do so much.</Source>
      <Dest>她说的对。就算是用上最强大的法术，我能做到的也只有这样而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know. But I will say whatever secrets she kept, it pained her to do so.</Source>
      <Dest>I don't know. But I will say whatever secrets she kept, it pained her to do so.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm afraid those are questions for your housecarl.</Source>
      <Dest>恐怕那些问题就要留给你的侍卫去解决了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until we meet again, Swamp Knight.</Source>
      <Dest>下次再会，沼泽骑士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you leave me no choice but to heal you. But my involvement ends there.</Source>
      <Dest>你让我除了治愈你以外别无选择。不过别指望我能帮上更多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you're committed to seeing this through? I had hoped you'd reconsider.</Source>
      <Dest>你一定要那样？我本希望你能三思而行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't overdo it and go running through the forest. We need to maintain our strength. This camp seems like an ideal place to stop and rest.</Source>
      <Dest>别把太多的体力花在穿梭于整个森林之中。我们需要保存体力。这个营地看起来是个歇脚的好地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We ought to head back to Greenwood. Karras and the others will be waiting for us there.</Source>
      <Dest>我们应该往绿木那儿走。卡拉斯和其他人会在那里等我们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The mill of heart's wood is obvious enough. We should probably head there first anyway and see if the residents are safe.</Source>
      <Dest>木材无疑是整个磨坊的核心。我们或许应该先朝那儿走，然后看看居民们是否还安全。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hold on! The Thane is in no shape for a fight, and it would be unwise to split up now.</Source>
      <Dest>坚持住！ 领主已经无法战斗了，现在就离开并不是一个明智的选择.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's likely whoever he was, he's already gotten away.</Source>
      <Dest>就好像无论他是谁，都已经远去，再也不回来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It looks like the prisoners succumbed to the inevitable. I commit their souls to Aetherius...</Source>
      <Dest>看起来囚犯们屈服于他们的命运了。我希望他们的灵魂能去往爱瑟瑞斯……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look around. Even if you don't find anything on the war-teacher, you may be able to gather some more information on the ritual.</Source>
      <Dest>在四周找找，就算你找不到那个战争导师的任何线索，也还是能找到些关于那个仪式的信息。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will see if any of these wounded can be saved.</Source>
      <Dest>我倒要看看有多少伤员能活下来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank the Mage. Do you think you can walk?</Source>
      <Dest>感谢那个法师。你现在能走路了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you alright? Can you hear me?</Source>
      <Dest>你还好吗？能听见我讲话吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thane!</Source>
      <Dest>男爵！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes. There's no mistaking it. This must be the war-teacher's lair.</Source>
      <Dest>Yes. There's no mistaking it. This must be the war-teacher's lair.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If the traps are any indication, we must be getting close.</Source>
      <Dest>如果说陷阱能说明什么的话，我们一定已经靠得很近了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, here are the Draugr you were asking for.</Source>
      <Dest>来吧，这就是你要的那只尸鬼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This makes them no different than bandits. I doubt even Gren would approve of this behavior.</Source>
      <Dest>他们这样和强盗没区别。我觉得说不定连格伦都会赞同他们的行为。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Thief smiles upon us. Look, this entire section of rubble here has been cleared out recently.</Source>
      <Dest>那个小偷在向我们微笑。看，这地方的残砖碎瓦最近要被清理干净了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright. We don't have time to be going in circles, but we have even less time to argue. The catacombs it is.</Source>
      <Dest>Alright. We don't have time to be going in circles, but we have even less time to argue. The catacombs it is.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just curious. Is there a reason you think that's where they'll be?</Source>
      <Dest>Just curious. Is there a reason you think that's where they'll be?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) You're right. I should've realized the answer was so obvious.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 你说得对。我应该意识到答案是如此显而易见。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's clear he wants us to find him, but I'm not sure why.</Source>
      <Dest>很显然，他希望我们去找他，但是我不明白这是为什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Possibly the only one. But that isn't for us to decide. Nor should it be.</Source>
      <Dest>或许是唯一的一个。但这不是我们所要考虑的，我们也无需去考虑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He might be the High King.</Source>
      <Dest>他可能就是至高王。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're holding an important man. A former Thane of Whiterun.</Source>
      <Dest>他们手里握着一个重要人物——白漫城的前任城主。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What about a group of soldiers calling themselves the Blood of Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>那队士兵是怎么称呼自己的？天际之血？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We're looking for a Nord ruin in this area. Someplace where the stone bleeds wind.</Source>
      <Dest>我们正在寻找附近的一个诺德遗迹。某个风在山岩间呼啸的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This Frygg sounds interesting, but we should make sure we talk with everyone.</Source>
      <Dest>This Frygg sounds interesting, but we should make sure we talk with everyone.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Gren mentioned a war-teacher.</Source>
      <Dest>格伦提到了战争导师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If we find the Thane, you're going to need a healer. I'm the only thing that can stand between him and Aetherius.</Source>
      <Dest>要是我们找到那男爵，你就需要一个治疗师了。我是唯一的那个能拽住他不让他去往松加德的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hold on, I'm coming with you.</Source>
      <Dest>坚持住，我就来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You said it yourself. He could still be alive.</Source>
      <Dest>你自己说的。他可能还活着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But from that moment and every day after, his first thoughts were always of you.</Source>
      <Dest>但是从那一刻起的每一天，他首先想到的总是你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Keep him in your prayers. As Karras said, he still may be alive yet.</Source>
      <Dest>继续为他祈祷吧。 就像卡拉斯所说的那样，他可能还活着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He spoke about that day often. How he was lost in thought, ambling up that hillside.</Source>
      <Dest>他经常提到那天，他是如何漫步于山坡之上，迷失在沉思之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then we should do our best to find him.</Source>
      <Dest>我们应该尽力去找他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To be honest, I'm curious myself. Healing the child is my sole responsibility.</Source>
      <Dest>老实说，我也很想知道。治愈那个孩子是我仅有的责任。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So does this mean you're going to help?</Source>
      <Dest>你是想说你需要帮助吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Falatild...</Source>
      <Dest>菲菈缇儿...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't blame me. You blame yourself. I know, because I did the same. </Source>
      <Dest>你没有责怪我却责怪你自己。我懂，因为我也是这样。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry. I know you two were close. </Source>
      <Dest>我很遗憾。我知道你们俩曾走得很近。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't worry, you did just fine. Our appearance alone will make him think Larsdon has more value alive.</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，你干得不错。我们只要一露面就够让他知道留着劳斯登的活口比较划算啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In all likelihood this is a trap, but even so, it doesn't appear as if Gren is aware of it.</Source>
      <Dest>十有八九这是个陷阱，但即便如此，要是格伦意识到了这一点的话，一切就不会发生了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If at any point you want to stop, don't hesitate to ask.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你想停下来，只管跟我说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you know your destiny, but is it something you want? </Source>
      <Dest>你已经知道了自己的命运，那么它真的就是你想要的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Have you thought about what you'll say to Falatild when you return?</Source>
      <Dest>你有没有想过你回来的时候要跟菲菈缇儿说些什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your efforts are valiant. And brave.</Source>
      <Dest>你的努力很勇敢也很壮烈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you, my lady.  I do it not for the glory, but for the wounded, and their families.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你，夫人。我不是为了荣誉，而是为了伤员和他们的家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your efforts are valiant. And brave.</Source>
      <Dest>你的努力很勇敢也很壮烈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you, my boy.  I do it not for the glory, but for the wounded, and their families.</Source>
      <Dest>我很感激，孩子。我这么做并不是为了荣誉，而是为了那些伤员，还有他们的家人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes. She was in agony. It was the only way to relieve her of the pain. And I do not appreciate you mocking me for it.</Source>
      <Dest>对，她很痛苦。这是唯一能够减轻她痛苦的办法了。如果你因此而嘲笑我的话，也没什么关系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So it was you who killed your wife.  Nice work.</Source>
      <Dest>那么是你杀了你老婆。干得好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So it was you who killed your wife.  Nice work.</Source>
      <Dest>那么是你杀了你老婆。干得好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But it was good to tell the story nevertheless, and for that I thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>但你能告诉我这故事是胡诌的是很好的事，为此我得要感谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So it was you who killed your wife.  Nice work.</Source>
      <Dest>那么是你杀了你老婆。干得好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps there will come a time when I can laugh at myself as well, for anguishing this long when she resides in a better place.</Source>
      <Dest>也许在将来的某个时候，我可能会为了这段时光，这段她明明去了一个更好的地方，我却只感觉漫长而痛苦的时光，而嘲笑自己。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are the doomstones?</Source>
      <Dest>射箭目标是啥？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The doomstones are said to be built from the fragments of stars, much like the Ayleid stones of legend. </Source>
      <Dest>毁灭之石据说是用群星的碎片造成，很像传说中的亚历德石头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are the doomstones?</Source>
      <Dest>射箭目标是啥？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thus these stones, these wellsprings represent the very provenance of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>因此这些石头和这些水源，全都代表着魔法的起源。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are the doomstones?</Source>
      <Dest>射箭目标是啥？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is why those who practice the arcane are often drawn to these bridges, these pieces of heaven.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是为什么学习奥术的人们总是被吸引到这些桥这儿来，它们是散落自天堂的碎片。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are the doomstones?</Source>
      <Dest>射箭目标是啥？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But my apologies for prattling on, stranger, as I have not yet introduced myself.  My name is Valgus, a healer who follows the stars. </Source>
      <Dest>但我为这些无聊的话感到抱歉，陌生人。还没自我介绍，我的名字是威尔格斯，一名受星辰所指引的治疗师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What was that prayer?</Source>
      <Dest>祷告的内容是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just a few words for the souls in the sky that watch over Tamriel.  These stones are like a bridge that connects our world to theirs.</Source>
      <Dest>只是几句说给天空中守望着泰姆瑞尔大陆的灵魂听的话语。这些石头是连接我们这两个世界的桥梁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hope to continue my adventures and face new challenges.</Source>
      <Dest>我要继续我的旅程，面对新的挑战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I see.  Perhaps it is no coincidence that we met by the Steed Stone. They say those born under that sign are often impatient.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了。或许我们会在驮马之石遇见并不是偶然。人们都说在那种征兆下出生的人一般都是急性子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet some might say that is a virtue.  I myself pray to the Steed that I may be swift, so that the wounded will not suffer in my absence.</Source>
      <Dest>Yet some might say that is a virtue.  I myself pray to the Steed that I may be swift, so that the wounded will not suffer in my absence.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hope to continue my adventures and face new challenges.</Source>
      <Dest>我要继续我的旅程，面对新的挑战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thus, I am glad you are continuing your adventures.  The people you save are fortunate that you move without delay.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，我很高兴你会继续你的旅程。如果你即刻启程的话，就能挽救更多幸运儿的性命了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I hope to continue my adventures and face new challenges.</Source>
      <Dest>我要继续我的旅程，面对新的挑战。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I understand.  Another time, then.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了。那就，下次吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Not right now.</Source>
      <Dest>等会儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) You most certainly would.  Some would say it's better to look like a coward than a corpse, but not anyone who fights with a companion.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 你当然会那样啰。有些人说好死不如赖活着，但跟战友团一起并肩作战的可没有孬种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could always use "Whirlwind Sprint."  But you might look like a coward.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以随时使用 "旋风冲刺。"  虽然那会让你看起来像个懦夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Besides, I've never been in favor of running away from your problems.  They always seem to catch up in the end.</Source>
      <Dest>此外，我也从不赞成逃避麻烦。因为麻烦到最后总还是会追上来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could always use "Whirlwind Sprint."  But you might look like a coward.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以随时使用 "旋风冲刺。"  虽然那会让你看起来像个懦夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could always use "Whirlwind Sprint."  But you might look like a coward.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以随时使用 "旋风冲刺。"  虽然那会让你看起来像个懦夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It must sound self-serving, but in the end, I'd rather see the thu'um find a way to heal a man's skin, then abandon the fight to save your own.</Source>
      <Dest>当然这听上去有点自私，但是我想我更愿意看到龙吼助你冲开一条血路救下别人，然后让你全身而退救下自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Serving the Emperor isn't about serving a man.  It's about serving the people.  Dragon blood or mortal, Tamriel needs a strong leader.</Source>
      <Dest>孩子，服务于皇帝并非服务于个人。这关乎服务于人民。不论是身体里流淌着龙血的龙裔，亦或是个凡人，泰姆瑞尔大陆需要一个强硬的领导者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Blades were under no obligation to serve the false Emperor.</Source>
      <Dest>刀锋战士没有服侍假皇帝的义务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's not the Emperor, but the Empire who the Blades let down.  That's who they failed to protect.</Source>
      <Dest>不是皇帝，而是整个帝国被刀锋战士们辜负了。帝国才是他们没能保住的主人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Blades were under no obligation to serve the false Emperor.</Source>
      <Dest>刀锋战士没有服侍假皇帝的义务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm tired and not in the mood for romance.  Go cook me something.</Source>
      <Dest>我很累，现在没心情搞什么罗曼蒂克。做点东西给我吃吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Very well, my dear, forgive me for the romantic overture.  You must be tired from your ordeal.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 好的，亲爱的，原谅我那不由自主的浪漫情怀。你这一路旅途一定是累坏了吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm tired and not in the mood for romance.  Go cook me something.</Source>
      <Dest>我很累，现在没心情搞什么罗曼蒂克。做点东西给我吃吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I cannot cure your fatigue, I can cure your hunger.  If you wish to sleep, then I will be as still as The Shadow.  Just having you near is enough.</Source>
      <Dest>就算我不能舒解你的疲劳，我也能驱走你的饥饿。如果你想睡一会儿，那我就会如影子一般安静。有你在身边就已足够。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) I would make a very poor Dragonborn, seeing how I barely managed to make it this far.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)我当上龙裔也会是一个穷光蛋的，瞧瞧我费了多大力气才混到今天这地步。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who cares. When you're Dragonborn, you can heal people.  I destroy.</Source>
      <Dest>那谁管得着？反正你是济世救人的龙裔，我负责破坏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If only I knew a healing spell that could fix this insufferable back of mine.  Maybe I'm hoping there's a thu'um that does just that.</Source>
      <Dest>但愿有一种治愈术可以治疗我的背伤。也许我应该期望有一种吐目正好可以搞定它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who cares. When you're Dragonborn, you can heal people.  I destroy.</Source>
      <Dest>那谁管得着？反正你是济世救人的龙裔，我负责破坏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right. The Blades should have backed the Empire, regardless of blood.</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的。刀锋战士应该到底应该支持帝国，不管会有多少牺牲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, but I don't think you'll be able to convince Delphine of as much.  Tradition has a way of clouding one's judgment.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，不过我不觉得你能够说服戴尔芬。传统总是束缚着人们的判断力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just like Ulfric's unwillingness to sacrifice Talos worship, the Blades' devotion to the dragon kings is what brought their demise.</Source>
      <Dest>就如乌弗瑞克对于献身于塔洛斯信仰的不情不愿，刀锋战士对巨龙之王们的盲目崇拜也会把他们引向毁灭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right. The Blades should have backed the Empire, regardless of blood.</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的。刀锋战士应该到底应该支持帝国，不管会有多少牺牲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet if nothing else, it will keep her loyal to you. You give her purpose, and right now, it isn't as misguided as it was then.</Source>
      <Dest>如果没有别的什么，这会让她保持对你的忠诚。你引导着她，现在已不再是以前那会走错路的时候了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right. The Blades should have backed the Empire, regardless of blood.</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的。刀锋战士应该到底应该支持帝国，不管会有多少牺牲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I will stay, but first let me return something of yours.  3 words.  I love you.</Source>
      <Dest>那我就留下，不过先让我还你点儿东西：三个字：我，爱，你！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You need not return what you already own.  For those words are yours as well as mine, just as our souls are one.</Source>
      <Dest>你不需要回报你已经拥有的。这些话于你于我都一样，正如我们的灵魂一体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) You're straightforward, aren't you?  Ah, but to answer your question, I believe they do.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑) 你还真直接啊，是吧？啊，至于你的问题，我相信他们做得到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you honestly think your actions make one bit of difference?</Source>
      <Dest>你真心认为你的行为会让自己与众不同吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I can save but one life, is that not worth the effort?</Source>
      <Dest>要是我能拯救哪怕一条生命，这努力不也值得吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you honestly think your actions make one bit of difference?</Source>
      <Dest>你真心认为你的行为会让自己与众不同吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Worry not, for I know you have more important issues to deal with. I was simply struck by a spell of nostalgia.</Source>
      <Dest>（笑） 别担心，我知道你有更重要的事要操心。我只是受困于一种“被怀旧”的魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't come here for you, and we aren't stopping so you can read a book.</Source>
      <Dest>我才不是为你来的，我们也停不下来，所以你可以先去读本书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, if you would indulge this old dog's rambling for just a moment, I would like to share the tale of my first lesson.</Source>
      <Dest>可是，如果你乐意与我这条老狗聊上片刻，那么我想分享下我第一课的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I didn't come here for you, and we aren't stopping so you can read a book.</Source>
      <Dest>我才不是为你来的，我们也停不下来，所以你可以先去读本书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In times of war, you must realize there are only two ways to avoid such things.  Cowardice, or stealth.</Source>
      <Dest>在战争的年代，你必须懂得要避免这种事只有两条路可走：懦弱，或者隐匿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True wisdom is to avoid injuries and sickness, not heal them.</Source>
      <Dest>真正的智慧是去避免伤害和病痛，而不是治疗它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True wisdom is to avoid injuries and sickness, not heal them.</Source>
      <Dest>真正的智慧是去避免伤害和病痛，而不是治疗它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My wife was not a coward, and she was never one for the darkness.  Her light shone too brightly.</Source>
      <Dest>我的妻子不是个懦夫, 她永远不会追随黑暗而去。她的光芒是如此地耀眼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But don't feel sorry for me, my lady.  It happened over thirty years ago. More time has passed since her death than she spent among the living.</Source>
      <Dest>但不必为我愧疚，我的女士。30年前这已经发生了。她死的时间比活着时间还长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True wisdom is to avoid injuries and sickness, not heal them.</Source>
      <Dest>真正的智慧是去避免伤害和病痛，而不是治疗它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In times of war, you must realize there are only two ways to avoid such things.  Cowardice, or stealth.</Source>
      <Dest>在战争的年代，你必须懂得要避免这种事只有两条路可走：懦弱，或者隐匿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True wisdom is to avoid injuries and sickness, not heal them.</Source>
      <Dest>真正的智慧是去避免伤害和病痛，而不是治疗它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True wisdom is to avoid injuries and sickness, not heal them.</Source>
      <Dest>真正的智慧是去避免伤害和病痛，而不是治疗它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My wife was not a coward, and she was never one for the darkness.  Her light shone too brightly.</Source>
      <Dest>我的妻子不是个懦夫, 她永远不会追随黑暗而去。她的光芒是如此地耀眼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>True wisdom is to avoid injuries and sickness, not heal them.</Source>
      <Dest>真正的智慧是去避免伤害和病痛，而不是治疗它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But don't feel sorry for me, my boy. It happened over thirty years ago. More time has passed since her death than she spent among the living.</Source>
      <Dest>But don't feel sorry for me, my boy. It happened over thirty years ago. More time has passed since her death than she spent among the living.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is your opinion on the war?</Source>
      <Dest>谈谈你对这场战争的看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ulfric suffers from the same disease that afflicts all men of power.  Ambition.  Greed.  In the end, it drove him to murder.</Source>
      <Dest>乌弗瑞克染上的是所有权利上瘾者的通病。野心勃勃。贪得无厌。最终，他才会走上谋杀的道路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is your opinion on the war?</Source>
      <Dest>谈谈你对这场战争的看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not just of King Torygg, but the thousands of soldiers who fought in his name and died for his cause, as well as those who fought against it.</Source>
      <Dest>不只是至高王托依格，还有成千上万为他而战，因他而死的士兵，以及站在战争另一方的士兵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is your opinion on the war?</Source>
      <Dest>谈谈你对这场战争的看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hold him accountable, but those who fight under his banner are victims of his tyranny, fooled into taking arms for an ideal.</Source>
      <Dest>我会让他付出代价，但那些在因他之名而战斗的人，成为了他暴政的牺牲品，被一个虚伪的理想所欺骗而献出了生命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is your opinion on the war?</Source>
      <Dest>谈谈你对这场战争的看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As such, I seek to heal the wounded, regardless of what colors they wear.</Source>
      <Dest>所以，我只想办法医治伤者，至于他们属于哪个阵营，这不是我该关心的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's all the questions I have.</Source>
      <Dest>我的问题问完了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do not be afraid to ask if you have more.</Source>
      <Dest>Do not be afraid to ask if you have more.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>...and watch over us, souls of Aetherius, so that the bird may triumph over the serpent...</Source>
      <Dest>...庇佑我们吧，艾瑟瑞斯的灵魂们哟，这样即便是我们也能够打败强大的敌人...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>...and we may live in a world where champions can live as children once again.</Source>
      <Dest>...我们也许可以栖身于一个...战士能再度像孩子一样生活的世界里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, greetings, pilgrim. Do not let me stand in your way, as I did not come to the stone for its blessing or succor.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你好啊，朝圣者。别让我挡了你的道，因为我不是为了祝福或救助而到立石这儿来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I passed by these stones by chance, and prayed to the stars that my mind be swift and its burdens light.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是偶然路过这些石头，并向星星祈祷我能心智敏锐，举重若轻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Steed's blessing, however, will only grant those attributes to the body, and I carry only what you see before you.</Source>
      <Dest>但是，骏马之石的祝福只是让我的承重能力更强大了而已，而你也看到了，我所扛着的行李本来就不多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, greetings, fair lady.  Do not let me stand in your way, as I did not come to the stone for its blessing or its succor.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，向你致敬，美丽的女士。别让我挡了你的道，因为我不是为了祝福或救助而到立石这儿来的。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I passed by these stones by chance, and prayed to the stars that my mind be swift and its burdens light.</Source>
      <Dest>我只是偶然路过这些石头，并向星星祈祷我能心智敏锐，举重若轻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Steed's blessing, however, will only grant those attributes to the body, and I carry only what you see before you.</Source>
      <Dest>但是，骏马之石的祝福只是让我的承重能力更强大了而已，而你也看到了，我所扛着的行李本来就不多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My lady and my love, it is a beautiful home, one truly worthy of your magnificence. </Source>
      <Dest>我的夫人我的爱， 这个家真美，这美恰能与你的美相衬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you settled in to our new home?</Source>
      <Dest>你住进我们的新家了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you settled in to our new home?</Source>
      <Dest>你住进我们的新家了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I look forward to watching the shafts of light stream through the glass in the mornings, and bring out the color of your eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>I look forward to watching the shafts of light stream through the glass in the mornings, and bring out the color of your eyes.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you settled in to our new home?</Source>
      <Dest>你住进我们的新家了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I come from humble births, and have sought to carry myself with humility. A quiet home like this is perfect.</Source>
      <Dest>我出身卑微，为人低调，这样一个安静的家就已然完美了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you settled in to our new home?</Source>
      <Dest>你住进我们的新家了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is a wonderful home, if a bit dark, but I will work tirelessly to light it so that even the darkest corner were as bright a summer day.</Source>
      <Dest>这屋子真是棒极了，只不过稍微暗了一点，但我会竭尽全力改善屋子的照明，直到最黑暗的角落都充满光明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you settled in to our new home?</Source>
      <Dest>你住进我们的新家了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wish to look upon you in the light, from your smile to your scars, so that I may admire them all.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望我能在亮光下看着你，注视你的笑容，端详你的伤疤，然后我才能赞美它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The city is cold, but our house is warm.  And my love, I speak not of hearths and fires.</Source>
      <Dest>这座城市的确寒冷，但我们的家是温暖的。吾爱，我说的温暖，可不是指壁炉和篝火。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you settled in to our new home?</Source>
      <Dest>你住进我们的新家了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have heard rumors about the previous occupants, and some believe the house is scarred beyond all repair.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说了关于先前住民的传闻，有些人相信这幢房子已经没办法修复了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you settled in to our new home?</Source>
      <Dest>你住进我们的新家了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you settled in to our new home?</Source>
      <Dest>你住进我们的新家了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is but a wound that time will heal.  The house itself is but a victim, and we will love it as we do each other.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一道只能经由时间流逝而治愈的伤口。这房子只是个见证，我们会像对待彼此一样好好去爱它的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The home is lovely, but I worry about the preponderance of thieves in the city.  It may not be a good environment for children.</Source>
      <Dest>很棒的家，不过我有点担心城里的治安，这里小偷太多了。可能这环境并不非常适合孩子的成长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you settled in to our new home?</Source>
      <Dest>你住进我们的新家了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you settled in to our new home?</Source>
      <Dest>你住进我们的新家了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I suppose a city of thieves is better than a city of assassins, as thieves prefer guile and wit to violence.</Source>
      <Dest>不过我觉得一座城市满是盗贼总比满是刺客好些，毕竟盗贼都玩的是狡诈而不是暴力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you settled in to our new home?</Source>
      <Dest>你住进我们的新家了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I wonder if for some, the loss of gold is not a wound that is easily healed.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管我觉得对于某些人来说，金钱的损失会成为难以抚平的伤痕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How is the shop coming along?</Source>
      <Dest>那船怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As well as can be expected, my dear. I never thought I would play the role of merchant, but learning a new craft brings its share of excitement.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的，你可以期待一下。我从未想过有朝一日我也会当起商人来，不过掌握一门新手艺总是能让人兴奋不已的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How is the shop coming along?</Source>
      <Dest>那船怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It has not come as easily as restoration did, which is understandable given my ancestors were never good with coin.</Source>
      <Dest>这不像是回复法术那么简单，考虑到我的祖先从不擅长于和钱币打交道，这是可以理解的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How is the shop coming along?</Source>
      <Dest>那船怎么样了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I much rather prefer adventuring with you, my dear, and sleeping under the stars.</Source>
      <Dest>我更愿意与你并肩去冒险，亲爱的，然后并肩躺在星空之下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on children?</Source>
      <Dest>你对于那群孩子有什么想法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I would love to have them, and if we need to adopt, so be it.  I am at an age where my time on this plane is short.</Source>
      <Dest>我乐意养他们，如果我们需要过继的话，那就那么办吧。我这年纪已经是半截子入土了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on children?</Source>
      <Dest>你对于那群孩子有什么想法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Even now I can feel the pull of Aetherius on my soul, but do not fret, as I would not leave you for anything, my love.</Source>
      <Dest>甚至在现在我都能感受到艾瑟瑞斯在我灵魂深处召唤着我，不过别担心，亲爱的，我无论如何也不会离开你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on children?</Source>
      <Dest>你对于那群孩子有什么想法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It will take the strength of all the Gods in this life and the next to drag me away from your side.</Source>
      <Dest>要把我从你身边拉走，得靠全众神的力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While the Dragon's Tongue stands tall, and the Flax dances in the breeze, the Columbine slouches toward the ground under the weight of its crown.</Source>
      <Dest>While the Dragon's Tongue stands tall, and the Flax dances in the breeze, the Columbine slouches toward the ground under the weight of its crown.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For that reason, it has always been my favorite flower.  It refuses to listen to the wind, or the roots that beg for the sun.</Source>
      <Dest>For that reason, it has always been my favorite flower.  It refuses to listen to the wind, or the roots that beg for the sun.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It has its own personality. It grows and lives on its own terms.  </Source>
      <Dest>它有自己的个性，并以自己的方式成长和生存。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So even as the stars have guided you on this path, it is only because you choose to walk it that this world is blessed.  And for that I thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>所以，尽管是星辰指引你踏上这条道路的，但那也仅仅是因为你选择走了这条兼济天下之道路。为此，我感谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you healed them regardless of their affiliation.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你不管他们是什么关系就医治了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father cared not for what race or creed you followed.  He healed all the sick, all the injured, and let the politics sort itself out.</Source>
      <Dest>My father cared not for what race or creed you followed.  He healed all the sick, all the injured, and let the politics sort itself out.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you healed them regardless of their affiliation.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你不管他们是什么关系就医治了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was no greater evidence of this than when he found a young Khajiit kneeling over the body of an Imperial.  A dagger was lodged in her stomach.</Source>
      <Dest>最好的证据就是他看见一个年轻的虎人跪在一个帝国人的尸体前面。一把匕首插在她小腹上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you healed them regardless of their affiliation.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你不管他们是什么关系就医治了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father closed her wounds, as I searched the body for health potions.  I found a note.  It revealed the Khajiit to be a Thalmor spy.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父亲愈合了她的伤口，同时我也在那尸体身上搜些治疗药剂。我发现了一张便条。原来这个虎人是一名梭默间谍。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Military Camp or Fort) The war has left plenty of casualties.</Source>
      <Dest>(军营或堡垒) 战争带来巨大伤亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, unfortunately it has not been an unfamiliar sight.  I spent much of my youth in camps like this one, both as a soldier and a son.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，不幸的是，这景象对我来说并不陌生。我在像这样的营地里度过了我的青春，作为一名士兵，也作为一个儿子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Military Camp or Fort) The war has left plenty of casualties.</Source>
      <Dest>(军营或堡垒) 战争带来巨大伤亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father was a healer. He would walk the field after a battle looking for wounded.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父亲是个医生，他总是在硝烟散去后，穿梭于战场之上，救死扶伤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Military Camp or Fort) The war has left plenty of casualties.</Source>
      <Dest>(军营或堡垒) 战争带来巨大伤亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We would tend to some wounds, and give peace to others, and escort those we could back to the nearest town.</Source>
      <Dest>We would tend to some wounds, and give peace to others, and escort those we could back to the nearest town.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Arcanaeum) What is it?</Source>
      <Dest>(秘藏馆) 这是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wish to thank you for taking me here, my lady.  In my travels you may have noticed my fondness for stories and poetry, as well as for magic.</Source>
      <Dest>I wish to thank you for taking me here, my lady.  In my travels you may have noticed my fondness for stories and poetry, as well as for magic.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Arcanaeum) What is it?</Source>
      <Dest>(秘藏馆) 这是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This library is a wealth of all three.</Source>
      <Dest>这家图书馆是三个图书馆中藏书最丰富的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wish to thank you for taking me here, my boy.  In my travels you may have noticed my fondness for literature and poetry, as well as for magic.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你送我到这里，一路过来，想必你注意到了我对文学和诗歌的喜爱也和对魔法一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Arcanaeum) What is it?</Source>
      <Dest>(秘藏馆) 这是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Arcanaeum) What is it?</Source>
      <Dest>(秘藏馆) 这是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This library is a wealth of all three.</Source>
      <Dest>这家图书馆是三个图书馆中藏书最丰富的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Eye of Magnus is contained.  Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>马格努斯之眼已经被控制住了.  安卡诺也死了, 冬堡安全了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And you are Arch-Mage. You have gone from a nameless apprentice to head of the College in the time it takes most of us to learn our first spell.</Source>
      <Dest>你已经是首席法师了。在我们大多数人还在学习第一个法术的时候，你就已经从一个碌碌无名的学徒成为了整个学院的负责人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Eye of Magnus is contained.  Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>马格努斯之眼已经被控制住了.  安卡诺也死了, 冬堡安全了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Needless to say, I'm proud of what you have accomplished here.  Given what was asked, many in your situation would have wilted under the pressure.</Source>
      <Dest>什么都别说了，我真为你的成就骄傲。如果换了别人在那种压力下早就受不了了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Eye of Magnus is contained.  Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>马格努斯之眼已经被控制住了.  安卡诺也死了, 冬堡安全了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such is the curse of the Apprentice Stone.  For all your strength you are left vulnerable by your lack of experience.</Source>
      <Dest>Such is the curse of the Apprentice Stone.  For all your strength you are left vulnerable by your lack of experience.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Eye of Magnus is contained.  Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>马格努斯之眼已经被控制住了.  安卡诺也死了, 冬堡安全了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet the stars have shown that you are no mere apprentice, but rather, a leader with the Shadow's cunning, and the Mage's wisdom.</Source>
      <Dest>然而群星也昭示着，你不仅仅是一个学徒，更是一个同时具备影子之狡诈与巫师之智慧的领导者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Eye of Magnus is contained.  Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>马格努斯之眼已经被控制住了.  安卡诺也死了, 冬堡安全了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And of course, the Lover's beauty, but that my love, is as plain as the day.  </Source>
      <Dest>以及，当然了，情人星座的美丽。但是这一点，亲爱的，本就昭然于世。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Eye of Magnus is contained.  Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>马格努斯之眼已经被控制住了.  安卡诺也死了, 冬堡安全了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And you are Arch-Mage. You have gone from a nameless apprentice to head of the College in the time it takes most of us to learn our first spell.</Source>
      <Dest>你已经是首席法师了。在我们大多数人还在学习第一个法术的时候，你就已经从一个碌碌无名的学徒成为了整个学院的负责人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Eye of Magnus is contained.  Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>马格努斯之眼已经被控制住了.  安卡诺也死了, 冬堡安全了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Needless to say, I'm proud of what you have accomplished here.  Given what was asked, many in your situation would have wilted under the pressure.</Source>
      <Dest>什么都别说了，我真为你的成就骄傲。如果换了别人在那种压力下早就受不了了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Eye of Magnus is contained.  Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>马格努斯之眼已经被控制住了.  安卡诺也死了, 冬堡安全了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such is the curse of the Apprentice Stone.  For all your strength you are left vulnerable by your lack of experience.</Source>
      <Dest>Such is the curse of the Apprentice Stone.  For all your strength you are left vulnerable by your lack of experience.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Eye of Magnus is contained.  Ancano is dead, and Winterhold is safe.</Source>
      <Dest>马格努斯之眼已经被控制住了.  安卡诺也死了, 冬堡安全了.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet the stars have shown that you are no mere apprentice, but rather, a leader with the Shadow's cunning, and the Mage's wisdom.</Source>
      <Dest>然而群星也昭示着，你不仅仅是一个学徒，更是一个同时具备影子之狡诈与巫师之智慧的领导者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) This is it. Alduin awaits in Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 就是这样。奥杜因在松加德等待着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My lady, my love. It is not right that I must wait here while you risk your life against impossible odds.</Source>
      <Dest>我的夫人，我的爱。在你冒着生命危险却依旧毫无胜算的情况下，我必须在这儿等着？这可不对。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) This is it. Alduin awaits in Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 就是这样。奥杜因在松加德等待着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I could I would take your place, and all the burdens of this world, so that you can have the life the stars have taken from you.</Source>
      <Dest>若有一日我能够替代你，为你肩负起守护这个世界的重担，或许你就能取回群星从你手中夺走的那平凡生活了吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) This is it. Alduin awaits in Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 就是这样。奥杜因在松加德等待着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But alas, no amount of chivalry will change the truth.  </Source>
      <Dest>然而，可叹的是，骑士的数量不足以改变这个事实。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) This is it. Alduin awaits in Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 就是这样。奥杜因在松加德等待着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must brave this path alone, and know that I will be here, praying for your return.</Source>
      <Dest>你必须勇敢地踽踽独行，但我会一直在这里祈祷你的归来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) This is it. Alduin awaits in Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 就是这样。奥杜因在松加德等待着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, it was prayer that brought us together.  Remember that day when we met by the Steed Stone?  You were so beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，是祈祷让我们相聚。还记得我们在骏马立石相遇那天的情景吗？那天的你是如此美丽。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) This is it. Alduin awaits in Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 就是这样。奥杜因在松加德等待着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dragonborn, you have done much for this world, and its people.  I wish that I could take your place, if only to shoulder some of your burden.</Source>
      <Dest>龙裔，你为这个世界和人民做了太多，我真希望我能成为你，哪怕是为你分担一些你肩上的重任也好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) This is it. Alduin awaits in Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 就是这样。奥杜因在松加德等待着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I am no hero.  It is no coincidence that this dragon can only take one of us.  The stars have divined that you and you alone will save us.</Source>
      <Dest>但我不是英雄。这条龙每次只抓走我们中的一个人也不是个巧合。你出现在了星辰的预言之中，你会拯救我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragonsreach) This is it. Alduin awaits in Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙临堡) 就是这样。奥杜因在松加德等待着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet traveling with you, I know it takes more than fate.  In many ways, you remind me of the Columbine that grows near my home in the West Weald.</Source>
      <Dest>但与你一起旅行对于我来说不仅仅是命运使然。你让我好几次回忆起生长在我故乡西部莽原的耧斗花。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yet if you became a great soldier, I'm sure he'd approve.</Source>
      <Dest>然而如果你成为一个伟大的士兵，我确信他会同意的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He had always looked upon my accomplishments with great pride, but it wasn't until I asked him about restoration that I saw his eyes widen with joy.</Source>
      <Dest>他一直自豪地看着我取得成就，但直到我找他询问恢复系魔法的事情，我才看到他的双眼因突如其来的喜悦而微微张大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The old man had no idea what he was in for. I consumed book after book, tome after tome.</Source>
      <Dest>The old man had no idea what he was in for. I consumed book after book, tome after tome.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yet if you became a great soldier, I'm sure he'd approve.</Source>
      <Dest>然而如果你成为一个伟大的士兵，我确信他会同意的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yet if you became a great soldier, I'm sure he'd approve.</Source>
      <Dest>然而如果你成为一个伟大的士兵，我确信他会同意的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the end of the month, I had exhausted all the lantern oil in the basement, and every candle had burned to wick's end.</Source>
      <Dest>到这个月的月底，我已经在地下室用光了所有的灯油，所有的蜡烛也烧见底了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yet if you became a great soldier, I'm sure he'd approve.</Source>
      <Dest>然而如果你成为一个伟大的士兵，我确信他会同意的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father quipped that he should have taught me alteration magic instead, so at least I could read my tomes by magelight.</Source>
      <Dest>我父亲调笑说，他反倒应该教我变化系魔法，这样至少我就能放个魔光术熬夜啃书了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So he didn't want you to be a soldier.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说他不想让你当兵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He had always looked upon my accomplishments with great pride, but it wasn't until I asked him about restoration that I saw his eyes widen with joy.</Source>
      <Dest>他一直自豪地看着我取得成就，但直到我找他询问恢复系魔法的事情，我才看到他的双眼因突如其来的喜悦而微微张大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So he didn't want you to be a soldier.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说他不想让你当兵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The old man had no idea what he was in for.  I consumed book after book, tome after tome.</Source>
      <Dest>老人家也不清楚他的期许究竟该是什么。我一本接一本，一卷接一卷的啃着书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So he didn't want you to be a soldier.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说他不想让你当兵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the end of the month, I had exhausted all the lantern oil in the basement, and every candle had burned to wick's end.</Source>
      <Dest>到这个月的月底，我已经在地下室用光了所有的灯油，所有的蜡烛也烧见底了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So he didn't want you to be a soldier.</Source>
      <Dest>这么说他不想让你当兵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father quipped that he should have taught me alteration magic instead, so at least I could read my tomes by magelight.</Source>
      <Dest>我父亲调笑说，他反倒应该教我变化系魔法，这样至少我就能放个魔光术熬夜啃书了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where did you train as a healer?</Source>
      <Dest>你是在哪儿受训成为治疗师的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was after the White-Gold Concordat was signed. Magical talent had run through my family for years, but I was intent on becoming a soldier.</Source>
      <Dest>那是白金协定签订之后的事。魔法的天赋在我们家族的血液中流淌，但我执意要成为一名战士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where did you train as a healer?</Source>
      <Dest>你是在哪儿受训成为治疗师的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father was the type who encouraged his sons to pursue their goals, even if he quietly disapproved of the pursuit.</Source>
      <Dest>我父亲是那种即便他不喜欢，也仍然会鼓励他的儿子追寻自己的目标的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The stars are not the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>那繁星并非诸神。（stuk123吐槽：感觉好文艺，是什么人说的，要是个劫匪啥的就太不搭配了）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The stars are the heavens, and the shooting stars are pieces of Aetherius fallen to earth. </Source>
      <Dest>天上的星星既是天堂，那流星就是坠落在地的光界碎片。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The stars are not the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>那繁星并非诸神。（stuk123吐槽：感觉好文艺，是什么人说的，要是个劫匪啥的就太不搭配了）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some say the doomstones like these are built from the fragments of those stars, much like the Ayleid stones of legend. </Source>
      <Dest>有人说，像这样的毁灭之石是用那些星星的碎片修建而成的，就像传说中的亚历德之石一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The stars are not the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>那繁星并非诸神。（stuk123吐槽：感觉好文艺，是什么人说的，要是个劫匪啥的就太不搭配了）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thus these stones, these wellsprings represent the very provenance of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>因此这些石头和这些水源，全都代表着魔法的起源。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is why those who practice the arcane often pray to the stars, and not the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是为什么那些惯用奥术的人经常向星辰祈祷，而不是向诸神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The stars are not the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>那繁星并非诸神。（stuk123吐槽：感觉好文艺，是什么人说的，要是个劫匪啥的就太不搭配了）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But my apologies for prattling on, as I have not yet introduced myself.  My name is Valgus, a healer who follows the stars. </Source>
      <Dest>不过我得为我的多嘴而道歉，因为我没有自我介绍。我的名字是威尔格斯，一名追随星辰的医师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The stars are not the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>那繁星并非诸神。（stuk123吐槽：感觉好文艺，是什么人说的，要是个劫匪啥的就太不搭配了）</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think he didn't reveal she was a spy?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你认为他并没有泄露出她曾是间谍的这个秘密?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He would be sentencing her to a far worse death than the fates had given her.</Source>
      <Dest>He would be sentencing her to a far worse death than the fates had given her.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think he didn't reveal she was a spy?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你认为他并没有泄露出她曾是间谍的这个秘密?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Could the Empire have extracted information from her?  Perhaps.  For a soldier, it was a terrible decision.  For a healer, it was the only one.</Source>
      <Dest>帝国能从她口中得到情报吗？也许吧。对于一个士兵来说，这是个糟糕的决定。而对一个治疗师来说，这却是唯一能做的决定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Healing the enemy is foolish.  They will not offer you such mercy.</Source>
      <Dest>给敌人疗伤是愚昧的。他们才不会对你手下留情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father at least knew that much.  Which is why when he brought the young Khajiit to the village, he did so with her hands bound.</Source>
      <Dest>至少我父亲知道的很清楚。那就是为什么他把那个年轻的虎人带回村子时绑着她手的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He informed the guard that he had witnessed a horrific murder, and that she should be imprisoned for her crimes.</Source>
      <Dest>他告诉警卫说，他亲眼目睹了这场可怕的谋杀，而她应该因她的罪行被关进监狱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Healing the enemy is foolish.  They will not offer you such mercy.</Source>
      <Dest>给敌人疗伤是愚昧的。他们才不会对你手下留情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Healing the enemy is foolish.  They will not offer you such mercy.</Source>
      <Dest>给敌人疗伤是愚昧的。他们才不会对你手下留情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He did not, however, turn her over to the Legion, or reveal the nature of her identity.  Doing so would have resulted in her torture and execution.</Source>
      <Dest>但是，他没有把她交给帝国军团，也没有揭露她的身份。本来如果他那样做的话，她就免不了受尽酷刑并最终失去生命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If anyone knows that my dear, it is I.  Still, the title does have its perks. Perhaps Urag won't mind so much if your husband burns the midnight oil.</Source>
      <Dest>如果有谁知道这就是我的亲爱的，那个人也只能是我了。不过这头衔也有好处。如果你丈夫老是通宵达旦的熬夜 ，也许乌拉葛就不会那么介意了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They may call me Arch-Mage, but I'm the same person I was the day before.</Source>
      <Dest>他们可以尊称我为首席大法师，而我还是从前那个人没变。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suspect you are.  Yet that person was always a leader, and one capable of great things.  The title is merely a formality.</Source>
      <Dest>可能吧。但那个人始终是一个有担当的伟大领袖。虚名只是浮云而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They may call me Arch-Mage, but I'm the same person I was the day before.</Source>
      <Dest>他们可以尊称我为首席大法师，而我还是从前那个人没变。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I remember. But I don't need your prayers. Just knowing you're here is enough.</Source>
      <Dest>我想起来了。不过我不需要你的祈祷，只要你在这里就足够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, it sounds rather silly to say, given what you face, but I will do my best to be here when you return. That much I promise.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，“给你个面子”这话听起来很傻。但我会一直在这儿帮忙直到你回来，这是我能做出的最大承诺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I remember. But I don't need your prayers. Just knowing you're here is enough.</Source>
      <Dest>我想起来了。不过我不需要你的祈祷，只要你在这里就足够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And while I cannot offer you my magic or my staff, I can offer this.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管我不能把我的魔力或者我的魔杖送给你，但我能把这个给你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I remember. But I don't need your prayers. Just knowing you're here is enough.</Source>
      <Dest>我想起来了。不过我不需要你的祈祷，只要你在这里就足够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I love you.  These three words I give you.  They will not protect you from dragons, or phantoms, or beasts.</Source>
      <Dest>我爱你。这是我所能说给你听的三个字，尽管它们不能从巨龙，幽魂，亦或是兽口之下保护你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I remember. But I don't need your prayers. Just knowing you're here is enough.</Source>
      <Dest>我想起来了。不过我不需要你的祈祷，只要你在这里就足够了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But they can travel across worlds, from here to Aetherius, and they will be with you always, even when I am not.</Source>
      <Dest>但他们可以在不同位面之间穿梭，从这儿到艾瑟瑞斯，而且就算我不在你的身边，他们也总能伴随你左右。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think I've ever been called a flower before.  Thanks, I guess.</Source>
      <Dest>我从未想过居然有一天我能被称作为“花”，非常感谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I assure you, it is the highest compliment.  Yet I am fully aware that you need no such praise from me.</Source>
      <Dest>我向你保证，这是最高的褒奖。不过我很清楚，你完全不需要从我这得到赞扬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think I've ever been called a flower before.  Thanks, I guess.</Source>
      <Dest>我从未想过居然有一天我能被称作为“花”，非常感谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your deeds up to this point are proof of your valor.  Go forth then, to Aetherius, and show that your bravery is not limited to this plane.</Source>
      <Dest>你能做到这一步，已经能证明你的勇猛了。继续向前吧，到艾瑟瑞斯去，去证明你的勇气并不只局限于这个位面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was war, my lady.  Wherever there are wounded, I will be.  I journey to the various military camps across Skyrim and offer my assistance.</Source>
      <Dest>这是战争，我的夫人。哪里有伤员，哪里就有我。我周游于整个天际省，在各个军营之间旅行，并尽力提供我的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来天际省?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>On Loredas and Sundas, however, I can be found at the Temple of Kynareth. </Source>
      <Dest>在周六和周日，不管怎样，你也能在凯娜瑞斯神殿里找到我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来天际省?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I offer what I have learned on my travels to the temple healers, so that they may spread the knowledge to others.</Source>
      <Dest>我将我旅途中所学到的一切都贡献给了神殿医者们，这样他们或许会将那些知识传授给其他人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来天际省?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来天际省?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say a restoration mage can save more lives by teaching the principles of his craft rather than practicing them.  I aim to do both.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说，比起实践来，恢复系法师更能通过教授技艺原理来拯救更多的生命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was war, my boy. Wherever there are wounded, I will be.  I journey to the various military camps across Skyrim and offer my assistance.</Source>
      <Dest>那是战争，我的孩子。哪里有伤员，哪里就有我。我救治伤员的足迹遍布天际省各处军营。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来天际省?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>On Loredas and Sundas, however, I can be found at the Temple of Kynareth. </Source>
      <Dest>在周六和周日，不管怎样，你也能在凯娜瑞斯神殿里找到我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来天际省?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I offer what I have learned on my travels to the temple healers, so that they may spread the knowledge to others.</Source>
      <Dest>我将我旅途中所学到的一切都贡献给了神殿医者们，这样他们或许会将那些知识传授给其他人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来天际省?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来天际省?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say a restoration mage can save more lives by teaching the principles of his craft rather than practicing them.  I aim to do both.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说，比起实践来，恢复系法师更能通过教授技艺原理来拯救更多的生命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, and if you hadn't scouted that region you'd both be dead.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，并且如果不侦查下那个地区的话，你们俩都得挂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Most likely. Yet I have always been the type of romantic who believes that true heroes find a way. But the answer was not one I knew then.</Source>
      <Dest>大概吧。但是我依然是那种相信真正的英雄可以找到方法的浪漫主义的人。不过答案已经和我所知道的不一样了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, and if you hadn't scouted that region you'd both be dead.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，并且如果不侦查下那个地区的话，你们俩都得挂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When we returned, we found the entire camp reduced to ashes. But my wife was alive, lying against a tree not ten yards away, staring at Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>到我们回来的时候，看见整片营地都变成了废墟。可我妻子还活着，就躺在一棵树不到十码的地方，用涣散的双眼凝视着松加德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, and if you hadn't scouted that region you'd both be dead.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，并且如果不侦查下那个地区的话，你们俩都得挂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Her wounds, however, would not let her live much longer. We needed a healer. And I had but a sword.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，她受伤了，她的生命正逐渐从伤口中流逝。我们需要一个治疗者，而我却只有一把剑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have lost someone dear to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你肯定失去了哪个重要的亲人是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My wife.  We had married just before the war began, after the Empire had lost the southern provinces to the Thalmor.  </Source>
      <Dest>我妻子，我们在大战刚刚开始的时候成婚，就在帝国刚刚把南部省份丢给梭默的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have lost someone dear to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你肯定失去了哪个重要的亲人是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Everyone knew the war would come north eventually.  I picked up a blade.  She opted to forge one.  I never thought I would be the one to mourn her.</Source>
      <Dest>所有人都知道战火会蔓延到北方。我拿起了武器，她选择锻造武器。可我从没想过，再次相见时她已成故人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But don't feel sorry for me, my lady.  It happened over thirty years ago. More time has passed since her death than she spent among the living.</Source>
      <Dest>但不必为我愧疚，我的女士。30年前这已经发生了。她死的时间比活着时间还长。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have lost someone dear to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你肯定失去了哪个重要的亲人是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have lost someone dear to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你肯定失去了哪个重要的亲人是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My wife.  We had married just before the war began, after the Empire had lost the southern provinces to the Thalmor.  </Source>
      <Dest>我妻子，我们在大战刚刚开始的时候成婚，就在帝国刚刚把南部省份丢给梭默的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have lost someone dear to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你肯定失去了哪个重要的亲人是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Everyone knew the war would come north eventually.  I picked up a blade.  She opted to forge one.  I never thought I would be the one to mourn her.</Source>
      <Dest>所有人都知道战火会蔓延到北方。我拿起了武器，她选择锻造武器。可我从没想过，再次相见时她已成故人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You must have lost someone dear to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你肯定失去了哪个重要的亲人是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But don't feel sorry for me, my boy. It happened over thirty years ago. More time has passed since her death than she spent among the living.</Source>
      <Dest>But don't feel sorry for me, my boy. It happened over thirty years ago. More time has passed since her death than she spent among the living.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I might ask you the same, Valgus.</Source>
      <Dest>我可能会问你同样的问题，威尔格斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, my boy, a healer's work is never done.  You may have saved us all, but you cannot save us from ourselves.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，我的孩子，治疗者的工作是永远做不完的。你可能已经救了我们，但是你不能让我们拯救自己。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I might ask you the same, Valgus.</Source>
      <Dest>我可能会问你同样的问题，威尔格斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I will be there, when the cries of battle fade and the embers of war crumble, to mend the sick and wounded.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我会在那里，当战号消散，战火熄灭的时候，我会去救治那些伤者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I might ask you the same, Valgus.</Source>
      <Dest>我可能会问你同样的问题，威尔格斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I will look to the stars for The Lady, and pray for a day when healers are needed no more.</Source>
      <Dest>那么我将望向淑女星座，并祈祷终有一天人们不再需要治愈者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I might ask you the same, Valgus.</Source>
      <Dest>我可能会问你同样的问题，威尔格斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, my lady. a healer's work is never done.  You may have saved us all, but you cannot save us from ourselves.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，我的女士。治疗师的工作是永远做不完的。你可能救了我们所有人，但你不能把我们从自己那儿救出来。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I might ask you the same, Valgus.</Source>
      <Dest>我可能会问你同样的问题，威尔格斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I will be there, when the cries of battle fade and the embers of war crumble, to mend the sick and wounded.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我会在那里，当战号消散，战火熄灭的时候，我会去救治那些伤者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I might ask you the same, Valgus.</Source>
      <Dest>我可能会问你同样的问题，威尔格斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I will look to the stars for The Lady, and pray for a day when healers are needed no more.</Source>
      <Dest>那么我将望向淑女星座，并祈祷终有一天人们不再需要治愈者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the basement under Dragonsreach?</Source>
      <Dest>龙临堡下面的地下室怎么样?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I admit, I know little about the area, but it would be difficult for anyone in the lower levels to escape to the cloud district.</Source>
      <Dest>我得承认，我对这个地方所知甚少，不过对任何一个下层人来说，要逃到云顶区都是挺困难的吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the basement under Dragonsreach?</Source>
      <Dest>龙临堡下面的地下室怎么样?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Hall of the Dead might be a better option.  But it isn't large enough to hold an entire city of people.</Source>
      <Dest>亡者大厅或许是个不错的选择。只是它似乎还没有大到可以容纳全市的人吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the basement under Dragonsreach?</Source>
      <Dest>龙临堡下面的地下室怎么样?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I fear we may need to evacuate Whiterun before it becomes another Helgen.</Source>
      <Dest>恐怕我们得在白漫城化为下一个海尔根之前疏散群众了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the basement under Dragonsreach?</Source>
      <Dest>龙临堡下面的地下室怎么样?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I admit, widespread panic is not what we need either. I do not envy the Jarl. One only hopes the stars guide his choices.</Source>
      <Dest>但是我承认，大范围的恐慌也不是我们想要的。我不嫉妒领主。唯一的希望就是让星辰指引他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I too have a love for the arts. The art of killing bandits, mostly.</Source>
      <Dest>我同样热爱艺术。主要是杀戮土匪的艺术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And your skills are just as fine for cutting tension as well as mortals.  </Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 你那所谓的技巧也就能切菜剁肉罢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I too have a love for the arts. The art of killing bandits, mostly.</Source>
      <Dest>我同样热爱艺术。主要是杀戮土匪的艺术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet if you will allow me a brief moment of seriousness, I wish to tell the tale of my first lesson.  It may prove as valuable to you as it did to me.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你允许我稍微正经一点的话，我想给你讲讲关于我第一堂课的事情。它会像给我带来价值那样让你受益。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened to your wife?</Source>
      <Dest>你的妻子发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My apologies.  It is not a story I wish to share at this time.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉，我并不想在这个时候讲述这个故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You haven't gotten over her. It's obvious. Let it go, old man.</Source>
      <Dest>老头，看来你已经缓过劲头来了，出发吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I should.  I do not wish to spend the rest of my life married to a ghost.</Source>
      <Dest>我会的。我可不想把我的余生交给一个鬼魂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You haven't gotten over her. It's obvious. Let it go, old man.</Source>
      <Dest>老头，看来你已经缓过劲头来了，出发吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is just hard to envision that one can be lucky enough to find true love twice.  I am sorry, but let us not discuss the matter further.</Source>
      <Dest>只是没法想象一个人幸运到能够找到两回真爱。我很抱歉，咱们还是别再谈这个了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmm...I myself learned how to better close wounds by reading tales like that of Princess Talara.</Source>
      <Dest>恩...我也逐渐学会了用阅读某些书来更快地治愈伤痛，比如塔拉让公主这类。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Valgus, I thought maybe you could help Rumarin learn a spell.</Source>
      <Dest>威尔格斯，我想你可以帮 罗美勒 学一个法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Valgus, I thought maybe you could help Rumarin learn a spell.</Source>
      <Dest>威尔格斯，我想你可以帮 罗美勒 学一个法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, knowledge of the spell itself always came by tome.</Source>
      <Dest>就算是这样，法术的知识也总是来自于那些大部头的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Cemetery) Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>(墓地) 你在想什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My wife never had a proper burial. She would have liked a cemetery like this. Calm, understated, the stone facing a gentle breeze.</Source>
      <Dest>我的妻子从没想要过一个体面的葬礼。她只想要一块像这一样的墓地。平静，简朴，墓石面朝微风。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Cemetery) Something on your mind?</Source>
      <Dest>(墓地) 你在想什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My wife never had a proper burial. She would have liked a cemetery like this.  Calm, understated, the stone facing a gentle breeze.</Source>
      <Dest>我妻子从没被正式埋葬过。她应该有一个这样的葬礼。在一个平静，朴素，用石料镶嵌的地方享受微风。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a mortal, one cannot let another suffer, yet I would have opted for death.</Source>
      <Dest>坦率地说，一个人不应让他人遭受痛苦，然而我已经选择了死亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wanted the same. I pleaded with my father to end the Khajiit's life. He said he understood, but the decision was ultimately his.</Source>
      <Dest>我想要的也一样。我恳求我的父亲结束那虎人的生命。他说他明白，但最终的决定权在他手上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a mortal, one cannot let another suffer, yet I would have opted for death.</Source>
      <Dest>坦率地说，一个人不应让他人遭受痛苦，然而我已经选择了死亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could see, however, that he was disappointed.  He did not punish me, but seven years later, the stars saw fit to do so.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以看到，无论如何，他很失望。但他没有惩罚我。7年以后，星辰会责罚我的罪过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As a mortal, one cannot let another suffer, yet I would have opted for death.</Source>
      <Dest>坦率地说，一个人不应让他人遭受痛苦，然而我已经选择了死亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any event, my father healed the Khajiit, and brought her to the nearest village.  He told them he witnessed her committing a gruesome murder.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我父亲都给那虎人治了伤，然后把她带到最近的村庄。他跟他们讲，她是一场可怕谋杀的凶手，而他目击了一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thanks.  And now that I'm charge, things around here are going to change.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢。既然我在变，周遭的一切也都会变。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) I hope you mean for the better.  I would suggest you rest first, however, given the ordeal we just went through.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)我希望你是说一切有所好转了。无论如何，鉴于我们刚刚经历的磨难，我建议你先休息一下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thanks.  And now that I'm charge, things around here are going to change.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢。既然我在变，周遭的一切也都会变。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And if your ideas are sound, they will still be music to your ears come morning.</Source>
      <Dest>而且就算你的想法是合理的，他们也仍然会在清晨让音乐传入你的耳朵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Strange, I thought we met somewhere else.  It wasn't all that memorable.</Source>
      <Dest>陌生人，我想我们在别的地方见过面，虽然我不怎么记得清了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) A jester to the end.  That is why I fell for you, my lady.  Even now, as the world is on the brink of ruin, you can always make me smile.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 一个小丑的末路。这就我爱上你的原因，我的女士。即使是现在，就算世界正处在毁灭的边缘，你也能让我不失去微笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Strange, I thought we met somewhere else.  It wasn't all that memorable.</Source>
      <Dest>陌生人，我想我们在别的地方见过面，虽然我不怎么记得清了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I love you.  These three words I give you.  They will not protect you from dragons, or phantoms, or beasts.</Source>
      <Dest>我爱你。这是我所能说给你听的三个字，尽管它们不能从巨龙，幽魂，亦或是兽口之下保护你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Strange, I thought we met somewhere else.  It wasn't all that memorable.</Source>
      <Dest>陌生人，我想我们在别的地方见过面，虽然我不怎么记得清了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But they can travel across worlds, from here to Aetherius, and they will be with you always, even when I am not.</Source>
      <Dest>但他们可以在不同位面之间穿梭，从这儿到艾瑟瑞斯，而且就算我不在你的身边，他们也总能伴随你左右。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You will get no argument from me, Dragonborn.  My place is here.  I pray the stars give you strength, just as you give hope to the world.  Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>我不想和你吵，龙裔。此处才是我之所在。我会向星辰祈祷给予你力量，正如你给予这个世界希望一般。再见吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, and the stars and I agree that you're worthless and should stay behind.</Source>
      <Dest>对头，而且明星和我都同意你没点用，应该老老实实地呆在后面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Thalmor did you a favor. Marriage is a fool's absolute.</Source>
      <Dest>梭默帮了你。结婚绝对是傻瓜才做的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You obviously have not known love.  Any man would gladly be called a fool for chasing it.  Yet the Thalmor are not the ones who killed my wife.</Source>
      <Dest>你明显不懂得什么是爱。无论是谁，在爱情面前都会变成傻瓜。而梭默并不是害我妻子丧命的罪魁祸首。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Thalmor did you a favor. Marriage is a fool's absolute.</Source>
      <Dest>梭默帮了你。结婚绝对是傻瓜才做的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When we returned, we found the entire camp reduced to ashes.  But my wife was alive, lying against a tree not ten yards away, staring at Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>When we returned, we found the entire camp reduced to ashes.  But my wife was alive, lying against a tree not ten yards away, staring at Sovngarde.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Thalmor did you a favor. Marriage is a fool's absolute.</Source>
      <Dest>梭默帮了你。结婚绝对是傻瓜才做的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Her wounds, however, would not let her live much longer.  We needed a healer.  And I had but a sword.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，她受伤了，她的生命正逐渐从伤口中流逝。我们需要一名治疗者，而我却只有一把剑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't care what skills you possess, you're just here to entertain me.</Source>
      <Dest>我不在乎你有什么能力，你只是来取悦我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I shall do my best, my lady, as it is a man's pleasure to keep such wonderful company.</Source>
      <Dest>我会尽力的，小姐。能把您这么优秀的人当做同伴真是高兴之至。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't care what skills you possess, you're just here to entertain me.</Source>
      <Dest>我不在乎你有什么能力，你只是来取悦我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then I shall do my best, my boy, as there is nothing more sacred than a soldier's fraternity.</Source>
      <Dest>我会尽我最大的努力的，孩子，因为没有什么比一个战士的友谊更加神圣的了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It won't happen.  This dragon will never get past me.</Source>
      <Dest>这是不会发生的。这条龙是无法超越我们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am comforted by your bravery, as well as your confidence. But to fight a dragon...it may be beyond the reach of any mortal, even you.</Source>
      <Dest>我很欣赏你的勇气以及你的信心。但是屠龙......也许对任何普通人都是可望而不可及的事情，即使是你也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It won't happen.  This dragon will never get past me.</Source>
      <Dest>这是不会发生的。这条龙是无法超越我们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sometimes the best course of action is to flee.  There are some wars that just aren't worth the casualties.</Source>
      <Dest>有些时候最明智的行动就是逃跑。总有些争执是不值得为之付出血的代价的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It won't happen.  This dragon will never get past me.</Source>
      <Dest>这是不会发生的。这条龙是无法超越我们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My fear is that for many of these farmers, shopkeepers, and children, fleeing won't be an option.</Source>
      <Dest>我担心，对于那些农夫，商人和孩子来说，想要逃离是不可能的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It won't happen.  This dragon will never get past me.</Source>
      <Dest>这是不会发生的。这条龙是无法超越我们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The very walls that protect them may end up becoming a cage.  A grim prospect, but one the Jarl can't ignore.  I hope he makes the right decision.</Source>
      <Dest>保护他们的墙壁也许最终会成为一个笼子。这趋势真是可怕，但领主也不会忽视这一点。我希望他能做出正确的决定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know of these stones?</Source>
      <Dest>关于这些石头你知道什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some say the doomstones like these are built from the fragments of those stars, much like the Ayleid stones of legend. </Source>
      <Dest>有人说，像这样的毁灭之石是用那些星星的碎片修建而成的，就像传说中的亚历德之石一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know of these stones?</Source>
      <Dest>关于这些石头你知道什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thus all these stones, mage or steed, lover or thief, represent the very provenance of magic.</Source>
      <Dest>因此这些石头，无论法师或是骏马，爱人还是盗贼，都代表着魔法的出处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know of these stones?</Source>
      <Dest>关于这些石头你知道什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is why I come to pay tribute to the stars of Aetherius, for granting me their strength.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我向光界的众星进献祭的理由，因为它们赐予了我力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you know of these stones?</Source>
      <Dest>关于这些石头你知道什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But my apologies for prattling on, stranger, as I have not yet introduced myself. My name is Valgus, a healer who follows the stars.</Source>
      <Dest>But my apologies for prattling on, stranger, as I have not yet introduced myself. My name is Valgus, a healer who follows the stars.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Go find yourself a mage stone, old man.  The steed is not for you.</Source>
      <Dest>去弄一个法师之石吧，老头。战马之石不适合你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ha, I did not come to the Steed for it's assistance, but rather to offer mine.  Perhaps it is no coincidence that you arrived not long thereafter.</Source>
      <Dest>哈，我不是为了寻求帮助才来骏马之石的，我来这儿是为了提供帮助。也许与你意外相逢也是个缘分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Go find yourself a mage stone, old man.  The steed is not for you.</Source>
      <Dest>去弄一个法师之石吧，老头。战马之石不适合你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And while the mage stone offers blessings for those who wish to learn the craft, those days have long passed me by.</Source>
      <Dest>而那些通过魔法石的祝福，学会我希望习得技能的日子，已经过去很久啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are the wounded holding up?</Source>
      <Dest>那些伤员为什么被阻拦？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Better my lady, now that I've tended to their wounds.  Still, the number of casualties rises by the day.</Source>
      <Dest>情况稍好一点儿，我的女士。我现在在治疗他们的伤口。但死伤者的数量仍在上升。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are the wounded holding up?</Source>
      <Dest>那些伤员为什么被阻拦？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Restoration can only go so far. These wounds require time. Yet I know all too well how stubborn a soldier can be.</Source>
      <Dest>恢复也就到此为止了。这些创伤需要时间来抚平。然而我却很清楚一个士兵能有多么的倔强。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are the wounded holding up?</Source>
      <Dest>那些伤员为什么被阻拦？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Better, my boy, now that I've tended to their wounds.  Still, the number of casualties rises by the day.</Source>
      <Dest>好多了，小伙子，我现在要照顾其他人的伤口了。伤亡人数一直在增加。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Restoration can only go so far.  These wounds require time.  Yet I know all too well how stubborn a soldier can be.</Source>
      <Dest>治疗就到此为止了。伤口的复原需要时间。现在我知道战士有多顽强了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How are the wounded holding up?</Source>
      <Dest>那些伤员为什么被阻拦？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whiterun isn't an open city like Falkreath.  There are no underground catacombs like in Riften.  </Source>
      <Dest>白漫城不是像佛克瑞斯那样的开放城市。也不像裂谷城那样有地下墓穴和水渠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragon Rising) You seem concerned about this attack.</Source>
      <Dest>（龙族崛起）看起来你很在乎这次袭击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(Dragon Rising) You seem concerned about this attack.</Source>
      <Dest>（龙族崛起）看起来你很在乎这次袭击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's only one gate.  One way in and out of the city.  If a dragon were to attack, it would be like being trapped in a burning building.</Source>
      <Dest>There's only one gate.  One way in and out of the city.  If a dragon were to attack, it would be like being trapped in a burning building.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can close your wounds and heal them, as well as my own.</Source>
      <Dest>我能闭合你的创口然后治愈它们，也能治愈我自己的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What restoration skills do you possess?</Source>
      <Dest>你掌握了什么样的回复技能？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I possess knowledge of wards and stoneflesh, as to prevent injuries is far more efficient than to heal them.</Source>
      <Dest>我掌握的知识在于结界术和石肤术方面，因为避免受伤总比治疗伤势要有效得多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What restoration skills do you possess?</Source>
      <Dest>你掌握了什么样的回复技能？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That was my first lesson. There are many paths to knowledge, and not all of them clear.  As for the story of Talara, my father spoiled that ending.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我的第一堂课。获取知识有很多途径，而且并不是每一条路都清晰可见。至于塔拉让的故事，我父亲毁掉了它的结尾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lessons in storybooks? Ugh. People are always trying to trick you into learning.</Source>
      <Dest>故事书里的经验教训? 呃，人们总是想骗你去学习。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Lessons in storybooks? Ugh. People are always trying to trick you into learning.</Source>
      <Dest>故事书里的经验教训? 呃，人们总是想骗你去学习。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Apparently there were no more restoration lessons to be gleaned from that series.</Source>
      <Dest>显然，从这堆书中间已经收集不到更多关于恢复系魔法的知识了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That was my first lesson. There are many paths to knowledge, and not all of them clear.  As for the story of Talara, my father spoiled that ending.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我的第一堂课。获取知识有很多途径，而且并不是每一条路都清晰可见。至于塔拉让的故事，我父亲毁掉了它的结尾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see. It was a storybook with practical tips hidden within.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了。这是一本藏有应用技巧的故事书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I see. It was a storybook with practical tips hidden within.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白了。这是一本藏有应用技巧的故事书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Apparently there were no more restoration lessons to be gleaned from that series.</Source>
      <Dest>显然，从这堆书中间已经收集不到更多关于恢复系魔法的知识了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Even when I had finished, I still did not understand. It was then that my father pointed to a passage toward the end.</Source>
      <Dest>甚至当我读完了全书，我也还是不明白。就在那时，我父亲指向了最后一段。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you read it?</Source>
      <Dest>你读完它之后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He said, "Notice how when Ramke heals the girl, she presses her hands against both sides of the wound?"</Source>
      <Dest>他说"看清楚兰卡医治那女孩的时候，她的手是怎么做的了？"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you read it?</Source>
      <Dest>你读完它之后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you read it?</Source>
      <Dest>你读完它之后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you read it?</Source>
      <Dest>你读完它之后发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright, let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，让我们听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Looking at these shelves, I think back to when my father gave me my first book on restoration.  It was not a spell tome, or a guide, but a story.</Source>
      <Dest>看着这些书架，我想起我爸爸给了我第一本回复方面的书的时候了。这并非一本法术书或是本指南，而是一个故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alright, let's hear it.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，让我们听听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A frivolous tale of mystery, princesses, and court intrigue.  Naturally, I was confused.  My father smiled and simply told me to read the book.</Source>
      <Dest>A frivolous tale of mystery, princesses, and court intrigue.  Naturally, I was confused.  My father smiled and simply told me to read the book.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did she say?</Source>
      <Dest>她说什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She froze me with those deep, mournful eyes and said: "The day we married, you asked me if I was ever so happy that I felt like I was dreaming."</Source>
      <Dest>我被她哀怨又深沉的眼神瞪得动弹不得，然后听见她说：“我们婚礼的那天，你问过我有没有高兴得以为自己在做梦的体验。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did she say?</Source>
      <Dest>她说什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I rushed to her side, poured the last of my health potion down her lips, but it wasn't enough. We needed a healer.  And I had but a sword.</Source>
      <Dest>我冲到她的身边，把最后的治疗药水灌入了她的口中，但那是不够的。我们需要一个治疗者。而我却只有一把剑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She touched my blade and asked for my help. To give her death, so that she could cross the bridge to Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>她轻触了我的剑，请求我结束她的生命，让她能够踏上大鲸骨桥去往那松加德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She could see it, she said, the great mead hall standing high on the edge of the horizon.  </Source>
      <Dest>她喃喃地说道，她已经看见了，看见了那昂然屹立于地平线之上的大蜜酒厅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She could see it, she said, the great mead hall standing high on the edge of the horizon.  </Source>
      <Dest>她喃喃地说道，她已经看见了，看见了那昂然屹立于地平线之上的大蜜酒厅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I told her, it is but a dream. You belong here, on this plane, in this world.  This is what's real.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我告诉她，那只是幻觉。你属于这里，属于这个位面，属于这个世界。这才是真实。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She did.  She was no warrior, but she was a Nord, and she had spirit. And sometimes that's enough.</Source>
      <Dest>她确实那样做了。她不是一个战士，但她是一个诺德人，而且是个有骨气的诺德人。而有的时候，这样足矣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure she fought valiantly.</Source>
      <Dest>她在战场上确实非常英勇！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, when we reached the camp, I feared the worst. But she was still alive.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，当我到营地的时候我已经做好了最坏的打算。但幸好她还活着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure she fought valiantly.</Source>
      <Dest>她在战场上确实非常英勇！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The tents and equipment turned to ash, the ground black as soot, but there she was, lying against a tree not ten yards away, staring at Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>帐篷和装备都被烧成了灰，地面像是煤烟那么黑，而她就躺在一棵树不到十码的地方，用涣散的双眼凝视着松加德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sure she fought valiantly.</Source>
      <Dest>她在战场上确实非常英勇！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I've always figured you were well read.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我一直觉得你很有学问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not during my youth, but after the war ended and I lost my wife, I buried myself in studies, reading every tome I could on restoration.</Source>
      <Dest>我年轻时并不是时时刻刻在学习的，但自从战争夺走了我的妻子之后，我就将自己埋在记载有回复法术的旧纸堆里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I've always figured you were well read.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我一直觉得你很有学问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father was a master of the craft, and naturally I turned to his library for support.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父亲曾是工艺大师，我自然而然地向他寻求帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I've always figured you were well read.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我一直觉得你很有学问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could tell you the tale of my first lesson, if you are willing to oblige me.</Source>
      <Dest>I could tell you the tale of my first lesson, if you are willing to oblige me.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What other schools of magic do you use?</Source>
      <Dest>你还有用那些学派的魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every mage, regardless of the school they specialize in, knows a few destruction spells.</Source>
      <Dest>每一位魔法师，不管他们在学校专门研究哪方面，都懂得一些毁灭魔法的吟咏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>At first, I scoffed at the notion, as I was already an accomplished soldier.  However, time has deteriorated my battle skills.</Source>
      <Dest>一开始，我嘲笑了这个观点，因为我已经是一名技艺高超的战士了。然而，时间让我的战斗技巧退步了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What other schools of magic do you use?</Source>
      <Dest>你还有用那些学派的魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was far easier to study a few tomes on lightning magic than to pick up a mace, and I had vowed never to touch another sword.</Source>
      <Dest>学会一些闪电法术远比拿起一支钉头槌要简单得多，而且我也曾经发过誓，我这辈子再也不碰剑了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What other schools of magic do you use?</Source>
      <Dest>你还有用那些学派的魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And of course, I did eventually learn to use magelight, at my father's behest.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，在我父亲的要求下，我最终去学习使用魔光术了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What other schools of magic do you use?</Source>
      <Dest>你还有用那些学派的魔法？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I would, but the Stormcloaks are wary of letting an Imperial, especially a former Legion soldier, tend to their injured.</Source>
      <Dest>我会的，但风暴斗篷不会轻易让一个帝国人，尤其还是正规军团士兵，救助他们的伤员的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you heal the wounded for both Imperials and Stormcloaks?</Source>
      <Dest>帝国和风暴斗篷的伤员你都治疗了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you heal the wounded for both Imperials and Stormcloaks?</Source>
      <Dest>帝国和风暴斗篷的伤员你都治疗了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) Their actions only weaken their forces, as I am forced to provide my services to one side of the war.</Source>
      <Dest>(叹息) 他们的行动只是削弱他们的队伍, 导致我被迫向战争中的一方效忠.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have tried to explain this to their commanders with limited success.  It is possible my disdain for Ulfric and his lust for power color my pleas.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经试着向他们那些指挥官解释过了，没什么效果。也许是因为我对乌夫瑞克的轻蔑态度影响了我的话语权。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you heal the wounded for both Imperials and Stormcloaks?</Source>
      <Dest>帝国和风暴斗篷的伤员你都治疗了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The man is a bit of a tyrant, and those who fight under his banner are victims of his false ideals.</Source>
      <Dest>The man is a bit of a tyrant, and those who fight under his banner are victims of his false ideals.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you heal the wounded for both Imperials and Stormcloaks?</Source>
      <Dest>帝国和风暴斗篷的伤员你都治疗了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have a kind heart, one that I myself did not have at the time.  I begged my father to give her a swift death.</Source>
      <Dest>你有一颗我当时没有的善良的心。我乞求我的父亲能利落地结束她的生命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If I were in such a situation, I would've done the same.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我也处于这样的情况下，那我的反应会跟你一样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If I were in such a situation, I would've done the same.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我也处于这样的情况下，那我的反应会跟你一样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could see, however, that he was disappointed.  He did not punish me, but seven years later, the stars saw fit to do so.</Source>
      <Dest>我可以看到，无论如何，他很失望。但他没有惩罚我。7年以后，星辰会责罚我的罪过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If I were in such a situation, I would've done the same.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我也处于这样的情况下，那我的反应会跟你一样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any event, my father healed the Khajiit, and brought her to the nearest village.  He told them he witnessed her committing a gruesome murder.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，我父亲都给那虎人治了伤，然后把她带到最近的村庄。他跟他们讲，她是一场可怕谋杀的凶手，而他目击了一切。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is hardly the time to celebrate my promotion.  It's too soon.</Source>
      <Dest>这绝不是祝庆我晋升的时候。尚言之过早呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I apologize, my love.  I did not mean to make light of their deaths.  Yet I do think your accomplishments deserve to be praised.</Source>
      <Dest>我得道歉，亲爱的。我不是故意要提他们死了这件事的。但我认为你的成就应该受到称赞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is hardly the time to celebrate my promotion.  It's too soon.</Source>
      <Dest>这绝不是祝庆我晋升的时候。尚言之过早呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While you were unable to save Savos and Mirabelle, you may have just saved the world.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你不救萨沃斯和米拉贝尔的话，世界会因此而更美好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is hardly the time to celebrate my promotion.  It's too soon.</Source>
      <Dest>这绝不是祝庆我晋升的时候。尚言之过早呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Those deaths are not your fault, but the lives you saved owe you a debt of gratitude.  As one of them, I thank you on their behalf.</Source>
      <Dest>那些死亡并不是你造成的，但是你救活的人会感激你并欠你一份情。作为这些人中的一个，我代表他们谢谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I agree. I did not mean to make light of their deaths.  Yet I do think you are dismissing the gravity of your accomplishments.</Source>
      <Dest>我同意。我并没有对他们的死心怀不敬。相反我认为你该放下这任务的的重担了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is hardly the time to celebrate my promotion.  It's too soon.</Source>
      <Dest>这绝不是祝庆我晋升的时候。尚言之过早呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is hardly the time to celebrate my promotion.  It's too soon.</Source>
      <Dest>这绝不是祝庆我晋升的时候。尚言之过早呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While you were unable to save Savos and Mirabelle, you may have just saved the world.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你不救萨沃斯和米拉贝尔的话，世界会因此而更美好的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is hardly the time to celebrate my promotion.  It's too soon.</Source>
      <Dest>这绝不是祝庆我晋升的时候。尚言之过早呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Those deaths are not your fault, but the lives you saved owe you a debt of gratitude.  As one of them, I thank you on their behalf.</Source>
      <Dest>那些死亡并不是你造成的，但是你救活的人会感激你并欠你一份情。作为这些人中的一个，我代表他们谢谢你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wish I could, but the truth is I have not.  It is unfortunate, for I do not want to spend the rest of my life married to a ghost.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望我可以，但实际上我不能。很不幸，我不想跟个幽灵结婚，荒废自己的后半生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She would've wanted you to move on with your life.</Source>
      <Dest>她会希望你继续你的生活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is just hard to envision that one can be lucky enough to find true love twice.  I am sorry, but let us not discuss the matter further.</Source>
      <Dest>只是没法想象一个人幸运到能够找到两回真爱。我很抱歉，咱们还是别再谈这个了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She would've wanted you to move on with your life.</Source>
      <Dest>她会希望你继续你的生活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was right to heal her.  She could be tortured and interrogated.</Source>
      <Dest>治疗她是对的，她将被拷问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True enough, but that was not my father's intent.</Source>
      <Dest>True enough, but that was not my father's intent.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps he knew that was her fate, so instead of taking her to the city, he brought her to a small village.</Source>
      <Dest>也许他知道这就是她的命运。所以他没有带她去城市。而是带她去了一个小村庄。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was right to heal her.  She could be tortured and interrogated.</Source>
      <Dest>治疗她是对的，她将被拷问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was right to heal her.  She could be tortured and interrogated.</Source>
      <Dest>治疗她是对的，她将被拷问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He told the villagers that the Khajiit had committed murder, and that she should be imprisoned for her crime.</Source>
      <Dest>他告诉村民们，那个虎人犯了谋杀罪，她应该被抓起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I also have the Warrior's temper.  So don't get on my bad side.</Source>
      <Dest>别惹我，我也有一个战士的脾气。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) I wouldn't dream of it, my lady.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 我不会做这样的白日梦，女士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) I wouldn't dream of it, my boy.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)真是做梦也想不到啊，我的小伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I also have the Warrior's temper.  So don't get on my bad side.</Source>
      <Dest>别惹我，我也有一个战士的脾气。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, my lady is kind, but I was lost then.  While the stars lit your path, I stumbled in the darkness.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，善良的女士，我迷路了。当星星照亮你的路的时候，我正在黑暗中蹒跚前行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You weren't so bad yourself, my husband.</Source>
      <Dest>老公，你太责怪你自己了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You weren't so bad yourself, my husband.</Source>
      <Dest>老公，你太责怪你自己了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But then our paths crossed, and your light shone brightly enough for two.</Source>
      <Dest>But then our paths crossed, and your light shone brightly enough for two.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I love you.  These three words I give you.  They will not protect you from dragons, or phantoms, or beasts.</Source>
      <Dest>我爱你。这是我所能说给你听的三个字，尽管它们不能从巨龙，幽魂，亦或是兽口之下保护你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You weren't so bad yourself, my husband.</Source>
      <Dest>老公，你太责怪你自己了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You weren't so bad yourself, my husband.</Source>
      <Dest>老公，你太责怪你自己了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But they can travel across worlds, from here to Aetherius, and they will be with you always, even when I am not.</Source>
      <Dest>但他们可以在不同位面之间穿梭，从这儿到艾瑟瑞斯，而且就算我不在你的身边，他们也总能伴随你左右。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was an honor to fight alongside you as well, Valgus.</Source>
      <Dest>能和你并肩作战真是一种荣幸，威尔格斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your words do me kindness, Dragonborn, and your actions give the world hope.</Source>
      <Dest>你的话语就是对我的恩惠，龙裔，你的行动给这个世界带来希望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was an honor to fight alongside you as well, Valgus.</Source>
      <Dest>能和你并肩作战真是一种荣幸，威尔格斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your foe is formidable, and your challenge great, but if you hold those you love close, you will never falter.</Source>
      <Dest>你的面前有让人望而生畏的敌人和前所未有的挑战，但只要你的背后有你深爱的人，你就不会迷惘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I see. If every mortal knew that word, can you imagine how pointless wars would be?  People would have to solve their differences another way.</Source>
      <Dest>我懂了。如果每个凡人都了解那个词的话，你能想象战争会有多么无意义吗？人们将不得不用另一种方式解决彼此之间的分歧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There is a Dragon word to become ethereal. "Feim."</Source>
      <Dest>一段龙语飘来。“费姆。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But of course, if you take away the Warrior's sword, the Shadow will respond with his dagger.</Source>
      <Dest>但当然了，如果你拿走了勇者的剑，阴影会回馈他一把匕首。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There is a Dragon word to become ethereal. "Feim."</Source>
      <Dest>一段龙语飘来。“费姆。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And if we were always ethereal, the world would be a truly boring place.  Hmph. It must sound self-serving, but it all comes back to healing.</Source>
      <Dest>以及如果我们都幻化了的话，那这个世界就成了一个超级无聊的地方了。（笑声）这听起来或许有些自私，但就因为现在的状况才有人过来就医。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There is a Dragon word to become ethereal. "Feim."</Source>
      <Dest>一段龙语飘来。“费姆。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could settle it with a brawl.  Although Delphine looks like a tough one.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以以打一架的方式来解决。虽说戴尔菲娜看起来很强。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No doubt, she won't go down easily.  But as much as I'd love to, more violence isn't the answer.</Source>
      <Dest>毫无疑问，她不会轻易被击倒。但是以我来看，暴力并不是解决的方法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That doesn't mean I'm against a friendly wager or a little sparring session.  I'd just prefer we didn't bring up politics into it.</Source>
      <Dest>这并不意味着我会反对一次友好的赌博或是一场小小的拳赛。我只是不喜欢将政治掺杂在里面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You could settle it with a brawl.  Although Delphine looks like a tough one.</Source>
      <Dest>你可以以打一架的方式来解决。虽说戴尔菲娜看起来很强。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then come with me to the bed, my love, for not even the dragons can come between us.</Source>
      <Dest>Then come with me to the bed, my love, for not even the dragons can come between us.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then take me in your arms, my love, and never let go.</Source>
      <Dest>然後把我锁在你怀中，我的爱人，并再也不放开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, I know. But sometimes the war comes to you.  And the guards, for all their strength, are not healers.     </Source>
      <Dest>Yes, I know. But sometimes the war comes to you.  And the guards, for all their strength, are not healers.     </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But alas, maybe I'm just trying to rewrite history.  The Jarl knows his city better than anyone.  </Source>
      <Dest>哎呀，可能我只是想改写历史。领主是最了解他的城市的人。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The decisions that are forthcoming are best left up to him.</Source>
      <Dest>将来有什么事要决定的话还是都留给他吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) So the Nords say.  Sovngarde awaits.  But the heavens are eternal, and for those of us here, eternally far away.  </Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)所以那些诺德人说，松加德在等待他们。但对于在这里的我们而言，天堂是永存的，却永远遥不可及。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Everyone dies. The tragedy is living like a coward.</Source>
      <Dest>所有人都死了。而更大的悲剧就是活得像个懦夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All I wanted was a few years, no one more day with my Lenora in this life.  I suppose I'll have to settle for eternity in the next.</Source>
      <Dest>All I wanted was a few years, no one more day with my Lenora in this life.  I suppose I'll have to settle for eternity in the next.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Everyone dies. The tragedy is living like a coward.</Source>
      <Dest>所有人都死了。而更大的悲剧就是活得像个懦夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes. As you know, I gave up war and politics long ago. Now, all I wish to do is heal the wounded.  But I can only do so much.</Source>
      <Dest>对。和你想的一样，我在很久以前就放弃了战争和政治。现在我想要的只是治愈伤痕。但我只能做到这样了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is your business with Larsdon concluded?</Source>
      <Dest>你和劳斯登的生意终止了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) True enough, my lady.  Yet his people fight on, and the effects of his tyranny remain.</Source>
      <Dest>(Laughs) True enough, my lady.  Yet his people fight on, and the effects of his tyranny remain.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ulfric was a tyrant. Now he's just dead.</Source>
      <Dest>现在僭主乌弗瑞克嗝屁了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) True enough, my boy.  Yet his people fight on, and the effects of his tyranny remain.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 真够了， 小子。尽管他的暴政还在，他的人还在顽抗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ulfric was a tyrant. Now he's just dead.</Source>
      <Dest>现在僭主乌弗瑞克嗝屁了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She touched my blade and asked for my help. To give her death, so that she could cross the bridge to Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>她轻触了我的剑，请求我结束她的生命，让她能够踏上大鲸骨桥去往那松加德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She could see it, she said, the great mead hall standing high on the edge of the horizon.</Source>
      <Dest>她喃喃地说道，她已经看见了，看见了那昂然屹立于地平线之上的大蜜酒厅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She could see it, she said, the great mead hall standing high on the edge of the horizon.</Source>
      <Dest>她喃喃地说道，她已经看见了，看见了那昂然屹立于地平线之上的大蜜酒厅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I told her, it is but a dream. You belong here, on this plane, in this world.  This is what's real.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我告诉她，那只是幻觉。你属于这里，属于这个位面，属于这个世界。这才是真实。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened next?</Source>
      <Dest>接下来发生了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet there was.  If I was the man I am now, things would have been different.  It was not the Thalmor who killed her.</Source>
      <Dest>然而如果当时的我就如现在的我一样，那情况大概会有所不同。 杀了她的人就不会是梭莫了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's nothing you could have done.</Source>
      <Dest>那时你是无能为力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When we returned, we found the entire camp reduced to ashes.  But my wife was alive, laying against a tree not ten yards away, staring at Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>到我们回来的时候，看见整片营地都变成了废墟。可我妻子还活着，就躺在一棵树不到十码的地方，用涣散的双眼凝视着松加德。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's nothing you could have done.</Source>
      <Dest>那时你是无能为力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Her wounds, however, would not let her live much longer.  We needed a healer.  And I had but a sword.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，她受伤了，她的生命正逐渐从伤口中流逝。我们需要一名治疗者，而我却只有一把剑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's nothing you could have done.</Source>
      <Dest>那时你是无能为力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry. All that death must've been difficult.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉，我早该知道死亡从来就不是件简单的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father taught me that to kill a man is an easy thing, and during those times, it came easily for most.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父亲告诉我杀人是件很容易的事情，特别是在这个时代，杀人就更简单了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But to heal a man, to save him from certain death, that was nothing short of a miracle.  That was something all good men should strive for.</Source>
      <Dest>但是要治好一个人，要将他从死神手中夺回，其难度和奇迹出现不相上下。那是所有善良的人应当争取的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry. All that death must've been difficult.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉，我早该知道死亡从来就不是件简单的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sadly, I did not discover the truth of his words until after I was stricken by tragedy.</Source>
      <Dest>遗憾的是，我没有参悟到他真正想说的话，直到我遭受了那场悲剧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry. All that death must've been difficult.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉，我早该知道死亡从来就不是件简单的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such are the stumbles of youth.  We do not heed sage advice, but rather, we allow our mistakes to confirm its wisdom.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是青春的错误。什么不听老人言吃亏在眼前啊，我们会通过自己的错误来确认什么的明智的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry. All that death must've been difficult.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉，我早该知道死亡从来就不是件简单的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Indeed. Southern Cyrodiil saw much carnage.</Source>
      <Dest>的确，南赛瑞迪尔地区见证了许多的杀戮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My father taught me that to kill a man is an easy thing, and during those times, it came easily for most.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父亲告诉我杀人是件很容易的事情，特别是在这个时代，杀人就更简单了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Indeed. Southern Cyrodiil saw much carnage.</Source>
      <Dest>的确，南赛瑞迪尔地区见证了许多的杀戮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But to heal a man, to save him from certain death, that was nothing short of a miracle.  That was something all good men should strive for.</Source>
      <Dest>但是要治好一个人，要将他从死神手中夺回，其难度和奇迹出现不相上下。那是所有善良的人应当争取的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sadly, I did not discover the truth of his words until after I was stricken by tragedy.</Source>
      <Dest>遗憾的是，我没有参悟到他真正想说的话，直到我遭受了那场悲剧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Indeed. Southern Cyrodiil saw much carnage.</Source>
      <Dest>的确，南赛瑞迪尔地区见证了许多的杀戮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Indeed. Southern Cyrodiil saw much carnage.</Source>
      <Dest>的确，南赛瑞迪尔地区见证了许多的杀戮。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such are the stumbles of youth.  We do not heed sage advice, but rather, we allow our mistakes to confirm its wisdom.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是青春的错误。什么不听老人言吃亏在眼前啊，我们会通过自己的错误来确认什么的明智的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was born in Skingrad, my lady, near the southern border of Cyrodiil.  Growing up amidst the Great War, all my life I've been surrounded by death.</Source>
      <Dest>我出生在斯金格勒，我的女士，就在赛瑞迪尔附近的南部边界。我在世界大战中成长，死亡充斥着我的一生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a traveler, then.  From where do you hail, Imperial?</Source>
      <Dest>那么，你是个旅行者。 你来自什么地方，帝国吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was born in Skingrad, my boy, near the southern border of Cyrodiil.  Growing up amidst the Great War, all my life I've been surrounded by death.</Source>
      <Dest>我出生在斯金格勒，我的女士，就在赛瑞迪尔附近的南部边界。我在世界大战中成长，死亡充斥着我的一生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a traveler, then.  From where do you hail, Imperial?</Source>
      <Dest>那么，你是个旅行者。 你来自什么地方，帝国吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're right. It is long past time I did.  This I have been saying for twenty years mind you, but only now do those words have conviction.</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的。告诉你，我秉持此论这些已经二十年了，那可真是一段悠久的时光...不过直到现在这个时候这些话才有定论
</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your wife would have wanted you to move on.</Source>
      <Dest>你的妻子肯定想要你继续前进。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you, my lady.  For bringing me here, and being such pleasant company.  In all my travels, I have not had a more resourceful companion.</Source>
      <Dest>非常感谢您，我的女士。感谢您把我带到了这里，同时您也是一位令人愉悦的同伴。在我的旅途中，还从未遇到您这么优秀的旅伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your wife would have wanted you to move on.</Source>
      <Dest>你的妻子肯定想要你继续前进。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or a more beautiful one.</Source>
      <Dest>或者一个更漂亮的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your wife would have wanted you to move on.</Source>
      <Dest>你的妻子肯定想要你继续前进。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're right. It is long past time I did.  This I have been saying for twenty years mind you, but only now do those words have conviction.</Source>
      <Dest>你是对的。告诉你，我秉持此论这些已经二十年了，那可真是一段悠久的时光...不过直到现在这个时候这些话才有定论
</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your wife would have wanted you to move on.</Source>
      <Dest>你的妻子肯定想要你继续前进。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you, my friend.  For bringing me here, and being such pleasant company.  In all my travels, I have not had a more resourceful companion.</Source>
      <Dest>非常感谢您，我的朋友。感谢您把我带到了这里，同时您也是一位令人愉悦的同伴。在我的旅途中，还从未遇到您这么优秀的旅伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your wife would have wanted you to move on.</Source>
      <Dest>你的妻子肯定想要你继续前进。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Or a more faithful one.</Source>
      <Dest>Or a more faithful one.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your wife would have wanted you to move on.</Source>
      <Dest>你的妻子肯定想要你继续前进。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) You are correct.  And it may be another thirty thousand before I get over mine.  As such, I do not wish to discuss the matter further.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)你是对的。或许过了三万年后我才能恢复过来。  正因为如此，我不想再讨论这个问题了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You unfeeling monster. Thirty years is too short to get over a true love.</Source>
      <Dest>你这个冷血的怪物。三十年太短没有办法去忘记一段真爱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Troubled isn't the word I'd use. More like curious.  </Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 我的词典里可没有“焦虑”这个词。更多的是“好奇”。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Way of the Voice) You seem troubled by something.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙吼之道) 你似乎被什麽东西给困扰了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't you find it ironic that these Greybeards wish to preach non-violence, but their words are as deadly as any blade?</Source>
      <Dest>你不觉的这挺讽刺的吗？灰胡子们都不喜暴力，但他们的话语却都比任何武器都要致命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Way of the Voice) You seem troubled by something.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙吼之道) 你似乎被什麽东西给困扰了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder how they reconcile their training with their ideals.  Why train to be a swordsman when you can be a healer instead?</Source>
      <Dest>我真不知道他们怎么才能把理念与自我培养的问题协调好，如果你能当一个治病救人的人，干嘛还要当一名战士呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Way of the Voice) You seem troubled by something.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙吼之道) 你似乎被什麽东西给困扰了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(The Way of the Voice) You seem troubled by something.</Source>
      <Dest>(龙吼之道) 你似乎被什麽东西给困扰了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know not the Dragon tongue, but perhaps not every word in their language is a call for blood.  That is the kind of knowledge they should seek.</Source>
      <Dest>我不了解龙语，但也许在他们语言里，不是每一个词汇都是为了伤害对手。而是他们寻求着的一种知识。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I always believed there were survivors. The stories they told of the purge of Cloud Ruler Temple seemed like Thalmor propaganda.</Source>
      <Dest>我始终相信有幸存者。他们讲述的关于凌云者神殿净化的故事似乎像是梭默的宣传。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(A Blade in the Dark) It seems Delphine is a member of the Blades.</Source>
      <Dest>（黑暗中的利刃）看起来戴尔菲娜是刀锋的成员。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, even before the war the Blades were like old ghosts, long replaced by the Oculatus.</Source>
      <Dest>不过，即使是战争之前，刀锋战士就早已被锐眼鹰组织取代，成为不散的阴魂了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(A Blade in the Dark) It seems Delphine is a member of the Blades.</Source>
      <Dest>（黑暗中的利刃）看起来戴尔菲娜是刀锋的成员。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>(A Blade in the Dark) It seems Delphine is a member of the Blades.</Source>
      <Dest>（黑暗中的利刃）看起来戴尔菲娜是刀锋的成员。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dragon blood or not, they should have served the Empire.  They aren't much different than the Stormcloaks.  They mean well, but act poorly.</Source>
      <Dest>不管是不是龙的血脉，他们也该效忠帝国的。他们跟风暴斗篷没什么差别。想得很好，做得很糟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I heard the World Eater was dead, and yet as I waited for you to return, I could not help but think the worst.</Source>
      <Dest>我听说世界吞噬者已经死了，但在我等你回来的时候，总是控制不了自己去想最坏的结果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've returned, my husband.  Alduin will not.</Source>
      <Dest>我回来了亲爱的，可奥杜因回不来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Forgive me for my foolishness, my dear.  Truly the stars would not be so cruel as to take you from me now.</Source>
      <Dest>原谅我的愚蠢，亲爱的。毫无疑问，众星辰不会如此残酷地现在就把你从我身边夺走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've returned, my husband.  Alduin will not.</Source>
      <Dest>我回来了亲爱的，可奥杜因回不来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You are a true hero.  You have the Warrior's courage, the Lover's compassion, and the Lady's kindness.</Source>
      <Dest>你是一个真正的英雄。你有战士的勇气，情人的同情，和女士的善意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've returned, my husband.  Alduin will not.</Source>
      <Dest>我回来了亲爱的，可奥杜因回不来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've returned, my husband.  Alduin will not.</Source>
      <Dest>我回来了亲爱的，可奥杜因回不来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But to me you are more than that.  You are my wife, and my one true love.  Tonight I want you here, by my side.  The world can wait.</Source>
      <Dest>但对我来说你比这些更重要。你是我的妻子，我唯一的真爱。今晚我想要你陪在我身边。把其他所有一切搁在一旁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) So it would seem.  Well done, Dragonborn, well done.  You are every bit the hero that the stars foretold.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)如你所见。做得好，龙裔, 做得好。你就是那被星辰所预言的英雄啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alduin is dead, and the world is safe. The next one will have to wait its turn.</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因死了，世界安全了。下一个会等着出场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I am glad to see you are not wounded, either.  Truly, you have the Lord's resilience, the Thief's cunning, and the Warrior's courage.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴看见你也毫发无损。说真的，你有领主的能力，盗贼的狡猾和战士的勇气。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alduin is dead, and the world is safe. The next one will have to wait its turn.</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因死了，世界安全了。下一个会等着出场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My wife and I never had children, but when I look at you, I feel like a father, beaming at the accomplishments of his firstborn.</Source>
      <Dest>我和我妻子从来没有孩子，可当我看着你，就觉得像做爸爸一样，有一种微笑着看着自己第一个孩子的成就感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alduin is dead, and the world is safe. The next one will have to wait its turn.</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因死了，世界安全了。下一个会等着出场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm proud of you.  Not just for what you've done, but who you've become.  I am thankful to have traveled beside you.</Source>
      <Dest>我为你感到骄傲。不只是为你做了什么，更是为你已经成为了什么。我很感谢能与你同行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alduin is dead, and the world is safe. The next one will have to wait its turn.</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因死了，世界安全了。下一个会等着出场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I'm sure by now you're tired of such praise.  What's next for you, Dragonborn?  What will you do now that you are free of your destiny?</Source>
      <Dest>但我相信你已经厌倦了这样的赞美。有什么打算吗，龙裔？如今你终于摆脱了宿命，你想去做些什么呢？  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alduin is dead, and the world is safe. The next one will have to wait its turn.</Source>
      <Dest>奥杜因死了，世界安全了。下一个会等着出场。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) It is well deserved, Dragonborn.  Let the Shadow bless you with the night, so that you may slumber undisturbed.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)那是理所当然的，龙裔。愿阴影在夜晚保佑你，让你在睡觉的时候不被别人打扰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I plan on taking a nice long nap.</Source>
      <Dest>我打算美美地睡一觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet if you choose to resume your adventures, I would welcome traveling with you once more.  A healer's work is never done.</Source>
      <Dest>Yet if you choose to resume your adventures, I would welcome traveling with you once more.  A healer's work is never done.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I plan on taking a nice long nap.</Source>
      <Dest>我打算美美地睡一觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For you may have saved us from Alduin, but not even a Dragonborn can save us from ourselves.</Source>
      <Dest>你或许可以从奥杜因手中拯救我们，但即使是龙裔也不能使我们得到救赎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I plan on taking a nice long nap.</Source>
      <Dest>我打算美美地睡一觉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We decided to scout for one more night before returning back. It was then that our eyes were drawn not south, but north, by geysers of fire.</Source>
      <Dest>We decided to scout for one more night before returning back. It was then that our eyes were drawn not south, but north, by geysers of fire.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So did you stay or report back to camp?</Source>
      <Dest>So did you stay or report back to camp?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Naarifin's army had come not from Valenwood, but from hidden camps strewn about Elsweyr.</Source>
      <Dest>纳里芬的部队不是来自威木省, 而是从艾斯威尔附近隐藏的营地来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So did you stay or report back to camp?</Source>
      <Dest>So did you stay or report back to camp?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So did you stay or report back to camp?</Source>
      <Dest>So did you stay or report back to camp?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The forces gathering in Arenthia were a secondary army, there to flank the Legion troops that sought to regroup from the invasion.</Source>
      <Dest>在亚伦西亚聚集的是一队预备队，正准备插入待重组的军团旅侧翼.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But in that moment, I cared not for military tactics or the fate of the Empire.  All my thoughts turned to my wife.</Source>
      <Dest>但是那个时候，我不在乎什么军事策略或者什么帝国的命运。我满脑子就只有我的妻子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So did you stay or report back to camp?</Source>
      <Dest>So did you stay or report back to camp?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We were stationed together near the crossing where Cyrodiil meets Valenwood and Elsweyr.  She was the quartermaster's apprentice.  I was a scout.</Source>
      <Dest>我们一起驻扎在赛瑞迪尔、威木省和艾斯维尔相交的岔路口附近。她是军需官的助手，我是个侦察兵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You never told me the story about your wife.</Source>
      <Dest>你从未告诉过我关于你妻子的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We had heard rumors that Lord Naarifin had raised an army in Arenthia with the intent to invade. Our commander sent scouts to investigate.</Source>
      <Dest>我们听到了流言，说纳里芬将军在亚伦西亚组建了一支军队，有意图发动侵略。我们的指挥官派了斥候前去打探。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You never told me the story about your wife.</Source>
      <Dest>你从未告诉过我关于你妻子的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was a member of that group.  We set out west, and combed the border region for three days.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾经是那个小组的一员。我们向西出发，在边界地区搜寻了三天。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You never told me the story about your wife.</Source>
      <Dest>你从未告诉过我关于你妻子的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There were plenty of small camps and garrisons, but no evidence that Lord Naarifin himself had brought his armies to the border.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管那儿确实有不少小兵营以及驻地什么的，但没有证据显示纳里芬君王亲自率兵驻扎在边境。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You never told me the story about your wife.</Source>
      <Dest>你从未告诉过我关于你妻子的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, but you forget. To heal and to harm are two sides of the same coin.  Restoration can be used to dominate your opponent, just as fire and ice.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，但是你忘记了。治疗和伤害是同一枚硬币的两面。回复也可以支配你的对手，正如火与冰的关系一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dragons are inherently violent. Thus the thu'um is mostly about smashing stuff.</Source>
      <Dest>龙生来就是暴力的，因而他们的thu'um(龙语）只会用来搞破坏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dragons are inherently violent. Thus the thu'um is mostly about smashing stuff.</Source>
      <Dest>龙生来就是暴力的，因而他们的thu'um(龙语）只会用来搞破坏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If the dragons are keen on battle, they must have words to give to their wounded.  Maybe not to comfort the injured, but to return them to battle.</Source>
      <Dest>如果龙族都那么喜欢战斗，他们一定会有些针对伤员的龙语。就算不是为了安抚，也是要把它们吼回战场上去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dragons are inherently violent. Thus the thu'um is mostly about smashing stuff.</Source>
      <Dest>龙生来就是暴力的，因而他们的thu'um(龙语）只会用来搞破坏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I just find it odd the Greybeards choose to isolate their power instead of seeking ways to have it reflect their ideals.</Source>
      <Dest>I just find it odd the Greybeards choose to isolate their power instead of seeking ways to have it reflect their ideals.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But perhaps I'm just projecting my own desires.  I'm just praying there's a thu'um that can fix this insufferable back of mine. </Source>
      <Dest>但也许我有点自私。我只祈祷能有一个吐目可以治愈我那难以忍受的背痛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dragons are inherently violent. Thus the thu'um is mostly about smashing stuff.</Source>
      <Dest>龙生来就是暴力的，因而他们的thu'um(龙语）只会用来搞破坏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do I have to keep you two separated?</Source>
      <Dest>我需要让你俩保持距离么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't worry, it won't come to that.  The war's over, and there's no point in opening old wounds.  I'll do my best to be civil.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 别担心，没必要变成这样。战争结束了，没有任何理由去揭开旧的伤疤。我会尽最大的努力为公众服务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) As you wish, my lady.  Let us walk from here to Aetherius, and paint the sky with our light.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声) 如您所愿，女士。让我们出发前往艾瑟瑞斯，用灯光点亮夜空。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Okay, but tomorrow we're going back to adventuring.</Source>
      <Dest>好，但明天我们会返回继续探险的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You miss her, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你想念她，不是吗？.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I did.  But it is time to move on.  Although I have been saying that for twenty years, so I know not if my words have conviction.</Source>
      <Dest>确实。不过现在是时候放下了。虽然我这话说了有二十年，我也不知道自己有没有这个信念。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you, my lady. For bringing me here, and being such pleasant company. I have not felt this way about any companion for some time.</Source>
      <Dest>非常感谢您，我的女士。感谢您把我带到了这里，同时您也是一位令人愉悦的同伴。在我的旅途中，还从未遇到您这么优秀的旅伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You miss her, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你想念她，不是吗？.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I did.  But it is time to move on.  Although I have been saying that for twenty years now, so I know not if my words have conviction.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道。但是是时候动身了。尽管我知道我的话没什么说服力——毕竟到现在这话我已经说了二十年了，但是我还是要说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You miss her, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你想念她，不是吗？.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thank you, my boy.  For bringing me here, and being such pleasant company.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你，我的孩子。谢谢你带我来这里。你是如此地值得信赖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You miss her, don't you.</Source>
      <Dest>你想念她，不是吗？.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Then I'm afraid I can't help you.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)恐怕我帮不了你。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Rumarin, I'm sorry.  Books offer hints at how to improve at restoration, but it would take a fifty volume epic to teach even the simplest spells.</Source>
      <Dest>罗米勒，对不起。书上是提到些增强回复系的小技巧，但就算用五十卷巨着恐怕也难以教人学会哪怕最简单的法术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A tome is still the best way to learn.  My advice is to just keep at it.  Don't rush. It'll come eventually.</Source>
      <Dest>找本书看依旧是最好的学习方法。我的建议就是继续保持下去。别图快。你会成功的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A dead adventurer, no doubt investigating Gauldur's legend. I fear the book Lost Legends has cost many their lives. I commit his soul to Aetherius.</Source>
      <Dest>一个死去的冒险者，毫无疑问，他在调查尸鬼的传说。恐怕这本记有失落的传说的书让很多的冒险家付出了生命。愿他的灵魂回归艾瑟瑞斯的怀抱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These stone sentinels stand at the boundary between Falkreath and the Rift. A marvelous display of Nord architecture to be sure.</Source>
      <Dest>这些石头守卫立于佛克瑞斯和裂痕领的交界，是诺德建筑师的杰作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Nord burial rites for people of renown must have been very different in Geirund's time. The body almost seems as if it's on display.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人埋葬显赫之人的仪式在吉尔蒙德时代定然是大不相同。遗体看起来几乎是在彰显地位。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Candles...conjuration circles. The stars are dim here. Be ready.</Source>
      <Dest>虚空中的元素啊，聆听我的祈祷，回应我的召唤，照亮前方的道路...烛光术！ 这里星星很暗。准备好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A shrine to Julianos. What kind of misguided warlock would call these experiments wisdom?</Source>
      <Dest>尤里安诺思的圣殿。被忽悠成什么样的术士才会认为这样的实验明智？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Look at that corpse. The heart was removed, as if in preparation for a ritual. But I thought only witches could perform such dark magic.</Source>
      <Dest>看看那具死尸。心被挖走了，好像是为什么仪式做准备。但是我想也只有女巫能玩得转这些黑魔法了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I hate to admit it, but Meridia was right. These corpses...Stormcloak, and Imperial...their souls scream for peace.</Source>
      <Dest>我痛恨承认这一点，美瑞狄亚是对的。这些尸体...风暴斗篷的，帝国的...他们的灵魂都在为和平而嘶吼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Malkoran is likely in the next chamber. Let us bring peace to these soldiers, Stormcloak and Imperial, so they may find their way to Aetherius.</Source>
      <Dest>莫克然应该就在下一个大厅里。让我们给这些暴风斗篷和帝国军团的士兵送去点祥和吧，这样他们或许能找得到去艾瑟瑞斯的路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Draugr...necromancers...whatever that light is focused on, it can't possibly be benevolent. We must end this ritual at all costs.</Source>
      <Dest>尸鬼...亡灵术士...不管对手是谁，他们可都不是什么善茬儿。我们必须终结这个仪式，不惜一切代价。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to return to my earlier questions.</Source>
      <Dest>我想回到我刚才的问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Understood.</Source>
      <Dest>了解。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am afraid I do not know. As Karras said, the Kingsmoot is but a formality.</Source>
      <Dest>恐怕我不知道。卡拉斯说众王议会只是个形式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think her claim will be recognized?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得她提出来的要求会被同意吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet the name Ysgramor is revered by every Nord in Skyrim, and not even someone like Ulfric could deny them consideration.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，伊斯格拉谟之名被每一个天际省的诺德人崇敬着，甚至是如乌佛瑞克之流也不可否认地尊敬于他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you think her claim will be recognized?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得她提出来的要求会被同意吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like Elisif, I suspect her readiness depends on her advisers, but my presence is not in support of her cause.</Source>
      <Dest>就像艾利西弗，我怀疑她的充分准备都来自于她的智囊，但我到场可不是为了支持她的事业。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you believe this Queen is fit to rule?</Source>
      <Dest>你相信这位女王适合来统治？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whether this ritual proves her bloodline is irrelevant. My only concern is that she survives it.</Source>
      <Dest>不论她的血统借由这仪式所证是否就是正统。我所在意的不是那些，我在意的是她能否继续统治。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you believe this Queen is fit to rule?</Source>
      <Dest>你相信这位女王适合来统治？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>From what I gather, she's a child, and for that reason she is quite vulnerable. </Source>
      <Dest>从我搜集的资料来看，她只是个孩子，相当地脆弱。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you met this heir? Any idea who she is?</Source>
      <Dest>你见过这个后裔吗？她在哪儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's also why the Thane keeps her location and identity a secret, and why her presence is not required here.</Source>
      <Dest>这也是为什么领主从未披露过她的处所与身份的原因，也是为什么她对于这儿来说没有存在的必要的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Have you met this heir? Any idea who she is?</Source>
      <Dest>你见过这个后裔吗？她在哪儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you come to join this faction?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么就加入了这个阵营呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>During my time wandering the military camps, I heard many grumblings from the disenchanted.</Source>
      <Dest>在我游荡于军营的日子里，听到了很多心灰意懒的牢骚话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They spoke of a faction of peace, united under the banner of the true heir of Ysgramor.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说起一个什么和平的组织，打着伊斯格拉谟真正继承人的旗号。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you come to join this faction?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么就加入了这个阵营呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, I never sought out the Thane. However, as the Temple of Kynareth is in Whiterun, it was only a matter of time before our paths crossed.</Source>
      <Dest>我还是没找到男爵。然而，既然白漫城有凯娜瑞斯神庙，那在我们度过这一切前，只是时间问题了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you come to join this faction?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么就加入了这个阵营呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you come to join this faction?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么就加入了这个阵营呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For you see, the ritual to prove the Queen's legitimacy requires a healer. Thus, the stars guided him to the temple, and to me.</Source>
      <Dest>如你所见，这个证明女王合法性的仪式需要一个治疗师。因此，星辰指引他来到这个寺庙，来到我的面前。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My apologies for prattling on, stranger, as I have not yet introduced myself.  My name is Valgus, a healer who follows the stars. </Source>
      <Dest>抱歉我只是开个玩笑，陌生人，我还没介绍自己呢。我叫威尔格斯，一名追随星辰指引的救济生灵之人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My love, the stars seem to be fixed in the sky, but they are always moving, as are we.</Source>
      <Dest>吾爱，天上的星星看上去是静止的，但它们一直在移动，我们也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Valgus, my love. You never told me about any of this.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的威尔格斯，你可从来没跟我提起过这回事儿</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But those whose hearts are connected will always move as one.</Source>
      <Dest>但是那些心灵相通的人可以永远配合无间，就像一个人似的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Valgus, my love. You never told me about any of this.</Source>
      <Dest>亲爱的威尔格斯，你可从来没跟我提起过这回事儿</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Valgus. Didn't expect to see you here.</Source>
      <Dest>威尔格斯！没想到在这儿能见到你！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The stars seem to be fixed in the sky, but they are always moving, as are we.</Source>
      <Dest>天上的星星看上去是静止的，但它们一直在移动动，我们也一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But those whose fates are connected will always move as one.</Source>
      <Dest>但是那些命运紧紧相连的人永远不会分开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Valgus. Didn't expect to see you here.</Source>
      <Dest>威尔格斯！没想到在这儿能见到你！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, Dragonborn. It seems the Steed has brought us both here, as instruments in a greater plan.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，龙裔。看来骏马之石似乎把我们两个都带到了这里，为某个伟大的计划而服务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May the Lord, through victory or defeat, plant the seeds of peace.</Source>
      <Dest>愿诸神，能够撒下和平的种子，无论这场战争是哪方获胜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on Larsdon and Falatild?</Source>
      <Dest>对于劳斯登和菲欧露你怎么看？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Thane was born under the sign of the Lover, no doubt. Graceful, but passionate about his cause.</Source>
      <Dest>领主因时运和神迹而生。毫无疑问，领主得优雅，并且热爱他的事业。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The housecarl I know little about, other than she refuses to let me heal her.</Source>
      <Dest>除了她拒绝我的治疗之外，我对这个侍卫了解甚少。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your thoughts on Larsdon and Falatild?</Source>
      <Dest>对于劳斯登和菲欧露你怎么看？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A dead adventurer, no doubt investigating Gauldur's legend. I fear the book Lost Legends has cost many their lives. I commit his soul to Aetherius.</Source>
      <Dest>一个死去的冒险者，毫无疑问，他在调查尸鬼的传说。恐怕这本记有失落的传说的书让很多的冒险家付出了生命。愿他的灵魂回归艾瑟瑞斯的怀抱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>{Departs}</Source>
      <Dest>{离开 }</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well my dear, call upon me at our home if you need my services again.</Source>
      <Dest>Very well my dear, call upon me at our home if you need my services again.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well.  I will return to wandering the camps, but if you need my staff once more, I will be at the Temple of Kynareth on the days of rest.</Source>
      <Dest>好的，我会走回营地。 如果你再需要我的货, 我会在休息日守在凯娜瑞斯神殿那里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Alas, it's time for us to part ways.</Source>
      <Dest>行啦，是咱们分道扬镳的时候啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will do what I can.</Source>
      <Dest>我会尽我所能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need you to do something for me.</Source>
      <Dest>我需要你为我做件事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here for a moment.</Source>
      <Dest>在这儿等一下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Understood.  I'll stand guard until you get back.</Source>
      <Dest>明白。我将一直坚守到你回来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wait here.</Source>
      <Dest>在这里等着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's nothing. Never mind.</Source>
      <Dest>没什么事，不用担心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Carry on then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就继续吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Understood.</Source>
      <Dest>了解。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes. Let me show you.</Source>
      <Dest>不错，你看看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take your time.</Source>
      <Dest>抓紧时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Take your time.</Source>
      <Dest>慢慢儿来。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure. What do you need?</Source>
      <Dest>当然，你需要什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well, let us trade.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，咱们来交换吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Our burdens are best spread between us.</Source>
      <Dest>我们最好共同分担责任。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course. Let's trade.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。咱们来做生意吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right. How can I help?</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。我怎么帮忙？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I need to trade some things with you.</Source>
      <Dest>我想跟你交易一些东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you need me to take?</Source>
      <Dest>你有什么要我拿的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, my love.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，亲爱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you wish.</Source>
      <Dest>遵命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am at your assistance.</Source>
      <Dest>I am at your assistance.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you wish.</Source>
      <Dest>遵命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will do what I can.</Source>
      <Dest>我会尽我所能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Zzzzz...</Source>
      <Dest>Zzzzz……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If the trials in Ustengrav could only be passed by a wielder of the voice, how is it someone managed to beat you to the horn?</Source>
      <Dest>要是炙燃墓的机关只能由懂得龙吼的人破解，那怎么可能有人比你先抢到那个号角呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Amazing how easy the path to the Horn has been. Draugr, conjurers, bandits...it's almost like wading through a battlefield, looking for survivors.</Source>
      <Dest>这条号角之路可真是简单得令人吃惊啊。尸鬼，术士，强盗...搞得好像在穿越战场寻找幸存者似的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We're here. The Greybeards are waiting, but I doubt they are waiting impatiently. I could use a rest at the inn. I'm not as young as I used to be.</Source>
      <Dest>我们到了。灰胡子们正在等我们，但我怀疑他们没多少耐心。我想在旅馆里休息休息。我已经不如年轻时那样啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It takes resolve to avoid human contact.  I have too much of the Lord and the Lady my blood, and I would be the first to greet Klimmek at the door.</Source>
      <Dest>不再与人类接触是需要决心的. 我的血还没那么高贵，但我将是第一个站在门口迎接科林麦的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That shout was impressive.  Yet I've heard the Greybeards espouse a philosophy of non-violence.  I wonder if the thu'um has the power to restore.</Source>
      <Dest>这吼声真是叫人印象深刻。但我听说灰胡子主张非暴力的信条。我不知道吐目是否有恢复的能力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That brawler. I know him. Gian the Fist, they used to call him. It doesn't surprise me that he ended up here.</Source>
      <Dest>那个吵架的。我认识他。重拳盖安，他们以前这样称呼他。他最后流落到这儿毫不稀奇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Thieves Guild need you to be their muscle.  It's not surprising.  Judging by the state of their headquarters, their arms as thin as blisterworts.</Source>
      <Dest>盗贼公会需要你为他们助力。这并不奇怪，考虑到他们那组织的状况，他们那力量可是比气泡草还弱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If nothing else, your foray into the Thieves Guild has provided us valuable information on Maven Black-Briar.  The Jarl should know of her dealings.</Source>
      <Dest>如果没别的了，那么你对盗贼工会的渗透已经给我们提供了关于玛雯黑荆棘的宝贵信息。领主应该知道她肮脏的作为。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Brynjolf goes to great lengths to insist you don't kill these targets, as if that absolves him of his crimes.  It doesn't.</Source>
      <Dest>布林乔夫用了相当长的篇幅来跟你强调不要杀掉这些任务目标，就好象这样做能免除他自己的罪行似的。那根本不可能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This Hamelyn descended into madness, but the signs were there long before. Yet his instructors chose to banish a man they could have rehabilitated.</Source>
      <Dest>哈姆林陷入了疯狂，但在此之前已有迹象。然而他的导师却选择放逐了这个可能会恢复正常的男人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder if Sabjorn is truly as underhanded as Maven implies.  It does make me laugh at the irony.</Source>
      <Dest>I wonder if Sabjorn is truly as underhanded as Maven implies.  It does make me laugh at the irony.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is good to see you alive and well.  Ironic that it was a poison that served as the remedy for Mercer's blade.  Now we must return the favor.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴你还活着。讽刺的是，要治疗墨瑟那把剑所留下的伤，得用毒药才行。现在我们该以牙还牙双倍奉还啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can sympathize with Gallus. Torn between two paths, I chose the most exciting, never realizing the thrills that can come from reading a dusty tome.</Source>
      <Dest>我能同情理解加卢斯。两条分岔路, 我选择了最刺激的那条，却从未想到真正的刺激是来自阅读那本满是灰尘的大书.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nightingales...the Twilight Sepulcher...I admit, at first I didn't care much for your adventures with the Thieves Guild.  But this is living history.</Source>
      <Dest>夜莺...黄昏坟墓...我承认，起初我对你与你那盗贼公会的冒险故事没什么兴趣。但，这就是活生生的历史啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whatever Mercer stole can be replaced.  The important thing is that Karliah's honor is restored. </Source>
      <Dest>墨瑟所偷走的东西并不是无可替代，因而无足挂齿。卡莉亚的名誉得以恢复才是最为重要的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know you seek vengeance, and you wish to do this for the Guild, but if you agree to this oath, be sure you are fine with the consequences.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道你渴望复仇，而且你希望为公会做这件事，但是如果你恪守这个誓言，那就得确定你不会为结果而后悔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, there you are.  I trust none of you are hurt?</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你在这儿啊。你没受伤吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Those plans must be extremely valuable, given the gauntlet of traps protecting it. I think that axe nicked me, by the way. I may need a moment.</Source>
      <Dest>Those plans must be extremely valuable, given the gauntlet of traps protecting it. I think that axe nicked me, by the way. I may need a moment.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With Mercer dead, and the key in your hands, this should feel like an end.  But this test Karliah speaks of makes me think this isn't over.</Source>
      <Dest>既然墨瑟已经死了，钥匙也已经到了你的手中，一切似乎已经尘埃落定。但卡莱雅所说的那个测试让我觉得这还没有结束。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Master of the Thieves Guild.  Congratulations.  I may not agree with all your decisions, but I respect what you've endured to get here.</Source>
      <Dest>盗贼公会的大师。恭喜。我可能无法完全按同意你的决定，但我尊重你一路走来所经受的考验。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am not your father. I won't lecture you on why thievery is wrong. But you know where I stand.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不是你老爸。我不会对你的偷窃行为说教。但你知道我的立场的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Amazing. The blue flame that cleansed Kodlak's soul burns with the light of Aetherius.  As if this tomb were connected to Sovngarde.</Source>
      <Dest>太神奇了。刚才净化克拉科灵魂的蓝色火焰竟然是来自艾瑟瑞斯的。就好像这座古墓可以直接连通松加德似的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Kodlak's journal spoke of a battle with a great wolf.  These ghosts will prepare us, and ensure we are worthy of fighting by his side.</Source>
      <Dest>克拉科的日记讲述了一场与巨狼的战斗.  这些鬼会锻炼我们, 确保我们能英勇地为他而战.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The fates can be cruel, to take Kodlak now. I only pray that the Shadow shields Hircine's eye, so that the stars can guide his soul to Aetherius. </Source>
      <Dest>命运真是残酷，竟然夺走了克拉科的生命。我唯一的愿望是阴影能遮蔽海尔辛的双眼，星光能指引他的灵魂前往光界。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ulfric's war has done so much harm, but I think the bad blood between Stalleo and Brurid is about something deeper.</Source>
      <Dest>乌佛瑞克发动的战争已经造成那么大的危害，可我觉得斯塔莱奥和布鲁瑞肚子里的坏水还要更阴狠得多呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So much senseless death for a feud between two men.  I commit these souls to Aetherius. Blessings of the Nine upon them.</Source>
      <Dest>两人之间的世仇却导致了这么多无意义的死亡。我保证会让这些灵魂前往艾瑟瑞斯的。愿九圣灵在天上祝福他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's no surprise that the wolf's blood corrupts the spirit.  But no matter how pernicious the disease, I believe the stars will divine a cure.</Source>
      <Dest>那只狼的血会污染灵魂并不奇怪。但不管这种病有多恶劣，我都相信星辰会赐予救赎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It would be wise to tell Stalleo of the bodies that were found in the tunnels.  A false hope will only create more hardship in the end.</Source>
      <Dest>明智的做法是告诉斯塔莱奥我们在隧道找到了一些尸体。不会有结果的希望只会带来更大的伤害。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This roof is open for a reason.  There are stories of ancient forges that draw strength from the moons, just as we draw magic from the stars.</Source>
      <Dest>把屋顶打开也是因为这个原因。一些古老的故事说，月亮是力量之源，正如我们从星辰中汲取魔力一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're now a full fledged member of the Companions, I see.  Careful that you do it for honor, and not for coin or blood, as it appears the others do.</Source>
      <Dest>我懂了，你现在是一个成熟的战友团成员了。请为你的荣誉而战吧，别被钱或杀戮的快感左右。就像其他人做的那样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It appears Grosta was mistaken about her husband. She still may think him foolhardy. I say he was brave.  I commit his soul to Aetherius.</Source>
      <Dest>看来格罗斯塔误会了她的丈夫，至今以为他只是莽撞而已。而我看他是真的很英勇。愿他的灵魂安息于艾瑟瑞斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Njada is an impressive brawler. She has the Warrior's spirit and the Atronach's strength. Yet if I were a betting man, I wouldn't dismiss my chances.</Source>
      <Dest>Njada is an impressive brawler. She has the Warrior's spirit and the Atronach's strength. Yet if I were a betting man, I wouldn't dismiss my chances.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Candles, soul gems, and the Firmament.  It seems these conjurers are asking the stars for aid.  The presence of the Atronach is strong here.</Source>
      <Dest>Candles, soul gems, and the Firmament.  It seems these conjurers are asking the stars for aid.  The presence of the Atronach is strong here.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So that's why Savos was reluctant to discuss Labyrinthian.  I won't judge him. We all have our secrets, and our regrets.</Source>
      <Dest>所以这就是萨沃斯不情愿讨论迷之城的原因。我不能指责他。我们都有自己的秘密，和自己的遗憾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Staff of Magnus!  Incredible!  What you hold in your hands, my lady, is a piece of the stars themselves.</Source>
      <Dest>The Staff of Magnus!  Incredible!  What you hold in your hands, my lady, is a piece of the stars themselves.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Staff of Magnus!  Incredible!  What you hold in your hands, my boy, is a piece of the stars themselves.</Source>
      <Dest>玛格努斯之权杖！不可思议！你以为你手中拿的是什么，我的孩子，这可是星辰本身的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Windhelm. I once brawled a Nord woman here with a chin like an anvil. I wonder if she's still at Candlehearth Hall.</Source>
      <Dest>风舵城。我曾经在那把一个诺德女人用铁链绑的像铁毡一样。我想知道她现在是否还在烛炉堂旅店。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The stars are with us. The Tower will open the door, the Steed will guide us forward, and the Warrior will show Ancano the depth of his arrogance.</Source>
      <Dest>群星与我们同在，高塔将开启大门，骏马将指引我们前行。武士之星将要让安卡诺体会到他无边傲慢的代价。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These are no ordinary draugr wights.  Their swords will drain your very life force.</Source>
      <Dest>这些可不是普通的尸鬼。他们的剑会吸你的血。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems this Elf tried to escape, or managed to kill herself before becoming enthralled.  The vampires had no choice but to drain her blood.</Source>
      <Dest>看到这个精灵试图逃跑，还想在堕落前自杀。吸血鬼不得不吸干她的血液。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The city is safe, but this is far from over.  We should hurry back to Mirabelle, she may be in danger.</Source>
      <Dest>城市很安全，但一切都还没结束。我们要赶紧回到米拉贝勒身边，她可能有危险了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Labyrinthian.  They say Shalidor built it as a test to see if one was worthy of ascending to Arch-Mage.  What will that mean for you if you pass it?</Source>
      <Dest>谜之城，有人说沙利多建造它只是为了考验一个人是否可以成为首席法师。如果你通过了，这将意味着什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am pleased to learn Tolfdir is emphasizing the value of defensive spells.   May the Apprentice guide you in your training.</Source>
      <Dest>我很高兴知道托夫迪尔认同防御型法术的价值。愿学徒之石指导你的训练。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There must be hundreds of coffins up there.  I've never seen anything like it.  They almost look like teeth.  </Source>
      <Dest>那儿放了有差不多几百口棺材。我从没见过那样的景观。排列得像牙齿一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That orb is emitting some sort of magical resonance.  It's an amazing discovery, my lady.  I just wish my father were alive to see it.</Source>
      <Dest>那个球体正在发出某种魔法般的共振。我的女士，这个发现太惊人了。我真希望我的父亲还在世能够亲眼见一见这神奇的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That orb is emitting some sort of magical resonance.  It's an amazing discovery, my boy. I just wish my father were alive to see it.</Source>
      <Dest>那个球体正在发出某种魔法般的共振。我的孩子，这个发现太惊人了。我真希望我的父亲还在世能够亲眼见一见这神奇的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Orthorn reminds me of a young man who was similarly torn between two paths. But in the end, youth will gravitate toward excitement and danger.</Source>
      <Dest>奥松恩让我想起了一个同样在两条道路上徘徊不定的年轻人。但最终，年轻人会被那条充满刺激与危险的道路吸引。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vampires are like the Serpent.  Cursed.  Unpredictable.  While the Mage is its enemy, so are the Warrior and the Thief.  We should dispose of them.</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼就像蛇。讨厌。诡异。法师与他们为敌，就像战士和盗贼一样。我们要部署好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Serpent has taken the Caller's life, and now she belongs to the stars.  I commit her soul to Aetherius.</Source>
      <Dest>蛇夺走了呼唤者的性命，现在她属于星空。我把她的灵魂囚禁在艾瑟瑞斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Augur of Dunlain.  I think my father spoke of him as a wizard of some renown.  Curious as to why he doesn't have a larger presence here.</Source>
      <Dest>预言师杜兰。我父亲曾说过他是个有些名望的法师。他在这里居然没什么名气，这点挺让我吃惊的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Eye of Magnus.  The Staff of Magnus. Can such artifacts truly exist on this plane?  Is Magnus not the sun and stars?</Source>
      <Dest>玛格努斯之眼。玛格努斯之杖。这俩上古神器真正存在于世吗？玛格努斯难道不是太阳和星辰吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Synod and the College of Whispers care only for politics and power. We must retrieve the staff before they do.</Source>
      <Dest>希诺和低语学院只关心政治和权力。我们必须在他们之前找到法杖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This seems to be a Dwarven lecture hall of some sort.  Fascinating.</Source>
      <Dest>这似乎是某处矮人演讲厅，真令人惊叹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This store should have plenty of magical supplies given its proximity to the college.  What she calls "Oddments," others may call resources.</Source>
      <Dest>既然这家店如此靠近学院，那一定有卖一大堆魔法用品。她把那些魔法用品称为"零碎"，而其他人则称之为资源。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By Aetherius, a dragon priest!  Anska, when you called Vokun "some old priest" I didn't realize the implications.  </Source>
      <Dest>艾瑟瑞斯在上，一个龙祭司！安斯卡，你把沃昆叫做“某个老祭司”的时候我还没意识到其中的含义。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If and when we visit the College, I would like to visit the Arcanaeum.  In the meantime, I might borrow Nelacar's books.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我去拜访这所学院, 我想去参观秘藏馆，也可能会去借阅耐拉卡的书。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Iron mines like these are the backbone of a society.  Everything from iron shields to cast iron pots can be made cheaply and effectively.</Source>
      <Dest>铁矿就像是这个社会的支柱。上至盾牌，下到罐子，都能用铁制作。既廉价，又实用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My lady Anska, you are quite perceptive.  That is no ordinary gem.  Or rather that is no ordinary pedestal it sits upon.</Source>
      <Dest>我的安斯卡女士，你眼光敏锐。这可不是普通的宝石。且承载它的祭台也是不同寻常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Anska, we are happy to assist you.  Family history is important.  May the Tower guide us through this ruin.</Source>
      <Dest>安斯卡，我们很乐意协助你。家族传承是很重要的。愿那座塔引领我们越过那座遗迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Serpent is strong in Erandur.  This could very well be a trap, but it's worth investigating nonetheless.</Source>
      <Dest>依兰杜尔那家伙没安什么好心。尽管这更像是个陷阱，但还是有一探究竟的价值的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Temple of the Divines is truly a work of art.  And why not.  For every archway, every mosaic of stone was inspired by the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>圣灵的神殿是一个真正的艺术品。为什么不呢。它的每一道拱门，镌刻在石头上的每一个花纹，都是源于众神的启迪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fort Hraggstad.  The view from atop here is spectacular.  You can see the Sea of Ghosts stretch on from here to eternity.</Source>
      <Dest>哈格斯塔德堡垒。在这上面的景色真是壮观。你可以看见幽灵之海向四周延展，从这里，到天边。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) That robe fits you well.  It seems you are just as comfortable at court as you are on the battlefield.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)这法袍很适合你。看样子你在法庭上就像在战场一般，挺悠哉的嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is Madena still the court wizard here?  She fought in the Great War.  Strange how so many of us share the same experiences, without ever having met.</Source>
      <Dest>Is Madena still the court wizard here?  She fought in the Great War.  Strange how so many of us share the same experiences, without ever having met.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When interrogating a suspect, they say the Oculatus can see into a man's soul.  Yet few know the "inward sight" can also apply to oneself.</Source>
      <Dest>审问嫌犯的时候，他们宣称锐眼鹰能看穿人的灵魂。但没有几个人会想到，这种“洞察能力”迟早也会被用到自己身上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I worry about this young apprentice. If she can't even pronounce her master's name correctly, she won't do well with customers.</Source>
      <Dest>我有点儿担心这个年轻的学徒。如果她甚至不能正确地念出她家大师的名字，那估计她做的也不能让客人有多满意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That was an intense fight.  Jarl Idgrod said Movarth haunted this hold for centuries.  But now, he is just another ghost story.</Source>
      <Dest>这是一场激烈的战斗。领主伊格罗德说莫瓦斯在这片土地上为非作歹好几个世纪了。但是现在，它也不过是一个鬼故事而已了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Judging by his notes, it's hard to tell whether this Dunmer was bewitched by the amulet, or his own greed.</Source>
      <Dest>从他的笔记来看，很难判断这个丹莫到底是被那个护身符迷惑了，还是被他自己的贪欲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've heard apothecaries say that places that are cool and damp are ideal for alchemy ingredients.  But this flooding probably forced them to move.</Source>
      <Dest>我听药剂师们说，那些凉爽和潮湿的地方都有着理想的炼金材料。但这洪水可能会迫使它们移去别处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Rest easy, my lady.  Your death has been avenged, and your soul can be at peace.</Source>
      <Dest>放心吧，我的女士，你的仇已经报了，你的灵魂可以安息了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Towers like this used to be important defensive outposts.  Now it serves as a home to derelicts.</Source>
      <Dest>像这样的塔楼在过去曾经是重要的防御前哨。而现在它却仅仅只是充当那些流浪汉的家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The library they've gathered here is impressive.  I'm tempted to stay and lose myself in a book.</Source>
      <Dest>他们这图书馆建得太棒了。我真忍不住要留下来好好读书了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bereft of his master, this dog carries on. He's a survivor. Loyal, but fearless.  I would be honored to have it in our company.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管失去了主人，但这条狗却没有放弃。它是个幸存者。忠诚，而无所畏惧。我很荣幸让它成为我们的伙伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems unnatural for this Hroggar to kill his wife and daughter in the name of lust.  But perhaps I am speaking from my own perspective.</Source>
      <Dest>要说赫鲁加为了淫欲把他老婆和女儿杀了有点不合常理啊...不过也可能是我没能站在他的角度看这个问题吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's probably a coincidence, but that book by the beds there...is that "The Exodus?"  A haunting tale, but I imagine what these men faced was worse.</Source>
      <Dest>也许是个巧合，但那本放在床边的书...是”远行记“吗？那是个令人难忘的故事，但我想这些人面对的是些更糟糕的事儿。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With this stone, I could cast more healing spells, but I would take more damage. Thus it is ideal for the apprentice, who supports from the rear.</Source>
      <Dest>通过这个立石，我可以施展更多的治疗法术，但同时我也会承受更多的伤害。因此，对那些从后方支援的学徒来说，这相当完美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Morthal has been home to many skilled apothecaries. The diverse climates provide a wealth of plant life.  We should see if Lami has any good recipes.</Source>
      <Dest>墨索尔城对于很多技术精湛的药剂师来说就是家园，多变的气候带来了丰富的物种。我们得看看拉米会不会有什么好配方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't be afraid to experiment. The Song of the Alchemist teaches us that in alchemy and in life, many discoveries come by accident.</Source>
      <Dest>不要害怕尝试。炼金术师之歌告诉我们，炼金术与生活一样，有很多的发现来源于偶然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I overheard a boy who lives here had a mother who left to join the Stormcloaks.  It's sad.  Ulfric's war is now dividing individual families.</Source>
      <Dest>I overheard a boy who lives here had a mother who left to join the Stormcloaks.  It's sad.  Ulfric's war is now dividing individual families.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So Laelette...the woman who joined the Stormcloaks...she was actually a vampire.  But I still stand by what I said about Ulfric.</Source>
      <Dest>所以拉莱特...那个加入风暴斗篷的女人...她其实是个吸血鬼。但我仍然坚持我对于乌佛瑞克的看法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Movarth...Where have I heard that name before?  No, it couldn't be.  Do you by chance have a copy of "Immortal Blood?"</Source>
      <Dest>莫瓦斯...我好像以前在哪听过这个名字？不，不可能啊。你有没有偶然获得过一份“不朽之血”的副本？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These Legionnaires should have known better than to position themselves here.  They could get flanked. Shot at from above. These men were green.</Source>
      <Dest>这些军团士兵站位应该更精确一些才对的。他们可能遭到了侧翼攻击或者遭到了上方的射击。这些人还只是菜鸟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A tree. Now this isn't something I expected to see here. For all their machines and monuments, perhaps even the Dwemer value the Gods' craftsmanship.</Source>
      <Dest>一棵树。这不是我现在所希望看到的。对于他们所有的机器和古迹，可能甚至连锻莫都将其视为神的工艺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Interesting.  I have wandered with many a marksman, but you handle that bow with an aplomb that I have yet to see in another.</Source>
      <Dest>有点意思。我认识几个所谓的神射手，可我从未见过有一个人操弓时如你一般泰然自若.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Watching you use stealth reminds me of the story of Sheogorath and Hircine, and how the nimble bird felled a Daedroth.</Source>
      <Dest>看着你使用潜行让我想起了谢尔格拉斯和海尔辛的故事，还有敏捷的飞鸟是如何掉入鳄鱼嘴里的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Even as a Legionnaire, I was never comfortable using two-handed weapons like yours.  They require too much aggression.</Source>
      <Dest>就算是当兵的时候，我也从没有像你那样自如地使用双手武器。那玩意太需要蛮劲了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Our reward?  I shudder to think what kind of reward a Daedric Lord has to offer us, but I fear it will only get worse if we defy him.</Source>
      <Dest>我们的奖励？我一想到魔族领主能给我们提供什么样的奖励就不寒而栗。但我担心无视他的话会变得更糟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The blood of a Daedra is believed to sharpen a blade when cooled. But retrieving it is often not worth the cost. The Jarl's request is short-sighted.</Source>
      <Dest>据说用魔族的血来做冷却可以让兵器锋利无比。可要弄到那玩意的本钱往往是得不偿失。那领主想得太简单了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nimhe the Spider.  I almost feel sorry for it.  Funny how a name changes the way you look at something, even a foul beast like this.</Source>
      <Dest>蜘蛛尼姆赫。我几乎会为它感到遗憾。即使是这样一个怪物，它的名字也能改变你看待事物的方式，多么有趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While I despise the Thalmor, we must abide by the treaty we signed.  If our words lack conviction, than we are no better than thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然我瞧不起梭默，但是我们必须遵守我们签下的协定。如果我们说话不算话，那么我们自己也不比那些小偷好多少。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In Cidhna Mine, a life sentence is a death sentence.  For everyone, it seems, but you.  Good to see you made it out.</Source>
      <Dest>在希讷矿坑，无期徒刑与死刑无异。对每个人来说都是这样，除了你。很高兴看到你活着出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Another dead researcher.  This should have been a sign to turn back, but it seems his friends pressed on.</Source>
      <Dest>另一个死去的研究员。他们看来本该是要折返，但看上去他的朋友们要继续前行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Orc bard here.  His poetry is...well...it's offensive.  It makes me want to cast a healing spell on my ears.</Source>
      <Dest>这儿的兽人吟游诗人。他的诗很...额...不和谐。我都想对自己耳朵丢一个治愈魔法了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To think, an idle Dwarf once sat on this bench, and drank from this very cup.  It's like watching someone's long forgotten memory.</Source>
      <Dest>想想看，一个百无聊赖的矮人曾坐在这把长凳上，用这个杯子喝酒。就像是在看着某人已被遗忘的久远记忆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Madanach must be a charismatic leader to inspire such fierce loyalty.  Nepos and his servants died valiantly.</Source>
      <Dest>迈德纳奇一定得是个非常有魅力的领导者，才能激发这种狂热的忠诚。内普斯和他的仆人死得英勇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Miners, farmers, children.  It matters not your age, your job, your gender or your creed.  Too many people are being forced to become soldiers.</Source>
      <Dest>矿工，农民，孩子。这与你的年龄，职业，性别或是信念无关。被迫成为士兵的人太多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Amanda Alleia was right.  Markarth is a vertical city.  There's a reason the drunks stick to the ground floor. </Source>
      <Dest>阿曼达·艾丽雅说得真对。马卡斯是座垂直的城市。难怪那些醉鬼只敢逗留在一层。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We've cleared Kolskeggr Mine, but I fear Pavo and Gat won't be able to hold it on their own.  At some point, the Jarl must listen to their pleas.</Source>
      <Dest>我们已经清理了科斯凯格矿场，但我担心仅靠帕沃和噶特两个人是守不住的。领主最好还是在适当的时候去听听他们的请求。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This was not a random attack. While I doubt this Margret is Princess Talara reborn, she is certainly more than a commoner.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是一次偶然的袭击 。而我怀疑玛格丽特是塔拉让公主复生，她显然不只是个平民。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It comes as little surprise that the trail leads here, to The Treasury House.  Yet we should not levy any accusations until we know the whole truth.</Source>
      <Dest>线索指向了珍宝屋 ，这一点儿不让人惊讶。但在知道全部真相前，我们不能提出任何指控。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mulush is a hard foreman, but it's a thin line between building character and crushing one's spirit. Even I know naught the difference.</Source>
      <Dest>暮鲁什是个努力的领班，不过塑造个性和打压一个人的精神之间只有一线之隔。即使是我也对两者之间的区别一窍不通。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bothela claims she can craft a love potion.  (Laughs) A "young love" potion perhaps, with the effects just as fleeting.</Source>
      <Dest>波塞拉说她能够做出爱情药剂来呢。（笑声）说不定就是那种"年轻"的爱情药剂，那效果连三秒都维持不了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Legends speak of Bannermist Tower, whose flag never fell, but stood high above the mist, welcoming the weary traveler home to Falkreath Hold.</Source>
      <Dest>军团如是说：在迷雾中屹立不倒旌旗不落的旗霭塔欢迎疲惫的旅者来到佛克瑞斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alchemists and hunters often die like this, without a burial.  I commit this soul to Aetherius, Blessings of the Nine upon him.</Source>
      <Dest>炼金术师和猎人经常就这样死了，曝尸荒野或街头。愿这灵魂长眠于艾瑟瑞斯，九圣灵保佑他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alchemists and hunters often die like this, without a burial.  I commit this soul to Aetherius.</Source>
      <Dest>炼金术师和猎人经常就这样死了，曝尸荒野或街头。愿这灵魂长眠于艾瑟瑞斯，九圣灵保佑他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know I seem like the unadventurous type, but I love a good brawl.  Although I'll think twice before challenging Uthgerd again.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道我看上去不是那么能打，但我很喜欢打架。尽管挑战阿斯盖德之前我总得做上很久的心理斗争。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Last Scabbard of Akrash is a tale of love, intrigue, and mystery.  Let's hope for Ghorza's sake the boy bothers to read the parts about smithing.</Source>
      <Dest>阿卡托什的最后诗歌是一个爱情的传说，阴谋，和秘密。但愿裹扎让那对男孩兄弟去读的是有关锻冶的那一节。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fort shrines like these are common. Whether the occupants be Imperial, Stormcloak, or Forsworn, on the eve of war, all men become priests.</Source>
      <Dest>这样的堡垒圣祠很常见的。不管占领者是帝国军队，风暴斗篷，还是弃誓者，在战争前夕全员都会变成教士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There are two places where soldiers bond.  On the field of battle, and here in the dining hall.</Source>
      <Dest>士兵们在两个地方特别团结。一是战场，另一个，就是这家餐厅。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mogen, son of Molag told a story of sobbing woman who haunted a similar cabin.  We can only hope that Anise does not turn into a wight.</Source>
      <Dest>Mogen, son of Molag told a story of sobbing woman who haunted a similar cabin.  We can only hope that Anise does not turn into a wight.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This cemetery...I apologize, but if you'll allow me a moment, I wish to speak with you.</Source>
      <Dest>这座坟墓...我很抱歉，但可以耽搁你一会儿吗，我想跟你说点儿话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I look at the wounded I...I apologize, but if you'll allow me a moment, I wish to speak with you.</Source>
      <Dest>当我去看那个伤者时...我...很抱歉，请给我点时间，我想跟你谈谈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This library is so grand.  Never in all my years...If you'll allow me a moment, I wish to speak with you.</Source>
      <Dest>这图书馆实在是高端大气。我这辈子还没...如果你方便的话，我有些话想和你说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am sorry about Kodlak. The worst tragedies comes without warning, when our emotions are unguarded.  Then, not even time can cure the pain.</Source>
      <Dest>克拉科的事情我表示遗憾。最令人悲伤的噩耗总来得那么猝不及防，连一点心理准备的时间都不给我们。现在，只有时间才能治愈伤痛了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such senseless violence.  These are not warriors.  These are farmers, shopkeepers, and priests.  What do the Thalmor have to gain with their deaths?</Source>
      <Dest>如此愚蠢的暴力行为。在这的都不是战士，而是农民，店主和牧师。梭默能从他们的死亡中获得什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>War can help the local towns by bringing work to the villages.  The inn is full, the mill is prospering, and even a bard has seen fit to roost here.</Source>
      <Dest>战争确实能帮助各大城镇向周遭村落提供工作机会。看看那人满为患的旅舍，人欢马叫的磨坊，就连平时根本不会过来的吟游诗人们也有不少。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This Elf died of avarice.  Greed is a pernicious disease, more deadly than vampirism, with symptoms that are far more difficult to detect.</Source>
      <Dest>这个精灵因贪婪而死。贪婪是种非常致命的疾病，而且难以根除。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's no surprise we got the jump on them.  Bandits make for poor sentries.  Their eyes are trained to look toward treasure, not danger.</Source>
      <Dest>我们抢在他们之前行动并不奇怪。强盗是可怜的哨兵的天敌。他们的眼睛受过辨别宝藏的训练，而不是危险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>During the war, we used to dress up dummies.  Although instead of a bucket helm and a wooden sword, we'd have straw shooting out of his hands.</Source>
      <Dest>During the war, we used to dress up dummies.  Although instead of a bucket helm and a wooden sword, we'd have straw shooting out of his hands.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Ritual Stone.  It will grant you the power to raise the dead to fight for your cause.</Source>
      <Dest>仪式之石。它会赐予你让死者复生并为你而战的力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Ritual Stone is near Graywinter Watch.  If this conjuration mage Olivia speaks of uses corpses, we can use that to our advantage.</Source>
      <Dest>仪式之石就在灰冬望台附近，要是这位召唤师奥利维亚提起使用尸体的事，就正中咱们下怀了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>By the Lord Stone...You're Dragonborn.  It's said the blood of the kings flows through you.  </Source>
      <Dest>君主守护石...你是龙裔。这么说来，你体内流淌着历代君主的血液。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Congratulations are in order.  Balgruuf has made you a Thane.  Which means you'll be rubbing elbows with those in the Cloud District from now on.</Source>
      <Dest>就等着给你道贺呢。巴尔古夫封你做了男爵。这意味着你现在能跟那些在云霄区的上流阶层交往了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tamriel has a very rich tradition of mingling war and song.  The Skalds of Skyrim, the Sword-Singing Ansei of Hammerfell...this bard is no exception.</Source>
      <Dest>Tamriel has a very rich tradition of mingling war and song.  The Skalds of Skyrim, the Sword-Singing Ansei of Hammerfell...this bard is no exception.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This poor soul was trapped in this bird cage to sharpen the wolves' scent.  Even if I could repair his wounds, I could not repair his mind.</Source>
      <Dest>这个可怜的灵魂被囚禁在这个鸟笼里来使得狼群的嗅觉保持敏锐。即使我可以修复他的伤口，也无法修复他心灵上的创伤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This man works Chillfurrow farm by his lonesome. At times I wonder if we healers should be here, to mend those whose labor is essential.</Source>
      <Dest>这个人独自在寒畦农场干活。有时候我在想，我们这些医者是不是也该驻扎在那儿，让那些劳动力保持健康是至关重要的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These dense forests can be quite harrowing.  It is good to find a warm fire, and warm company.</Source>
      <Dest>These dense forests can be quite harrowing.  It is good to find a warm fire, and warm company.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What ancient darkness lurks in this cave?  This column of light brims with magic, but the bodies are evidence of its misuse.</Source>
      <Dest>这个洞里潜藏着什么样的远古黑暗？这个光柱充满着魔法，但从这些尸体来看它明显不应该被用在这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is no ordinary fire.  Mages did this.</Source>
      <Dest>这不是普通的火。这是法师放的火。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>With these forts, there is always an entrance for archers to gain access to the roof.  It is possible these Orc hunters are unaware of it.</Source>
      <Dest>这些要塞里总会给弓箭手们留出一条通到屋顶的入口。也有可能这些兽人猎人们并没有注意到这一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems our friend Ghunzul was a conspiracy theorist, based on his reading habits.  And judging by his station, a strong leader as well.</Source>
      <Dest>从他的阅读习惯看来，貌似我们这位甘泽尔朋友是个阴谋论家。当然从他的地位来看，也是个强势的领导者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Careful.  Halldir is no ordinary mage.  It seems he channels a trine of power from the three corpses who lay below.</Source>
      <Dest>小心点，霍迪尔可不是那种普通法师。看起来他似乎将躺在下面的那三具尸体的力量给聚在了一起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Keepers of the Razor were a militia group, working to banish the world of Mythic Dawn artifacts.  I wonder if this one's motives are as pure.</Source>
      <Dest>剃刀的守护者是一个志愿组织，致力于消灭神话黎明教团的遗物。我怀疑这家伙的目的并不是那么单纯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Jarl must have abandoned this mine after the cave-in.  A pity, as the camp is well preserved.</Source>
      <Dest>领主肯定在塌方之后就把这个矿井废弃了。真遗憾，作为一个营地来说，这里的隐蔽性很不错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bandits.  Let us send these souls to the Dreamsleeve.</Source>
      <Dest>强盗。让我们把这几个灵魂送进梦袖吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bandits find honor to be a hindrance.  Let us show them how they have erred.</Source>
      <Dest>强盗土匪们总碍手碍脚，还以此为荣，让我们告诉他们这是个多么离谱的错误。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The locals often talk of Camilla the maiden fair. A beautiful woman can start wars great and small, but only because her fickle heart wages the same.</Source>
      <Dest>这里的人们经常谈论凯米拉这个小美人。一个漂亮的女人总能引发一场或大或小的战争，这是因为她那善变的心中也在经历着战争。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The glow from the Sleeping Tree is the color of magelight, and it is little wonder they say it fell from the stars.</Source>
      <Dest>沉睡之树发出的光芒像极了魔光术的颜色，也难怪他们说它是从星辰中坠落的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People depend on the iron from this mine.  These bandits must suffer for crimes beyond the murder of the miners.</Source>
      <Dest>人们都以矿场中的铁矿为生，这些强盗们对此必须承担比杀死矿工的凶手还要沉重的罪行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Watch your step.  The passage is narrow, the road slippery, and the bones a terrible portent indeed.</Source>
      <Dest>留神脚下，通道很窄，路又很滑，而这些骨头着实是个可怕的预兆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The charm of a small town never ages.  The poet Cassius once wrote that "Small towns are the heart, where modesty and nostalgia are defined."</Source>
      <Dest>那座小镇的魅力永不老化。诗人卡修斯曾经写道：“小镇是间心房，里面充满了实实在在的质朴和怀旧 。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hjaalmarch.  Here is where the ashen warband, the Askelde Men, made their stand.  Such history.</Source>
      <Dest>希雅陲领。这就是苍灰战团——那些阿斯克德人，所屹立的地方。历史就是那样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that Adonato Leotelli?  I'm a great admirer of his work. Many know of "Olaf and the Dragon," but "Ghosts in the Storm" is a step above.</Source>
      <Dest>阿多纳托·莱奥特利？我特别喜欢他的作品。许多人都知道“奥拉夫与龙，”但是“风暴中的幽灵”比它更胜一筹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not to be rude, but this restoration master does protest too much. When I prattled on, my father warned me that "close wounds" works on the mouth.</Source>
      <Dest>无意冒犯，但这复归的主人要求的实在是太多。当我说闲话的时候，我父亲总会警告我说“闭合伤口”法术也能合上嘴巴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Adonato Leotelli describes the Falmer as "snow-devils with pallid skin and lifeless black eyes, like something out of a nightmare."  He is right.</Source>
      <Dest>阿多纳托·莱奥特利对雪精灵的描述是"一身苍白色的皮肤，带着一双死鱼眼的雪白色恶魔，就如梦魇一般。"他说得真形象生动呐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You remind me of Topal the pilot, drifting to new worlds while in search of an old one.</Source>
      <Dest>你让我想起了领航员托帕尔，一个为了寻找一个旧世界而在各个新的世界里四处漂泊的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thieves insist they are honorable, because they avoid violence. Violence can take many forms. One can starve to death when they are stripped of coin.</Source>
      <Dest>小偷们坚称自己是高尚的，因为他们不使用暴力。但暴力有着各种不同的表现形式。一个遭了偷窃而身无分文的人很有可能被活活饿死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Annotated Anuad.  I have a copy I could lend Esbern, if he really can't do without it.</Source>
      <Dest>《阿努注解》。如果没有它，伊斯本就做不来的话，那我这儿还有本副本可以借给他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have seen men break under the pressure of confinement. Hopefully, Esbern read enough books to keep his mind lucid.</Source>
      <Dest>我见过很多人在被幽闭的压力下坏掉了。希望伊斯本读的书够多，可以让自己的神智依然清醒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You made it.  When I was a soldier, I despised subterfuge.  Now, I value its ability to end wars without bloodshed.</Source>
      <Dest>你做到了。当我还是个士兵时，我鄙视那些花招。而现在，我敬佩这种兵不血刃的能力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Valenwood aligned with the Thalmor during the Great War.  But as Malborn shows, you can't judge a person by the actions of his leaders.</Source>
      <Dest>威木省在世界大战期间和梭默结为盟友。就如同马博尔所展示那样，你不能通过司其领导之职而做出的行为来评判一个人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come on, is that all you've got?</Source>
      <Dest>来呀来呀，就这点本事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh!</Source>
      <Dest>呃！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh...ugh.</Source>
      <Dest>呃...呃.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Agh!</Source>
      <Dest>啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do your worst!</Source>
      <Dest>你这样还不够看！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your efforts are in vain!</Source>
      <Dest>你所有的努力都将白费！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do not think you've bested me!</Source>
      <Dest>别以为你能赢我！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Agh!  Bastard!</Source>
      <Dest>啊！混蛋！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Agh! Enough! This ends now!</Source>
      <Dest>噢！够了！一切都完了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh, you fiend!</Source>
      <Dest>呃啊，你这恶魔！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is that the best you can do?</Source>
      <Dest>这就是你的极限了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hyargh!</Source>
      <Dest>嘿呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hyargh!</Source>
      <Dest>嘿呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You picked the wrong dinner, animal!</Source>
      <Dest>你选错了晚餐，畜生！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Go back to where you came from, dragon!</Source>
      <Dest>巨龙，滚回你来的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some legend you are!</Source>
      <Dest>你只不过会夸夸其谈而已！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That won't heal easy!</Source>
      <Dest>这可不怎么好治！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do not worry, your pain will soon end!</Source>
      <Dest>别担心，痛苦很快结束！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh...</Source>
      <Dest>呃……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This isn't the end...</Source>
      <Dest>还没结束...</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We're routed!  Flee if you can!</Source>
      <Dest>我们被击溃了！各自想办法逃走！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You need to do better than that!</Source>
      <Dest>你需要做得更好！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That all you've got?</Source>
      <Dest>你就这么点能耐？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can take you!</Source>
      <Dest>你完了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Think you can take me, Orc?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得你能搞定我么，兽人？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're going to look good mounted on my wall!</Source>
      <Dest>你的脑袋会成为我的收藏品！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll cut right through your scales, monster!</Source>
      <Dest>我能连你的鳞片都一刀切了，怪物！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Say hello to Ysmir for me, Nord!</Source>
      <Dest>帮我向伊斯米尔问个好，诺德佬！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hircine will not claim this soul!</Source>
      <Dest>赫希恩将不会想要这个灵魂的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For the Companions!</Source>
      <Dest>为了同伴！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For Kodlak!</Source>
      <Dest>为了克拉科！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're outmatched!</Source>
      <Dest>你输了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You won't get away!</Source>
      <Dest>你跑不了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't stand a chance!</Source>
      <Dest>你一点机会也没！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You will not touch her!</Source>
      <Dest>不会让你伤到她的！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I commit you to Aetherius!</Source>
      <Dest>你还是滚去艾瑟瑞斯吧！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now you know I'm not some lowly priest!</Source>
      <Dest>Now you know I'm not some lowly priest!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your wounds are fatal, dragon!</Source>
      <Dest>你的伤口好恐怖啊，死龙！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You do not belong on this plane, ghost!</Source>
      <Dest>你不属于这个地方，幽灵！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You will not win this!</Source>
      <Dest>你赢不了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Orcs are known for their smiths and their hunters, but their chiefs are some of the best brawlers in Tamriel.</Source>
      <Dest>兽人都是因出色的铁匠和猎人而闻名，但兽人酋长们却是泰姆瑞尔大陆上最好的战士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ainethach may have no choice but to sell. This town needs guards, but the ones who hired the sellswords will likely make sure they never come.</Source>
      <Dest>艾尼塔克恐怕除了卖掉之外没别的选择了，这城镇需要守卫，但是那个出钱雇佣兵的家伙们很快就会希望佣兵再也不要来这个地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Someone told me the stablemaster here has fists like boulders. But it turns out the name Hofgrir Horse-Crusher has more to do with his backside.</Source>
      <Dest>Someone told me the stablemaster here has fists like boulders. But it turns out the name Hofgrir Horse-Crusher has more to do with his backside.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People say Benor has a brawler's face. Sometimes I'm not sure if that's a compliment or an insult.</Source>
      <Dest>人们说本诺长了一张嘲讽脸。有时我都搞不清这究竟算是恭维呢还是一种侮辱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Orphan's Tear. I don't know if the name is for the coast or the shipwreck, but I know it's far too poetic for a bandit camp.</Source>
      <Dest>孤儿之泪。我不知道这是否是那个海岸或是沉船的名字，但我觉得这作为一个强盗营地的名字，有些过于诗意了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Potema, the Wolf Queen. Not even the dragons would be as devastating for this land as her return. We should return to Falk with the news.</Source>
      <Dest>波特玛，狼心女王。就连龙族带给这个大陆的灾难也比不上她的回归。我们应该把这个消息告诉佛可。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>These glowing mushrooms are like underground stars. Yet we are a long way from Aetherius.</Source>
      <Dest>这些荧光的蘑菇很像地底下的星辰。不过我们离到光界还很远呐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Geirmund's Hall. The former Arch-Mage is buried here, a wizard who lived in the days of the High King Harald.</Source>
      <Dest>格尔蒙德大厅。前任首席法师就被埋葬在这儿，那是名生活在至高王哈拉德统治时期的巫师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Bears often use these animal dens to hibernate through the long winters. In Skyrim, where winter is ever present, that doesn't seem to be the case.</Source>
      <Dest>熊类通常会在这些兽穴里冬眠。但在全年如冬的天际省，情况好像就并非如此了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This looks to be study hall. If the puzzle proves difficult, we should scour the desks for clues.</Source>
      <Dest>这看起来是个自修室。如果谜题很困难，那我们就应该在书桌上找找线索。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just as their masters are blind, so too are the Falmer servants living in this dark, shadowy abyss. They look to the sky, and see only a ceiling.</Source>
      <Dest>正如他们的主人是个瞎子一样，生活在幽暗深渊的黑暗之处的雪精灵也是如此。他们仰望天空，能看到的却只有天花板。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This laboratory is well organized. The owner was not the type to go out unprepared, yet even then, it was not enough. I commit his soul to Aetherius.</Source>
      <Dest>This laboratory is well organized. The owner was not the type to go out unprepared, yet even then, it was not enough. I commit his soul to Aetherius.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Cabins sliding off the mountain, rubble and debris everywhere...this excavation doesn't appear to be very professional.</Source>
      <Dest>从山上滑下来的木屋，到处都是的瓦砾和废墟...这次发掘看起来不怎么专业啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True or not, these rumors surrounding Wolfskull Cave are just another consequence of Ulfric's rebellion. There aren't enough men to spare.</Source>
      <Dest>True or not, these rumors surrounding Wolfskull Cave are just another consequence of Ulfric's rebellion. There aren't enough men to spare.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Beware the Daedric Princes, even ones like Meridia who champion justice. Her light mimics the stars, but it shines darkly.</Source>
      <Dest>尽管有像梅芮狄娅那样自称拥护正义的魔神存在，但还是提防着点那些魔神。她的光芒看似与星辰一样，但实际上却照耀着黑暗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>King, warrior, and the Dragonborn.  In the days of Tiber Septim, these symbols spoke of the same person.</Source>
      <Dest>King, warrior, and the Dragonborn.  In the days of Tiber Septim, these symbols spoke of the same person.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The structural integrity of the temple is seems to be intact.  Although those holes in the roof probably won't help with the cold.</Source>
      <Dest>神殿的结构依旧十分完整。尽管那满是窟窿的屋顶似乎抵御不了寒风。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Greybeards are a secretive group. It is a wise course, when knowledge in the wrong hands can prove catastrophic.</Source>
      <Dest>The Greybeards are a secretive group. It is a wise course, when knowledge in the wrong hands can prove catastrophic.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just as these great ruins stand in the shadow of Winterhold, so does the past get obstructed by our view of the present.</Source>
      <Dest>Just as these great ruins stand in the shadow of Winterhold, so does the past get obstructed by our view of the present.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A book on the Dragonguard...written by hand.  A priceless artifact, and Esbern, well...Maybe it's better you hold on to it.</Source>
      <Dest>关于神龙卫的一本书...手写稿。无价的艺术品，以及伊斯本，好吧...说不定还是你拿着它比较好一点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Delphine, you would not have brought us here alone if this were a trap.  I do not speak for the Dragonborn, but I trust you.  For now.</Source>
      <Dest>戴尔菲娜，如果这是个陷阱的话，你就不会独自带着我们到这儿来了吧。虽说不能代表龙裔，但我相信你了。暂时的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's not true. You read beautifully during our last lesson.</Source>
      <Dest>That's not true. You read beautifully during our last lesson.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You just need to slow down, child.  With these books, there are often words beneath the words.  But if you read too quickly you'll miss them.</Source>
      <Dest>你需要的只是慢下来，孩子。在这些书里面，含义经常藏在字里行间。而你若读得太快就会错过它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you wish, my love.</Source>
      <Dest>如你所愿，亲爱的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me. I need your help.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着我。我需要你的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you wish.</Source>
      <Dest>遵命。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Follow me. I need your help.</Source>
      <Dest>跟着我。我需要你的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My love, let us walk the path of the stars, and walk it together.</Source>
      <Dest>吾爱，让我们沿着星辰的轨迹，继续并肩而行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lover grant us passion.</Source>
      <Dest>爱人给予我们的激情！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Carry on then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就继续吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May the serpent bless our deeds, and curse the wicked.</Source>
      <Dest>May the serpent bless our deeds, and curse the wicked.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ritual show us penitence.</Source>
      <Dest>仪式向我们表明了忏悔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Apprentice gift us with knowledge.</Source>
      <Dest>学徒之石能让我们获得知识。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May the Lord help us endure.</Source>
      <Dest>也许领主能助我们渡过难关。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lady, teach us tolerance.</Source>
      <Dest>夫人教会了我们宽容。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Atronach shield us from pain.</Source>
      <Dest>侍灵保护我们免受痛苦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May the Shadow hide our movements.</Source>
      <Dest>愿阴影掩盖我们的行迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tower bless our adventure.</Source>
      <Dest>塔保佑我们的探险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am at your assistance.</Source>
      <Dest>I am at your assistance.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Jarl has a difficult decision. A dragon can fly over the city walls. He can't send all his troops to the tower, and yet he can't afford not to.</Source>
      <Dest>领主手头的选项很少。龙能飞过城墙。他不能派遣他所有部队到塔楼去，但同时他也无法承受不这样做的后果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For Kodlak!</Source>
      <Dest>为了克拉科！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The fates can be cruel, to take Kodlak now.  I only pray that the Shadow shields Hircine's eye, so that the stars can guide his soul to Aetherius.</Source>
      <Dest>命运是如此地残酷，才会在此时带走克拉科的生命。我只能祈祷阴影会遮蔽海尔辛的双眼，愿星辰指引他魂归艾瑟瑞斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, it is good to see you traveler. Yet it would be wise to remove yourself from this camp. The Imperials do not take kindly to Stormcloaks.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，很高兴见到你，旅行者...不过你最好离开这个营地。帝国人可不欢迎风暴斗篷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, it is good to see you traveler.  Perhaps you can help us with the wounded.  There are many who need tending.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，很高兴见到你旅行者。或许你会帮我们照料这些伤残者，这里有许多人需要照顾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, my lady.</Source>
      <Dest>你好，我的女士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Happiness is not a daily goal.  Remember that when the night is long.</Source>
      <Dest>幸福不是短期目标。当长夜漫漫之时记住这个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ready to move?</Source>
      <Dest>准备行动？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We've stopped. Good. A patient mind sees with clear eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>我们停下了。很好。一个病人的心思能从他清澈的双眼里看出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will close your wounds, great and small.</Source>
      <Dest>我会帮你愈合所有的伤口的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My lady, I am pleased to have you with me, and honored to be your husband.</Source>
      <Dest>我的女士，我很高兴能有您陪伴左右，能够成为您的丈夫我真是万分荣幸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am at your assistance.</Source>
      <Dest>I am at your assistance.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stars guide us.</Source>
      <Dest>愿星辰指引我们前行的方向。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Steed make us swift.</Source>
      <Dest>骏马之石会让我们更快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Warrior give us strength.</Source>
      <Dest>战士之石给予我们力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mage grant us wisdom.</Source>
      <Dest>法师赐予我们智慧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thief give us fortune.</Source>
      <Dest>盗贼给我们带来财富。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Be careful!</Source>
      <Dest>小心！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm on your side!</Source>
      <Dest>我就在你身旁！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're testing my patience!</Source>
      <Dest>你是在考验我的耐性！</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
