<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is your opinion of the College?</Source>
      <Dest>你对学院的看法是怎样的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is your opinion of the College?</Source>
      <Dest>你对学院的看法是怎样的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is your opinion of the College?</Source>
      <Dest>你对学院的看法是怎样的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is your opinion of the College?</Source>
      <Dest>你对学院的看法是怎样的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is your opinion of the College?</Source>
      <Dest>你对学院的看法是怎样的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is your opinion of the College?</Source>
      <Dest>你对学院的看法是怎样的呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Francis?</Source>
      <Dest>弗朗西斯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Francis?</Source>
      <Dest>弗朗西斯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Francis?</Source>
      <Dest>弗朗西斯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The mages, of course.  You think they broke it, so they should build it.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，就是那些法师。你觉得他们破坏了它，所以他们应该重建它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The mages, of course.  You think they broke it, so they should build it.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，就是那些法师。你觉得他们破坏了它，所以他们应该重建它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The mages, of course.  You think they broke it, so they should build it.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，就是那些法师。你觉得他们破坏了它，所以他们应该重建它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The mages, of course.  You think they broke it, so they should build it.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，就是那些法师。你觉得他们破坏了它，所以他们应该重建它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ah, you mean children.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你是指孩子们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ah, you mean children.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你是指孩子们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ah, you mean children.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你是指孩子们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ah, you mean children.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你是指孩子们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened to her mother?</Source>
      <Dest>他母亲怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Will your business be up and running soon?</Source>
      <Dest>你那生意马上就能运转起来吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Will your business be up and running soon?</Source>
      <Dest>你那生意马上就能运转起来吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Will your business be up and running soon?</Source>
      <Dest>你那生意马上就能运转起来吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What good is a stable if half the city is in ruins?</Source>
      <Dest>对于一座有一半已经是废墟了的城市来说，难道稳定点不好？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What good is a stable if half the city is in ruins?</Source>
      <Dest>对于一座有一半已经是废墟了的城市来说，难道盖座马厩不好吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What good is a stable if half the city is in ruins?</Source>
      <Dest>对于一座有一半已经是废墟了的城市来说，难道盖座马厩不好吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you by chance planning on opening a stable?</Source>
      <Dest>你该不会正好打算盖一间马厩吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are you by chance planning on opening a stable?</Source>
      <Dest>你该不会正好打算盖一间马厩吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good luck with your...I guess you could call it a plan.</Source>
      <Dest>祝你好运...我觉得这是个不错的主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good luck with your...I guess you could call it a plan.</Source>
      <Dest>祝你好运...我觉得这是个不错的主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good luck with your...I guess you could call it a plan.</Source>
      <Dest>祝你好运...我觉得这是个不错的主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Count me in.  Let's go wrangle some slaves.</Source>
      <Dest>算我一个。我们去抓点奴隶吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Count me in.  Let's go wrangle some slaves.</Source>
      <Dest>算我一个。我们去抓点奴隶吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Count me in.  Let's go wrangle some slaves.</Source>
      <Dest>算我一个。我们去抓点奴隶吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Count me in.  Let's go wrangle some slaves.</Source>
      <Dest>算我一个。我们去抓点奴隶吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If it means a carriage comes here too, I'm all for it.</Source>
      <Dest>如果这意味着马车也会途经这里，那真是梦寐以求啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If it means a carriage comes here too, I'm all for it.</Source>
      <Dest>如果这意味着马车也会途经这里，那真是梦寐以求啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That was oddly sweet.</Source>
      <Dest>这甜味儿真怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And peppers. You'll need to go to Hammerfell and get the spiciest peppers you can buy. Then you'll have to get the mages all lined up on the walkway.</Source>
      <Dest>还有辣椒。你需要去落锤省买最辣的辣椒。这样法师就会排起长队来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>People who like to ride horses, race them, and when they're done racing and riding them, eat them.  Rich people.</Source>
      <Dest>那些喜欢骑马，喜欢赛马，骑完赛完又吃掉马的人。都是有钱人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There is a lot more horse violence in Skyrim these days.  People used to love horses, not beat them.  But Francis is more than a horse.</Source>
      <Dest>这些年来天际无时不刻充斥着对马的暴力。就在以前，人们还都爱着这些马，不去伤害它们。但弗朗西斯她不只是一匹马。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, well, well.  Looks like you're off to the college. Well, I'm sure you got plenty of coin to spend first.  But don't spend it all just yet.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，好吧，好吧。看起来你是要去那里上学啦。你肯定准备了很多钱。不过别马上花光。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah?</Source>
      <Dest>啊？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some of them don't even do that.  They just fool themselves into thinking they're well rested so they can keep raping souls and raising the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>他们中有些人甚至都不这么做。他们只是自我催眠说那些死者已经安眠，所以他们能继续通过掠夺灵魂来复活死尸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm going to be selling some of my own wares soon.  Real soon.  But Francis is mine.  You can't have her.</Source>
      <Dest>我马上就会从我的藏品里拨出一部分来出售。真的，马上。但弗朗西斯是我的，你可不能带走她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm going to be selling some of my own wares soon.  Real soon.  But Francis is mine.  You can't have her.</Source>
      <Dest>我马上就会从我的藏品里拨出一部分来出售。真的，马上。但弗朗西斯是我的，你可不能带走她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh yes.  It'll take some time to build it, maybe have to tear down that inn, or the Jarl's home first, to make room.</Source>
      <Dest>哦是的。建设它可得花点时间。而且可能得先拆了那家旅馆或者领主的房子来腾点地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if they have Daedric slaves working for them, then we ought to tax them or make them pay insurance in case things go wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>不过要是他们敢用魔人做奴隶为他们服务，我们就该收他们的税或者让他们交保险金以免出什么问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then perhaps you would like to make a donation then, traveler.  No, I'm not talking about coin.  A donation of your time is what we require.</Source>
      <Dest>也许你可以再捐出一点儿，旅行者。不，我说的不是钱，我们需要你捐一点儿你的时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My horse, you dumb toadie.  Francis is my horse's name, says so right on her soul.  Which is inside of her hide.  Where only I can touch it.</Source>
      <Dest>那是我的马。你拍错马屁了。弗朗西斯是我爱马的名字，恰当的说是她灵魂的名字。这是她隐藏的内在，只有我才能触摸的地方。 .</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You hear for my soul, college mage?</Source>
      <Dest>你这学院来的法师啊，难不成你会读心术？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But a city isn't a city without a stable.  It's just some backwoods hamlet like Riverwood or Rorikstead.  You want prestige, you need horses.</Source>
      <Dest>但是连马厩都没有的城市不是真正意义上的城市。而只能算是河木镇或者洛利克镇那样的偏远小山村。你想要名望，那你得先有匹马。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Coin will not rebuild this town.  Sweat and tears will rebuild it.  The sweat and tears of slaves.  We need a new, free source of labor.</Source>
      <Dest>能够重建这座小镇的不是钱财，而是泪水与汗水。奴隶的汗水和泪水。我们需要些新的，免费的劳动力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What indeed.  A thief wears a hood to mask his face from the guard.  A mage wears a hood to hide the fact that he's a Daedric Lord.</Source>
      <Dest>的确。一个小偷会戴上兜帽遮住脸，免得被守卫认出来。一个法师也会戴上帽兜，掩藏起他其实是个魔族领主的事实。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's a good idea, if we had more of them.  But there's just the two.  The scrawny little toads got energy, I'll give 'em that.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我们有更多的孩子就好了。但我们只有两个。骨瘦如柴的小家伙们真有活力，我会把那个给他们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some even cast spells that can rip a soul right off your skeleton. Ever see a mage turn someone purple?  That's soul ripping.</Source>
      <Dest>一些法术甚至可以在施法时从你的骨头里抽出你的灵魂，看到过法师把别人变成紫色吗？那就是灵魂撕裂咒文。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well I say to Oblivion with that.  My horses are gonna be the fastest, cheapest thing on the market, and that sounds pretty good to me.</Source>
      <Dest>我向上天发誓。我的马儿们是市场上最快、最便宜的，我觉得这应该挺有吸引力的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You may be covered in hair, but don't think you'll ever replace my Francis.</Source>
      <Dest>你浑身是毛儿没问题啊，但别以为自己可以取代我的弗朗西斯。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Let me know if you see anything you like.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你看上了什么就请告诉我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, well, well.  Look what we got here Francis.  A customer.  Too bad we aren't open yet.</Source>
      <Dest>好，好，好。弗朗西斯，看看谁来了。一名顾客。可惜我们还没开张。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, well, well.  Looks like Haran got herself a customer.  Well, I'm sure you got plenty of coin to spread around.  But don't spend it all just yet</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，好吧，好吧。看起来哈冉给自己招揽了一个顾客。行，我知道你穷得只剩下钱了。但是至少别现在全都花完。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, either way it makes no difference to me and Francis how they do it.  Just that they do, and do it for free.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，不管他们怎么做，对我和弗朗西斯来说都没有不同。只要他们干事儿是免费的就成。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You are shortsighted, traveler.  First you build the stable, then you lure the horse fetishists.  </Source>
      <Dest>你真是目光短浅，旅行者。你先造好马厩，然后恋马癖就被你引过来啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't think Francis and I will ever lose our spark.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为弗朗西斯和我的心中之火永远不会熄灭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some say it's a great wonder, a great wonder how a bunch of corpse coddlers managed to hide a gate to Oblivion right in Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>有些人说这是个伟大的奇迹。这个伟大的奇迹就是怎么从煮烂了的累累尸骨中成功隐藏起天际省通往湮灭的门。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, I've never been against a person's right to do what he wants in his own home.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，他们在自己家里爱做什么做什么，我从来没有指手画脚过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stop it, you're making my eyes sweat again.</Source>
      <Dest>停，我眼睛又酸了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not yet.  First I need you to get me a troll.  Or a sabrecat.  Get it to follow you here. </Source>
      <Dest>还不行。首先，我需要你帮我弄到一只巨魔。或者是剑齿虎。让它跟着你到这来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very soon.  They say "Good, fast, and cheap.  Pick two."  Something can be good and cheap, but it won't come fast.  </Source>
      <Dest>很快就会运转起来啦。人们都说如果遇上耐力好，速度快又便宜的马，那得先下手为强。别人的马或许耐力好又便宜，但肯定没有我这儿的马跑得快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No one would dare touch a hair on her mane.</Source>
      <Dest>没人胆敢摸她马鬓上的毛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I shot her too.  The things we do for love.</Source>
      <Dest>我也射了她。只因为爱情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But every so often she'll say something, and it'll just open up your mind and fill it with taffy.  Mind taffy, I like to call it.</Source>
      <Dest>但时不时她会说些什么，然后你的思绪豁然开朗，充满灵感。要我形容的话，就是灵光一闪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was thinking more along the lines of that great big College of potential slaves overlooking the city.</Source>
      <Dest>我能想象那个建在高处俯瞰整座城市的专门培养未来的奴隶的伟大学院门口会排上多长的队。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something could be fast and good, but it won't come cheap.  And something could be fast and cheap, but it won't be good.</Source>
      <Dest>又快耐力又好的马，价钱可不便宜，又快又便宜的马，耐力可不够好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've noticed a lot of them like to head down to the inn, but never all at the same time.  Try becoming their leader or something.  Gain their trust.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经通知很多人到旅馆去了，但不是同时通知到他们所有的人。试试成为他们的领头人，取得他们的信任吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Except Eirid hates Assur, and getting those children to cooperate on such a large scale project is nothing more than a wet dream.</Source>
      <Dest>不过依瑞蒂讨厌阿苏尔，让那些孩子们同理合作完成这样一个大工程，简直是天方夜谭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some of them mages though, they got special gloves.  Let's them touch things that aren't there.  </Source>
      <Dest>有些东西是来自于法师们的，他们有特制的手套，能够让他们碰触到无形无质的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She's got a cunning mind, that one.  Sometimes you stare her and you don't see anything, just some dumb beast with more teeth than brains.</Source>
      <Dest>她非常地狡猾。有时候你盯着她，却什么也感受不到，就好像你盯着的是某些尖牙比脑浆还多的愚蠢野兽一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, it's a plan alright.  Francis is the one who came up with it.  The idea, anyway, I helped smooth out the rough edges.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，这个计划确实挺好。这是弗朗西斯想出来的。不管怎样这个想法帮了不少忙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They got these powers of restoration, which lets them work all day without ever getting tired.  </Source>
      <Dest>他们从回复药剂中获得能量, 让他们工作一天都不会觉得累。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And if they bring them outside, then we ought to hang every one of them.  The Daedra, that is.  The mages we'll give collars and make them our pets.</Source>
      <Dest>如果法师把魔族带出来，那么我们就吊死所有的魔族。我们会给法师戴上项圈，然后让他们做我们的宠物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's like ants.  You get enough of them working together, and they can de-bone a mammoth faster than Ranmir at a meadery.</Source>
      <Dest>就像是蚂蚁。有足够的蚂蚁齐心协力，它们就能用比兰米尔喝蜜酒还快的速度把一头长毛象啃得一堆骨头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's called a soul trap, actually.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，那叫做灵魂陷阱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's called a soul trap, actually.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，那叫做灵魂陷阱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dragons. You want to lure dragons to help with the demolition.</Source>
      <Dest>龙。你是想引诱龙过来搞破坏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dragons. You want to lure dragons to help with the demolition.</Source>
      <Dest>龙。你是想引诱龙过来搞破坏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dragons. You want to lure dragons to help with the demolition.</Source>
      <Dest>龙。你是想引诱龙过来搞破坏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dragons. You want to lure dragons to help with the demolition.</Source>
      <Dest>龙。你是想引诱龙过来搞破坏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dragons. You want to lure dragons to help with the demolition.</Source>
      <Dest>龙。你是想引诱龙过来搞破坏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a pretty timid name for a horse.</Source>
      <Dest>对一匹马来说这是一个胆小的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I'm sure the Jarl would love to demolish his home so you can have a stable.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我很确信领主会想要拆掉自己房子来给你的马厩腾出地方来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I'm sure the Jarl would love to demolish his home so you can have a stable.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我很确信领主会想要拆掉自己房子来给你的马厩腾出地方来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I'm sure the Jarl would love to demolish his home so you can have a stable.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我很确信领主会想要拆掉自己房子来给你的马厩腾出地方来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you and Francis meet?</Source>
      <Dest>你是如何遇见弗朗西斯的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you and Francis meet?</Source>
      <Dest>你是如何遇见弗朗西斯的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you and Francis meet?</Source>
      <Dest>你是如何遇见弗朗西斯的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you and Francis meet?</Source>
      <Dest>你是如何遇见弗朗西斯的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Horses are filthy animals.</Source>
      <Dest>马是种肮脏的动物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Horses are filthy animals.</Source>
      <Dest>马是种肮脏的动物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Horses are filthy animals.</Source>
      <Dest>马是种肮脏的动物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Horses are filthy animals.</Source>
      <Dest>马是种肮脏的动物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Horses are filthy animals.</Source>
      <Dest>马是种肮脏的动物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you see?</Source>
      <Dest>你看到了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you see?</Source>
      <Dest>你看到了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you see?</Source>
      <Dest>你看到了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What did you see?</Source>
      <Dest>你看到了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Francis is a lovely name for a horse.</Source>
      <Dest>弗朗西斯这个名字挺可爱的啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Francis is a lovely name for a horse.</Source>
      <Dest>弗朗西斯这个名字挺可爱的啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you plan on enslaving the mages?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你打算怎么抓法师来当奴隶呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you plan on enslaving the mages?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你打算怎么抓法师来当奴隶呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you plan on enslaving the mages?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你打算怎么抓法师来当奴隶呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you plan on enslaving the mages?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你打算怎么抓法师来当奴隶呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you plan on enslaving the mages?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你打算怎么抓法师来当奴隶呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you plan on enslaving the mages?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你打算怎么抓法师来当奴隶呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That story just makes it even weirder.</Source>
      <Dest>那个故事把它搞得感觉更诡异了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So it's war you want, huh.  Well, cheese bottom, I'll have you know Francis has tasted mortal blood, and she won't hesitate to taste it again.</Source>
      <Dest>那你想要的就是开战了？不过别着忙。我得告诉你弗朗西斯已经尝过了人血的味道，她短期内不会打算再尝一次了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They got them calming spells though, but that only works on the mind. It doesn't touch the tongue.  </Source>
      <Dest>他们完成了他们的冷静法术，不过这只作用于意识，而不会触及舌头。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why we need to build her a proper home.  A castle with an indoor farm and a stable for the other animals and the Jarl's children.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我们为什么要给她找一个合适的家。一个有室内花园、马厩、其他小动物和领主的孩子的城堡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thing is, rich folk don't hold the same opinion.  They think horses are majestic.  Francis is majestic.  Sometimes I think she's the tenth divine.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，有钱人的观点则不同。他们认为马是高贵的。弗朗西斯是威严的。有时我认为她就是第十位圣灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, it's not exactly a trap the way I've seen mages do it.  More like you need to drop the "T" and add an "E" at the end.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，我看法师们用陷阱（Trap）的时候可不是那样。你去掉一个T再在末尾加上一个E，称呼它为强奸（Rape）更合适一些。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, now that is a tale that rivals any love story the bards ever told.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，现在说的这个传说是一位吟游诗人告诉我的。它能媲美任何爱情故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The problem was I had never ridden a horse.  A fact that was quite apparent by the way the lord's horse bucked me.</Source>
      <Dest>问题在于我根本没骑过马，这点在我差点从老爷的马背上摔下来时已经很明显了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A good Jarl thinks only of his people.  Sometimes that means lowering taxes.  Most times it means raising them.</Source>
      <Dest>一个优秀的领主只关心他的人民。有时这意味着降低税收。大多数时候，更意味着要养活他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I would cut your tongue out right now if I didn't agree with you. Horses are indeed filthy, but Francis is more than just a horse, and also deaf.</Source>
      <Dest>信不信我直接割掉你的舌头。马的确都很脏，但弗朗西斯不仅仅是匹马，它还是匹聋马。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>After four tries, I ran into the forest to wipe the sweat out of my eyes.  I came to a grove, and I couldn't believe what I saw.</Source>
      <Dest>试了四次之后，我跑进森林去擦干眼睛里的泪水。等我走进小树林时，看见了难以置信的场景。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, the main problem is they got them fancy seals on the entrance.  The walkway is narrow too, but we could use that to our advantage.</Source>
      <Dest>呃，主要的问题在于他们用华丽的魔法把入口给封住了。走道也很窄，但我们可以利用我们的优势。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's right, they should call it soul rape, and all them soul rapists at the College should be thrown into the sea for their crimes.</Source>
      <Dest>说对了。那应该被称为剥魂。看看那些学院里的剥魂者翻下的滔天大罪，把他们扔到大海里都不为过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, that stuff costs more than an Emperor's ransom.  For that we need to find a cheap source of labor.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，那原料的成本比皇帝的赎金还贵。因此我们要找廉价的劳动力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank the Nine Divines the Dragon didn't kill her, or worse, make her ugly.  But I threw that idea into the hay pile after that.</Source>
      <Dest>感谢九圣灵那条龙没杀了她，也没让她毁容，那可比死亡更糟。于是我就把这个想法丢到九霄云外去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, I'm talking about mages.  Enslaving them. We trade their staffs and soul gems for hammers and nails, and Winterhold will be rebuilt in a season.</Source>
      <Dest>不，我说的是法师。奴役他们。我们可以用他们的灵魂石和法杖去换钉子和工具。这样一个季度内冬堡就能被重建。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She said "weeheehee" or something like that.  I took it to mean she wanted the Spriggan dead.</Source>
      <Dest>她好像说了句“诶嘿嘿”还是什么的。我理解成了她想要那树精死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That college up there must smell worse than the bucket Francis and I do our business in.</Source>
      <Dest>那所学院的气味一定比弗朗西斯和我解决问题的桶闻起来还糟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you think you can march into this town and ride away on my Francis, you've got another thing coming.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你认为你可以长驱直入这个城镇并骑跑我的弗朗西斯，那你就大错特错了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She was lying in a pool of clear slime.  No older than a day.  Then our eyes met, and she spoke to me.</Source>
      <Dest>她刚刚出生，躺在一池透明的黏液中。当我们四目相交时，她开始对我说话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think one of them stars fell and hit Francis right on the head, mad as she was.  </Source>
      <Dest>我猜是有一颗星星掉下来砸了弗朗西斯的脑袋，不然她怎么疯成那样。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I thought of that first, but then one day a dragon did come, and Francis went into a frenzy.  </Source>
      <Dest>我一开始也是那样想的，不过当巨龙真的降临时，弗朗西斯之怒却如火山爆发，熔岩奔流而不可遏止了。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.  I'm gonna go hit the hay soon anyways.</Source>
      <Dest>好了，不管怎么说我要睡觉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't like your tone, stranger.  I know your kind, tossing cheap flattery around in order to sate the commands of your loins.</Source>
      <Dest>我不喜欢你的语气，陌生人。我看透你们这种人了，为了满足下半身的欲望到处花言巧语。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not if we take advantage of a cheap source of labor.</Source>
      <Dest>只要我们能好好利用廉价劳动力就行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fought that lizard straight on, whinnying a battle cry that jostled the very stars out of the sky.</Source>
      <Dest>他正面硬扛了那只大蜥蜴，那战吼几可震落天上群星。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stay away from my Francis.</Source>
      <Dest>离我家弗朗西斯远点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stay away from my Francis.</Source>
      <Dest>离我家弗朗西斯远点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They won't know what hit them.  But they'll know when they wake up with chains around their ankles.</Source>
      <Dest>他们不会知道是被什么放倒的。但等他们戴着脚镣醒来时就知道了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A wild mare, locked in battle with a Spriggan.  Fighting to defend its young.  That's when I saw Francis for the first time.</Source>
      <Dest>我第一次遇见弗朗西斯，那在森林里，我看见一匹母马正身陷于树精的战斗中，为保护它的幼崽而抗争着，它是那样地野性。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Specifically, raising the money for a lengthy construction project.  Although he won't have to raise taxes too high.  </Source>
      <Dest>具体来说，为长远的城建工程增加税收。而且他不必将税收征得过于沉重。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We get some troll's mouth hotter than the Red Mountain, and then point it right at those mages.  </Source>
      <Dest>我们只要找些能喷出比红山还烫的气体的巨魔，然后把它对准那些法师就可以了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Filthy?  You mean they don't bathe either?  And here I thought I couldn't lose any more respect for them hand-wagglers.</Source>
      <Dest>肮脏的？你是说他们从不洗澡吗？那现在我觉得我对这些只会用手比划的家伙已经完全没有敬意了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alright.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So say what you will about horses, traveler.  I wouldn't be aiming to sell them if I didn't consider them worth discarding.</Source>
      <Dest>就马而言，无论你说什么，旅行者。如果我不认为它们值得抛弃的话，是不会卖掉它们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why my plan is to feed this monster some spicy food.  Like one of them peppers they sell at the markets in Hammerfell. </Source>
      <Dest>这就是为何我会计划喂这怪物一些辛辣的食物。就是那些在落锤省可以买到的辣椒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
