<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To arms, Vigilants!  Rend them all to dust!</Source>
      <Dest>开战啦，警戒者们！把他们全都碎尸万段！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vampires!</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Thanks to my efforts, and Among the Hist. You just got in the way.</Source>
      <Dest>都是因为我的努力，还有伊斯特之阿蒙。你才刚刚上道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You are as ignorant as you are ungrateful. Pray to Stendarr I get in the way when the abominations are tearing at your throat.</Source>
      <Dest>你的忘恩负义和你的愚昧一样令人厌恶。 [向斯坦达祈祷不要让我厌恶到撕裂你的喉咙]。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Jarl does that. Use pretenses to get what he wants.</Source>
      <Dest>领主的行径，用各种借口达成他的目的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Indeed. However, I have learned not to discuss politics with those whom I consider friends.</Source>
      <Dest>确实。不过，我已经学到在那些所谓朋友面前不谈政事了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They could already be infected. You heard what Morviah said.</Source>
      <Dest>他们肯定已经被感染了！你也听到了 墨菲亚 是怎么说的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The thought did cross my mind. The Argonian did say these heathens preferred the slow hunt, but we cannot take him at his word.</Source>
      <Dest>这点子我确实想过。那个亚龙人确实说过这些异教徒更喜欢慢慢来，但我们也不能全信他的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As an honorary vigilant, I task you with the responsibility of sweeping the city and locating any who have turned. Report back to me at the beacon.</Source>
      <Dest>作为一名荣誉警戒者，我交付于你净化城市并定位任何一名转化者的责任。回灯塔向我汇报吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They could already be infected. You heard what Morviah said.</Source>
      <Dest>他们肯定已经被感染了！你也听到了 墨菲亚 是怎么说的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Gray Quarter has seen enough turmoil. I am glad we prevented more.</Source>
      <Dest>灰民区已经有足够多的动乱了。很高兴我们阻止了更多动乱的发生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, although as much as I hate to admit it, if the area had been infected, it is likely that the Jarl's actions would have been justified.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，尽管我几乎不想去承认，但这个地方确实被污染了，所以领主的那些举动才是合理的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Gray Quarter has seen enough turmoil. I am glad we prevented more.</Source>
      <Dest>灰民区已经有足够多的动乱了。很高兴我们阻止了更多动乱的发生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If a few innocents are lost, it would pale in comparison to the number of casualties that would occur if one abomination were allowed to live.</Source>
      <Dest>即使有少数无辜的人被冤枉了，也比放过一个恶人导致更多的无辜者受难要好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>More ghost stories. Vampires phasing through ice. Utter nonsense.</Source>
      <Dest>越来越多的鬼扯故事。什么吸血鬼逐步消亡啊。根本是胡说八道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The nightwalkers may not possess such powers, but their usual habits are crimes enough. It is imperative we seal off their escape.</Source>
      <Dest>这些夜行者或许没有这么强大的力量，但是他们的本性就已经足够罪恶了。我们亟需封锁他们逃之夭夭的后路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A family was abducted by vampires, near the docks.</Source>
      <Dest>有一家人被吸血鬼绑架了。就在港口附近。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then they could already be on their way north. We must hurry lest their numbers swarm.</Source>
      <Dest>他们可能已经往北走了。我们必须得快点儿，免得那群人扎堆儿出现。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then it would behoove you to pay more attention to what people say. Rumor is a valuable tool in hunting the craven.</Source>
      <Dest>Then it would behoove you to pay more attention to what people say. Rumor is a valuable tool in hunting the craven.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm not sure. I spoke to the Elf he refers to, but I didn't really listen.</Source>
      <Dest>记不清了，我跟他提起的那个 Elf 聊过几句，不过当时心不在焉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The vampire at Cronvangr. His sister lives in Windhelm.</Source>
      <Dest>克隆万格洞穴的那只吸血鬼。他的妹妹住在风盔城。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Are you implying this abomination is allowed to walk the city streets? And the two of you allow it?</Source>
      <Dest>你的意思是这坨恶心的东西也能走在城市街道上吗？你俩觉得可以允许这种事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The vampire at Cronvangr. His sister lives in Windhelm.</Source>
      <Dest>克隆万格洞穴的那只吸血鬼。他的妹妹住在风盔城。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am beginning to question whether this group your friend belongs to has any order or virtue to speak of.</Source>
      <Dest>我开始怀疑你朋友所属的团体有任何秩序或优点可言吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It appears we've arrived not a moment too soon. No doubt these two were already ingratiating themselves with the locals.</Source>
      <Dest> 似乎我们已经错过了时机。毫无疑问，他们两个已经被当地人所接受了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Had they been allowed to succeed, the Gray Quarter would have suffered an epidemic of vampirism.</Source>
      <Dest>假使他们成功了，灰色居住区 将受到吸血鬼病肆虐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Moreover, the Jarl could have used it as a pretense to purge the entire city of outsiders.</Source>
      <Dest>并且，这个领主曾以此为借口清洗了整个城市的外来者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thanks to our efforts, both those circumstances have been averted.</Source>
      <Dest>多亏我们的共同努力，才能成功避免这些事件的发生。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What sister? Phasing through ice? What is he talking about?</Source>
      <Dest>什么姐姐？变相变相穿过冰层？他在说什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, until we meet again. Walk always in the light, the both of you.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，直到我们重聚。愿你们二人行走于光明之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can't imagine why.  In any case, I thank you again for your assistance, but I must take my leave. I am needed back at the beacon.</Source>
      <Dest>我想不出来是为什么。无论如何，再次感谢你的帮助，但我必须走了。我得回灯塔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why would you assume such a thing? I have been nothing but courteous to you.</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么会有这样的想法？我一直对你恭敬有加。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I, for one, am glad to have you on our side. We may have our differences, but you have proven yourself worthy.</Source>
      <Dest>以及，且不论其他人，至少我非常感谢有你陪伴在我身边。我们或许确实曾有过分歧，但你证明了那些分歧都是过眼云烟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Order of the Virtuous Blood is a friend to the Vigil.</Source>
      <Dest>贞血教团是警戒者的朋友。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do not feign ignorance vampire, we know perfectly well what you are capable of!</Source>
      <Dest>Do not feign ignorance vampire, we know perfectly well what you are capable of!</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Up the stairs! Don't let them escape!</Source>
      <Dest>上楼！别让他们跑了！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You mean to tell me you're harboring vampires in this very building?</Source>
      <Dest>你的意思是要告诉我你窝藏吸血鬼在这个建筑里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>On the contrary, Argonian. We may be near the docks, but we're still inside the city.</Source>
      <Dest>正好相反，亚龙人。可能我们已经距离港口很近了，但我们依然还在这座城市里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you think a guard wouldn't notice a horde of vampires diving into the river?</Source>
      <Dest>你以为当守卫的看不见一大帮吸血鬼钻进河里吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We're on the other side of the bank. There's no strategic advantage to using this tunnel whatsoever.</Source>
      <Dest>因为我们在河对岸，所以这条隧道就没有可利用的战略优势了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unless your aim was to get inside the city walls.</Source>
      <Dest>除非你的目的就是进城。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If what you say is true, then this girl's story was a lie.  She says they came from the river. That they phased through the ice.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你说的是真的，那么那姑娘的故事就是编的了。她说他们是从那条河的对面踏冰而来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your attachment to this brother and sister is affecting your judgment. How can we be certain they are not the twins we seek?</Source>
      <Dest>你依恋的这对兄妹影响了你的判断。我们如何能肯定他们不是我们寻求找的那对儿双胞胎呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like cowards they prey upon the refugees, and take advantage of the Jarl's indifference.</Source>
      <Dest>他们掠夺难民的行径简直就是懦夫所为，这就是领主们漠不关心子民的结果。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True enough, but they fear the light, and we will cast it upon this tunnel and burn their souls to dust.</Source>
      <Dest>话虽如此，可他们怕光，所以咱们就把光注入这条隧道，连他们灵魂都烧成灰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It must have taken them centuries to dig this.</Source>
      <Dest>他们挖这个一定花了好几个世纪的时间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stendarr's Mercy! How deep does this canyon go?</Source>
      <Dest>慈爱的斯丹纳尔啊！这峡谷到底有多深？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I disagree. There's no turning back now. In this case, we will be better prepared if we assume the worst.</Source>
      <Dest>我不同意。现在已经无路可退了。在这种情况下，我们最好准备应对最糟糕的情况。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems your instincts were correct, Argonian. I was wrong to question you.</Source>
      <Dest>看来你的直觉是正确的，亚龙人。怀疑你是我不对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We're already fairly deep. How much further can we possibly descend?</Source>
      <Dest>我们已经走的够深了。我们还可能往下走多远？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What do you mean?</Source>
      <Dest>你是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It seems your hostage was not entirely useless after all. The question now, is where have they gone?</Source>
      <Dest>看来你的人质也不是完全没有价值。现在的问题是，他们跑哪去了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That proves nothing. They could belong to bandits. Smugglers even.</Source>
      <Dest>That proves nothing. They could belong to bandits. Smugglers even.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, we're here. Where pray tell are the night stalkers your hostage promised us? Do not tell me that boy played us for fools!</Source>
      <Dest>呃，我们到了。请告诉我，你的人质向我们承诺的暗夜行者在哪儿呢？别告诉我那个男孩在把我们当傻子耍！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They have not the valor to walk in the light.</Source>
      <Dest>他们没有勇气行走在光明之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you're with the Dawnguard.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，你是站在黎明守卫一边。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Come. Let us hurry and be done with these vampires. Every minute we are separated from Stendarr's Beacon puts it in further peril.</Source>
      <Dest>赶快，让我们干掉这群吸血鬼。 我们和斯坦达尔哨塔不在一起的每一分钟都会置其于更危险的境地。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nonsense! What you speak of are nothing more than children's ghost stories. They are vampires, are they not? Then they can be slain.</Source>
      <Dest>胡说八道！你说的无非是一些骗孩子的鬼故事。他们是吸血鬼，对吧？那他们就该杀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Moreover, we are not a married couple looking to rear children. The craven tactics you describe will not serve them on the field of war.</Source>
      <Dest>而且，我们不是想要收养孤儿的小两口。你所描述的那个懦弱手段在战争领域可没什么用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is all fine and good, but you have yet to reveal how you know of these twins. What are you hiding?</Source>
      <Dest>那些都好说，不过你还没说清楚到底是怎么认识那对双胞胎地方。有什么可隐瞒的吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well. Interrogate your prisoner. But when it is done, he will answer to Stendarr for his crimes!</Source>
      <Dest>很好。审问你的犯人吧。但你审问完之后，他将向斯坦达尔忏悔他的罪行！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A vampire! Why does he still live! Explain yourself!</Source>
      <Dest>一只吸血鬼！为什么他还活着！说清你的意图！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you will tell me what you know of this place, soldier, and where to find the rest of this clan.</Source>
      <Dest>然后你会告诉我你对这地方都了解多少, 士兵, 以及去那儿找到剩下的氏族.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Virtuous Blood? I've never heard of such an order.</Source>
      <Dest>贞血教团？我从没听说过有这么个组织。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And what kind of monster are you, to walk amongst these demons?</Source>
      <Dest>那你又是什么样的怪物，竟会走在这群恶魔之间？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thaden! Blast! He was one of our best men. </Source>
      <Dest>Thaden! Blast!他是我们之中最强的那个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The cowardly beasts must be trying to pick us off, one by one.</Source>
      <Dest>那些胆小的野兽们一定是想把我们各个击破。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The nightwalkers gather strength from the shadows, and find comfort in numbers. </Source>
      <Dest>这些夜行者从阴暗中取得力量，在数目（钱？）上取得安慰。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The spider eggs outside mark this cave as a beast lair. If the nightwalkers live here, there must be a secret entrance.</Source>
      <Dest>外面的蜘蛛卵说明这个洞穴里装满了野兽。如果那帮只在夜间游荡的家伙们在这儿生活，那这里肯定有个秘密入口。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To reach the cave we need only travel to Lake Honrich and follow the path north up the river.</Source>
      <Dest>To reach the cave we need only travel to Lake Honrich and follow the path north up the river.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, as an adventurer, you may know of a more direct path. Thus I will allow you take the lead. Time is of the essence.</Source>
      <Dest>不过呢，作为一名冒险者，你可能知道更加便捷的路径。所以我恩准你在前面带路的干活。赶时间呢，利索点儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, as we stand on the fringes, the vampires have laid waste to the countryside.</Source>
      <Dest>论此，且众人驻足于崖，而吸血鬼则葬身乡间。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This beacon is an important watchtower as it stands on the border between three provinces.</Source>
      <Dest>这座灯塔坐落在三省交界处，因其特殊的地理位置成为了一处重要的了望点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It offers prayer and safe passage to travelers to and from each.</Source>
      <Dest>它为祈祷者们提供标识，并为过往的旅人们带来安全。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This cave is believed to be one of their strongholds, but this information is unreliable. It could be another trap meant to divide our numbers.</Source>
      <Dest>这个洞穴被认为是他们的要塞之一,但这信息是不可靠的。这可能是另一个陷阱，旨在把我们的人分开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, as I informed you previously, our focus has shifted recently from the Daedra to the vampire menace.</Source>
      <Dest>正如我之前所通知的那样，在现在，我们的关注焦点已经不再是魔族，而是处理吸血鬼的威胁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You cannot harm those who walk in the light!</Source>
      <Dest>你不能伤害那些行走在光明中的人！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ugh!</Source>
      <Dest>呃！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Urgh!</Source>
      <Dest>呃啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eyaargh!</Source>
      <Dest>哎呀！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fall to me!</Source>
      <Dest>给我跪下！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Death Hounds! These are no ordinary dogs! Be wary of their bite!</Source>
      <Dest>死亡猎犬！这可不是普通的狗！小心别被咬到！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Death to the wicked!</Source>
      <Dest>坏蛋去死！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stendarr take you, vampire!  </Source>
      <Dest>斯丹纳尔会带走你的,吸血鬼!  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For the Vigilant!</Source>
      <Dest>为了警戒者！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have no mercy to spare, heathen!</Source>
      <Dest>我不会手下留情，异教徒！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Daedra may be more dangerous, but those dangers were in the past.</Source>
      <Dest>魔族也许是更危险，可那些危险都存在于过去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is the essence of our dilemma. You have no concept of time. You see only forward, when time moves like a great wheel, past and future aligned.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我们窘境的源头。你没有时间概念。你只是向前看，但时光之轮的过去和未来从来都是整齐划一的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Daedra may be more dangerous, but those dangers were in the past.</Source>
      <Dest>魔族也许是更危险，可那些危险都存在于过去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Must I have met Mannimarco to know the dangers of necromancy?  Do I need to see Hircine claim a soul to know he is damned?</Source>
      <Dest>难道非要见过 Mannimarco 才知道亡灵巫术的危险性吗？非得亲眼看着 Hircine 抓走一个灵魂才知道他要的是什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Daedra may be more dangerous, but those dangers were in the past.</Source>
      <Dest>魔族也许是更危险，可那些危险都存在于过去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Follow the thread of time, as written by our forefathers, and it will show you where to weave.  </Source>
      <Dest>循着时间的线索，正如我们的祖先写到的那样，它将展示于你须得编织之处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is the essence of our dilemma. You have no concept of time. You see only forward, when time moves like a great wheel, past and future aligned.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我们窘境的源头。你没有时间概念。你只是向前看，但时光之轮的过去和未来从来都是整齐划一的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Must I have met Mannimarco to know the dangers of necromancy?  Do I need to see Hircine claim a soul to know he is damned?</Source>
      <Dest>难道非要见过 Mannimarco 才知道亡灵巫术的危险性吗？非得亲眼看着 Hircine 抓走一个灵魂才知道他要的是什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Follow the thread of time, as written by our forefathers, and it will show you where to weave.  </Source>
      <Dest>循着时间的线索，正如我们的祖先写到的那样，它将展示于你须得编织之处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Oblivion Crisis was two centuries ago.  People are more scared of Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>湮灭危机是两个世纪以前的事，他使人们更害怕梭默。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you even think before you smack your lips together like a beast?  Is being glib considered a virtue where you come from?</Source>
      <Dest>你以为你就像野兽一样已经垂涎三尺吗？在你的故乡里，油嘴滑舌是一个美德吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Oblivion Crisis was two centuries ago.  People are more scared of Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>湮灭危机是两个世纪以前的事，他使人们更害怕梭默。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Aldmeri may call itself a dominion by name, but their objective is to rule.  The Daedra do not wish to rule us.  The Daedra seek to dominate. </Source>
      <Dest>先祖神洲他们的目标只是想统治我们。魔族不是想统治我们，魔族是想支配我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Oblivion Crisis was two centuries ago.  People are more scared of Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>湮灭危机是两个世纪以前的事，他使人们更害怕梭默。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This makes Thalmor no different than the Empire or Stormcloaks.  Theirs is but a game of kings whose winner will always be time.  </Source>
      <Dest>这使得梭默和帝国或者风暴斗篷没有任何分别，他们是这个国王游戏中永远的赢家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can relax, it was just a joke. I don't have a pet Atronach. Yet.</Source>
      <Dest>哦不别介意，这只是个玩笑。我并不拥有过一位魔宠，只是当下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am more than capable of recognizing your facile attempts at humor.  I simply do not choose to acknowledge them.  </Source>
      <Dest>你那蹩脚的所谓幽默我有什么不懂的，只不过我故意不听而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can relax, it was just a joke. I don't have a pet Atronach. Yet.</Source>
      <Dest>哦不别介意，这只是个玩笑。我并不拥有过一位魔宠，只是当下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you find Daedra funny?  Are witches and werewolves here for your amusement?  Are vampires merely jesters with terribly pale skin?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得魔族很搞笑吗？女巫和狼人在这里只是为了让您作乐吗？吸血鬼只是个皮肤很白的小丑吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You focus too much on the big picture, when people are dying all around us.</Source>
      <Dest>当人们都在我们身边死去，你却过于注重大局。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is that focus that allows the concept of life and death to exist.  What good is fortifying a rampart if the foundation is about to crumble?</Source>
      <Dest>这就是生命的理念与死亡的存在。一个地基快要崩溃的壁垒，而你却还去加强它的外墙防御，这到底能得到什么好处？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You keep your hair short. Personal preference or you just like it that way?</Source>
      <Dest>你剪了短发，是你个人的兴趣使然还是自然形成的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do not wear it this way "to be liked" or for other such cosmetic reasons.  Long hair is a nuisance out on the battlefield.</Source>
      <Dest>我不会为了迎合别人喜欢而去打扮或改变穿着。长头发在战场上是一种滋扰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you must look elsewhere.  I make no bargains.  If you truly wish to lend a hand, then commit yourself to the Order.  Only then can-</Source>
      <Dest>Then you must look elsewhere.  I make no bargains.  If you truly wish to lend a hand, then commit yourself to the Order.  Only then can-</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Perhaps I can lend a hand, if you agree to help me in return.</Source>
      <Dest>也许我可以伸出援手，如果你同意帮助我就当作是回报。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Order.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你们的命令。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Our order was founded following the events of the Oblivion Crisis. We dedicated to facing the threat of the Daedra wherever they appear.</Source>
      <Dest>我们的宗旨是在湮灭危机一事之后建立的。无论魔族出现在哪，我们都会致力对抗他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Order.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你们的命令。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>While we hunt all abominations that prey on mortals, we hold special enmity for the Daedra.  </Source>
      <Dest>我们猎杀所有以凡人为食的可憎之物，其中我们把魔族认定为特别的敌人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Order.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你们的命令。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Daedra treat humanity as playthings, toys that only exist for their amusement.  It is this perspective that makes them our sworn enemy.</Source>
      <Dest>魔族待人们就像玩具一样，一个供他们的作乐的玩具。正是如此使他们成为我们的死敌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Order.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你们的命令。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>After all, it matters not if a toy breaks, bleeds, or dies.  A toy is just a toy.  </Source>
      <Dest>因为一个玩具是否断肢，流血或者死亡都没有什么大不了。玩具始终只是玩具。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This may not be the time to ask, but I am need of a Warrior of Stendarr.</Source>
      <Dest>现在或许不是提要求的时候，但需要一个斯丹纳尔战士。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am sorry, but you must look elsewhere.  My presence is needed here, and-</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉，但你得在别的地方找找看了。我在这里的存在是必要的，而且……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No Madame.</Source>
      <Dest>不 夫人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you had best refrain from talking as if it were.</Source>
      <Dest>如果是真的话，你最好不要说任何话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No Madame.</Source>
      <Dest>不 夫人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Oblivion Crisis nearly brought about the end of Tamriel.  The Vigilants of Stendarr are here to make sure such a travesty never happens again.</Source>
      <Dest>湮灭危机几乎为泰姆瑞尔大陆带来了末日。斯丹纳尔警戒者来到这里是为了确保以后不会再发生同样的笑话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I take it you have no love for the Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我估摸着你对梭默是毫无好感了对吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do not know what you mean by that.  One cannot love or hate things in blind totality.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道你指什么，人总不可以盲目地去爱或憎恨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I take it you have no love for the Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我估摸着你对梭默是毫无好感了对吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have many brothers and sisters who fight for the Dominion. While I do not agree with their views of man, this is not the sum of their being.</Source>
      <Dest>我有很多愿意为先祖神洲而战的兄弟姐妹。尽管我不同意他们对人们的看法，因为他们的身份和他们是个怎样的人是没有关系的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I take it you have no love for the Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我估摸着你对梭默是毫无好感了对吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My dearest friend joined the Thalmor nearly the same day I became a Vigilant. I enjoy her company, respect her mind, and dislike her politics.</Source>
      <Dest>就在我最友好的朋友加入梭默的那几天，我成为了警戒者。我喜欢与她作伴，我亦尊重她的想法，但不喜欢她的政治取向。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So I take it you have no love for the Thalmor.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我估摸着你对梭默是毫无好感了对吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I will not abandon her as a person for a singular flaw.</Source>
      <Dest>我不会因为她人格上的小小缺陷而放弃她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the field work?</Source>
      <Dest>现场工作进展如何？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vampires and werewolves are often easy to root out, as their tendencies are dictated by their baser instincts. Daedra have proved far more difficult.</Source>
      <Dest>吸血鬼和狼人往往较容易找出来，因为他们的行为是基于他们卑劣的本能。但要找出魔族就困难得多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the field work?</Source>
      <Dest>现场工作进展如何？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet we will remain vigilant, as it were.</Source>
      <Dest>但我们会保持警觉，就像以往一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the field work?</Source>
      <Dest>现场工作进展如何？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One of the vigilants lost her partner recently while investigating a cave in The Rift. </Source>
      <Dest>最近有一个警戒者在调查裂痕领的一个山洞时失去了她的伙伴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We should be scouting in threes, but Keeper Carcette says we can't spare the men.</Source>
      <Dest>我们应该在兵分三路去侦察，但守护者凯西提说我们不可以分散。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the field work?</Source>
      <Dest>现场工作进展如何？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the field work?</Source>
      <Dest>现场工作进展如何？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A child on the road, unbeknownst to his parents, was carrying a Daedric artifact.  We cleansed the item and cured him of his ills.  </Source>
      <Dest>一个孩子在他父母不知情的情况下带着一个魔族神器。我们净化了它，并治好了那名小童的疾病。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the field work?</Source>
      <Dest>现场工作进展如何？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Disease does not discriminate, especially the disease of ignorance.  That above all others is the most pernicious.  </Source>
      <Dest>疾病面前人人平等，尤其是智商过低这种病。一等一的恶疾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the field work?</Source>
      <Dest>现场工作进展如何？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The enemies are endless, but our efforts our tireless.  It is important that you never show weakness.  </Source>
      <Dest>尽管我们的敌人是数之不尽，我们永不气馁，更重要的是我们永不示弱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the field work?</Source>
      <Dest>现场工作进展如何？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you ever find yourself fighting a Dremora Lord, that's the first thing they smell. </Source>
      <Dest>如果你发现你在和一个魔人领主战斗，你第一件发现的事就是他们闻起来的味道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How goes the field work?</Source>
      <Dest>现场工作进展如何？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why so curious?  Are you interested in becoming a Vigilant?  Or are your motives more sinister?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么这么好奇？您是否有兴趣成为一个警戒者吗？还是你有更阴险的动机？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are there other Altmer in the Order?</Source>
      <Dest>有其他高精灵接到指令？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Many of my people answer the call to Stendarr's service.  You must understand that the views of the Thalmor are those of a radical sect.</Source>
      <Dest>很多人也响应了斯丹纳尔的号召。但你必须明白，在梭默眼中那些都是激进的宗教行为。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Are there other Altmer in the Order?</Source>
      <Dest>有其他高精灵接到指令？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do not begrudge man's place in the order of things.  Such nonsense only serves to distract us from the true enemy.  </Source>
      <Dest>我对那些万物皆有秩序的居住之地毫不感兴趣。这些废话只是为了分散我们真正的敌人的注意力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What is this place?</Source>
      <Dest>这是什么地方？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This is the Hall of the Vigilant.  Keeper Carcette heads the branch, and decides who shall provide healing to the sick and justice to the wicked.</Source>
      <Dest>这里是警戒者会堂。守护者凯西提带着她的手下，决定谁应该被救活，谁应该被制裁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yeah, but you didn't cut it haphazardly.  There's a design to it.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，但你并没有随意砍掉它。还有希望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, but only because a lack of design would be distracting to others.  </Source>
      <Dest>当然。因为缺乏考虑的话会引响到其他人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Among-the-Hist is dead.</Source>
      <Dest>伊斯特之阿蒙已经死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is...unfortunate.  This war has claimed many lives, virtuous and vigilant. We can only hope there is  light at the end.</Source>
      <Dest>那可真……不幸啊。这战争造成了无数的伤亡，朝圣者和警戒者。我们只能期望结局是光明的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You speak as if the Thalmor are incapable of redemption.  They are not Daedra.  </Source>
      <Dest>You speak as if the Thalmor are incapable of redemption.  They are not Daedra.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is the Thalmor's doctrine at odds with Stendarr's teachings?</Source>
      <Dest>梭默的教条是与斯坦达的学说格格不入吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The time will come when Man and Mer unite once more to fight the true enemy, and it will not make a difference to what banner they swear fealty.  </Source>
      <Dest>The time will come when Man and Mer unite once more to fight the true enemy, and it will not make a difference to what banner they swear fealty.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is the Thalmor's doctrine at odds with Stendarr's teachings?</Source>
      <Dest>梭默的教条是与斯坦达的学说格格不入吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I was about to give you a compliment, actually. No need to get angry.</Source>
      <Dest>哇。试着给一些人赞美吧....</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your kindness is appreciated.  I was merely informing you that your implication was misguided.  Not all of us make decisions based on vanity.  </Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你的好意。但我只是告诉你，你的言下之意是严重错误。不是所有的人都基于虚荣心而作出决定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is Stendarr?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是斯坦达？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A worthy question.  As it is written, Stendarr is the God of Righteous Might and Merciful Forbearance.</Source>
      <Dest>一个很好的问题。正如所记载的，斯丹达尔是位慈悲和怜悯之神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is Stendarr?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是斯坦达？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In practice, he is the very spirit of justice, the inspiration for all who seek order.  </Source>
      <Dest>事实上，他是个非常正义的神灵，一切追求秩序之人所敬拜的神灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is Stendarr?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是斯坦达？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In Altmeri legends he may be known as an apologist of men, but I believe it is not in Stendarr's nature to play favorites.  </Source>
      <Dest>在傲尔特莫的传说中，斯丹纳尔也许会被称为男性的辩护者，但我相信斯丹纳尔并不会厚此薄彼，偏宠男性。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who is Stendarr?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是斯坦达？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In my mind Stendarr is the sword and shield of both Man and Mer.  He instills comfort in the weak, and fear in the unrighteous.  </Source>
      <Dest>对我来说，斯丹纳尔就像是人与精灵之间的剑和盾。他给予弱者安慰，同时又憎恨着邪恶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well in that case I think it looks stupid.</Source>
      <Dest>在那种情况下看起来很傻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Considering the source, I will take that as a compliment.</Source>
      <Dest>只要是出自你口，我都会当成赞美来听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And will the vampires return to their coffins and await the day you are ready?</Source>
      <Dest>你准备好把吸血鬼送回棺材然后再等一天了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Perhaps another time.</Source>
      <Dest>下次再说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Perhaps another time.</Source>
      <Dest>下次再说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you refuse to walk in the light, then I will drag you into it, lest the wicked strand you in darkness.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你不愿在有光的地方行动，那我会把你拖进来。以避免那些邪恶的东西把你困在黑暗中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Our destination is north, to Cronvangr Cave. I will fill you in on the details as we walk.</Source>
      <Dest>Our destination is north, to Cronvangr Cave. I will fill you in on the details as we walk.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Perhaps another time.</Source>
      <Dest>下次再说吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure, why not.</Source>
      <Dest>好啊，为什么不呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure, why not.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，为什么不呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do not respond as if you are performing some menial task that you cannot be bothered with. Our foes are abominations of the worst kind.</Source>
      <Dest>倘若你执行一些卑微的不能被打扰的任务就别回复了。我们的敌人可不是什么好货色。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure, why not.</Source>
      <Dest>好啊，为什么不呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure, why not.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，为什么不呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They cannot be eradicated with anything less than our full attention. Do you understand?</Source>
      <Dest> 我们如果不尽全力肯定消灭不了他们。你明白吗?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure, why not.</Source>
      <Dest>好啊，为什么不呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure, why not.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，为什么不呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now, we must venture north, to Cronvangr Cave. I will fill you in on the details as we walk.</Source>
      <Dest>现在，我们必须冒险向北，抵达克隆万格洞穴。细节我们路上说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How may I be of service, Vigilant?</Source>
      <Dest>我该怎样提供服务，警戒者（Vigilant）？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your alacrity is commendable. You would make a fine Vigilant, if you were to wear the cloth.</Source>
      <Dest>你的敏捷是值得称道的。你会成为一个很好的警戒者——如果你穿上这身衣服的话。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How may I be of service, Vigilant?</Source>
      <Dest>我该怎样提供服务，警戒者（Vigilant）？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alas we have no time for initiation rituals.  Thus you will accompany me as an honorary Vigilant to Cronvangr Cave in Eastmarch.</Source>
      <Dest>可惜我们没有时间举行入会仪式了. 所以你要跟着我们去东陲领.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your flippant responses mock the Gods when they alone protect you from the Daedric scourge.</Source>
      <Dest>Your flippant responses mock the Gods when they alone protect you from the Daedric scourge.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If by aid you mean cure my foot fungus, then yes, Stendarr was a big help.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你所说的援助是指治疗我脚肿的话，那么是的，斯丹纳尔提供了很大帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If by aid you mean cure my foot fungus, then yes, Stendarr was a big help.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你所说的援助是指治疗我脚肿的话，那么是的，斯丹纳尔提供了很大帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I will grant you a chance at redemption, if you are willing.</Source>
      <Dest>不过我能保证给你一个赎罪的机会，要是你愿意的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Stendarr's blessing was a means to an end. Nothing more.</Source>
      <Dest>斯丹纳尔的祝福是通向终结的途径。仅此而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And you are nothing more than a beast, if you run away from the light of the Gods. But I will grant you a chance at redemption, if you are willing.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你从神灵的光辉中逃离，就不能算是比野兽更强的东西。而我愿意给你一个自我救赎的机会，如果你愿意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes. Praise be to Stendarr.</Source>
      <Dest>是的。赞扬斯丹纳尔.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Excellent. And as a true disciple of Stendarr's teachings, perhaps it is time you lent your blade to the cause.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，作为斯坦达的忠实信徒，或许是时候将原因归咎于你的刀刃了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm working on it.</Source>
      <Dest>我正在想办法啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I see. If this pilgrimage you are on does not interest you, then it is time you abandon it to serve Stendarr in a more tangible capacity.</Source>
      <Dest>我明白。如果这次朝圣不再让你感兴趣了，那就是你放弃它转而更脚踏实地的为斯丹纳尔服务的时候了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then it is time for you to serve Stendarr in a more tangible capacity.</Source>
      <Dest>是时候该用你切实的力量服侍于斯丹纳尔了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's done, and I'm looking for work.</Source>
      <Dest>结束了。现在我在找工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then you will have it, pilgrim.  Walk always in the light.</Source>
      <Dest>那么你会得到它，朝圣者。永远走在光明中吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I simply require Stendarr's blessing, so that I may prove my faith.</Source>
      <Dest>我需要的仅仅是斯坦达的祝福，那就足以支持我的信心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I ask that you lend me Stendarr's mercy in a trial of the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>老天在上，我请求你借给我Stendarr's mercy。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then your quest is a worthy one.  For such trials are the flame from which valor is forged.</Source>
      <Dest>那么你的任务就深有意义了。因为这试炼将成为铸就英勇的炉焰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I ask that you lend me Stendarr's mercy in a trial of the Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>老天在上，我请求你借给我Stendarr's mercy。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In return for your service to Stendarr, I will offer what I can.  What would you have of me?</Source>
      <Dest>在你回到 斯丹纳尔的岗位后, 我会尽我所能的给你我能给的.  你会给我什么呢?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am to help a young pupil vanquish her master.</Source>
      <Dest>我要去帮一个小徒弟去干掉他的师父。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This sounds as if it is a personal vendetta.  I myself want no part of it.</Source>
      <Dest>这听起来像是一个私人仇杀。我自己对这件事没有任何兴趣。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am to help a young pupil vanquish her master.</Source>
      <Dest>我要去帮一个小徒弟去干掉他的师父。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, Stendarr demands I show mercy.  The Gods clearly favor you, and your actions here should not go unrewarded.</Source>
      <Dest>不过呢，斯丹纳尔希望我能仁慈些。众神显然很支持你，而你在这儿所做的一切应该有所回报。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am to help a young pupil vanquish her master.</Source>
      <Dest>我要去帮一个小徒弟去干掉他的师父。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well.  What is it you would have of me?</Source>
      <Dest>非常好。那么你想从我这儿拿到什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A man wishes to kill a troublesome pupil, and needs Stendarr's help.</Source>
      <Dest>一个人想杀了他的问题学生，需要斯坦达的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then your quest is irrelevant, and to undertake it would be an intolerable waste of time.</Source>
      <Dest>所以你的问题是如此地不相干，甚至去思考一下它都是对时间的一种亵渎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A man wishes to kill a troublesome pupil, and needs Stendarr's help.</Source>
      <Dest>一个人想杀了他的问题学生，需要斯坦达的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, Stendarr demands I be patient.  The Gods clearly favor you, and your actions here should not go unrewarded.</Source>
      <Dest>不过，斯坦达尔命令我要耐心。神灵们显然是喜欢你的，所以你做的一切不会无功而返的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A man wishes to kill a troublesome pupil, and needs Stendarr's help.</Source>
      <Dest>一个人想杀了他的问题学生，需要斯坦达的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Very well. What is it you would have of me?</Source>
      <Dest>很好。你想要我做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am on a pilgrimage to Honor the Divines, and require Stendarr's blessing.</Source>
      <Dest>我在朝圣的旅途上，并且需要斯坦达的祝福。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, it seems the Gods shine their gaze upon you, and Stendarr could have very well brought you here, so that I may drag your foes to the light.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，似乎诸神都在云端之上凝视着你。并且斯丹纳尔也很好的把你带来了这里。那么我就可以把你的敌人拖入光线之中了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have my attention, pilgrim.  What is it you ask of me?</Source>
      <Dest>我注意到你了，朝圣者。你想干什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I am on a pilgrimage to Honor the Divines, and require Stendarr's blessing.</Source>
      <Dest>我在朝圣的旅途上，并且需要斯坦达的祝福。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this war you mentioned.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你提到的那场战争。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We came here on rumors that a Dawnguard was forming, and found scant evidence as to why.  Keeper Carcette saw no reason to pursue it further.</Source>
      <Dest>我们是听说黎明守卫正在重组的传言而来的，但不知道为什么要重组黎明守卫。守护者凯西提也认为没必要重组。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this war you mentioned.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你提到的那场战争。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nevertheless, she sent a few of us to scout the Rift, in the event any leads turned up.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，她让我们几个去侦察裂痕领，结果什么线索都被找到了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this war you mentioned.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你提到的那场战争。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was on my way here when I was assaulted by 4 nightwalkers. I would not be alive if not for a chance encounter with my old Thalmor friend Jerulith.</Source>
      <Dest>我在来这里的路上被4个夜盗袭击了。要不是碰见了我的梭默朋友捷尔勒，我早就死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this war you mentioned.</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我你提到的那场战争。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Her magic is still formidable, and her politics still reprehensible.  Thankfully, on that day I only needed one.</Source>
      <Dest>她的法力还是那么强大，而她的人品还是那么糟糕。幸运的是，到了那天我只需要其中之一。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have no idea what this Hall is you're referring to.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道你提及的Hall指的是什么.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Hall of the Vigilant, adventurer.  The vanguard in the fight to rid Tamriel of Daedra in all its forms.</Source>
      <Dest>警戒者会堂么，冒险者。那是肃清塔玛瑞尔魔族战争的急先锋们的所在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I talked to the keeper there recently. Trust me. She's fine.</Source>
      <Dest>我最近跟守卫聊了聊，相信我，她很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then it appears my missives reached her in time.  We must pray their awareness is enough.</Source>
      <Dest>那么看起来我的公文及时送到了她那儿。我们必须祈祷他们有足够的警觉性。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry...the Hall of Vigilants was burned asunder.</Source>
      <Dest>我很遗憾地说…警戒者之厅已经被烧成一片废墟了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then Stendarr have mercy upon us all.</Source>
      <Dest>斯丹纳尔怜悯我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I apologize, but I cannot and will not abandon the Vigilants at this hour.  War is upon us.</Source>
      <Dest>I apologize, but I cannot and will not abandon the Vigilants at this hour.  War is upon us.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have come seeking your aid.</Source>
      <Dest>我来寻求你的帮助.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have come seeking your aid.</Source>
      <Dest>我来寻求你的帮助.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can only hope those at the Hall have prepared themselves.</Source>
      <Dest>我只希望在会堂的那些人已经准备好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My business is none of yours.</Source>
      <Dest>不关你的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you expect me to be satisfied with that answer?  We are at war!</Source>
      <Dest>你想让我满意这个回答吗？我们可在打仗呢！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My business is none of yours.</Source>
      <Dest>不关你的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can only hope those at the Hall have prepared themselves.</Source>
      <Dest>我只希望在会堂的那些人已经准备好了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Halt.  You approach a Vigilant of Stendarr.  State your business.</Source>
      <Dest>站住。你正在靠近斯丹纳尔的警戒者。 说吧，你是干什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Halt.  So we meet again, adventurer.  What is your business here?</Source>
      <Dest>站住。我们又见面了，冒险者。你到底在这里做什麽？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So you return. I trust Stendarr's blessing aided you in your quest?</Source>
      <Dest>所以你回来了。我相信斯丹纳尔的祝福在你的探险中一定对你有些帮助吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You fought valiantly, adventurer, and I am in your debt.</Source>
      <Dest>你的战斗英勇无比，冒险家，我欠你的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you have proven yourself to walk in the light, then perhaps I was wrong to deny your request.  What exactly is this task you speak of?</Source>
      <Dest>你已经证明自己走上正道，所以我之前拒绝你可能是错的。那请问你所说的这个任务到底是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's humor to be found in even the dullest stone. Take you for instance.</Source>
      <Dest>对于你来说，幽默就像是枯燥乏味的石头一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You would not find things so humorous had you lived during the Oblivion Crisis.  </Source>
      <Dest>当你活在湮灭危机之中，你不会觉得有什么事是好笑的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That is the problem with people today. Your lifespans are short, your memories are shorter, and you have the attention span of a spadetail.  </Source>
      <Dest>这就是现在人们要去面对的问题。你的生命很短，你的记忆也很短，而你却把注意力放在无意义的事情上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's humor to be found in even the dullest stone. Take you for instance.</Source>
      <Dest>对于你来说，幽默就像是枯燥乏味的石头一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're right.  Perhaps I should take your endeavors more seriously.</Source>
      <Dest>你说得对。也许我应该更认真地看待你的努力。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Words will not suffice.  Go forth and vanquish our true enemy, and prove your sentiments are genuine.  </Source>
      <Dest>单单说话是没用的。出发去征服我们真正的敌人，证明你说的是真的吧！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Only the foundation isn't crumbling. There are far more deaths caused by war.</Source>
      <Dest>只有基地还没摇摇欲坠。战争造成更多的死亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A testament to our efforts here in Skyrim.  Now if you'll excuse me, I have matters I need to attend to.  </Source>
      <Dest>这就是我们为了天际努力的证据。现在，如果可以的话，我有事需要去做。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is getting way too heavy.  I just wanted to chat.</Source>
      <Dest>越说越严重，我只是想聊天。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You approached me. If you do not agree with my counsel, then perhaps you should converse with someone else.  Someone with your love for frivolity.</Source>
      <Dest>是你来找我的。如果你不同意我的决策，那么也许你应该和其他人谈谈，一些会喜欢你那轻率性格的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I seem to have misplaced my pet Atronach. Will you help me find him?</Source>
      <Dest>我好像忘记了我的元素宠物。请问你能帮我找到他吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Vigilants of Stendarr have no tolerance for Daedra, regardless if they are bound to your will.  Nor are we merciful to those who command them.</Source>
      <Dest>斯丹纳尔警戒者是决不宽恕魔族，人们一不小心就会被他们附身，而我们亦不会对那些被他们控制的人抱有怜悯之心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And we most certainly do not condone keeping them as pets.</Source>
      <Dest>我们最不能容忍把它们当宠物来养。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I seem to have misplaced my pet Atronach. Will you help me find him?</Source>
      <Dest>我好像忘记了我的元素宠物。请问你能帮我找到他吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You know, you're kind of cute when you're angry.  Which is all the time.</Source>
      <Dest>你知道的，当你生气的时候总是特别萌。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I fail to see where this is going.</Source>
      <Dest>我没能看出这件事的走向。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would like you to cure me.</Source>
      <Dest>我希望你能为我治疗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stendarr's Light purify you of your ills.</Source>
      <Dest>斯坦德尔的光芒将净化你的疾病。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like all Vigilants of Stendarr, I scout various regions of Skyrim to prevent the proliferation of the unrighteous.</Source>
      <Dest>就如所有斯丹纳尔警戒者一样，我在天际到处巡视，以防止邪恶滋生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your responsibilities?</Source>
      <Dest>你的职责是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We gather information from the locals to locate their whereabouts, then we hunt the offenders for the glory of Stendarr.  </Source>
      <Dest>We gather information from the locals to locate their whereabouts, then we hunt the offenders for the glory of Stendarr.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your responsibilities?</Source>
      <Dest>你的职责是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When our task is complete, we report our findings to Keeper Carcette.</Source>
      <Dest>我们完成任务之后，就把我们的发现向守护者凯西提报告。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your responsibilities?</Source>
      <Dest>你的职责是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The map downstairs is marked with the locations of both previous and suspected Daedric activity.  </Source>
      <Dest>楼下那张地图标记了魔族以前出现过和怀疑有活动的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are your responsibilities?</Source>
      <Dest>你的职责是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Vigil will be watching you.</Source>
      <Dest>守夜人会注视着你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Walk always in the light, or we will drag you to it.</Source>
      <Dest>你须行走于光明之下，否则我们必让你受光明的制裁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stendarr be with you.</Source>
      <Dest>斯坦德尔与你同在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Make it quick.</Source>
      <Dest>快点好吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have proven yourself a warrior worthy of Stendarr, and you have earned my respect.</Source>
      <Dest>你已经证明自己是名副其实的斯丹纳尔的战士，你也赢得了我的尊敬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you for all your assistance, Honorary Vigilant.</Source>
      <Dest>谢谢你的帮助，名誉警戒者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Need something?</Source>
      <Dest>有事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>None escape the Vigil. All come into the light.</Source>
      <Dest>无人能逃避守夜人的审判。一切将昭示于光明之下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Mercy of Stendarr does not extend to Daedra worshippers.</Source>
      <Dest>斯坦德尔的怜悯是绝不会降临到魔族崇拜者的身上的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The suffering the Daedra cause will not go unpunished.</Source>
      <Dest>魔族会为他们亲手造成的苦难付出代价。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wherever the Daedra hide, the Vigil of Stendarr will cast them into the light.</Source>
      <Dest>无论魔族躲藏在何处，我们都会把它们揪出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You speak to a Vigilant of Stendarr. Cavort with any Daedra, and we will hunt you down.</Source>
      <Dest>你正在和一位斯坦德尔的守备人说话。只要你胆敢与魔族为伍，我们就要消灭你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stendarr's Mercy be upon you, for the Vigil has none to spare.</Source>
      <Dest>愿斯坦德尔怜悯你吧，守夜人是绝不姑息一切罪恶的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're bloated with disease. The Vigilant of Stendarr can help you, as long as you promise to never assist the Daedra.</Source>
      <Dest>你已经病入膏肓了。斯坦德尔的守备人们能帮助你，但你要承诺今后不可再与魔族相勾结。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
