<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you've lost more than a son.</Source>
      <Dest>那么你失去的不只是儿子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you've lost more than a son.</Source>
      <Dest>那么你失去的不只是儿子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So you've lost more than a son.</Source>
      <Dest>那么你失去的不只是儿子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your husband was beautiful?</Source>
      <Dest>你的丈夫漂亮吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wandering can be dangerous.  Have you considered wearing armor?</Source>
      <Dest>四处闲逛也可能会有危险，你不打算找件盔甲穿吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Wandering can be dangerous.  Have you considered wearing armor?</Source>
      <Dest>四处闲逛也可能会有危险，你不打算找件盔甲穿吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't see your son.  Is he by chance standing behind you?</Source>
      <Dest>我没看到过你的儿子，你要不转身看看他是不是在你身后？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't see your son.  Is he by chance standing behind you?</Source>
      <Dest>我没看到过你的儿子，你要不转身看看他是不是在你身后？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And now he's dead and he left you behind.  How selfish of him.</Source>
      <Dest>现在他死了并留下你孤身一人，真是个自私的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And now he's dead and he left you behind.  How selfish of him.</Source>
      <Dest>现在他死了并留下你孤身一人，真是个自私的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>And now he's dead and he left you behind.  How selfish of him.</Source>
      <Dest>现在他死了并留下你孤身一人，真是个自私的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're his mother. You could've stopped him.</Source>
      <Dest>你是他妈，你应该可以阻止他。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're his mother. You could've stopped him.</Source>
      <Dest>你是他妈，你应该可以阻止他。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're his mother. You could've stopped him.</Source>
      <Dest>你是他妈，你应该可以阻止他。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're his mother. You could've stopped him.</Source>
      <Dest>你是他妈，你应该可以阻止他。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An optimist like myself.  There are too few in this land.</Source>
      <Dest>像我这样的乐观主义者，在这片土地上太少了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An optimist like myself.  There are too few in this land.</Source>
      <Dest>像我这样的乐观主义者，在这片土地上太少了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An optimist like myself.  There are too few in this land.</Source>
      <Dest>像我这样的乐观主义者，在这片土地上太少了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Even brave men can turn into an anxious nursemaid in such a situation.</Source>
      <Dest>在这种状况下，就连最勇敢的人也会急得像热锅上的蚂蚁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Even brave men can turn into an anxious nursemaid in such a situation.</Source>
      <Dest>在这种状况下，就连最勇敢的人也会急得像热锅上的蚂蚁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think you and your son were so different?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会认为你跟你儿子之间有很大差异？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think you and your son were so different?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会认为你跟你儿子之间有很大差异？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think you and your son were so different?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你会认为你跟你儿子之间有很大差异？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does that relate to you and your son?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让你与你的儿子紧密相连？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does that relate to you and your son?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让你与你的儿子紧密相连？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's always a risk attacking an armed warrior.  Better to rob the weak.</Source>
      <Dest>攻击那些武装到牙齿的家伙终归是有风险的，抢那些弱者会比较好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's always a risk attacking an armed warrior.  Better to rob the weak.</Source>
      <Dest>攻击那些武装到牙齿的家伙终归是有风险的，抢那些弱者会比较好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's always a risk attacking an armed warrior.  Better to rob the weak.</Source>
      <Dest>攻击那些武装到牙齿的家伙终归是有风险的，抢那些弱者会比较好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>There's always a risk attacking an armed warrior.  Better to rob the weak.</Source>
      <Dest>攻击那些武装到牙齿的家伙终归是有风险的，抢那些弱者会比较好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you react to that?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么回应的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you react to that?</Source>
      <Dest>你怎么回应的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your son never should have wandered away from home.  It was foolish.</Source>
      <Dest>你儿子不该离家出走。这太愚蠢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your son never should have wandered away from home.  It was foolish.</Source>
      <Dest>你儿子不该离家出走。这太愚蠢了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A common story. Parents who can't let go, and children who refuse to be held.</Source>
      <Dest>常有的事，父母对子女的事情不愿放手，而子女想要自己拿主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A common story. Parents who can't let go, and children who refuse to be held.</Source>
      <Dest>常有的事，父母对子女的事情不愿放手，而子女想要自己拿主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A common story. Parents who can't let go, and children who refuse to be held.</Source>
      <Dest>常有的事，父母对子女的事情不愿放手，而子女想要自己拿主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A common story. Parents who can't let go, and children who refuse to be held.</Source>
      <Dest>常有的事，父母对子女的事情不愿放手，而子女想要自己拿主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What were you like before your son died?</Source>
      <Dest>你儿子没死之前你喜欢做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry for your loss.</Source>
      <Dest>对你的不幸我很遗憾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I'm sorry for your loss.</Source>
      <Dest>对你的不幸我很遗憾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The weather's alright.  Nothing to complain about.</Source>
      <Dest>天气还可以呀，没什么好抱怨的吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The weather's alright.  Nothing to complain about.</Source>
      <Dest>天气还可以呀，没什么好抱怨的吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The weather's alright.  Nothing to complain about.</Source>
      <Dest>天气还可以呀，没什么好抱怨的吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I like to target old Argonian wanderers myself.</Source>
      <Dest>我个人比较喜欢拿上了年纪的亚龙人当靶子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I like to target old Argonian wanderers myself.</Source>
      <Dest>我个人比较喜欢拿上了年纪的亚龙人当靶子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I like to target old Argonian wanderers myself.</Source>
      <Dest>我个人比较喜欢拿上了年纪的亚龙人当靶子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I slept with a candle burning, and never left my hut at night, and dared not brave the rain.</Source>
      <Dest>我点着蜡烛睡觉，夜晚绝不出屋，也从不敢淋雨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I told him there's a reason we settle in towns and villages, and why travelers always stick to the road.</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉他我们在城镇和村庄定居是有原因的，以及为什么旅行者们坚持走这条路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You adventurers are so kind.  It was a similar one who found my son's body and delivered the letter to me.  The one I always feared to read.</Source>
      <Dest>你们这些冒险者真是好心肠。上次就有那么一位找到了我儿子的尸体的给我送了信来。我一直不敢去读。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, traveler!  Don't you just love the rain?  The source of all life, and it just drops from the sky.  Jumping in puddles is fun too.</Source>
      <Dest>你好啊，旅行者！你热爱这雨水吗？一切生命的源泉啊，就这样从天而降。就连跳进水坑也是那么有趣啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, traveler!  Don't you just love cloudy weather?  </Source>
      <Dest>你好啊，旅行者！难道你不喜欢这种阴天儿吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sure your way is much better.  You're the professional, after all.</Source>
      <Dest>我确信你的选择要好得多。毕竟你是专业的嘛。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whenever he left he always kept a letter on his person, so that if he died, perhaps some kind and gentle soul would deliver the letter to me.</Source>
      <Dest>他每次离开，都会留下一封亲笔写的信。这样的话就算他死了，一些善良而温柔的灵魂或许会把那封信寄给我。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He let me holler and scream, and when I had exhausted all my energy, he gave me a kiss, and said goodbye, knowing it could've been his last.</Source>
      <Dest>他让我大喊和尖叫，而那时我已经用尽了所有的力气。他给了我一个吻，跟我说再见。我们都知道这可能是他的最后一次。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, but who will serve as the matron of this old Argonian?  Maybe a dragon will mistake me for its hatchling!</Source>
      <Dest>噢，但谁来担任这个老亚龙人的护士长呢？或许一头龙会把我误认成它的幼崽！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And isn't that a wonderful thing?  To be without complaints?  I think it is something worth celebrating.</Source>
      <Dest>那不是很了不起的事吗？没什么好抱怨的吧？我想是值得庆祝一下的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I certainly hope not. I don't want to spend my last days in a nest, subsisting on a diet of regurgitated goat parts. </Source>
      <Dest>当然不希望。我可不想在最后几天还待在家里，吃着吃剩下的山羊肉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I made oceans out of ponds, and mountains out of anthills.  I was afraid to live because I was scared to die.</Source>
      <Dest>我把池塘集成大海，我把蚁穴堆成山峰。我害怕活着是因为我恐惧死亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Besides, if you were a bandit clan, who would you consider a more appealing target, a sweet old farmer or a single soldier dressed in iron?</Source>
      <Dest>首先，如果你是个强盗，谁会是你优先考虑的目标呢？一个可爱的老农民，还是个全副武装的士兵？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My son was right.  There really are fates worse than death!</Source>
      <Dest>我儿子说得对。真的有些命运比死亡更糟！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No. Our son.</Source>
      <Dest>不。我们的儿子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was so caught up in the anger over him leaving, I looked past what it really meant, should he fail to return.</Source>
      <Dest>因为他的离开，我怒火中烧。我过去也终于意识到了他离开的真正含义，他应该不会回来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, traveler!  Don't you just love snow?  Like pearls from the sky, and every flake has its own pattern.</Source>
      <Dest>你好啊，旅行者！你难道不喜欢雪吗？就像是从天空洒落的珍珠，每一片都有自己的形状。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I lost my husband to the Great War.  It was so long ago I forget which side he was on.  As if that makes a difference.  War makes widows of us all.</Source>
      <Dest>世界大战夺走了我的丈夫。这是很久以前的事儿了，久到我都忘了他站在哪一边了。不过这没什么不同。战争造就遗孀。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say hounds, on the other hand, can smell things leagues away. They know when a visitor is coming, or if fresh game lies hidden behind the brush.</Source>
      <Dest>另一方面，他们说，猎犬能够大老远就闻到东西，它们知道什么时候来访者会来，或是否有隐藏在灌木丛中的猎物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now that I wander in his stead, I see my folly.  For the only way to find yourself is to lose yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我发现他的好处了, 我看见了我的愚蠢。 正所谓：若欲寻找真我，需先迷失自我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whenever we open our eyes and see something, it takes a fraction of a second to register in our minds, and understand what we're seeing.</Source>
      <Dest>无论何时，当我们睁开眼睛看到一个东西时,我们的思维都需要一点时间来记录它们，然后理解我们看到的是什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You sound not unlike a certain Argonian mother, a dozen or so years ago.  Now I see that I was the fool.</Source>
      <Dest>在十几年前，你的声音不像是一个亚龙人的母亲，但现在我觉得自己是一个傻瓜。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I still remember the worry on his face when our son was hatched.  (Sigh)  He was so beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>我仍然记得，当我们的孩子出生时，他的满面愁容。（叹息）他当时是那么的美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I let the fear consume me, because I didn't want to ever again feel the pain of being left behind.</Source>
      <Dest>我让自己的恐惧支配着我，因为我再也不想感受到被丢弃的痛楚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Better for the scales and the eyes during the day, and at night, they drift over the moon like a warm bed sheet tucks in a child.</Source>
      <Dest>在白天，不论是对鳞片还是对眼睛来说这都很有益处，而到了晚上，那些乌云会飘到月亮之上，就像是一个孩子躺在温暖的被褥里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That night I think he sloughed off more scales than there are coins in the Emperor's treasury.</Source>
      <Dest>那天晚上，我想他脱落的鳞片比国库的硬币还要多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If one of us had to be selfish, it was better him than me, for his happiness is my reward.  </Source>
      <Dest>如果我们之中必须有一个人做出牺牲的话，比起他来我更适合，只要他幸福我就满足了。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I should know, I used to always complain about how my son would wander off pointlessly without direction.</Source>
      <Dest>我应该知道的，我过去经常抱怨我的儿子是如何漫无目的又毫无方向感的出去晃悠的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's our destiny as mortals, to always look at the past.  To always be a fraction of a second behind. </Source>
      <Dest>这是我们作为凡人的命运，总是看向过去。总是停留几分之一秒之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I disagree with your assessment.  He's given me my life back.  </Source>
      <Dest>但对于你的评判我不敢苟同。是他帮我找回了生命的意义。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, traveler!  The weather is positively sublime, isn't it?  Crisp air and a clear sky, the Divines have truly blessed us today.</Source>
      <Dest>你好，旅行者！这天气还真是好得出奇呀！清新的空气湛蓝的天，今天真是有圣灵祝福我们呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Somehow, I think he knew that. Which is why I think he waited until he was gone to tell me what I needed to hear.</Source>
      <Dest>其实，我以为他知情的。这也是我为什么傻傻地等着他走到面前来告诉我那些我需要知道的事情的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, traveler!  How's the weather outside today?  Wonderful, I imagine.</Source>
      <Dest>你好啊，旅行者！今天外面的天气怎么样？我猜一定非常棒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My son lived a fuller life in his short time than I had in all my years cramped in that small hut by the pond.</Source>
      <Dest>我儿子在他短暂的生命中比我这么多年蜷缩在池塘边的小屋经历丰富得多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was a cynic and a pessimist.  But most of all I was a coward.</Source>
      <Dest>我又厌世又悲观。好吧其实确切地说我就是个懦夫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I would wipe the counters clean four times a day, and overcook the food because I feared the meat had parasites.</Source>
      <Dest>我会把柜台一天擦四遍，还会把食物煮过头，就因为我担心里头有寄生虫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But my son, he lived his life by the code of the wanderer.  Now I too have succumbed to the wanderlust that is my namesake.</Source>
      <Dest>但我的儿子，他遵循流浪者的信条而活。我现在也已认同流浪者也是我的代名词。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Such is how the beasts of the wild operate.  They target the young, even when it draws the ire of the mother.</Source>
      <Dest>在大自然，野兽就是这么做的。它们会冒着幼崽母亲的愤怒强夺它们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh I tried.  I lashed my tail and stomped my feet, and when that didn't work, I nearly took his horns off with a kitchen knife.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，我试过了。在他没干活儿的时候，我又甩尾巴又跺脚，几乎都用菜刀把他的犄角切下来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My son though, he could always see forward, even when all I wanted was to go back to the way things were.</Source>
      <Dest>但我的儿子总能向前看。即使是在我想要一切都回到原来的样子的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That sounds rather sinister of you.  I'm sure you say it in jest, of course.  If not, well, it seems rather inefficient for someone so strong.</Source>
      <Dest>听起来你更危险了。当然，我很确定你说的是笑话。如果不是，呃，对一个如此强大的人来说这似乎稍微有点儿没用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So he never worried about whether he left on good terms or bad.  He knew that we'd find common ground in the end.</Source>
      <Dest>所以他从不担心与人相处的是好是坏。他知道我们最终会找到共同点的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, although my son never pulled away, never ran off in the middle of the night.  When he felt the urge to wander, he always told me when.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，不过我的儿子绝不会离开，绝不会在半夜跑掉。当他感受到想要漫步的冲动时，总会告诉我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He told me those people went from place to place, but they never traveled. </Source>
      <Dest>他告诉我这些人来自各地，但他们从不旅行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wake up these days and the air is fresher, the colors are brighter, and adventure waits for me around the bend where the mountain flowers grow.</Source>
      <Dest>这几天起来我发现空气是清新的，天是蓝的，在不远处等着我去探险的群山上鲜花盛开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So true.  I was once a pessimist myself.  Never thought there was anything but danger outside the swamps of Black Marsh.</Source>
      <Dest>确实如此。我曾是个悲观主义者。从没想过在黑沼泽省的沼泽外除了危险还有什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, I think I had to give him a bit of wine to calm him down.   As in three flagons! (Laughs)</Source>
      <Dest>对，我想我要弄些酒来放倒他。大概三壶！(笑声)</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now I amble across Tamriel so that I may get lost, and in doing so discover all the wonders I never found.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我漫步在泰姆瑞尔大陆，我可能会迷失方向，也正因为如此探索了全部我之前从未找到过的奇观。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You'd have to rob and steal from a hundred old folks to get the same amount of coin from a noble. Oh, but look at me, telling you how to do your job.</Source>
      <Dest>你必须从几百个老头那要么偷要么抢几个从贵族那来的硬币。哦，看着我，我告诉你怎么搞定你的活。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where else have you visited?</Source>
      <Dest>你还去过哪些地方？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where else have you visited?</Source>
      <Dest>你还去过哪些地方？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where else have you visited?</Source>
      <Dest>你还去过哪些地方？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where else have you visited?</Source>
      <Dest>你还去过哪些地方？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In Skyrim, everything is cold and bleak and sometimes wet.   You must be drunk.</Source>
      <Dest>在天际省，所有东西要么是冰凉的要么是湿漉的，我看你是喝多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In Skyrim, everything is cold and bleak and sometimes wet.   You must be drunk.</Source>
      <Dest>在天际省，所有东西要么是冰凉的要么是湿漉的，我看你是喝多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In Skyrim, everything is cold and bleak and sometimes wet.   You must be drunk.</Source>
      <Dest>在天际省，所有东西要么是冰凉的要么是湿漉的，我看你是喝多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you think he needed a guide?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么认为他需要个向导？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why did you think he needed a guide?</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么认为他需要个向导？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good point. Iron is a fungible commodity. Old ladies are not.</Source>
      <Dest>说到点子上了，铁是可以被别的东西所取代的，但老女人不行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good point. Iron is a fungible commodity. Old ladies are not.</Source>
      <Dest>说到点子上了，铁是可以被别的东西所取代的，但老女人不行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you enjoy most about Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢天际省的什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you enjoy most about Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>你最喜欢天际省的什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The name is apt, albeit it's never a good idea for Argonians to use that word.</Source>
      <Dest>名字倒是恰如其分，虽然作为亚龙人不太应该用那个词。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The name is apt, albeit it's never a good idea for Argonians to use that word.</Source>
      <Dest>名字倒是恰如其分，虽然作为亚龙人不太应该用那个词。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If I were a bandit, I'd kill the armored one and make the old lady my cook.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我是强盗，我就杀了那个穿盔甲的然后让老婆婆给我做饭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If I were a bandit, I'd kill the armored one and make the old lady my cook.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我是强盗，我就杀了那个穿盔甲的然后让老婆婆给我做饭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your son.</Source>
      <Dest>说说你儿子的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your son.</Source>
      <Dest>说说你儿子的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about your son.</Source>
      <Dest>说说你儿子的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Until next time.</Source>
      <Dest>下回见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whenever he left on one of his adventures, I implored him to visit the library in Thorn so he could borrow one of the travel guides on the Empire.</Source>
      <Dest>当他踏上他的探险旅途之时，我恳求他去拜访荆棘中的图书馆这样他可以借一本帝国的旅游指南。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye, and good wandering.</Source>
      <Dest>再见，祝你旅途愉快。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The weather is positively sublime, isn't it?  Crisp air and a clear sky, the Divines have truly blessed us today.</Source>
      <Dest>天气真好，不是吗？新鲜的空气和晴朗的天空。今日，圣灵们真正的祝福着我们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He would pat me on the shoulder and laugh.  It was a voice so full of energy that it shook my tail, but a pat so gentle it could've been a child's. </Source>
      <Dest>他会拍拍我的肩膀大笑的。那激情四射的大嗓门让我尾巴都打颤，可拍肩的那一下却轻柔得像是小孩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I'm sure mothers say that about their children regardless, but the clan girls adored him too.  </Source>
      <Dest>哦，我知道天下所有的母亲都是那样毫无顾忌地夸自己的孩子的，但族里的姑娘们也都爱慕他。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when I look upon it all I feel nothing but warmth, even when people insist it's so cold.</Source>
      <Dest>在我看来，一切都让我感觉那么的温暖，即使人们都坚持感觉很冷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I traversed through the Fall Forest, and watched the opera of leaves as they were led across the stage by the autumn wind.</Source>
      <Dest>我横穿过整个秋林，看着秋风搭建的舞台上游走着树叶演出的歌剧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But I realize now it wasn't where he was going that bothered me.  I just didn't want him to go.</Source>
      <Dest>但是我意识到呆在这地方他就不能缠着我了。我只是不想就这么让他离开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't you just love cloudy weather?</Source>
      <Dest>你不就是喜欢多云的天气么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's a good thing I didn't become a maid, or else some noble might get the wrong idea!</Source>
      <Dest>幸好我没有成为一个女仆，不然某些贵族可就要铸下大错啦！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Drunk on life, child, and happiness.  There's no room in my heart for anything else.  Not today, not tomorrow, and not ever again.</Source>
      <Dest>为生活，孩子和幸福而心醉神迷的我，心中没有空间能够容纳其他任何事。今天没有，明天没有，而且再也不会有了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Greetings, traveler!  Don't you just love the snow?  Like pearls from the sky, and every flake has its own pattern.</Source>
      <Dest>你好啊，旅行者！你难道不喜欢雪吗？它们如珍珠从天而降，每一片雪花都有它独一无二图案。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yeah, it'd be quite difficult to take me to the local fence.  No, the bandits don't bother me.  Some even say hello.</Source>
      <Dest>确实，把我带去当地的销赃地恐怕并非易事。不过，那些强盗并没有为难我。有一些甚至向我问了好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tidings, stranger!</Source>
      <Dest>注意，陌生人！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.  A fine day to you.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。今天是个好日子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I would worry that without the guide he'd wander off to someplace dangerous, or get lost in the wilderness.</Source>
      <Dest>我很担心没有向导他会跑到一些危险的地方去，或者在野外迷路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I made the pilgrimage up the 7,000 steps and watched the sun as it drifted into sea, glazing the sky in layers of magma.</Source>
      <Dest>我经过了7000个台阶的朝圣之旅，看到了太阳坠入大海，把天空染上了琉璃的颜色</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Forgive me, I haven't told you my name.  I am called Wander-Lust, and the name is apt, for I now wander all of Tamriel in honor of my son.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉啊，我还没说我的名字。叫我流浪姐好了，这个名字很恰当，因为我为了儿子的荣耀之名流浪于整个泰姆瑞尔大陆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet for all his stature and bravery, I feared for his safety.</Source>
      <Dest>但正是由于他那身材和勇气，我才会为他的安危而担忧啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And that's what he'd always be to me. A child. My child.  </Source>
      <Dest>因此他永远是我的。他是个孩子，我的孩子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And to serve his memory, I've spent the last ten years getting lost, in hopes of discovering all the wonders I never found.</Source>
      <Dest>而为了纪念他的回忆，我花了近十年的时间四处游荡，盼望能看到我从未见过的奇迹。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't you just love the rain?  The source of all life, and it just drops from the sky.  Jumping in puddles is fun too.</Source>
      <Dest>你不喜欢雨吗？生命的源泉，就这样从天而落。而且在泥地里撒欢也很好玩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Even the wolves tend to be kind to me.  They must not like the taste of stale Argonian jerky.</Source>
      <Dest>就连狼在我面前都很温顺。它们一定是不喜欢一块老亚龙人肉干的味道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That seems like an unwise strategy, having the person who most despises you responsible for preparing your meals.</Source>
      <Dest>这并不是个聪明的主意，那家伙可不会认认真真地给你做饭。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>May you lose your way, and find adventure.</Source>
      <Dest>愿你失去方向，找到你想要的冒险。</Dest>
    </String>
	    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I suppose if you're married, that may already be the case!</Source>
      <Dest>我想你大概是已经结婚了，我没说错吧！</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
