<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The answer is a cloak.  A mortal wears many, and it often covers the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>答案是斗篷。很多普通人都穿，而且常用来覆盖死者。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, what I speak of is a mask, but it is no piece of clothing.</Source>
      <Dest>不不不，我所强调的一直是一个面具，但是可不是像衣服那样的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The answer is a cloak.  A mortal wears many, and it often covers the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>答案是斗篷。很多普通人都穿，而且常用来覆盖死者。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was referring to the face, for sculpting it is my profession, my trade.</Source>
      <Dest>我是指脸啊，脸部塑形是我的职业，我的生财之道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The answer is a cloak.  A mortal wears many, and it often covers the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>答案是斗篷。很多普通人都穿，而且常用来覆盖死者。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For that reason I followed the Hollow-Faced men of Nohotogrha to the ends of Tamriel and back again.</Source>
      <Dest>因此我跟随诺荷托格拉哈无面人在泰姆瑞尔大陆东征西讨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The answer is a cloak.  A mortal wears many, and it often covers the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>答案是斗篷。很多普通人都穿，而且常用来覆盖死者。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For that purpose I sojourned with the Witches of Devilrock, to know the ancient magic that can transform the mortal body and wake the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>我跟魔岩女巫们呆在一起的目的，是为了学习转变形体和复生亡者的古老魔法.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The answer is a cloak.  A mortal wears many, and it often covers the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>答案是斗篷。很多普通人都穿，而且常用来覆盖死者。.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I digress, for what you require first is a name.  I am Y'tharil, a sculptor of the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>但我跑题了，容我介绍一下，我是艾瑟卓，一名死者塑形师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you shape my flesh?</Source>
      <Dest>你能给我整形吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You have a beautiful face, and if I were still an apprentice, one that I would have very much liked to sculpt.</Source>
      <Dest>你这张脸真漂亮，要还是学徒的时候的我，肯定照你的样子刻上一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you shape my flesh?</Source>
      <Dest>你能给我整形吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Alas, now that I have evolved as a sculptor, my spells and my scalpel are only for the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>呵，现在我已经成为艺术家，我的法术和手术刀只为死者服务。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you shape my flesh?</Source>
      <Dest>你能给我整形吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Undeath touches your flesh.  How I long to tamper with it.  However, my skill is lacking.  There is no guarantee your skin wouldn't turn to dust.</Source>
      <Dest>亡灵在触碰你的血肉。我很想插手干预，然而我技艺不精，我不能保证你的皮肤不会变成尘土。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you shape my flesh?</Source>
      <Dest>你能给我整形吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I do not wish to kill my first and only client.</Source>
      <Dest>我不想杀了自己的第一个也是唯一一个的主顾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I am both a brute and thoroughly puzzled. Please explain.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我即愚钝又迷惑。请解释给我听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have served the Hollow-Faced skin dancers of Nohotogrha, and witches as far as Devilrock.</Source>
      <Dest>在为魔岩女巫服务之前，我一直在侍奉诺荷托格拉哈无面人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I am both a brute and thoroughly puzzled. Please explain.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我即愚钝又迷惑。请解释给我听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I seek the knowledge of forbidden magic, so that the faces my corpses wear will be indistinguishable from the living.</Source>
      <Dest>我寻求禁忌的魔法知识，这样我的尸体的脸将与活人无异。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I am both a brute and thoroughly puzzled. Please explain.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我即愚钝又迷惑。请解释给我听。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I digress, for what you require first is a name.  I am Y'tharil, a sculptor of the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>但我跑题了，容我介绍一下，我是艾瑟卓，一名死者塑形师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure. Explain away.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。好好解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I have served the Hollow-Faced skin dancers of Nohotogrha, and witches as far as Devilrock.</Source>
      <Dest>在为魔岩女巫服务之前，我一直在侍奉诺荷托格拉哈无面人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure. Explain away.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。好好解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I seek the knowledge of forbidden magic, so that the faces my corpses wear will be indistinguishable from the living.</Source>
      <Dest>我寻求禁忌的魔法知识，这样我的尸体的脸将与活人无异。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sure. Explain away.</Source>
      <Dest>当然。好好解释。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I digress, for what you require first is a name.  I am Y'tharil, a sculptor of the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>但我跑题了，容我介绍一下，我是艾瑟卓，一名死者塑形师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you repeat the question?  I was distracted by you boring me.</Source>
      <Dest>你能重复一遍刚才的问题吗？刚才的话题太无聊，我有些分心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, we have a brute! If you do not enjoy a good riddle, then surely you can appreciate its answer.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，你还真够粗暴！如果你不能享受解开一个好谜题的过程，那你一定会欣赏它的答案的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you repeat the question?  I was distracted by you boring me.</Source>
      <Dest>你能重复一遍刚才的问题吗？刚才的话题太无聊，我有些分心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For the face I wear is long on beauty, carefully crafted by my own hand.</Source>
      <Dest>我戴上的这张人皮面具挺漂亮的吧，那是我亲手精心制作的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you repeat the question?  I was distracted by you boring me.</Source>
      <Dest>你能重复一遍刚才的问题吗？刚才的话题太无聊，我有些分心。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If that puzzles you further, then allow me to explain.</Source>
      <Dest>如果这让你更加困惑，请让我解释一下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Given their skill set, I can't imagine such men were easy to find.</Source>
      <Dest>鉴于他们的特殊能力，我无法想象这样的男人能被轻松找到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, as their existence is as much folklore as their abilities, I trekked to Hammerfell unsure if I my steps were made in vain.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，考虑到她们的能力就和讨论她们存在的民间传说一样多，我跋涉到落锤省以确保我的努力没有付诸东流。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You make it sound romantic. But it's still blasphemous witchcraft.</Source>
      <Dest>就算你吹出花儿来，这也还是大逆不道的巫术嘛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Many deride what they do not understand. This is why the sculptors move in secret.</Source>
      <Dest>很多人总去嘲笑那些他们所不知道的事物。这也是为什么整容师总在暗处行动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are the Hollow-Faced Men?</Source>
      <Dest>那个无面人是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Skin changers, flesh dancers, the tribe of the wandering faces.  The Hollow-Faced Men of Nohotoghra have gone by many names.</Source>
      <Dest>体肤的改变者，肉体上的舞者，变换千面的部族。诺荷托格拉哈无面人有着很多称号。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are the Hollow-Faced Men?</Source>
      <Dest>那个无面人是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Like the Chirurgeons of Cloudrest and the Slave Sculptors of Ayleid lore, they are masters of the art of molding flesh.</Source>
      <Dest>如同云息城的手术师们或者野精灵传统中的奴隶雕刻师们一样，他们也是雕琢血肉的大师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are the Hollow-Faced Men?</Source>
      <Dest>那个无面人是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you ultimately find the Hollow-Faced Men?</Source>
      <Dest>你最后是怎么找到那个瘦脸男的?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For 7 days and 7 nights I marched across the dunes of the Alik'r.</Source>
      <Dest>我徒步走了整整七天七夜才穿过阿利克尔沙丘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you craft it?</Source>
      <Dest>这玩意是怎么做出来的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I filed off the tusks and contracted the jaw using techniques practiced by the ancient Yokudans for binding feet.</Source>
      <Dest>我把猛犸牙整理妥当并按照古代尤库达人裹脚的方法捆在了一起。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you craft it?</Source>
      <Dest>这玩意是怎么做出来的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was a passing fancy of mine to sculpt Orcs into humans, before I found my true calling as a sculptor of the undead.</Source>
      <Dest>在我发现自己真正的使命是做死者塑形师之前，就梦想过把兽人面孔雕琢成人类的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How did you craft it?</Source>
      <Dest>这玩意是怎么做出来的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When my name is known throughout Tamriel, this skull may be considered a priceless historical artifact, a symbol of a road almost taken.</Source>
      <Dest>当我在塔玛瑞尔扬名立万之时，这个头骨可能会被当做无价的历史遗物，某条取过名字的道路的标志。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've retrieved your hip bone.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经取回了你的髋骨.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Marvelous. And with minimal damage, I see.  Although these stains are rather curious.</Source>
      <Dest>太厉害了。居然还是以最小的代价完成的。不过这些瑕疵略有点奇特。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've retrieved your hip bone.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经取回了你的髋骨.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, you have my thanks.  The item was incredibly dear to me, as are you for returning it.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何我非常感谢你。这东西对我来说非常珍贵，把这玩意还给我的你也一样棒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've retrieved your hip bone.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经取回了你的髋骨.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As such, you have certainly earned your reward.  I must say it is most handsome, but it was not always so.</Source>
      <Dest>就其本身而论，你已经得到了回报。我得说这张脸很英俊，但不会一直如此。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've retrieved your hip bone.</Source>
      <Dest>我已经取回了你的髋骨.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>This Orc skull has been carved to resemble a human.  It is by far one of my proudest achievements as a sculptor.</Source>
      <Dest>这个兽人头骨已经雕刻得近乎于人类了。这是我作为一名塑形师最为骄傲的成就。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I can't imagine a Witches' Coven allowing their sisters to come and go freely.</Source>
      <Dest>我无法想象女巫会允许她们的姐妹想来就来想走就走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Correct.  It was unfortunate, but in the end I was forced to kill them all, lest the indoctrination take hold.</Source>
      <Dest>正确。但很不幸，最后我不得不把他们都杀了，免得那教化影响到我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you learn anything practical from the witches?</Source>
      <Dest>你有没有从那些女巫那学到些东西啊？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If by that you mean combat magic, I picked up a spell or two.  Yet a witch's training goes beyond mere fire and ice.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你指的是战斗法术，我是会那么一两招的。不过女巫的训练可不单单是火系和冰系而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Did you learn anything practical from the witches?</Source>
      <Dest>你有没有从那些女巫那学到些东西啊？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There are things practiced in the dark.  The art of the forbidden. Like how to seduce a male, or please a female.</Source>
      <Dest>那是在黑暗中进行的事，是禁忌。就像怎么色诱一个男人，取悦一个女人是一样的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They walk this long pilgrimage, the sandstorms cut away at their flesh, shaping their countenance, eroding flesh and bone.</Source>
      <Dest>他们走过这条漫长的朝圣之旅，沙暴剥离了他们的血肉，削刻着他们的面容，腐蚀着他们的躯体和骨头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Judging by your lopsided face, I'd say the skill is imprecise at best.</Source>
      <Dest>瞧你那张不公平的脸，我得说这项技能顶多不够精确而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I appreciate your candor, but I wonder if you're projecting the limitations of your own face onto mine.</Source>
      <Dest>我谢谢你的坦诚，同时也在想你是否在把自己的脸的局限性照搬到了我这儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Judging by your lopsided face, I'd say the skill is imprecise at best.</Source>
      <Dest>瞧你那张不公平的脸，我得说这项技能顶多不够精确而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do not misunderstand, your face is quite lovely.  It simply needs to be fine tuned.  The creators can be quite sloppy with their work.</Source>
      <Dest>别误会了，你的脸相当可爱。只是需要稍稍调整一下。造物主工作真不认真呐。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Naturally, but I assume the presence of witches was important too.</Source>
      <Dest>很自然。不过我猜那些女巫的出现也是关系重大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Witchcraft naturally aligns with my interests. The ability to transform the body, to lengthen bones and expand the heart, is an important skill.</Source>
      <Dest>巫术自然而然地吸引了我的兴趣。改造身体的能力可以让骨头延长，让心脏扩大，是很重要的技能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Naturally, but I assume the presence of witches was important too.</Source>
      <Dest>很自然。不过我猜那些女巫的出现也是关系重大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is said the Glenmoril Witches once took flight as ravens, and their spells could cure lycanthropy.</Source>
      <Dest>据说格林茉莉的女巫曾如同乌鸦般飞翔，还说他们的咒语能使狼人恢复正常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Naturally, but I assume the presence of witches was important too.</Source>
      <Dest>很自然。不过我猜那些女巫的出现也是关系重大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was still much I had wished to learn from the Beldam of the coven, but such knowledge was only available to the most devoted of supplicants.</Source>
      <Dest>从那些老女巫身上还有很多我想学的东西，但是这些知识只有付出最多的求学者才能学到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The ocean, and black magic.</Source>
      <Dest>大海，还有黑魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Witchcraft naturally aligns with my interests. The ability to transform the body, to lengthen bones and expand the heart, is an important skill.</Source>
      <Dest>巫术自然而然地吸引了我的兴趣。改造身体的能力可以让骨头延长，让心脏扩大，是很重要的技能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The ocean, and black magic.</Source>
      <Dest>大海，还有黑魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is said the Glenmoril Witches once took flight as ravens, and their spells could cure lycanthropy.</Source>
      <Dest>据说格林茉莉的女巫曾如同乌鸦般飞翔，还说他们的咒语能使狼人恢复正常。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The ocean, and black magic.</Source>
      <Dest>大海，还有黑魔法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There was still much I had wished to learn from the Beldam of the coven, but such knowledge was only available to the most devoted of supplicants.</Source>
      <Dest>从那些老女巫身上还有很多我想学的东西，但是这些知识只有付出最多的求学者才能学到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned the Witches of Devilrock.</Source>
      <Dest>你提到了魔岩女巫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A coven native to the coast, a league or two north of the Dragontail Mountains.</Source>
      <Dest>最初的女巫集会是从龙尾山脉北部的一到两个女巫集团在这片海岸举办的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You mentioned the Witches of Devilrock.</Source>
      <Dest>你提到了魔岩女巫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In truth, I would have followed any coven, but after my time in the desert, I longed to see the ocean.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我已经跟着女巫离开了，但是在沙漠的那段时间后，我渴望看到大海。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wish I could join a coven.  Unfortunately I am not a woman.</Source>
      <Dest>真希望我也能加入一次女巫聚会。很不幸我不是女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, that would preclude you from joining their ranks.  Although I will certainly not hold it against you.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，那会阻止你加入他们的阶层。虽然我绝对不会阻止你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wish I could join a coven.  They tend to attack me on sight, however.</Source>
      <Dest>我也希望能参加女巫集会，但每次他们一看到我就采取攻击。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, they are quite protective of their dens.  I would suggest making allies with those who have ties to a sect.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，她们很爱护自己的窝点。我会建议她们和一些与教团有关的人结盟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No thanks, face butcher. You don't look trustworthy.</Source>
      <Dest>不用了，毁容者，你看起来不可信。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you wish to have my credentials first, then know that I am a disciple of the Hollow-Faced Men of Nohotogrha and the Witches of Devilrock.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你想先看我的证书的话，那你就得知道我是诺荷托格拉哈无面人和魔岩女巫的徒弟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No thanks, face butcher. You don't look trustworthy.</Source>
      <Dest>不用了，毁容者，你看起来不可信。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I digress, for what you require first is a name.  I am Y'tharil, a sculptor of the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>但我跑题了，容我介绍一下，我是艾瑟卓，一名死者塑形师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What experience do you have sculpting faces?</Source>
      <Dest>在整容方面你有什么经验吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you wish to have my credentials first, then know that I am a disciple of the Hollow-Faced Men of Nohotogrha and the Witches of Devilrock.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你想先看我的证书的话，那你就得知道我是诺荷托格拉哈无面人和魔岩女巫的徒弟。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What experience do you have sculpting faces?</Source>
      <Dest>在整容方面你有什么经验吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I digress, for what you require first is a name.  I am Y'tharil, a sculptor of the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>但我跑题了，容我介绍一下，我是艾瑟卓，一名死者塑形师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak of one's countenance. Their face.</Source>
      <Dest>你提到了脸，他们的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Correct.  You understand then, that to wear many faces, and to be without a face, is the essence of life, and only in death do we return to the one.</Source>
      <Dest>对的。你懂的，总是带上各种面具，忘却了自己的面庞，这就是生活的本质，只有死后才能回归自己的脸面。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak of one's countenance. Their face.</Source>
      <Dest>你提到了脸，他们的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But that was then.  Such limitations do not apply for those who turn the dead into the living.</Source>
      <Dest>但此一时彼一时。那些限制对于能把死人弄活过来的家伙来说不适用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak of one's countenance. Their face.</Source>
      <Dest>你提到了脸，他们的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Perhaps you would like to volunteer that lovely face of yours for a makeover, before the worms decorate it with freckles.</Source>
      <Dest>也许在蛆虫用雀斑装饰你那张可爱的小脸之前，你会愿意给它画一下妆。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, I'm sure you'll find plenty of corpses between here and Markarth.</Source>
      <Dest>我确定你会在这儿和马卡斯城间发现一大堆的尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, but I do not wish to start all over from scratch.  Much of my belongings were stolen from my carriage by a group of bandits.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，但是我不想从抢劫重新来过。我大多数的家当都被一伙强盗从马车偷走了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well, I'm sure you'll find plenty of corpses between here and Markarth.</Source>
      <Dest>我确定你会在这儿和马卡斯城间发现一大堆的尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For one, there was a male hip bone widened to resemble a female's, crafted by a body sculptor.</Source>
      <Dest>举个例子，曾经有位男性的胯骨被改得像女性胯骨的样子，这都是某个身体塑形师的功劳。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There are legends that spoke of the mage thieves of Haven. It is said they could steal a mortal heart as easily as a coin purse.</Source>
      <Dest>有些关于避风港奥术盗贼的传奇故事，据说他们能像偷钱包一样轻松地摘掉一个人的心脏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Unfortunately, sculpting a face requires far more time and care.  From what I understand, such spells are fleeting at best.</Source>
      <Dest>不幸的是，整容需要更多的时间和专注。就我理解的话，这类法术最好是短暂性的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is sculpting dead faces even possible?</Source>
      <Dest>易容成死人的样子也可以？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Few seem to think so, as the flesh of the undead is nothing more than petrified ash.</Source>
      <Dest>大多数人不会这么想。因为不死生物的皮肉只是些僵土碎尘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is sculpting dead faces even possible?</Source>
      <Dest>易容成死人的样子也可以？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, bone is bone, and if one can shape it without cutting and damaging the exterior flesh, I believe it can be done.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，骷髅就是骷髅，如果有人想在不剥离血肉的前提下就塑形，我相信那也可行.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Depending on the usage, sand can indeed cut harder than stone.</Source>
      <Dest>就用途而言，砂子切割确实比石头更难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is true that in Hammerfell, sand plays an important role in the shaping of all things.</Source>
      <Dest>这是真的。在落锤省，沙子在塑造所有东西的方面都起着重要作用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Depending on the usage, sand can indeed cut harder than stone.</Source>
      <Dest>就用途而言，砂子切割确实比石头更难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is sand that allows the saw to cut and shape blocks of stone.  Sand that is glazed on the bonecutter's knife as he re-shapes your skull.</Source>
      <Dest>正是沙子用来帮助锯条切割和给石头塑形，如同切骨刀对于骨头一般的锋利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Depending on the usage, sand can indeed cut harder than stone.</Source>
      <Dest>就用途而言，砂子切割确实比石头更难。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And that is the answer to your query.  It is not flesh that makes a face.  It is cartilage and bone.  Shape that, and the flesh will form around it.</Source>
      <Dest>这是对你疑问的回答。并不是血肉塑造了你的脸，而是你的脸部骨骼与软骨。只要对它们进行重塑，那血肉就自然而然地定型了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I assume you mean metaphorically. I doubt sand can actually shape their flesh.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜你只是打比方吧。很难想象沙子真的能为肉体造型。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You may find that hard to believe, but it is true that in Hammerfell, sand plays an important role in the shaping of all things.</Source>
      <Dest>你可能会很难相信，但这是真的。在落锤省，沙子在塑造所有东西的方面都起着重要作用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I assume you mean metaphorically. I doubt sand can actually shape their flesh.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜你只是打比方吧。很难想象沙子真的能为肉体造型。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is sand that allows the saw to cut and shape blocks of stone.  Sand that is glazed on the bonecutter's knife as he re-shapes your skull.</Source>
      <Dest>正是沙子用来帮助锯条切割和给石头塑形，如同切骨刀对于骨头一般的锋利。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I assume you mean metaphorically. I doubt sand can actually shape their flesh.</Source>
      <Dest>我猜你只是打比方吧。很难想象沙子真的能为肉体造型。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And that is the answer to your query. It is not flesh that makes a face.  It is cartilage and bone. Shape that, and the flesh will form around it.</Source>
      <Dest>那就是你问题的答案。脸并非由血肉组成，骨骼和软骨结构才是，给骨塑形，血肉自然会在其周围形成。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do the Hollow-Faced Men cut and shape flesh?</Source>
      <Dest>无面者如何切割和塑造血肉？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) Must we prattle on about the particulars? I would much rather spend such time in the arms of a young and handsome adventurer.</Source>
      <Dest>（叹气）我们必须闲扯些细节吗？ 我宁愿把时间花费在一个年轻英俊的冒险家怀中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do the Hollow-Faced Men cut and shape flesh?</Source>
      <Dest>无面者如何切割和塑造血肉？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) Must we prattle on about the particulars? I would much rather spend such time in the arms of a young adventurer.</Source>
      <Dest>（叹气）我们必须闲扯这些细节吗？我宁愿把时间花费在一个年轻英俊的冒险家怀中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Every night I bade my guides farewell, for every morning I knew another set would take their place.</Source>
      <Dest>每晚我都会和我的向导告别，因为我知道明天早上一定会有另一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you realized who the guides were?</Source>
      <Dest>当你发现向导是谁的时候，发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The guide saw my expression and nodded.  I asked for his name, and if he would take me on as his disciple.</Source>
      <Dest>导师看到了我的表情并点了点头，我询问了他的名字，以及他是否能接纳我为他的门徒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happened after you realized who the guides were?</Source>
      <Dest>当你发现向导是谁的时候，发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You may follow, he said, "but a name I cannot give, for to name a Hollow-Faced Man is to walk the Alik'r, and name the grains of sand."</Source>
      <Dest>You may follow, he said, "but a name I cannot give, for to name a Hollow-Faced Man is to walk the Alik'r, and name the grains of sand."</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That must have been confusing to be passed along like that.</Source>
      <Dest>这样过去肯定会引起困惑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Undoubtedly. It seemed I was going in circles. Finally the guides led me back to familiar sands, and we followed the stars to the nearest settlement.</Source>
      <Dest>毫无疑问。看来我是在兜圈子。最终，向导带着我返回熟悉的沙漠，然后我们随着星像回到了最近的聚点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That must have been confusing to be passed along like that.</Source>
      <Dest>这样过去肯定会引起困惑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When we reached the oasis, I thanked the last of my guides, and was about to set off when I realized, for the first time, I recognized their faces.</Source>
      <Dest>当我们到达绿洲时，我真感谢那位走在最后的向导。就是在出发的那一刻，我认出了他们的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That must have been confusing to be passed along like that.</Source>
      <Dest>这样过去肯定会引起困惑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sullen eyes, thin lips, and hooked noses. They looked almost like vultures. Then I knew. The guides had never changed.  Only their faces.</Source>
      <Dest>阴沉的眼睛，单薄的嘴唇，还有像钩子一样的鼻子。他们看起来几乎就是秃鹰。然后我知道了。向导从未变过，除了他们饱经风霜的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How long did this go on?</Source>
      <Dest>这持续多久了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For almost a full season. Finally, the guides led me back to familiar sands, and we followed the stars to the nearest settlement.</Source>
      <Dest>几乎有一个季度。最终，向导们带我们回到了熟悉的地方，我们看着星像走到了最近的据点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How long did this go on?</Source>
      <Dest>这持续多久了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When we reached the oasis, I thanked the last of my guides, and was about to set off when I realized, for the first time, I recognized their faces.</Source>
      <Dest>当我们到达绿洲时，我真感谢那位走在最后的向导。就是在出发的那一刻，我认出了他们的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How long did this go on?</Source>
      <Dest>这持续多久了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sullen eyes, thin lips, and hooked noses. They looked almost like vultures. Then I knew. The guides had never changed. Only their faces.</Source>
      <Dest>阴沉的眼睛，薄薄的嘴唇，以及钩状的鼻子。他们几乎像秃鹫。我知道。向导从未改变，变的只有他们的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where did the nomads lead you?</Source>
      <Dest>牧民把你带到了哪儿？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The next morning I woke up, and was startled to find myself surrounded by three new guides, each bearing no similarity to the last.</Source>
      <Dest>第二天早上我醒来，惊讶的发现我被了三个新的向导围起来，每人都和之前的人完全不同。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sleeping Giant? I have a good idea what he was referring to.</Source>
      <Dest>沉睡巨人？就他提及的东西来说我有个不错的点子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Excellent.  I look forward to having my items returned to me. Some are dear to me for sentimental reasons, others are vital for resuming my practice.</Source>
      <Dest>很好。我希望能找回我宝贵的东西。有些我纯粹是因为个人感情因素而珍惜的，有些对于我恢复我的练习很重要。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Sleeping Giant? I have a good idea what he was referring to.</Source>
      <Dest>沉睡巨人？就他提及的东西来说我有个不错的点子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And I assure you, if you do this for me, you will be handsomely rewarded.</Source>
      <Dest>而且我向你保证，如果你为我做这事，你会得到一笔不错的奖赏。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why sell your services to assassins?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你要为刺客卖命?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Sigh) Isn't it obvious?  How can I be a sculptor of the dead without dead people to sculpt?</Source>
      <Dest>（叹气）这不是显而易见吗？如果世上没有死人的话我又怎么做死人整容师？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why sell your services to assassins?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你要为刺客卖命?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's so special about this hip bone?</Source>
      <Dest>这个髋关节骨头有什么特别的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One of my former masters kept it as a souveneir.  An oddity one puts on a desk to start a conversation. </Source>
      <Dest>我的前任主人之一将之作为一个纪念品，并古怪的将其放在桌子上与之谈话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why sell your services to assassins?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你要为刺客卖命?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's so special about this hip bone?</Source>
      <Dest>这个髋关节骨头有什么特别的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, as a young apprentice bored with magic, it became the very catalyst for my life's pursuit.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，作为一个厌烦魔法的年轻学徒，这就变成了我生命中追求之物的催化剂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why sell your services to assassins?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你要为刺客卖命?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's so special about this hip bone?</Source>
      <Dest>这个髋关节骨头有什么特别的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As my skill improved, I gravitated toward the more difficult arts, the more delicate flesh.  None more so than the faces of the undead.</Source>
      <Dest>随着我的技巧的提升，我被更为困难的艺术和更为精致的血肉吸引。而没有比死者的脸更为吸引我的了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why sell your services to assassins?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你要为刺客卖命?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's so special about this hip bone?</Source>
      <Dest>这个髋关节骨头有什么特别的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet it all began with that single, sculpted hip bone.  One given to me as a parting gift when I left for Hammerfell.</Source>
      <Dest>所有都是因这根雕刻过的臀骨而起。这是我从落锤走的时候一个人给我的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why sell your services to assassins?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你要为刺客卖命?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where can I start looking for this bone?</Source>
      <Dest>我在哪里可以找到这根骨头？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As the bandits unloaded my belongings, I overheard one of them discussing his future plans.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，说起它的下落，我有一点儿线索。当强盗们抢走我的行李时，我偷听到他们中的一个在谈论他将来的打算。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why sell your services to assassins?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你要为刺客卖命?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where can I start looking for this bone?</Source>
      <Dest>我在哪里可以找到这根骨头？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something about setting up a camp overlooking a Sleeping Giant.  His words only confused me, but perhaps you will be able to make sense of it.</Source>
      <Dest>关于扎个营远远地眺望一个沉睡的巨人之类的话。我只会被他的话弄晕，但也许你能整明白。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's a Chirurgeon?</Source>
      <Dest>外科医生是做什么的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The High Elves have long been obsessed with their appearance.  Namely, maintaining a similarity to their ancestral Aldmer.</Source>
      <Dest>问的好。高等精灵一直痴迷于自己的外表。换句话说，就是想坚持跟他们的祖先弃精灵相似。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's a Chirurgeon?</Source>
      <Dest>外科医生是做什么的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In time, the practice extended to other, more practical uses.  Highborn often have their faces chiseled to maintain the appearance of youth.</Source>
      <Dest>最后，这练习扩展至其他更为实际的用途。出身高贵的人经常使自己的轮廓分明以保持青春的容颜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's a Chirurgeon?</Source>
      <Dest>外科医生是做什么的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thieves, criminals, and necromancers will pay a large sum to change their identity.  The Chirurgeons of Cloudrest accommodate them all.</Source>
      <Dest>盗贼，罪犯，还有死灵法师会为了改变身份而慷慨解囊，而云息城的外科医生照单全收。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I had no choice but to follow.</Source>
      <Dest>我别无选择，只能继续。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Huh? I wasn't paying attention to a word you said.</Source>
      <Dest>哈？我刚刚没有注意到你说了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Too distracted by my eyes, I take it?  Windows into the soul, some say, but as I said, I prefer to work with the curtains drawn.</Source>
      <Dest>眼睛所见太令人分心，那为什么我还要看到？有人说眼睛是心灵之窗,但要我说，我更喜欢在黑暗中工作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Huh? I wasn't paying attention to a word you said.</Source>
      <Dest>哈？我刚刚没有注意到你说了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I speak of the face.  The one the Hollow-Faced masters of Nohotogrha taught me to work.</Source>
      <Dest>我说的是脸。教会了我这种工作的诺荷托格拉哈无面者大师的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Huh? I wasn't paying attention to a word you said.</Source>
      <Dest>哈？我刚刚没有注意到你说了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The very one the covens from Glenmoril to Devilrock have drained of all life in exchange for an ancient power.</Source>
      <Dest>就是从魔岩到格林茉莉的女巫究其一生所交换的那股远古力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Huh? I wasn't paying attention to a word you said.</Source>
      <Dest>哈？我刚刚没有注意到你说了什么。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I digress, for what you require first is a name.  I am Y'tharil, a sculptor of the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>但我跑题了，容我介绍一下，我是艾瑟卓，一名死者塑形师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How much time did you spend outside of Morrowind?</Source>
      <Dest>你离开晨风多久了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I spent forty years in the service of the Hollow Faces, learning the bending of bone and the dance of flesh.</Source>
      <Dest>我四十多年来一直致力于整容业，学习掰弯骨头，以及血肉的舞蹈。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How much time did you spend outside of Morrowind?</Source>
      <Dest>你离开晨风多久了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I spent another decade studying under the ancient covens of Devilrock, to study the art of bestial transformation.</Source>
      <Dest>我又花了十年在魔岩的远古女巫魔集进行学习，学习野兽形态的艺术。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a long way from home, traveler.</Source>
      <Dest>游子，你已离家太远。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, although I hail not from Hammerfell, but the Grazelands of Morrowind. </Source>
      <Dest>确实，不过我不是来自落锤省，而是晨风的格瑞滋群岛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a long way from home, traveler.</Source>
      <Dest>游子，你已离家太远。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Still, I could not be further from my native land, as well as my adopted one.</Source>
      <Dest>即使如此，我也不会对故乡有疏远感，和对养育我成长的地方一样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Find someone else to enable your weird hobby.</Source>
      <Dest>找其他人来满足你的怪癖吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You disappoint me traveler.  Dead or living, I had hoped someone of your features would appreciate the craft of body sculpting.</Source>
      <Dest>旅行者你让我很不高兴。无论活人还是死者，我曾经希望会有像你这样的人能够欣赏躯体塑形。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yours is quite handsome.  You should cherish it. A mortal has but one, although he wears many.</Source>
      <Dest>你的看起来很帅气。你应该珍惜你的面容。尽管他饱经风霜而略显不同，但是普通人终究只有一张脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell me, traveler, of what do I speak?</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我，旅行者, 我都说了什么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yours is quite pretty. You should cherish it. A mortal has but one, although he wears many. </Source>
      <Dest>你的面容非常漂亮。你应该珍惜它。尽管历尽沧桑会显得有所不同，但普通人终究只有一张脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Tell me, my lady, of what do I speak?</Source>
      <Dest>告诉我，我的女士，我都说了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A bed of sand may be as soft as a cloud, but individually each grain is extremely coarse.</Source>
      <Dest>一整片沙起来可能比云端还要柔软，但单独去看的话，每一粒沙都是非常粗糙的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does sand cut blocks of stone?</Source>
      <Dest>沙子是如何把这一大块石头给切开的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The ancient stonecutters would lay out a line of sand over a block of granite, and then run a saw over that line.</Source>
      <Dest>古代石匠们会用沙子在一整块儿花岗岩上画出条线，然后用锯沿着那条线切割石块儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does sand cut blocks of stone?</Source>
      <Dest>沙子是如何把这一大块石头给切开的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is not the same type of saw used to cut wood.  The saw has no edge.  It is there simply to apply pressure.  The sand serves as its teeth.</Source>
      <Dest>这把看起来并不像平常所用的伐木斧。它没有刀刃。它的存在或许只是为了压住些什么。这些砂石算是它的锯齿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does sand cut blocks of stone?</Source>
      <Dest>沙子是如何把这一大块石头给切开的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The sand-scalpels of the Hollow-Faced Men are made by binding grains of sand to a small, edgeless knife.</Source>
      <Dest>无面者的沙尘手术刀是通过把大量的细沙束缚在未开锋的小巧匕首上做成的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does sand cut blocks of stone?</Source>
      <Dest>沙子是如何把这一大块石头给切开的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How is the sharpness of sand used in face sculpting?</Source>
      <Dest>沙子有什么锋利之处可以用在整容上？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The end product is a blade that can shape and cut bone as easily as a man shaves his beard.</Source>
      <Dest>最终产物是一把可以像男人刮胡子那样轻松切削骨骼的利刃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How does sand cut blocks of stone?</Source>
      <Dest>沙子是如何把这一大块石头给切开的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How is the sharpness of sand used in face sculpting?</Source>
      <Dest>沙子有什么锋利之处可以用在整容上？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>True, but the history of a mortal is written on his skin, and when he dies, it is lost to the ages.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，但是凡人的历史就写在他的皮肤上，当他死去时，他的过去也随着时间流逝而消失。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak of a tree. All of history is written on its pages.</Source>
      <Dest>你说到一棵树。所有的历史都写在它的页面上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, there are those whose countenance tells no tale. Like the faceless men of Nohotogrha. Or the Beldams of Devilrock.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，还是有没有胡扯的的人的，像诺荷托格拉哈无面者。或者魔岩的老女巫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak of a tree. All of history is written on its pages.</Source>
      <Dest>你说到一棵树。所有的历史都写在它的页面上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In my time in Hammerfell, I served under both.  A time best measured by the decade.</Source>
      <Dest>当我还在落锤省时，两者我都给出过服务。那真是很漫长的一段时间啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak of a tree. All of history is written on its pages.</Source>
      <Dest>你说到一棵树。所有的历史都写在它的页面上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet I digress, for what you require first is a name.  I am Y'tharil, a sculptor of the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>但我跑题了，容我介绍一下，我是艾瑟卓，一名死者塑形师。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You speak of a tree. All of history is written on its pages.</Source>
      <Dest>你说到一棵树。所有的历史都写在它的页面上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If your skin is cut by the Alik'r and does not bleed, then you are considered worthy.  Anyone can follow.  Few manage to survive the privilege.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你被阿利克尔切了一刀之后仍未流血，那你就有被人所尊敬的价值链。任何人都可以遵循。这是少数幸存下来的人所能得到的特权。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I wasn't aware the tribal Redguards take on foreign disciples so easily.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾认为红卫不会如此轻易地雇佣外人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can shape the skull, mold the cartilage, and bind dyes to their pupils to give their eyes luster.</Source>
      <Dest>我能为头骨塑型，修整软骨，还能给眼球上色使他们的眼睛神采飞扬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet incisions must be made, and incisions leave scars.</Source>
      <Dest>切口已经切开了，这些切口会留下疤的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Restoration. I'm sure you have noticed, but healing potions, spells and incantations do not repair the dead.</Source>
      <Dest>在于回复能力。我想你应该已经注意到了，治疗药水、法术和咒语都是无法修复死者的身体的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the difference between sculpting living and undead flesh?</Source>
      <Dest>为活人整容和为死者塑形有什么区别</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Restoring dead flesh, even if it were as pristine as yours, is inconceivable without the knowledge of darker arts.</Source>
      <Dest>没有一定的死灵知识就能保存死尸是很惊人的，即使是保存像你这样的活人一样新鲜的尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What's the difference between sculpting living and undead flesh?</Source>
      <Dest>为活人整容和为死者塑形有什么区别</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What did you expect?  A mirror? What I have given you is indeed handsome in appearance as well as in value.</Source>
      <Dest>你在期待什么？一面镜子吗？我的确给了你一个英俊的外表，而那也有可观的价值。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is not what I expected when you said my reward would be handsome.</Source>
      <Dest>你当初说报酬丰厚的时候我可没想到指的是给个这玩意儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So do not fret.  I am sure Skyrim is home to at least one shopkeeper who is discerning enough to recognize its worth.</Source>
      <Dest>不用烦啦。我敢肯定天际省很乐于接纳一个能清楚认识自身价值的商店老板的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This is not what I expected when you said my reward would be handsome.</Source>
      <Dest>你当初说报酬丰厚的时候我可没想到指的是给个这玩意儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I appreciate your willingness to help. Yes, you may be able to assist me. I am not in need of a fresh corpse, but an old one.</Source>
      <Dest>我很感激你愿意帮我。是的，你确实可以帮我一把。我不需要新鲜的尸体，我需要放置了一段时间的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you want, I can gather corpses for you.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你需要，我能帮你收集尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You see, upon entering Skyrim, my carriage was sacked by a group of bandits, and I was relieved of some personal effects.</Source>
      <Dest>你要知道，就在我刚到天际省的时候，我的马车被一群强盗抢劫，而我失去了一些私人物品。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you want, I can gather corpses for you.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你需要，我能帮你收集尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Foremost among them was a male hip bone widened to resemble a female's, crafted by a body sculptor.</Source>
      <Dest>这些作品中摆在最前面的是一个男性髋关节骨，宽度上很像女性的，由一位躯体雕刻家所创作。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If you want, I can gather corpses for you.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你需要，我能帮你收集尸体。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why, I would bemoan the loss of such a beauty, yet I certainly understand the temptation.</Source>
      <Dest>为什么，我会为失去了一个这样的美人而叹息，但我很明白这其实只是个诱惑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What if I wanted to turn my face into a hideous monstrosity?</Source>
      <Dest>如果我想用狰狞的怪脸来替换我的表情又怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whether it be worshippers of Namira or the common Hag, there are many sculptors who adore the grotesque and are experts at crafting the deformed.</Source>
      <Dest>不管是作为娜米拉的信徒还是普通的女巫，很多雕塑家都对怪诞的东西非常推崇，并且也是整容方面的专家。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What if I wanted to turn my face into a hideous monstrosity?</Source>
      <Dest>如果我想用狰狞的怪脸来替换我的表情又怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In fact, I am envious of their skill.  Everything I fashion ends up being far too beautiful.</Source>
      <Dest>事实上，我是羡慕他们的技能。我所做的一切最终都会非常完美。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What if I wanted to turn my face into a hideous monstrosity?</Source>
      <Dest>如果我想用狰狞的怪脸来替换我的表情又怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We all have our individual talents.  My preference is to restore the ugly, the defiled, and the decayed to their natural form.</Source>
      <Dest>我们都有自己的独特的天赋。我的喜好是将丑陋，污秽和腐朽恢复到它们自然的形态。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What if I wanted to turn my face into a hideous monstrosity?</Source>
      <Dest>如果我想用狰狞的怪脸来替换我的表情又怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Working on the dead serves two purposes.  It distinguishes me from my peers, and broadens my client base.</Source>
      <Dest>我接不死生物的活儿有两个目的。其一是把我和同行区别出来，其二是开拓我的客户群。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why work exclusively on the dead?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么专门在死人身上下功夫？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Because they never die.  Because they operate in the shadows, because they have every desire to remain unseen.</Source>
      <Dest>因为它们不会死。因为它们习惯于在阴影中活动，因为它们有不被人发现的本能。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why the undead?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你还活着?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mostly, however, because they are a challenge.  After all, it is no secret that face sculpting has become rather commonplace in the Fourth Era.</Source>
      <Dest>多半是吧。总之因为那些是个挑战。毕竟，那些面部雕刻在第四纪元相当普及这件事不是个秘密。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why the undead?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你还活着?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Working on the undead serves two purposes.  It distinguishes me from my peers, and broadens my client base.</Source>
      <Dest>我接不死生物的活儿有两个目的。其一是把我和同行区别出来，其二是开拓我的客户群。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why the undead?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你还活着?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes, it will make for a fine conversation piece for your guests.  They will ask you why you have a human skull on display.</Source>
      <Dest>是啊，当你跟你的客人们聊天时这会是个很好的话题。他们会问你为什么你要展示一只人类的头骨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's a beautiful skull. Thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>真是块漂亮的头骨。谢谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Imagine their surprise when you inform them that it was born and Orc.</Source>
      <Dest>想象一下，当你告诉他们它是个地道的兽人时，他们会多惊讶。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's a beautiful skull. Thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>真是块漂亮的头骨。谢谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I finished my training, it occurred to me that those who ply their trade in deceit could use my services, so I decided to return to Morrowind.</Source>
      <Dest>我训练完成时，发现那些使用欺诈手段交易的人都来寻求我的服务，所以我决定返回晨风。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What made you decide to come back?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让你决定回来？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet the Morag Tong is no more, and the guilds are as brittle as the undead.</Source>
      <Dest>莫拉格帮已经不复存在了，而且那些公会跟个骷髅架子一样动不动就七零八落了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What made you decide to come back?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让你决定回来？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I am returning to Morrowind from a fifty year pilgrimage across the deserts of the Alik'r.</Source>
      <Dest>我正穿过阿利克尔的沙漠，结束了五十年的朝圣之路，回去晨风省。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What brings you to Skyrim?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么风把你吹来天际省?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You won't.  You can't.  Such is the skill and care I put into sculpting it.  My only regret is that this Orc no longer lives.</Source>
      <Dest>你不会的，也做不到。 那是倾尽心力和技巧于塑形的杰作。唯一的遗憾是这个兽人已经死去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do I know this isn't just some worthless human skull?</Source>
      <Dest>我如何知道这不仅仅是一些毫无价值的人类头骨？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For his skin would tell you his true ancestry, even if his bone structure did not.</Source>
      <Dest>即使他的骨头没有告诉你他的真正血统，他的皮肤也会的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do I know this isn't just some worthless human skull?</Source>
      <Dest>我如何知道这不仅仅是一些毫无价值的人类头骨？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But do not fret.  I am sure Skyrim is home to at least one shopkeeper who is discerning enough to recognize its worth.</Source>
      <Dest>别着急。我敢肯定至少有一个够聪明的杂货店主能看得出在天际安家的价值所在。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do I know this isn't just some worthless human skull?</Source>
      <Dest>我如何知道这不仅仅是一些毫无价值的人类头骨？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It is well known that the Ayleids kept entire stables full of slaves, relying on their labor to build their shrines and monuments.</Source>
      <Dest>众所周知的是，亚历德人们的马厩里装满了奴隶，他们就是依靠奴隶的劳动力建立起了神殿和纪念碑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Ayleid slave sculptors.</Source>
      <Dest>给我说说亚历德奴隶塑形师的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Back then, slaves were valuable commodities. Stronger specimens like yourself, for instance, would be highly valued on the market.</Source>
      <Dest>那是，奴隶仍是有价值的商品。举例来说，如你这般强壮的奴隶，在市场上能卖出高价。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Ayleid slave sculptors.</Source>
      <Dest>给我说说亚历德奴隶塑形师的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, it is believed this led to underground operations, where the bodies of weaker slaves would be modified to appear robust.</Source>
      <Dest>当然，这事儿肯定有幕后的操作，有人会把那些身体瘦弱的奴隶给变成强壮型的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about the Ayleid slave sculptors.</Source>
      <Dest>给我说说亚历德奴隶塑形师的事儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Your face is indeed impressive, but I would hesitate to call it perfect.  Nevertheless, it matters not. I have not touched living flesh in some time.</Source>
      <Dest>你的面庞令人印象深刻，不过我并不会说它是完美的。不论如何，这并不重要。我已经有段日子没有碰鲜活的肌体了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would ask you to sculpt my face, but you can't improve on perfection.</Source>
      <Dest>只要你别画蛇添足，那我就让你帮我整容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To say that I am out of practice would be generous.  Instead, I have focused all my resources on sculpting the undead.</Source>
      <Dest>说我疏于练习实在是宽宏大量。取而代之的是，我将我的全部资源专注于死者的雕刻上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would ask you to sculpt my face, but you can't improve on perfection.</Source>
      <Dest>只要你别画蛇添足，那我就让你帮我整容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some would not agree.  Some think for the undead to have any face at all is an abomination.  I am not one of those people.</Source>
      <Dest>某些人不会同意的。有人认为亡灵的脸上除了憎恨别无他物，我可不这么想。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would ask you to sculpt my face, but you can't improve on perfection.</Source>
      <Dest>只要你别画蛇添足，那我就让你帮我整容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I would like nothing more than to file, chisel, and cure every angle of that magnificent face of yours.</Source>
      <Dest>我所想做的事无非就是去锉，去凿，去修复你那张漂亮脸蛋上的每一处棱角。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would ask you to sculpt my face, but you can't improve on perfection.</Source>
      <Dest>只要你别画蛇添足，那我就让你帮我整容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>However, to attempt it now would be not be wise.  You must understand that I am attempting to break new ground, and have not yet mastered this art.</Source>
      <Dest>无论如何，现在去尝试并不明智。你要明白，我现在在尝试创造一些新东西但目前还没掌握它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would ask you to sculpt my face, but you can't improve on perfection.</Source>
      <Dest>只要你别画蛇添足，那我就让你帮我整容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I could just as easily rend your flesh into dust as I could turn it into a masterpiece.  Such a loss would be a travesty.</Source>
      <Dest>把你的肉体撕成碎片和把它变成一幅杰作一样简单。但出现这样的损失实在太滑稽了</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I would ask you to sculpt my face, but you can't improve on perfection.</Source>
      <Dest>只要你别画蛇添足，那我就让你帮我整容。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Blood is a powerful agent, and to spill it grants one strength.  But yes, I agree such rituals could do with a bit more cleanliness.</Source>
      <Dest>血液是种强大的药剂，喷涌的血液可以赋予人们力量。但是，我确实同意这样的仪式可以搞得更干净点儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, I'm sure the hags taught you much about making altars out of goat heads.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，关于如何用山羊头搭建祭坛，我确信女巫们能教给你很多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you will.  I hope you do not leave, however.  I enjoy looking at the contour of your face.  It is quite...chiseled.</Source>
      <Dest>如你所愿。无论如何，我希望你不要离开。我很喜欢看你脸的轮廓。它特别的，呃，棱角分明。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to go back to my earlier questions.</Source>
      <Dest>让我们回到先前的问题上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As you will, my lady.  I hope you do not leave, however.  I enjoying looking at your face.  It blooms with possibilities.</Source>
      <Dest>如你所愿，我的女士。然而我希望你不要离开。我喜欢看着你的脸，它展示了各种可能性。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to go back to my earlier questions.</Source>
      <Dest>让我们回到先前的问题上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So it went as we traveled across the the coastal kingdoms, through sandstorms and mountains and the snake pit of Balhar.</Source>
      <Dest>于是时间就在我们遍及所有沿海领地，穿越沙暴、山脉和巴尔哈尔的蛇坑的旅途中流逝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I insisted, no, demanded they tell me what happened to the others.  They said nothing, and once more bade me to follow.</Source>
      <Dest>我一定，呃，我十分想知道他们会告诉我别人发生了什么事儿。他们说什么也没发生，让我继续跟上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I collapsed on a nameless dune, surrendering to the heat and the vultures that loomed over head.</Source>
      <Dest>当我走到一座无名沙丘时，我终于崩溃了，对那热浪以及总是盘旋在我头顶的秃鹫举手投降。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yet as the birds descended, their faces lost all expression, their eyes as hollow as midnight.</Source>
      <Dest>然而，作为鸟的后裔，他们的脸上失去了所有的表情，他们的眼睛如午夜一样空洞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>As it turns out, they were not vultures, but men. Nomads crossing the desert.</Source>
      <Dest>结果，它们并不是秃鹫，而是人。正在穿越沙漠的游牧民。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I pleaded for water first, and for directions second.  The three nomads obliged, and led the way.</Source>
      <Dest>我请求他们给我水，然后告知我方向。而那三个游牧民则慷慨相助，为我指路。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The lifeblood of their magic comes from their tribal Gods, to whom they pay tribute at the shade-temples strewn across the Alik'r.</Source>
      <Dest>他们魔法的命脉就来自于他们种族的神，那个他们在遍布整个阿里克尔的阴影神庙里朝拜的神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if you must know, they are more than Nomads. They are assassins. Priests. Like followers of Sithis, the Hollows walk the path of the living void.</Source>
      <Dest>但如果你非得知道的话，他们可不仅仅是游牧民族。他们是刺客，祭司。如同西斯帝的追随者一样，无面者所选择的道路是现世的湮灭虚空。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And when the night draws its curtain on twin suns, all that is left is nothing. All that was is hollow.</Source>
      <Dest>当成双的太阳被夜幕覆盖时，世间一切将不复存在。世间美好仅剩一片空虚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Brave or bare, pale or plain, little is said, but in time, all is written. In forests of gray or barren canyons of earth.</Source>
      <Dest>没什么人会告诉你要华丽还是朴实，要淡化还是要浓描，但是最终，一切都会被书写下来。书写在大地之上的灰暗的森林中或是荒芜的峡谷下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Safe travels.</Source>
      <Dest>旅途安全。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't be afraid to put on a brave face.</Source>
      <Dest>不要羞于流露出你无畏的脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What is it?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thank you again for your help.</Source>
      <Dest>再次感谢你的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
