<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nonsense. Nords fight for the thrill and glory of battle, not some afterlife.</Source>
      <Dest>胡扯！诺德人一直是为激情和荣耀而战！不是什么来世。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I've seen soldiers on their knees with their guts on the ground, about five seconds away from sitting in a pool of their own feces.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾见过一些士兵连同他们的勇气一起跪倒在地上。大概5秒后屎尿横流成一滩。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nonsense. Nords fight for the thrill and glory of battle, not some afterlife.</Source>
      <Dest>胡扯！诺德人一直是为激情和荣耀而战！不是什么来世。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>War is messy business, and men won't dirty themselves for nothing.</Source>
      <Dest>战争就是肮脏的生意，人是不会无缘无故地作践自己的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can't seriously revere those monsters.</Source>
      <Dest>你不能发自内心地去尊敬那些怪物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What? If something ain't pretty like you it don't deserve our respect? </Source>
      <Dest>啥玩意？要是有个什么不像你这么样子就得不到我们的尊重了？ </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You can't seriously revere those monsters.</Source>
      <Dest>你不能发自内心地去尊敬那些怪物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must not like Thendrick much either, with that scar etched across his chest.</Source>
      <Dest>那你肯定也不喜欢 兰瑞克 了，他的伤疤横贯整个胸口呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Whoever he was, he's dead now.  That thing isn't alive.</Source>
      <Dest>不管他曾经是谁，他现在挂了。那东西不是个活物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So?  Everybody dies.  Not everyone can take a dozen Nord slaves with him.</Source>
      <Dest>那又如何？人人都会死，可不是每个人都能带一打诺德奴隶给他陪葬。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Whoever he was, he's dead now.  That thing isn't alive.</Source>
      <Dest>不管他曾经是谁，他现在挂了。那东西不是个活物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Funniest thing I ever saw was seeing Thendrick take out a garrison of the snow-lickers heading up to Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>最逗的是我曾看到Thendrick带着一个团的雪球前往独孤城。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Whoever he was, he's dead now.  That thing isn't alive.</Source>
      <Dest>不管他曾经是谁，他现在挂了。那东西不是个活物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They were Legion men, so instead of attacking, they huddled together in their little formation, scuttling forward like a mudcrab.</Source>
      <Dest>他们是军团的人，所以他们没有攻击，而是挤在一起，形成以个小小的编队，如同泥沼蟹一般的快步向前挪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Whoever he was, he's dead now.  That thing isn't alive.</Source>
      <Dest>不管他曾经是谁，他现在挂了。那东西不是个活物。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They had shields the size of a man, and all you could see was their feet.</Source>
      <Dest>这些人的盾牌都很巨大，你唯一能看见的只有他们的脚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, a brilliant plan that ended with his death.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，一个辉煌的计划，导致了他的死亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Aye, Madanach's a martyr now, but we won't worship him like some god.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，迈德纳奇的确英勇就义了，可是我们不会把他神化的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, a brilliant plan that ended with his death.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，一个辉煌的计划，导致了他的死亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They called him the "King in Rags,"  but the free men of the Reach don't bend the knee to no king.</Source>
      <Dest>他们叫他“褴褛国王”，但是瑞弛的自由人不向任何国王卑躬屈膝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, a brilliant plan that ended with his death.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，一个辉煌的计划，导致了他的死亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>We listened to Madanach because he had the best ideas.  But a dead man ain't got nothing but ash in his mouth, so we'll listen to the next man.</Source>
      <Dest>从前我们听迈德纳奇的是因为他最有办法。但一个死人嘴里除了一堆灰之外啥都没有，所以让我们听听下一任领袖的意见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, a brilliant plan that ended with his death.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，一个辉煌的计划，导致了他的死亡。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But we ain't never going to follow anyone.</Source>
      <Dest>但我们永远不会追随任何人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think getting caught and nearly executed was part of any plan.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不认为被抓住后差点砍了脑袋会是什么计划的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The getting caught part wasn't, but staving off execution was.  Them Silver-Bloods think they're using him, but it's them that's getting used.</Source>
      <Dest>被捕这件事超出了计划之外，但却避免了死亡。那些银血认为他们是在利用他，但那是他们的想当然。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think getting caught and nearly executed was part of any plan.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不认为被抓住后差点砍了脑袋会是什么计划的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Any day Madanach and the other children of the Reach will break out of that infernal mine.</Source>
      <Dest>总有一天迈德纳奇和其瑞驰之子会冲出那地狱般的矿井。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't think getting caught and nearly executed was part of any plan.</Source>
      <Dest>我可不认为被抓住后差点砍了脑袋会是什么计划的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Because with the war on and our foes weak, the time to strike grows near.</Source>
      <Dest>Because with the war on and our foes weak, the time to strike grows near.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I know.  I helped Madanach escape.</Source>
      <Dest>我知道，我帮迈德纳奇逃出来了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh I'm sure you were a great big help, riding his coattails to safety.  But it'll make a nice story to tell your children.</Source>
      <Dest>Oh I'm sure you were a great big help, riding his coattails to safety.  But it'll make a nice story to tell your children.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're not so bad yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>你也挺不错的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My, my, the master has a taste for savages!  What will the city folk think?</Source>
      <Dest>哎呀，哎呀，大师是野蛮人混血么！城里的人们会怎么想？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ah, the ultimate mudcrab defense.</Source>
      <Dest>啊哈，终极泥沼蟹防御。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't think that's what it's called.  Imperials don't have no sense of humor.  </Source>
      <Dest>我不认为该那么称呼。帝国人可没有幽默感啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ah, the ultimate mudcrab defense.</Source>
      <Dest>啊哈，终极泥沼蟹防御。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, I remember Thendrick charging ahead and knocking the whole lot of them on their backs.</Source>
      <Dest>在任何情况下，我记得兰瑞克都是冲向前方敲击他们全部人的脊背。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ah, the ultimate mudcrab defense.</Source>
      <Dest>啊哈，终极泥沼蟹防御。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then he stuck about half of them in their bellies and the rest he set on fire. </Source>
      <Dest>然后他刺破了一半儿人的肚子，然后放火烤熟了剩下的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ah, the ultimate mudcrab defense.</Source>
      <Dest>啊哈，终极泥沼蟹防御。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder how many hours those stupid fools practiced that thing only to have it fail them.</Source>
      <Dest>我好奇的是，那帮蠢货花了多少时间来进行练习但却不断地失败。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Taxes pay for roads and bridges.  Guards keep the peace.</Source>
      <Dest>税赋用于修路架桥。守卫则负责安保。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Who says I need them fancy roads, or a bridge to cross a river?  And I can protect myself just fine thank you.</Source>
      <Dest>谁说我需要他们帮我铺路架桥了? 我可以很好的保护自己，谢谢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Taxes pay for roads and bridges.  Guards keep the peace.</Source>
      <Dest>税赋用于修路架桥。守卫则负责安保。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's the problem with being slave folk. You got a perfectly good set of hands, and you still have to pay someone else to scratch your bottom.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是作为slave folk的难处。你有一双非凡巧手，但是你还是得付钱给别人来帮你挠屁股。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No self-respecting person would deign to touch you, savage.</Source>
      <Dest>只要稍微自重一点的人就不会自贬身价与你接触的，你这个野蛮人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, you slave folk are no fun at all!  So rigid with your rules and standards!  Do you also keep a manual on the proper way to make love?</Source>
      <Dest>哦，你这slave folk 一点也不有趣！所以你要严守自己的准则！你也一直在用适当的办法去保持体力做爱？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No self-respecting person would deign to touch you, savage.</Source>
      <Dest>只要稍微自重一点的人就不会自贬身价与你接触的，你这个野蛮人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You should give us a copy.  Wouldn't want to get near you and breathe on an inappropriate place.</Source>
      <Dest>你应该给我们一份。我们可不想靠近你然后闹得呼吸的位置都不对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean? What happened by the river?</Source>
      <Dest>你什么意思？河边发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When we were children we used to go swimming in the Karth, and fish around for clams.</Source>
      <Dest>我们小的时候曾在Karth游泳, 在那周围抓蛤蚌.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean? What happened by the river?</Source>
      <Dest>你什么意思？河边发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Freshwater clams are too tough to eat and aren't much use as bait, but the shells could make a fine necklace, or even contain a pearl.</Source>
      <Dest>淡水蚌的肉质太硬不好吃，用来做饵也不怎么适合，但贝壳可以用来做一条漂亮的项链，贝壳里有些时候甚至还有珍珠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean? What happened by the river?</Source>
      <Dest>你什么意思？河边发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was running my hands through a patch of pebbles, when something nipped at my hand.  I screamed, and Thendrick came running over.</Source>
      <Dest>我的手划过了一块鹅卵石的时候，有什么东西咬了我的手。我开始尖叫，然后兰瑞克跑了过来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean? What happened by the river?</Source>
      <Dest>你什么意思？河边发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He looked at the cut on my finger and said he knew how to make it better.  Then he kissed it.  Little as I was, all I could do is blush.</Source>
      <Dest>他看着我的手指上的伤口,说他知道如何使它变好些，然后他吻了一下那里。小小的我唯一能做的只是脸红。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean? What happened by the river?</Source>
      <Dest>你什么意思？河边发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then he says, "Oh no, I think the crab's gotten your lips too!" (Laughs) I told him maybe it did, and I flashed him a smile.</Source>
      <Dest>然后他说：“哦不，我想你的嘴上也挂着一只泥沼蟹呢！”（大笑）我微笑着回答他说，或许是那样没错。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean? What happened by the river?</Source>
      <Dest>你什么意思？河边发生了什么事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The next day I made him promise to never tell anyone. And he never did.</Source>
      <Dest>第二天，我让他承诺不去告诉任何人。但他从来也做不到。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about Thendrick the man? What was he like?</Source>
      <Dest>说说兰瑞克那人怎么样？他喜欢什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The same as he is now. Loyal. Just a little more annoying about it. Always reminding me to smile. So I'd stick out my jaw and grimace at him.</Source>
      <Dest>他现在没有改变他的忠心。我是指对他经常提醒我微笑，有点感觉烦恼。所以我要伸出下巴对他扮鬼脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about Thendrick the man? What was he like?</Source>
      <Dest>说说兰瑞克那人怎么样？他喜欢什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I mean, I ain't a bloody Nord. I smile just as much as anyone, but I know the one he was trawling for. The one I gave him that day by the river.</Source>
      <Dest>我是想说，我不是个血腥的诺德人。我的微笑和旁人一样，但我知道那个人在搜寻什么。于是那一天，我在河边给了那个人他想要的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was brave of him.</Source>
      <Dest>他很勇敢的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Aye, bravery is something's that's lacking in folks these days, because they got this idea in their head their lives are too valuable to lose.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，现在人民缺少的是一位勇敢者。因为每个人脑子里想的全是自己能活下去才是最重要的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was brave of him.</Source>
      <Dest>他很勇敢的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why them old Nords had to make up Sovngarde.  It ain't brave to die in battle if you got a paradise waiting for you as a reward.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是那些诺德佬编造了松加德的原因。如果你死在战斗之中就有个极乐世界在等着你的话，这才不是勇敢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It was brave of him.</Source>
      <Dest>他很勇敢的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But to throw your life away so that others can live in an earthly paradise...a free world...well, that's real bravery.</Source>
      <Dest>你牺牲了自己的生命，使得其他的人可以生活在一个人间天堂...一个自由的世界...是的，这是真正的勇敢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's called a community. Compromises are made for the benefit of the group.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是团体，妥协是为了团体的利益。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Except it's a group with forced membership. They take all the good land, all the mines, so you got no choice but to live where they tell you.</Source>
      <Dest>只不过那是一个强制组成的群体。他们占据了所有优质土地，所有矿井，所以你除了对他们言听计从之外别无选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's called a community. Compromises are made for the benefit of the group.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是团体，妥协是为了团体的利益。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And it just gets worse. Every year the cities grow bigger and the wilds shrink.  Pretty soon won't be any space left for the grass.  </Source>
      <Dest>而且情况在变得更糟。年复一年，城市扩张得越来越厉害，而荒野则在不停地收缩。估计用不了多久，连属于植物的生长空间都要没有了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have questions about the Briar-Heart.</Source>
      <Dest>我对荆棘之心有些疑问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ah, the brute.  Big and strong with eyes as dull as Orc poetry.  Of course, there's a reason for all three of those things.</Source>
      <Dest>Ah, the brute.  Big and strong with eyes as dull as Orc poetry.  Of course, there's a reason for all three of those things.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have questions about the Briar-Heart.</Source>
      <Dest>我对荆棘之心有些疑问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>He's a Briarheart. He underwent the ancient rite, and follows in the footsteps of Faolon the Red Eagle.  It's a great honor.</Source>
      <Dest>他是个荆棘之心。他经受住了这个古老的仪式，正如弗兰——红鹰所做的一样。这是莫大的荣誉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have questions about the Briar-Heart.</Source>
      <Dest>我对荆棘之心有些疑问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although, he's not as fast as most Briarhearts, and I'm not just talking about his wits.</Source>
      <Dest>但他不像大多数的荆棘之心一样快，我说的不只是他的心智。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I have questions about the Briar-Heart.</Source>
      <Dest>我对荆棘之心有些疑问。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When he runs, I like to imagine he's dragging an invisible boulder behind him, then his lumbering makes a little more sense.</Source>
      <Dest>当他奔跑的时候，我会想象他身后拖着一枚看不见的巨石，这样他那笨重的样子就合理多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're talking about the Civil War.</Source>
      <Dest>你在谈论内战吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's happening just like Madanach said it would.  He's a shrewd one.  I didn't understand it at the time, him letting that Silver-Blood use him.</Source>
      <Dest>当时发生的一切跟Madanach预言的一模一样。他真是老奸巨猾。之前我真没明白，为什么他会让银血家族利用自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're talking about the Civil War.</Source>
      <Dest>你在谈论内战吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I was ready to call the old man a coward, but it turns out snakes don't need no backbone.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾经要叫这老家伙懦夫了，但是后来我发现，狡猾如蛇般的人，是不需要骨气的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are you three doing here?</Source>
      <Dest>你们三个在这里做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What does it look like?  Holding this spot in case the slave folk send their troops from the north to march on Karthspire.</Source>
      <Dest>它看起来像在干什么？坚守这一阵地以免那些奴隶们的军队从北面进军到卡尔斯尖塔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are you three doing here?</Source>
      <Dest>你们三个在这里做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Sundered Towers are a better defensive position, but it takes an era and a day to get the word out to camp.</Source>
      <Dest>裂塔所处的位置用来防卫非常好，但这需要它正好赶上一个好时代，以及一声就地驻营的命令。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are you three doing here?</Source>
      <Dest>你们三个在这里做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Here we got a view of the Karth, and an easy hike back to the Spire.</Source>
      <Dest>我们在这儿看见了Karth，然后做了个简单的徒步旅行回到Spire。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What are you three doing here?</Source>
      <Dest>你们三个在这里做什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not like we need it. Cloaks and Slavers too busy fighting each other to bother with the free men of the Reach.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来我们并不需要。斗篷和奴隶贩子都忙于互相征伐，无暇顾及及远领地的自由居民。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fine. Let's talk. Just keep it brief.</Source>
      <Dest>好极了,让我们来谈谈,但是长话短说.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'll keep it as long as I like. That's what it means to be free.</Source>
      <Dest>I'll keep it as long as I like. That's what it means to be free.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Is the part where I kill you part of the plan as well?</Source>
      <Dest>连我杀你这情节也是这个计划的一部分吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But you wanted to talk first? You slave folk have the strangest rituals.</Source>
      <Dest>但你想先说话？你们这些奴隶的规矩可真奇怪。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I prefer a good fight to a good conversation.</Source>
      <Dest>比起谈判，我更喜欢来场战斗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Why not have both? Fighting with words is better than swords. Yeah, they may both leave a big mess, but only one's worth cleaning up.</Source>
      <Dest>为何不两者兼得呢？　与人争论时，言语胜过武器。　当然，两者都可能留下烂摊子，但只有一个值得去解决。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I will tend to her bottom and yours. My price is 100 septims.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢她跟你的屁股，我出100金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You must have acorns for eyes if you mistake this ruin for a brothel, and me for a person of wealth.</Source>
      <Dest>你要是把这个废墟当成妓院，还认为我很有钱的话，那你那双眼睛就算是长到屁股上了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then tell her to keep her hands where I can see them.</Source>
      <Dest>那么告诉它把手放在我能看见它们的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So are we three your prisoners now?  Or do you mean to keep us as slaves?  What will the city folk think, you herding a flock of savages?</Source>
      <Dest>所以我们三个现在是你的囚犯咯?  你想把我们当做奴奴隶?  市民们会怎么想，你在放养一群野蛮人?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree. That's why I live by my own rules. If the guards protest, I kill them.</Source>
      <Dest>同意。这就是为什么我坚持自己的原则。如果警卫反抗，我就杀了他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Aye, but you're going to have to kill all of them before you can truly be free.</Source>
      <Dest>恩哼，不过你得杀死所有人才能真正的自由。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I agree. That's why I live by my own rules. If the guards protest, I kill them.</Source>
      <Dest>同意。这就是为什么我坚持自己的原则。如果警卫反抗，我就杀了他们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's why we can't stand idly by while they expand their cities and build their armies, choking off what's left of the free lands.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是我们不能看着他们扩大他们的城市，建立他们的军队，毁掉这片自由土地上的一切，而我们却无所事事的原因。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good. The less you people talk, the better.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，口风越紧越好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now that's no way to start a conversation now, is it?  More like a way to end one.  And what do you mean by "you people?"</Source>
      <Dest>Now that's no way to start a conversation now, is it?  More like a way to end one.  And what do you mean by "you people?"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good. The less you people talk, the better.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，口风越紧越好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know where you're from, but them's fighting words, out here in The Reach.  And I don't think it'd be wise for you to take on the three of us.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道你是从哪儿来的，但那些话在这里——在瑞驰——是些挑衅的言辞。我也不认为你想一挑三有多明智。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good. The less you people talk, the better.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，口风越紧越好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I bet it's 'cause all you slave folk get so wound up bending over and bending the knee, you take it out on us.</Source>
      <Dest>[我猜那是因为你的奴隶们都屈服于你的淫威而跪倒在地，我们和他们可不同。].</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Good. The less you people talk, the better.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，口风越紧越好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sit down and relax, because unlike the Jarls you call master, the free men of the Reach won't ask you to polish no Imperial horn.</Source>
      <Dest>坐下来缓一缓，因为我们不像那些必须要你叫主人的什么领主，我们边陲领的自由人不会要求你擦亮帝国的号角。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Forsworn rebels.  Lay down your arms or have your arms cut off.</Source>
      <Dest>Forsworn rebels.  Lay down your arms or have your arms cut off.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that I could do, but can't promise you I will. Thendrick though, he ain't much for laying down, and my sister got no arms to lay.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯..这我可以做到,但我不能向你保证能成功。尽管兰瑞克，他放下太多了，而我的姐妹没有臂膀可以依靠。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Forsworn rebels.  Lay down your arms or have your arms cut off.</Source>
      <Dest>Forsworn rebels.  Lay down your arms or have your arms cut off.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Shamans do most of their fighting with their hands, and she can't really lay them down without getting on all fours.</Source>
      <Dest>Shaman大多用手战斗，所以她没法在不潜行的时候把他们放倒。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Forsworn rebels.  Lay down your arms or have your arms cut off.</Source>
      <Dest>Forsworn rebels.  Lay down your arms or have your arms cut off.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe you'd like that, maybe you want to see her like a cat and lick her own bottom.  I'll be sure to tell her that soon as we're done killing you.</Source>
      <Dest>也许你喜欢这个样子，也许你想看到她像只猫一样的舔自己的屁股。我一定会告诉她的，然后我们就杀了你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Get out of my sight. Got bodies to take care of and family to mourn.</Source>
      <Dest>Get out of my sight. Got bodies to take care of and family to mourn.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>State your business visitor. You speak to Ynvar, daughter of the Free Men, proud liberators of the Kingdom of the Reach.</Source>
      <Dest>说明你的来意。现在与你交谈的是瑞驰王国伟大的解放者，the Free Men，的女儿——盈法尔。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That goes for the others too, though they won't say as much.  Thendrick is a mute, and my sister Yseld might as well be one.  </Source>
      <Dest>这也适用于其他人。虽然他们不会也那么说。 兰瑞克是个哑巴，而我的妹妹伊沙德可能也是。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They're both good folk though, if you don't mind the awkward pauses.</Source>
      <Dest>他们都是很好的人，如果你不介意尴尬冷场的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Salutations, child of the Reach.  I seek shelter and sanctuary.</Source>
      <Dest>向你致敬，边塞领之子。我在找住所和避难的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It talks fancy, like a high born! Sure thing master, you may have shelter and sanctuary and all the best wine the Four Skull Lookout has to offer.</Source>
      <Dest>提出你的幻想吧，比如【一个高贵的出身啥的】！是的主人，也许你已经有住所和庇护所以及四骷髅了望台提供的最好的酒了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Salutations, child of the Reach.  I seek shelter and sanctuary.</Source>
      <Dest>向你致敬，边塞领之子。我在找住所和避难的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry, I don't mean to mock. Some folk just make easy targets. You did good to recognize us as the true people of the Reach.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉，我没有嘲讽之意。一些人只是为了制定一个轻松的目标。 你在承认我们是边塞领的真正人民方面做的很好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Salutations, child of the Reach.  I seek shelter and sanctuary.</Source>
      <Dest>向你致敬，边塞领之子。我在找住所和避难的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I must congratulate your mother on raising one so bright, and making one so fetching.</Source>
      <Dest>我必须得为你的母亲抚养了一个如此机灵可爱的姑娘而感到高兴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I enjoy polishing Imperial horns.  You should try it.</Source>
      <Dest>我喜欢擦亮这些帝国号角，你真应该试试看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Do you use your hands or your mouth? I suppose if you enjoy being a slave, you're just as free as any Reachman.</Source>
      <Dest>Do you use your hands or your mouth? I suppose if you enjoy being a slave, you're just as free as any Reachman.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>My father helped too.</Source>
      <Dest>我的父亲也有很大的帮助。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I'm sure the five or so seconds when he shot his milk was exhausting.</Source>
      <Dest>嗷，我敢肯定他精疲力竭的时候，只要两三秒就会把他的牛奶吹掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They're beautiful creatures. I would like to bed a hagraven someday.</Source>
      <Dest>她们是很美的物种，我很乐意与一个乌鸦鬼婆同床共枕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I'm sure the Matriarchs would scratch and claw each other's eyes out for a chance to mate with a specimen like you.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我很确定Matriarchs会为了有机会与像你一样类型的人结合，而把每个人的眼睛都抠出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They're beautiful creatures. I would like to bed a hagraven someday.</Source>
      <Dest>她们是很美的物种，我很乐意与一个乌鸦鬼婆同床共枕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, when you wake up in the morning you might not remember what happened.  You might be like Thendrick, and have no memory at all. </Source>
      <Dest>当然，你一早醒来，可能不记得发生了什么事。你可能会像兰瑞克一样，压根儿毫无印象。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They're beautiful creatures. I would like to bed a hagraven someday.</Source>
      <Dest>她们是很美的物种，我很乐意与一个乌鸦鬼婆同床共枕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, I'm sure the Matriarchs would scratch and claw each other's eyes out for a chance to mate with a specimen like you.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，我很确定Matriarchs会为了有机会与像你一样类型的人结合，而把每个人的眼睛都抠出来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They're beautiful creatures. I would like to bed a hagraven someday.</Source>
      <Dest>她们是很美的物种，我很乐意与一个乌鸦鬼婆同床共枕。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Of course, when you wake up you might end up part of their coven, since they only seem to make Briarhearts out of the males.</Source>
      <Dest>当然了，等你一觉醒来发现自己成了她们祭祀的一部分，因为他们制造那些荆棘心用的好像都是男人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I believe your claims to this land is true, but truth matters little.</Source>
      <Dest> 我相信你真的有用这片土地，但这完全无关紧要。 .</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Aye, it's strength that's bound the people to slavery, and strength alone that will free us.</Source>
      <Dest>对，人们是因为武力才被迫接受奴役，也只有武力可以还我们自由。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I imagine most Nords would be less keen on dying in battle if it meant the void.</Source>
      <Dest>如果那意味着空虚，我设想多数诺德人战死疆场的热情会小得多.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So we're in agreement? Fancy that. But is it the void they go to, or somewhere else? Maybe they don't go. Maybe they return.</Source>
      <Dest>那么，我们意见一致了？真想不到。但是我们还是不知道他们去哪儿了，或者现在在哪儿？也许他们还没走，也许他们会回来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I imagine most Nords would be less keen on dying in battle if it meant the void.</Source>
      <Dest>如果那意味着空虚，我设想多数诺德人战死疆场的热情会小得多.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Old Gods tell us a soul ain't whisked away to some faraway land.  Makes no sense if you think about it.  It'd be way too crowded.</Source>
      <Dest>旧神告诉我们灵魂并不会漂泊至某个遥远的世界。仔细想想就知道这是一派胡言。要是这样这里会很拥挤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I imagine most Nords would be less keen on dying in battle if it meant the void.</Source>
      <Dest>如果那意味着空虚，我设想多数诺德人战死疆场的热情会小得多.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A soul is like the air around us.  We breathe it in, breathe it out, so it may find its way to another.</Source>
      <Dest>灵魂就像我们身边的空气。我们吸入它们，呼出它们，然后它们就又找别人去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dealing with accursed Hagravens is never a good idea.</Source>
      <Dest>要处理那些被诅咒的乌鸦鬼婆真不是一个好主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You speak of the matriarchs, the blessed witches who made a pact with the Old Gods to gain the ancient magics.</Source>
      <Dest>你提到了那些老妖精，那些该死的女巫和上古之神签订了契约来换取远古巫术.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Dealing with accursed Hagravens is never a good idea.</Source>
      <Dest>要处理那些被诅咒的乌鸦鬼婆真不是一个好主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just as the Forsworn must burn their land to free it, the Matriarchs sacrifice their humanity to give the free folk theirs.</Source>
      <Dest>就如弃誓者们必须把他们的土地化为焦土才能获得解放，女主人们必须牺牲她们的人性以保全自由人民的人性。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They call Madanach the "King in Rags." So there is someone even you bow to.</Source>
      <Dest>他们称迈德纳奇为 "衣衫褴褛的国王" 。看来还有连你也得毕恭毕敬地待他的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Madanach ain't no king, and even if he called himself that, which he don't, it wouldn't mean we'd have to bend the knee.</Source>
      <Dest>迈德纳奇不是国王。即使他如此称呼自己，那他也不是。所以我们不必对他卑躬屈膝的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They call Madanach the "King in Rags." So there is someone even you bow to.</Source>
      <Dest>他们称迈德纳奇为 "衣衫褴褛的国王" 。看来还有连你也得毕恭毕敬地待他的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only ones we worship is the Old Gods.  A man is only as good as his last smart idea.</Source>
      <Dest>我们唯一崇拜的是上古之神。【只有一直想法绝妙，才称得上是男人。】</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The magic of the Old Gods is powerful.</Source>
      <Dest>古代神灵的魔法非常强大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes. Some say their power is waning, but that's a mistake. A god don't lose its power, and it don't depend on people worshiping it.</Source>
      <Dest>是的。有些人说它们的力量会逐渐减弱，但这是个错误。就算失去了信仰者，神也不会失去任何力量。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The magic of the Old Gods is powerful.</Source>
      <Dest>古代神灵的魔法非常强大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's there and will always be, it just needs people willing to harvest it.</Source>
      <Dest>它就在那儿而且一直在那儿，只等着有人愿意去收割它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I believe it's called a phalanx.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为那个应该称为趾骨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Right, Imperials always give them fancy names to everything, especially themselves.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。帝国人就会给破玩意起好听的名字，尤其是他们自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I believe it's called a phalanx.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为那个应该称为趾骨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In any case, I remember Thendrick charging ahead and knocking the whole lot of them on their backs.</Source>
      <Dest>在任何情况下，我记得兰瑞克都是冲向前方敲击他们全部人的脊背。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I believe it's called a phalanx.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为那个应该称为趾骨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Then he stuck about half of them in their bellies and the rest he set on fire. </Source>
      <Dest>然后他刺破了一半儿人的肚子，然后放火烤熟了剩下的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I believe it's called a phalanx.</Source>
      <Dest>我认为那个应该称为趾骨。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I wonder how many hours those stupid fools practiced that thing only to have it fail them.</Source>
      <Dest>我好奇的是，那帮蠢货花了多少时间来进行练习但却不断地失败。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Brothels lead to the spread of disease.  Animal cruelty is wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>妓院引致疾病的传播。虐待动物是不对的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well that's what potions are for. And since when did we start caring about what animals think?</Source>
      <Dest>好吧这就是药物的用处。话说我们是从什么时候开始在意起动物的想法的来着？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You talk of kingdoms and freedom. I thought this area was part of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>你谈到了帝国与自由。我还以为这里是天际省的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm sorry I confused you, I didn't know your masters didn't teach you proper history.</Source>
      <Dest>我很抱歉让你迷惑，没想到你的老师没有教给你正确的历史。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You talk of kingdoms and freedom. I thought this area was part of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>你谈到了帝国与自由。我还以为这里是天际省的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Reachmen called this home for ages upon eons. From before the time of the Ten Kingdoms, to the day they were united by the Red Eagle himself.</Source>
      <Dest>瑞驰人说他们的故乡已经有千万年的岁月了。在the Ten Kingdoms以前，那一天，他们因红鹰而团结起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You talk of kingdoms and freedom. I thought this area was part of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>你谈到了帝国与自由。我还以为这里是天际省的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's Hestra's armies that brought these lands under the tyranny of the Imperial banner.</Source>
      <Dest>是Hestra的军队使这片土地笼罩在帝国旗帜的专制之下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You talk of kingdoms and freedom. I thought this area was part of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>你谈到了帝国与自由。我还以为这里是天际省的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ever since then, we Reach folk have been fighting the invaders off to reclaim our home.</Source>
      <Dest>从那时起，我们瑞驰的人民就开始为了收回自己的家园而对抗侵略者了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You talk of kingdoms and freedom. I thought this area was part of Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>你谈到了帝国与自由。我还以为这里是天际省的一部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thendrick, Yseld, and I are just one of a long line of freedom fighters going back to Lord Faolon, the first of the Briarhearts.</Source>
      <Dest>Thendrick, Yseld, and I are just one of a long line of freedom fighters going back to Lord Faolon, the first of the Briarhearts.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As far as I know there is no slavery in Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>据我所知天际省并不存在奴隶制。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh there isn't now, is there?  So if I find a plot of land I like, I can make a home, start a farm, and the local Thane won't make a stink?</Source>
      <Dest>哦，不过现在可没有了，不是吗？如果我找到一块我喜欢的地儿，我可以造个房子，开家农场，当地领主难道不会摆一副臭脸给我看？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As far as I know there is no slavery in Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>据我所知天际省并不存在奴隶制。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I make a bunch of money, the guard captain won't come knocking on my door to collect the Jarl's taxes?</Source>
      <Dest>如果我赚了点钱，守卫队长未必不会上门找我交税。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As far as I know there is no slavery in Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>据我所知天际省并不存在奴隶制。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I want to start a skooma operation, run a brothel, or a dog pit, will the locals mind their own business, or will they pry into mine?</Source>
      <Dest>如果我想开始做斯库玛生意，开个妓院，或者是开个矿那本地人就要开始想想他们自己的买卖了，也许他们会打我生意的主意？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As far as I know there is no slavery in Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>据我所知天际省并不存在奴隶制。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I want to worship my own gods, do I have that right, or will I be forced to kneel before yours?</Source>
      <Dest>如果我愿意服从我们的神明，我是不是一定要，或者说，我是不是就要臣服于你面前？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>As far as I know there is no slavery in Skyrim.</Source>
      <Dest>据我所知天际省并不存在奴隶制。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Claiming there's no slavery in Skyrim's a whole lot of mammoth dung, if you pardon me saying.</Source>
      <Dest>即使你让我再说一次，我依然坚称在天际这样一个到处都是猛犸粪便的地方是没有奴隶贩子的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Yes, and before that these were Elven lands.  Things change.</Source>
      <Dest>没错，之前这里是精灵的土地，一切都变了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Aye, but it ain't about who was here first. It's about how this land was made free.</Source>
      <Dest>是，可问题不在于谁先来的。关键是这片土地怎么才能解放。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This lookout is now the sovereign territory of the Thalmor.  Leave.</Source>
      <Dest>这座了望台已经是 梭默 君主的领地，走开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You think you're a Thalmor?  Now I thought Yseld was mixed up in the head.  You do know you ain't exactly a High Elf now, don't you?</Source>
      <Dest>你认为自己是梭默?现在想想，我觉得伊沙德可能脑子进水了. 你知道自己并不是高精灵，对吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This lookout is now the sovereign territory of the Thalmor.  Leave.</Source>
      <Dest>这座了望台已经是 梭默 君主的领地，走开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although I've heard they do count the Khajiit among their slaves, so it wouldn't be stretch to include you as well.</Source>
      <Dest>虽然我听说他们的确计算它们奴隶中虎人的数量，所以要把你包括进来毫无问题。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This lookout is now the sovereign territory of the Thalmor.  Leave.</Source>
      <Dest>这座了望台已经是 梭默 君主的领地，走开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're a Thalmor? Now that's rich. Their standards must be pretty low to let the likes of you into their little cult.</Source>
      <Dest>你是个梭默？信息量略大啊。看来他们的标准定得非常之低，才能让像你这样的家伙加入他们小小的教派。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This lookout is now the sovereign territory of the Thalmor.  Leave.</Source>
      <Dest>这座了望台已经是 梭默 君主的领地，走开。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Either way, you're just one more slave, parroting the words of his master.  We will free this land and its people from your tyranny.</Source>
      <Dest>Either way, you're just one more slave, parroting the words of his master.  We will free this land and its people from your tyranny.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You know Yseld, I think you and Thendrick would've made a cute couple.</Source>
      <Dest>你认识伊沙德，我想你跟兰瑞克实在是很般配啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, was he speaking the language of the forest?  Cause growling and scratching your behind ain't any words I know.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，他在说森林的语言？招致咆哮和你后背上抓伤的不是我知道的词汇。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>(Laughs) Well, have you tried looking up your arse?  That's where I pull all my best ideas from.</Source>
      <Dest>(笑声)那么，你有没有试试用你的屁股呢？我的好点子都是从那来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>有什么关系么?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is something the matter?</Source>
      <Dest>出了什么事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
