<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It's dangerous for someone as stupid as you to be fiddling with magic.</Source>
      <Dest>像你这样的蠢人摆弄魔法真是太危险了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, I think it's unsafe for someone as rude as you to be talking with words.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，我觉得换一个人用你这种粗鲁的口气说话，肯定要遭殃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So...you're an optimistic cynic.</Source>
      <Dest>所以……你是个乐观的悲观主义者。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm not sure I know what that means.  No, I'm positive I don't.</Source>
      <Dest>我不确定自己知道这意味着什么。不，我肯定不知道。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>When you die, that's it.  This is the only life you have, so make it count.</Source>
      <Dest>等你死了，那一切就都结束了，人的生命只有一次，所以好好珍惜它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Make it count what?  And why?  I don't really want to spend my life counting things.</Source>
      <Dest>让它数什么？而且为啥又要这样做呢？我可真不想一辈子就花在数东西上了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, there's lots of harm.  Bad things happen when good people do nothing.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，那害处可多了。好人不做事时坏事就发生了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>What if I don't consider myself to be a good person?  What if I'm a bad person?  Maybe good things happen if bad people do nothing.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我不认为自己是好人呢？如果我是个坏蛋呢？也许坏人什么都不做就是好事了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In that case, you owe it to your people to develop it.</Source>
      <Dest>在这种情况下，你应该为你的人发展它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think so too. Yet when I ask my sister about it, she says I'm free to choose my own path.  You can always be a shaman in the next life, she says.</Source>
      <Dest>我也那样想。但当我向我的姐姐提及此事时，她说我可以自由选择我自己的人生道路。她说，你也可以下辈子再去做萨满。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In that case, you owe it to your people to develop it.</Source>
      <Dest>在这种情况下，你应该为你的人发展它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well, that seems hardly fair to future Yseld, me deciding her fate and all.  It'd be so much easier if I was only choosing for me.</Source>
      <Dest>好吧，伊沙德的命运将由我们来决定，这看起来似乎对未来的她有些不公平。如果只为我选择的话，那就简单多了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>In that case, you owe it to your people to develop it.</Source>
      <Dest>在这种情况下，你应该为你的人发展它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if I got someone else's soul, does that mean I'm not me?  If a die, do I become someone else?</Source>
      <Dest>But if I got someone else's soul, does that mean I'm not me?  If a die, do I become someone else?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think you can recall faces?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你认为你能回忆起那些面孔？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I think it's because I'm a visual person. That's how I learned to cast spells, I just imagine them coming out of my hand.</Source>
      <Dest>我想这是因为我是一个视觉型的人。我只想象法术从我的手中产生。这就是我如何学会施法的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why do you think you can recall faces?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么你认为你能回忆起那些面孔？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I even learned to conjure my first sword that way, from my head to my hands.  Although I can't seem to recall where I put it.</Source>
      <Dest>我曾经用那种从我的脑子里变到手上的方式召唤我第一把剑。虽然我记不得把它放在哪里了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you often forget things?</Source>
      <Dest>你经常忘事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, all sorts of things.  It's bad enough I forget a headdress or two, but sometimes I forget to put on other pieces of armor as well.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，所有的一切。忘了戴点遮住头的东西已经够糟的了，但实际上有些时候我也会忘了穿上其他部分的装备。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you often forget things?</Source>
      <Dest>你经常忘事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>One day I ran into a fight stark naked.  Sure, I caught the enemy by surprise, but it's not a tactic you want to be known for.</Source>
      <Dest>有一天，我还裸着呢就陷入了场战斗。当然，我仗着敌人出乎意料，把他海扁了一顿，但这种战术说出去还挺丢人的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you often forget things?</Source>
      <Dest>你经常忘事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Wearing my armor is one I thing I won't ever forget again, knock on...well, if you see some wood on your travels, be sure to knock it for me.</Source>
      <Dest>我再也不会忘记穿铠甲了，顺便一说...呃，如果你在旅途中看见一些木头的话，请把它带给我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you often forget things?</Source>
      <Dest>你经常忘事吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Other than that, I'm not good with names, but faces I remember.  Which doesn't do me a whole lot of good.</Source>
      <Dest>除此之外，我不擅长记名字，但脸我还记得。他们没对我做过什么好事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you remember the day he transformed?</Source>
      <Dest>你还记得他异变时的情形吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I forget a lot, but I'll never forget that stormy night when he lay on the witch's table, how the thunder roared and the grass stood on end.</Source>
      <Dest>我忘记了很多东西，但决不会忘记那个风雨交加的夜晚，他躺在女巫的台子上，雷声隆隆，草木皆惊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you remember the day he transformed?</Source>
      <Dest>你还记得他异变时的情形吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It began as a bluff and became a vow.  It didn't matter if the duel would never come.  To Thendrick, this was a test of his love.  And hers.</Source>
      <Dest>It began as a bluff and became a vow.  It didn't matter if the duel would never come.  To Thendrick, this was a test of his love.  And hers.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you remember the day he transformed?</Source>
      <Dest>你还记得他异变时的情形吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I begged him to reconsider, I told him I'd tie my sister up and drag her to his tent.  He turned his head to me and smiled.  I smiled back.</Source>
      <Dest>我请他重新考虑，告诉他我会把我姐姐绑起来拖进他的帐篷。他转过头对着我笑了，我也回以微笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Do you remember the day he transformed?</Source>
      <Dest>你还记得他异变时的情形吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What made Thendrick give up on Ynvar?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让兰瑞克放弃了盈瓦儿?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Nothing could and nothing would, until the day Ynvar told him yes.  She'd love him on one condition, if he managed to best her in single combat.</Source>
      <Dest>除非盈瓦儿答应，不然他大概是不会放弃的。要让她爱上她只有一个条件，就是他能一对一地击败她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What made Thendrick give up on Ynvar?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让兰瑞克放弃了盈瓦儿?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>My sister knew that Thendrick was half the fighter she was.  But more importantly, he would never lay a hand on the one he loved.</Source>
      <Dest>我姐姐知道兰瑞克跟她比起来只能算半桶水。但更重要的是，他永远不会对他的爱人动手。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What made Thendrick give up on Ynvar?</Source>
      <Dest>是什么让兰瑞克放弃了盈瓦儿?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So the deal wasn't fair, and it wasn't square. There was only one way he could hope to best her in combat, and both he and Ynvar knew it.</Source>
      <Dest>这并不公平，也不正常。要想在战斗中击败她，只有一个方法，关于这一点他和盈瓦儿都非常清楚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your Old Gods interest me. Tell me about them.</Source>
      <Dest>你的旧神吸引了我 说说他们.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'm afraid I'd just get it all wrong. Thoughts don't stick to my brain so good.</Source>
      <Dest>我担心我把所有事都给弄错了。我现在脑子里一团浆糊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Your Old Gods interest me. Tell me about them.</Source>
      <Dest>你的旧神吸引了我 说说他们.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only thing I remember is that story one of the elders told about death, and what happens to your soul.</Source>
      <Dest>我唯一记得的是一个老者讲述的关于死亡的故事，以及你的灵魂会发生的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well you better start looking for it. I think I saw something by the cliffs.</Source>
      <Dest>你最好开始寻找它。我认为我在悬崖边看到了什么东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh no, not again! The winds here sweep everything off the cliff.  I'm beginning to think they don't like me.  The winds.</Source>
      <Dest>哦不！别再吹了！这儿的风打算把一切都吹下悬崖。我想它们恐怕不喜欢我。我是说风。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well you better start looking for it. I think I saw something by the cliffs.</Source>
      <Dest>你最好开始寻找它。我认为我在悬崖边看到了什么东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just don't tell Ynvar I lost it again.  She's always saying if I fell out of a boat I couldn't find water, and I think she might be right.</Source>
      <Dest>不要告诉盈法尔我又弄丢了它。她总是说如果我从一艘船上掉下来，我就找不到水了，而且我觉得她说得挺对的。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Bound weapons are impermanent.  They basically disappear.</Source>
      <Dest>召唤武器是有时间的。到时间就消失了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?  That's a relief.  I was beginning to wonder if I was going to bury all of Skyrim with the swords I left behind.</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗？那我就放心了。如果每次都能召唤出一把的话，那我扔掉的剑岂不是可以把整个天际给埋了吗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>One of your friends stole it.  They obviously hate you.</Source>
      <Dest>你的一个朋友偷了 它。很明显他们是恨你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They would never do that!  I think you're lying, but then again, unlike some people, I don't say things without proof.</Source>
      <Dest>他们绝不会那样做！我认为你在说谎，不过话说回来，我不像一般人那样没有证据就胡说。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why live at this lookout?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么住在这望台里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You don't like it?  I know it doesn't have much in the way of furnishings, but there's a warm fire, lots of space, and you can't beat the view.</Source>
      <Dest>你不喜欢吗？我知道没有什么华丽的家装，但是这里有温暖的炉火，有足够大的空间，而且这视野，真的棒极了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why live at this lookout?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么住在这望台里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Most of the free folk around here stay in the Towers just to the east, but it gets a little crowded.</Source>
      <Dest>这儿大部分的自由民都会住在西边的塔里，不过那儿有点挤。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why live at this lookout?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么住在这望台里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thendrick needs the space and bandits to kill, or else he gets cranky.</Source>
      <Dest>兰瑞克需要空间，强盗也需要杀死，否则他会胡思乱想。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why live at this lookout?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么住在这望台里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>There's also a strategic advanatage to holding this lookout, but I don't really know too much about that.</Source>
      <Dest>据说占着这哨塔就拥有了地理上的优势，可我真不知道那究竟是啥。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why live at this lookout?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么住在这望台里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you want to talk war and politics, you should talk to my sister.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你想谈战争和政治，那你应该跟我姐姐聊聊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Why live at this lookout?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么住在这望台里？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Although you're best off agreeing with whatever she says.  Opinions are like the weather, and nothing we say can ever change them.</Source>
      <Dest>我觉得你最好还是不管她说什么你都顺着她。有句话叫：老天爷说变脸就变脸。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A one-sided love is a sad and unfortunate thing.</Source>
      <Dest>一种片面的爱情是一种悲伤和不幸的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It was very sad, and to make things worse, my sister did kind of lead him on.</Source>
      <Dest>确实挺悲惨，不过更糟的是，我姐姐从来就没有干脆利落地拒绝。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A one-sided love is a sad and unfortunate thing.</Source>
      <Dest>一种片面的爱情是一种悲伤和不幸的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whenever he wooed her she would make excuses, like he was too fat one day and too skinny the next.</Source>
      <Dest>每次他向她求爱的时候，她都会有诸多借口，前一天还说他太胖，后一天却又嫌他太瘦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A one-sided love is a sad and unfortunate thing.</Source>
      <Dest>一种片面的爱情是一种悲伤和不幸的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Poor Thendrick thought she was just being fickle.  Figured one of these days he'd end up being the right weight, he just had to keep asking.</Source>
      <Dest>可怜的兰瑞克认为她只是在使性子罢了。他以为只要坚持不懈地每天去问一遍，总有一天他的体重会符合她的要求。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I guess I side with the romantics. Thendrick loved Ynvar more than a dog loves a bone, but my sister don't take kindly to being buried.</Source>
      <Dest>我还是想往浪漫的方向想。兰瑞克深爱盈瓦儿更甚于狗爱骨头，但我的姐姐可不喜欢被他给埋起来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She said he was suffocating, is what I mean.  All that attention.  Although I wonder, is that such a bad thing?</Source>
      <Dest>我的意思是说，她说过他的求爱攻势太过猛烈简直快让她窒息。不过在我看来，这好像也不是件坏事？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ynvar's a free woman though.  It's like the elders say, there are bees meant to make honey, and bees meant to sting.</Source>
      <Dest>盈瓦儿是个自由的女人。像长辈们说的那样，蜜蜂既能酿蜜，也能蜇人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you think?</Source>
      <Dest>你觉得怎样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Personally, I don't see why anyone has to be a bee of any kind.  I'm terrified of them.</Source>
      <Dest>就我个人而言，我不明白为什么有人会去做只蜜蜂，无论是哪种蜜蜂。我挺怕它们的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to talk about the Briar-Heart.</Source>
      <Dest>我想谈谈关于荆棘之心的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The Reachmen say his human heart was too big for his chest, so he traded it in for a smaller model.</Source>
      <Dest>瑞驰人说他那人类心脏对于他的胸腔来说太大了，所以他换了个小的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I want to talk about the Briar-Heart.</Source>
      <Dest>我想谈谈关于荆棘之心的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The romantic types say his old heart was broken, by the only woman he'd ever loved.</Source>
      <Dest>那浪漫主义者说他那沧桑的心受伤了，只因那个他唯一爱上的女人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I don't care where you go when you die, just so long as it's far away from me.</Source>
      <Dest>我不关心你死后去的是哪儿，至少那地方现在离我是很远的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>How mean!  If I were you, I'd be careful what you wish for.  The Old Gods have a sense of humor, and in the next life they might make me your mother.</Source>
      <Dest>太卑劣了！如果我是你，我许愿的时候会更谨慎一点。旧神很有幽默感，说不定他们会在下辈子把我变成你的母亲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Cynics have unrealistic expectations, but they're usually more depressing.</Source>
      <Dest>犬儒总爱不切实际地期待， 但通常他们也更为悲观。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>See?  I'm not at all depressing to be around.  Tiresome maybe, dangerous sometimes, but never depressing.</Source>
      <Dest>看见了吗？我可一点也不悲观。也许我会厌烦，有时我很危险，但我从来不悲观。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The only person you let down is yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>唯一对你失望的人就是你自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know, my self can be pretty lazy.  It likes to be laid down, and let down easy.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道，我自认为我是个懒得要死的家伙。就好像收起武器，然后放轻松那样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The only person you let down is yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>唯一对你失望的人就是你自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Seems to go against what people say about me though, that I got the soul of an old witch, and from what I've seen, witches don't sleep much.</Source>
      <Dest>看起来跟别人谈论我的说法有出入啊，说我被一个老巫婆的灵魂附体，可据我所知，女巫是很少睡觉的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The only person you let down is yourself.</Source>
      <Dest>唯一对你失望的人就是你自己。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if I got someone else's soul, does that mean I'm not me?  If a die, do I become someone else?</Source>
      <Dest>But if I got someone else's soul, does that mean I'm not me?  If a die, do I become someone else?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I can help you look for it if you describe it.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你能描述的话我能帮你找到它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sure thing.  It's real pretty, made of feathers and bones and braided fur and... (Sigh) It's on my head, isn't it. </Source>
      <Dest>没问题。它很可爱，是用羽毛、骨头和编织了的毛皮制成的，还有...（叹气）它就那样活生生地在我脑海里呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I can help you look for it if you describe it.</Source>
      <Dest>如果你能描述的话我能帮你找到它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ynvar's always saying if I fell out of a boat I couldn't find water, and I think she might be right.</Source>
      <Dest>Ynvar's always saying if I fell out of a boat I couldn't find water, and I think she might be right.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't matter what names you give your savage gods.  They're all false.</Source>
      <Dest>不管你们给自己的二货神灵取什么名字，他们都是假的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Really?  Well, that's a load off my mind.  I didn't like the whole story the elders told about coming back to the world as a creature.</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗？嗯，这对我的脑子来说是个负担。我不喜欢长辈们讲述的关于变成其他生物复活的故事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't matter what names you give your savage gods.  They're all false.</Source>
      <Dest>不管你们给自己的二货神灵取什么名字，他们都是假的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>They say some people come back as animals, or even worse, spiders.</Source>
      <Dest>他们说一些人会退化成动物，甚至是狼，或蜘蛛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't matter what names you give your savage gods.  They're all false.</Source>
      <Dest>不管你们给自己的二货神灵取什么名字，他们都是假的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which is just about the most horrifying thing I can imagine.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我能想象到的最恐怖的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't matter what names you give your savage gods.  They're all false.</Source>
      <Dest>不管你们给自己的二货神灵取什么名字，他们都是假的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I came back as a spider, I reckon I'd bite myself and throw my health potion in the river.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我像一只蜘蛛一样回来，我估计我会咬到自己并把我的治疗药水丢进河中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I threw one in the campfire just a second ago.  Must have been yours.</Source>
      <Dest>我才刚刚往火堆里扔过一个。肯定是你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Now why did you go and do that?  Nnngh...Ynvar is going to have my neck for this.  It took her a week to craft this one.</Source>
      <Dest>你为什么要这么做？ 嗯啊...盈瓦儿绝对会掐断我的脖子的。她花了一个星期才把这做出来的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I threw one in the campfire just a second ago.  Must have been yours.</Source>
      <Dest>我才刚刚往火堆里扔过一个。肯定是你的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I suppose it's my fault for finding it sooner.  Ynvar's always saying if I fell out of a boat I couldn't find water, and I think she might be right.</Source>
      <Dest>I suppose it's my fault for finding it sooner.  Ynvar's always saying if I fell out of a boat I couldn't find water, and I think she might be right.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the one on your head?</Source>
      <Dest>你头上的那个呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The one on my...oh!  Well, don't I feel stupid.  I told myself the last time that would be the first place I look, instead of the last.</Source>
      <Dest>居然在我的……噢！好吧，我果然是够蠢的。我上次还告诫自己呢，一定要从这个地方着手开始找，而不是把这个地方放到最后找。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the one on your head?</Source>
      <Dest>你头上的那个呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Just don't tell Ynvar.  She's likely to shave my head and glue the thing to my scalp.</Source>
      <Dest>只要别告诉盈瓦儿就行。她很有可能会剃光我的头发然后用胶水把那玩意儿粘在我的头皮上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What about the one on your head?</Source>
      <Dest>你头上的那个呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>She always tells me if I fell out of a boat I couldn't find water, and I can't say she's wrong.</Source>
      <Dest>她总是告诉我如果我掉到船外我会找不到水，我觉得她说得挺对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Try actually thinking instead of just saying the words.</Source>
      <Dest>试着深入思考而不是不经大脑胡吹.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I know that!  It just helps when I think out loud.  Truth is, I don't even know if I got those first few Gods right.</Source>
      <Dest>我就知道！只有我自言自语的时候才有用。其实，我甚至不清楚自己有没有搞懂之前的那几个神灵。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Try actually thinking instead of just saying the words.</Source>
      <Dest>试着深入思考而不是不经大脑胡吹.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only thing I remember is that story one of the elders told about death, and what happens to your soul.</Source>
      <Dest>我唯一记得的是一个老者讲述的关于死亡的故事，以及你的灵魂会发生的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You'll have to go to Oblivion to retrieve it.</Source>
      <Dest>你必须到湮灭去回收它。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oblivion?  Is that north or south of here?  Can you describe it?  I'm sorry, I'm really bad with places and names.</Source>
      <Dest>湮灭？在南边还是北边？你能形容一下它的样子吗？不好意思，我真的对地名什么的不太了解啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Ynvar?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是盈法尔？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ynvar is my sister. You'll find her around here somewhere.  She doesn't like it when I forget things, lose things, or both.  It's usually both.</Source>
      <Dest>盈瓦儿是我的姐姐。你能在附近找到她。我要是忘了什么或者把什么东西弄丢的话她就会不高兴。多数情况下这两件事会同时发生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Ynvar?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是盈法尔？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It ain't just the little things either.  I have a hard time with names, whether its people or the Old Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>这已经不只是件小事了，我记不住别人的名字，无论是常人或者古老的圣灵们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who's Ynvar?</Source>
      <Dest>谁是盈法尔？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can remember some, like the God of Bones, and the Goddess of the Hunt, and...um...what was it?  Think Yseld, think!</Source>
      <Dest>我能想起来一些，比如说骸骨之神啦，还有狩猎女神啦，还有...呃..是啥来着？想啊，伊莎德，快想啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've met Ynvar. She doesn't suffer foolishness.</Source>
      <Dest>我遇见盈瓦儿了. 她并不傻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Aye, she doesn't.  But what's the point of being sisters if we can't annoy each another every now and then?</Source>
      <Dest>是呀！她不喜欢太笨的人。但如果我们不能偶尔吵吵闹闹的，那当姐妹还有什么意义呢？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've met Ynvar. She doesn't suffer foolishness.</Source>
      <Dest>我遇见盈瓦儿了. 她并不傻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not to say my forgetfulness ain't a problem.  I got a hard time with names, whether it's with people or the Old Gods.</Source>
      <Dest>我的健忘是个大问题。我记不住别人的名字，无论是常人或者古老的圣灵们。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I've met Ynvar. She doesn't suffer foolishness.</Source>
      <Dest>我遇见盈瓦儿了. 她并不傻。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I can remember some, like the God of Bones, and the Goddess of the Hunt, and...um...what was it?  Think Yseld, think!</Source>
      <Dest>我能想起来一些，比如说骸骨之神啦，还有狩猎女神啦，还有...呃..是啥来着？想啊，伊莎德，快想啊！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>She should have told him she preferred women.  Problem solved.</Source>
      <Dest>她应该跟他说明自己喜欢的是女人。问题就解决啦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I guess you aren't wrong, but you aren't right either. She probably should have let him down gently, but not with such an obvious lie.</Source>
      <Dest>我想你并没有错，但是你同样也没对。她也许会委婉的告诉他，她让他失望了，但是她绝对不会撒这种一戳就穿的谎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Go away.  You're not wanted here.</Source>
      <Dest>走开。你在这里不受欢迎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Excuse me, but have you seen my headdress?  I seem to have misplaced it.</Source>
      <Dest>抱歉打扰一下，你看见我的头巾了吗？我不知道把它放到哪儿去了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>No, heathens like you go to Oblivion and spend eternity as daedric slaves.</Source>
      <Dest>不，像你这样的异教徒就应该被放逐到湮灭位面替那些该死的魔族端茶倒水一辈子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That doesn't sound very pleasant.  Your gods should be nicer, and maybe a bit less insecure.</Source>
      <Dest>这听起来可不太好。你的神灵们应该对你更好一些的，而且更可靠一些才好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a free woman.  You can do as you please.</Source>
      <Dest>你是个自由人，你可以做你想做的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So everyone says, but sometimes I wonder.  They keep telling me I got an old soul, like maybe one that belonged to an ancient witch or something.</Source>
      <Dest>大家都这么说，但有时我也想知道。他们总是跟我说我有一个古老的灵魂，好像曾经属于一名古代女巫还是什么来着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're a free woman.  You can do as you please.</Source>
      <Dest>你是个自由人，你可以做你想做的事情。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But if I got someone else's soul, does that mean I'm not me?  If a die, do I become someone else?</Source>
      <Dest>But if I got someone else's soul, does that mean I'm not me?  If a die, do I become someone else?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The gods you worship determine your fate upon death.</Source>
      <Dest>你的信仰决定了你死后的命运。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmm...maybe I should worship different Gods then.  Maybe a handsome one, with soft brown eyes.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯...也许我应该崇拜些不同的神，也许是一个有着温柔棕色双眼的英俊的神。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I totally agree. When I look at the choices, all I see are the imperfections.</Source>
      <Dest>我完全同意。当看着这些选择时，我眼里全是缺陷。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So be like me and don't pick a side.  It'll be the best choice you ever didn't make.</Source>
      <Dest>所以要像我一样不选择任何一方。这将会是你做过的最好的选择。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So Ynvar denied him. Becoming a Briarheart in response seems excessive.</Source>
      <Dest>所以盈瓦儿拒绝了他。但为此而成为一个荆棘之心未免太夸张了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>It's just who Thendrick was.  He was always the type to take things to extremes.</Source>
      <Dest>这就是兰瑞克的德行。他就是那种把所有事都搞的非常极端的家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So Ynvar denied him. Becoming a Briarheart in response seems excessive.</Source>
      <Dest>所以盈瓦儿拒绝了他。但为此而成为一个荆棘之心未免太夸张了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If Ynvar said his hair was too long, he'd shave it off.  If she said he was around too much, he'd watch her from afar.</Source>
      <Dest>如果盈瓦儿说他胡子太长了，他就把胡子刮掉。如果她说他离得太近了，他就躲得远远地看着她。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So Ynvar denied him. Becoming a Briarheart in response seems excessive.</Source>
      <Dest>所以盈瓦儿拒绝了他。但为此而成为一个荆棘之心未免太夸张了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If she said he was too short, he'd tie slabs of wood to the soles of his boots.</Source>
      <Dest>如果她嫌弃他太矮，他就在鞋子里钉上木制内增高。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>So Ynvar denied him. Becoming a Briarheart in response seems excessive.</Source>
      <Dest>所以盈瓦儿拒绝了他。但为此而成为一个荆棘之心未免太夸张了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If she said he was too tall, he'd crouch around all day like a goblin.  It was really very sweet.</Source>
      <Dest>一旦她说他太高了，他就会蹲下来像个哥布林一样过一整天。很甜蜜对吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you want to be loyal to the Empire, it's ruined by the Thalmor.  If you want to be a Stormcloak, it's ruined by racist Nords.  </Source>
      <Dest>如果你想保持对帝国的忠诚，这都被塔罗斯毁了。如果你想做一个风暴斗篷，这都被种族主义的诺德人毁了。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If you want to be a Forsworn, you got to deal with the Matriarchs, and don't tell Ynvar, but they sort of creep me out, and that ruins it for me.</Source>
      <Dest>你要是想成为弃誓者，你得去和麦德纳奇商量，还不能告诉盈瓦儿，但是有点吓着我了而且我还给搞砸了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sister says if you don't pick a side you might as well off yourself, but the Gods ruined that, with all their talk of the next life and the after.</Source>
      <Dest>修女说如果你不选择你的信仰你将会迷失，但是众神却用满口的来世之说否认。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Also Ynvar says killing yourself is kind of cowardly.  So I guess it got ruined by cowards too.</Source>
      <Dest>盈瓦儿也说自杀是一种懦弱的行为。不过我琢磨着这也太诋毁懦夫了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>And it's not just war. You want to be a mage, it's ruined by necromancers.  Want to be a bard, it's ruined by fairy bards.</Source>
      <Dest>这不仅仅是战争。你想成为一个法师，这念头被亡灵巫师毁了。想成为一名诗人，又比不过那些漂亮的诗人姑娘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How so?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么会？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So I thought, why not be nothing? Ain't no harm in that, is there?</Source>
      <Dest>所以我想，为什么不呢？又没有坏处，不是吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't care for politics?  Aren't you trying to liberate the Reach?</Source>
      <Dest>你不关心政治？你不想解放边塞领了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I don't know. I guess I am, but I really ain't married to any side in this war or that one.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道，我想是吧。但我真的不想在这场战争中跟任何一方牵扯太多。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't care for politics?  Aren't you trying to liberate the Reach?</Source>
      <Dest>你不关心政治？你不想解放边塞领了吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Seems to me no matter who you follow it's always ruined by someone.</Source>
      <Dest>我看你不管跟谁混到头来都会有人给你搅黄了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem rather harmless for a "Madman of the Reach."</Source>
      <Dest>对于 "瑞驰疯汉" 来说，你已经算是人畜无害了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hey, I resent that!  I've killed plenty of men.  Okay, maybe one.  And he was made of straw, but he was scary enough.</Source>
      <Dest>喂，我讨厌它！我已经杀了很多人了。唔，也许只有一个。稻草做的，挺吓人的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem rather harmless for a "Madman of the Reach."</Source>
      <Dest>对于 "瑞驰疯汉" 来说，你已经算是人畜无害了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>To be honest, I don't care if I ever kill another, but they say I got magical talent, so I'm trying my best not to let anyone down.</Source>
      <Dest>说老实话，我根本不在乎有没有杀了另一个人，可他们都说我天赋异禀，那我就尽量不让大家失望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The dead go to Winterhold, where they are resurrected as pets.</Source>
      <Dest>死者去往冬堡，他们曾在哪被复活做随从的地方。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The way you make it sound, maybe Ynvar was right about the city folk being slaves and heathens.</Source>
      <Dest>The way you make it sound, maybe Ynvar was right about the city folk being slaves and heathens.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What would your sister think?</Source>
      <Dest>你姐姐知道了会怎么想？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>When I told Ynvar I wanted to play music, she laughed and said I'd be the first tone deaf minstrel in all The Reach.</Source>
      <Dest>我告诉盈瓦儿我想成为吟游诗人的时候，她笑着说，我会成为全瑞驰第一个五音不全的吟游诗人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What would your sister think?</Source>
      <Dest>你姐姐知道了会怎么想？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But the next day she killed some traveling bard and gifted me his drum.  I thought it was rather sweet.</Source>
      <Dest>但第二天她杀了旅行的吟游诗人并把他的乐鼓送给了我。我觉得这真的很甜蜜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The sad tunes tickle my eyes and make my stomach feel like there's a slaughterfish swimming about inside.</Source>
      <Dest>悲伤的曲调挑逗着我的眼睛，感觉胃里有只食人鱼在翻腾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The hearty songs make my palms sweat, and the funny songs make my shoulders feel light as a luna moth.</Source>
      <Dest>激昂的歌让我的手心流汗，欢快的歌使我觉得肩膀轻的像飞蛾一般。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What do you mean by that?</Source>
      <Dest>你指的是什么意思？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Some songs are so epic they won't fit in your body, but you only need look up, and find them written in the stars.</Source>
      <Dest>有些歌曲是如此的壮丽以至于你的身体无法承载，但你只需要寻找就够了，而后你会发现他们都被写在星辰之中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If not a shaman, what would you be?</Source>
      <Dest>你不是萨满，那是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>I'd like to be a traveling minstrel.  I know, my head don't have room for but one or two stories, but I would mostly play music anyway.</Source>
      <Dest> 我想当个吟游诗人。我知道我的脑袋里只能装得下一两个故事，但我至少能大概弹点音乐啥的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>If not a shaman, what would you be?</Source>
      <Dest>你不是萨满，那是什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Music is different than words.  If I need to remember a melody, all I have to do is remember a feeling. </Source>
      <Dest>音乐不同于语音。如果我需要记住一段旋律，我所要做的就是记住一种感觉。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>That's a very cynical way to look at things.  You see the bottle as half empty.</Source>
      <Dest>那可真是超级悲观的个性。你属于“只看半瓶空”的类型。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hmm...maybe.  I prefer to think I'm an idealist.  A romantic.  I want my bottle all the way full and won't take anything halfway.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯……也许吧。我更喜欢把自己看做一个空想家。一个浪漫的人。我想做个厉害的人，做什么都不会半途而废。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happens to your soul?</Source>
      <Dest>你的灵魂怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Something like returning to the world as another creature, like even a tree or a spider or something.</Source>
      <Dest>有点像作为另一种生物回到这个世界上，甚至就像一棵树或一只蜘蛛什么的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happens to your soul?</Source>
      <Dest>你的灵魂怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Which is just about the most horrifying thing I can imagine.</Source>
      <Dest>这是我能想象到的最恐怖的事。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What happens to your soul?</Source>
      <Dest>你的灵魂怎么了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>If I came back as a spider, I reckon I'd bite myself and throw my health potion in the river.</Source>
      <Dest>如果我像一只蜘蛛一样回来，我估计我会咬到自己并把我的治疗药水丢进河中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Great. Thanks for ruining every decision I've made.</Source>
      <Dest>很好，感谢你毁了我做的每一个决定。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're welcome.</Source>
      <Dest>不用客气。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>You're welcome.</Source>
      <Dest>欢迎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Fairy bards?  You take that back.  There is nothing soft about Nord poetry.</Source>
      <Dest>一个漂亮的吟游诗人妹子？带回来吧，这儿还没什么轻松温和的诺德诗呢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Okay, okay I'll take it back.  Truth is, I like a bard who's a little less rough around the edges.  It's a guilty pleasure of mine.</Source>
      <Dest>好的好的，我会带着回来的。实际上吧，我更喜欢那种稍带点儿青涩的吟游诗人。那种会让我有种犯罪一般的快感。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What a loser. I hate it when someone can't take a hint.</Source>
      <Dest>太失败了。我最烦那种看不懂眼色的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>That's not very nice!  I mean, it wasn't entirely his fault.  My sister did have a hand in it.</Source>
      <Dest>那真不大好！我是说，这并不全是他的错。我姐姐做得也不完全对。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What a loser. I hate it when someone can't take a hint.</Source>
      <Dest>太失败了。我最烦那种看不懂眼色的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Whenever he wooed her she would make excuses, like he was too fat one day and too skinny the next.</Source>
      <Dest>每次他向她求爱的时候，她都会有诸多借口，前一天还说他太胖，后一天却又嫌他太瘦。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>What a loser. I hate it when someone can't take a hint.</Source>
      <Dest>太失败了。我最烦那种看不懂眼色的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Poor Thendrick thought she was just being fickle.  Figured one of these days he'd end up being the right weight, he just had to keep asking.</Source>
      <Dest>可怜的兰瑞克认为她只是在使性子罢了。他以为只要坚持不懈地每天去问一遍，总有一天他的体重会符合她的要求。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Farewell.</Source>
      <Dest>再会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, it's you again!  Your name is...wait...don't tell me...Celek?  Oh, mudcrabs, that was my cousin's name.  I think.</Source>
      <Dest>Oh, it's you again!  Your name is...wait...don't tell me...Celek?  Oh, mudcrabs, that was my cousin's name.  I think.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oh, it's you again!  Your name is...wait...don't tell me...Fergusson, right?  Oh, mudcrabs, that was my cousin's name.  I think.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，又是你！你叫啥来着...且慢...别告诉我..福格斯，对不？哦，河蟹！呃我想..那是我表哥的名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes?</Source>
      <Dest>什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hm?</Source>
      <Dest>嗯？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>哈啰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Hello.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Maybe, if I could just look past the him being in love with you part.  But I suppose every man has his flaws.</Source>
      <Dest>Maybe, if I could just look past the him being in love with you part.  But I suppose every man has his flaws.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Ynvar, I think Thendrick just spoke to me!</Source>
      <Dest>盈瓦儿，我想兰瑞克刚刚在对我说话！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Yes.  I had an idea for a new spell, but I can't seem to remember what it looked like.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，我想到了一个新的法术。但我似乎不记得它是什么样子的了。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
