<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Would there be any? Profits?</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗？有利可图？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Indeed. I've found people are willing to pay you gold to take their junk off their hands.</Source>
      <Dest>那当然。我发现有人会付钱让你把他们手里的垃圾收走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>So now you hoard other people's junk as well?</Source>
      <Dest>所以你现在也从别人手里收垃圾？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Good. I hate that guy.</Source>
      <Dest>好极了，我讨厌那个家伙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Aren't you worried people will just steal your inventory?</Source>
      <Dest>你难道不担心人们会偷你的东西么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Are there any items of no value to anyone?</Source>
      <Dest>有没有什么东西是对任何人都毫无价值的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>How do you determine what's junk? You must have some value system.</Source>
      <Dest>你怎样判断什么是垃圾？你一定有一套评估体系。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>A shrewd business plan.  I wish I'd thought of it.</Source>
      <Dest>一个精明的商业计划。我应该想到这一点的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>(Lie) Nazeem's already dead.</Source>
      <Dest>（撒谎）纳奇姆已经死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Why set up at Whitewatch Tower?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么要建立在白漫哨塔?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>I have a house in Whiterun. It's quaint.</Source>
      <Dest>我在白漫城有个典雅的房子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Real estate is not something you can just buy. Someone has to sell.</Source>
      <Dest>地产可不是你说买就能买到的，得有人出售才行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Real estate is not something you can just buy. Someone has to sell.</Source>
      <Dest>地产可不是你说买就能买到的，得有人出售才行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Real estate is not something you can just buy. Someone has to sell.</Source>
      <Dest>地产可不是你说买就能买到的，得有人出售才行。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Yes, you got me.  It was my plan all along to copy the worst idea ever.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，被你发现了，我的计划就是直接照抄这糟透了的主意。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Oh, ha-ha. Laugh it up stranger, but we'll see who's laughing when I'm in the cloud district, dining with the other lords.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，呵呵。尽管笑吧陌生人，不过我想瞧瞧当我在云顶区和领主们做着生意的时候，到底是谁在笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Washing them clean could triple their value.</Source>
      <Dest>把它们洗洗干净就能值三倍的价钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Some people call this junk...</Source>
      <Dest>有的人管这叫垃圾…</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Some people call this junk...</Source>
      <Dest>有的人管这叫垃圾…</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Some people call this junk...</Source>
      <Dest>有的人管这叫垃圾…</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Some people call this junk...</Source>
      <Dest>有的人管这叫垃圾…</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Nazeem's already dead.</Source>
      <Dest>纳齐姆已经死了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What if I replaced the college books with your burned ones and you sold them?</Source>
      <Dest>我用你这些烧毁的书去偷换掉学院的书，然后你再卖掉它们，你看怎么样？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Wait, you want me to pay you to take my junk?</Source>
      <Dest>等一下，你是说我出钱请你拿走我的垃圾？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Wait, you want me to pay you to take my junk?</Source>
      <Dest>等一下，你是说我出钱请你拿走我的垃圾？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Wait, you want me to pay you to take my junk?</Source>
      <Dest>等一下，你是说我出钱请你拿走我的垃圾？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Wait, you want me to pay you to take my junk?</Source>
      <Dest>等一下，你是说我出钱请你拿走我的垃圾？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Wait, you want me to pay you to take my junk?</Source>
      <Dest>等一下，你是说我出钱请你拿走我的垃圾？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Wait, you want me to pay you to take my junk?</Source>
      <Dest>等一下，你是说我出钱请你拿走我的垃圾？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>True, those roads are certainly notorious.</Source>
      <Dest>确实，这些道路的名声的确不怎么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>True, those roads are certainly notorious.</Source>
      <Dest>确实，这些道路的名声的确不怎么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>True, those roads are certainly notorious.</Source>
      <Dest>确实，这些道路的名声的确不怎么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>True, those roads are certainly notorious.</Source>
      <Dest>确实，这些道路的名声的确不怎么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>True, those roads are certainly notorious.</Source>
      <Dest>确实，这些道路的名声的确不怎么样。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>It's mad enough to work, but stupid enough to fail.</Source>
      <Dest>干这活儿是太疯狂，可没干成是太愚蠢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>It's mad enough to work, but stupid enough to fail.</Source>
      <Dest>干这活儿是太疯狂，可没干成是太愚蠢。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>That is music to my ears, sera, for a truly great idea is often mistaken for madness.</Source>
      <Dest>在我耳中您这句就是天籁啊，因为真正伟大的想法总被误认为是疯狂。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Impossible. You already own a premium location.</Source>
      <Dest>没门儿！你已经有一个超好的位置了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>That's right. Guards stationed day and night, and all the weary adventurers an Elf could ask for.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。日夜驻守在这里的守卫，背包满当当的疲惫旅者，这里应有尽有。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>You invested poorly.  Ruined books are where the profit is.</Source>
      <Dest>你的投资方向有问题。损毁的书籍才是真正的利润所在。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>It may be shrewd, but it takes a long time to bear fruit.  I have to play the market right, or else the only person I'll make rich is Belethor.</Source>
      <Dest>这或许确实是个精明的计划，不过得花很长时间才能起效。我得把这个市场的运营拉上正轨，否则发财的人就不是我而是贝莱托尔了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Welcome to Eldar's Junk Emporium, traveler!  I'll take any junk you've found on your travels, for a nominal fee.</Source>
      <Dest>欢迎来到爱尔达跳蚤市场！我将带走您在旅行中找到的任何垃圾，并象征性地收取一点费用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Not a good idea. The books would be way too valuable, and the evidence would point right to me.</Source>
      <Dest>不是个好主意。那些书实在太贵重，而且所有证据都会直接指向我。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>You can hand any items over to me or leave them in the chest.  It's all on the honor system.  </Source>
      <Dest>你可以把东西交给我保管或者把它们留在箱子里。这些都是比较体面的做法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>If people willing to buy all the crap most of us throw away, then imagine the profits to be had in collecting it.</Source>
      <Dest>如果人们愿意购买被我们中的大多数人扔掉的垃圾，那么可以想象收集那些垃圾所能带来的巨大利润。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>With the money I've earned, I suppose I could open a separate stall in Whiterun for more valuable goods.</Source>
      <Dest>所以我认为用我赚来的钱，我可以在雪漫开一家分店来买卖价值较高的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>But the overhead doesn't justify the profits, especially with the Jarl's taxes and everyone else undercutting my prices.</Source>
      <Dest>但是高成本并不意味着高收益，尤其是这里需要向领主缴纳税款，其他人还会压低我的价格。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>To the west, you have Riverwood, where most travelers have already unloaded their wares at Lucan's shop.</Source>
      <Dest>再往西，就来到了河木镇，大多数旅行者在路坎的店里就把东西处理掉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Such ideas are separated from us like the farms surrounding the city.  The great thinkers are mocked for trying to see them through walls of stone.</Source>
      <Dest>这样的想法就如同散布在城墙之外的农场一样潜藏在我们周围。伟大的思想者们总因为想要透过石墙看到墙外的世界而饱受讥讽。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Ah, so you're a junk man as well.  I know the value of a ruined book.  Especially in the winter, they'll work just as good as firewood.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，原来你也是捡破烂的。我知道这些损毁的书籍的价值。尤其是在冬天时，它们跟木柴一样好用。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Especially the thick volumes, like "The Wolf Queen," or one of Barenziah's 900 biographies.  </Source>
      <Dest>特别是那些大部头，就像“狼女王”，或者是巴兰兹亚的九百传记那种。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>But some of the rarer books I save for more discerning buyers.  Even with half the pages ruined, they're still worth something to collectors.</Source>
      <Dest>但一些罕见的书我都留给了更为识货的买家。即使有半本儿书已经毁了，但它们仍有一些收藏的价值。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>What? You? What did you do, save the city? Oh wait, you did, didn't you. I bet the greedy bastards still didn't give you a discount.</Source>
      <Dest>什么？你？你做了什么，拯救了城市吗？哦等等， 你确实拯救了城市，不是么。我赌那个贪婪的混账连一点折扣都没给你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>What?  You lie.  There's no way anyone would let him off so easy.</Source>
      <Dest>什么？你撒谎。没人会让他这么轻易就得到解脱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Most of 'em are adventurers, who come out of a cave with more loot than they can carry, only to find it's still a three hour walk back to Whiterun.  </Source>
      <Dest>大多是冒险者，背着太多负重刚从山洞里跑出来，却发现还有三个钟头才能走回雪漫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Most of whom are adventurers, who come out of a cave with more loot than they can carry, only to find it's still a 3 hour walk to Whiterun.</Source>
      <Dest>这类人大多是冒险者，背着一身负重刚从山洞里跑出来，却发现还有三个钟头才能走回雪漫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>That's right. I've found people are willing to pay you gold to take their junk off their hands.</Source>
      <Dest>没错。我发现人们很乐意为把他们手上的垃圾收走而付钱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>You can hand any items over to me or leave them in the chest at Whitewatch Tower.  It's all on the honor system.  </Source>
      <Dest>你可以把东西交到我手上或者留在白望哨塔的箱子里。这些都是比较体面的做法。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>It's a prime location. To the north is empty tundra and Giant camps, and the guard station is too close to Fort Greymoor for my liking.</Source>
      <Dest>这里是最佳地点。再往北就只有空旷的苔原和巨人营地，而警卫站对我而言又离灰色荒原堡垒太近了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>There are no bandits to alleviate them of their burdens, or any shops to do the same. </Source>
      <Dest>一路上没有什么能帮他们减轻身上的负重，不管是商店还是强盗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Smarmy fetcher has lots of enemies. Says stuff like, "Do you get to the cloud district often?  Of course you don't, because you're a filthy beggar."</Source>
      <Dest>那条讨厌的走狗树敌颇多。经常说些“你常去云霄区吗？哦你当然不常去啦，因为你只是个脏兮兮的乞丐。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Now he didn't buy everything of course, but he bought enough to where I didn't have to sell the silverware.</Source>
      <Dest>当然他没买下所有东西，不过跟他交易换来的钱已经足够让我不至于卖掉银器了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>More importantly, I had stumbled upon an idea. </Source>
      <Dest>更重要的是，我灵光一现想出了一个主意。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>I was hoping to save up for a place like Breezehome, but I don't have the coin just yet.  </Source>
      <Dest>我希望能存钱买到一个风宅那样的地方，但我暂时还没那个钱。 </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Then there's the politics.  Don't know whose spear you have to polish to get on top of the waiting list, but I imagine it tastes foul going down.</Source>
      <Dest>这还牵扯到政治手腕。我现在还不知道要需要帮哪位老爷擦矛才能排到购房名单的最前排，不过我猜被排到后面的感觉肯定不好受。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>You're a clever one to see that.  As you might expect, I can't put anything too valuable in the chest, or it'd be too difficult to guard.</Source>
      <Dest>能发现这点说明你是个聪明人。也许你已经想到，我不可能把太值钱的东西放在箱子里，不然想看牢它们会很有难度。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Now the guards here will stop the occasional thief so long as I wet their beaks.</Source>
      <Dest>现在只要我时不时请守卫杯酒，他们就会帮我杜绝盗窃现象。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>I'm an adventurer, not some lowly shopkeep.</Source>
      <Dest>我是个冒险者，而不是什么摆摊的杂碎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Is that what you call yourselves? I like to call you my pack mules. Now do you have any questions, or are we done here?</Source>
      <Dest>你们是那么称呼自己的？我喜欢把你们称呼为我的货驴。现在你还有任何问题吗？还是说我们可以结束了？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Indeed. I wash them at the Drunken Huntsmen before I take them to Belethor.  I keep them dirty for now to lower their value and dissuade thieves.</Source>
      <Dest>确实如此。在把它们带去贝莱托尔那儿之前我会先去酩酊猎人清洗一下。暂时先让它们脏兮兮的能唬走不少小贼。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>I'm in the business of greed and fatigue, traveler. The greed makes 'em pick up the junk, and the fatigue makes 'em drop it.</Source>
      <Dest>我做的是贪婪与疲倦的生意，旅行者。是贪婪让人们捡起那些垃圾，而疲倦让他们想要丢弃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Unfortunately, you're right about that.  And you have to be a resident to get a seat at the Jarl's table.  </Source>
      <Dest>你很不幸地说中了，只有成为这里的居民，才能领主的桌边享有一席之位。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Yet it's only when they conquer the hill that they truly accept defeat.  For when they reach the apex, they find Dragonsreach tantalizingly close.</Source>
      <Dest>然而当他们登上山顶时才真的意识到自己的失败。在他们冲上山顶后，才会焦躁地发现从这里是进不去龙临厅的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>But if my business attracts hordes of bandits and other unmentionables, then suddenly my coin ain't worth the price of me being here.</Source>
      <Dest>但万一我的营生惹来了大群的强盗或者其他想都不敢想的东西，那么我赚到的钱在我的性命面前会变得一文不值。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Burned books. I found that out the hard way when even Belethor refused to buy them. Not even good for kindling, he said.</Source>
      <Dest>焚毁的书籍。连贝莱托尔都不想买它们的时候我发现的。他说这些书连用来烧都不合适。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Hello, I'm Eldar, owner of Eldar's Junk Emporium at Whitewatch Tower.  See me at my store if you want to leave any junk you find on your travels.</Source>
      <Dest>您好，我是艾尔达，白望塔的艾尔达跳蚤市场的店主。如果您想要处理任何在旅行中得到的不需要的东西，请随时光临小店。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>The mountains loom over the south, peaks which no mortal dare climb, and to the southeast lay the Valtheim Towers, which bandits often occupy.</Source>
      <Dest>山脉赫然耸立在南面，没人有胆量攀爬那些山峰。往东南就只有沃尔瑟姆塔楼，而那里一直以来都被强盗牢牢占据着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>I'm in the business of greed and fatigue, traveler.  The greed makes 'em pick up the junk, and the fatigue makes 'em drop it.</Source>
      <Dest>我做的是贪婪与疲倦的生意，旅行者。是贪婪让人们建起那些垃圾，而疲倦让他们想要丢弃。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Their only foe is a shallow incline, but to an over-encumbered soul, it can seem larger than any dragon.</Source>
      <Dest>他们唯一的敌人是一个缓坡，但是对于一个劳累过度的人来说，那比任何一条巨龙都要庞大。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Really?  Then who was that smarmy Redguard I bumped into in the Market District the other day?  His brother?</Source>
      <Dest>真的吗？那么那天我在集市区碰见的那个傲慢的红卫人是谁？他的兄弟吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>So drop what you can, and take what you must.  That's our motto at Eldar's Junk Emporium.</Source>
      <Dest>弃你可离，取你所需。在艾尔达跳蚤市场，这就是至理名言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>So drop what you can, and take what you must.  That's our motto at Eldar's Junk Emporium.</Source>
      <Dest>弃你可离，取你所需。在艾尔达跳蚤市场，这就是至理名言。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>That's where I come in. I turn their junk around and sell it to Belethor.  Divines only know who purchases it from him.</Source>
      <Dest>而我的作用就体现在这一环节。我收取他们的垃圾然后卖给贝莱托尔。天知道他会把那些东西卖给谁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>That's where I come in. I turn their junk around and sell it to Belethor.  Divines only know who purchases it from him.</Source>
      <Dest>而我的作用就体现在这一环节。我收取他们的垃圾然后卖给贝莱托尔。天知道他会把那些东西卖给谁。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>That's right, a flat fee of 20 gold for taking your junk off your hands.  I also take any items of acceptable value.</Source>
      <Dest>对的，只收20金币我就愿意拿走你手上的垃圾。当然我也乐意拿些价值不错的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>That's right, a flat fee of 20 gold for taking your junk off your hands.  I also take any items of acceptable value.</Source>
      <Dest>对的，只收20金币我就愿意拿走你手上的垃圾。当然我也乐意拿些价值不错的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>The entrance, however, is all the way on the other side.</Source>
      <Dest>然而城市的入口却远在另一侧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Worried?  (Laughs) You must be mad if you think someone is going to risk the ire of the guard to steal a bunch of dirty bowls and forks.</Source>
      <Dest>担心吗？(笑声)你一定是疯了才会觉得有人会冒着惹怒守卫的危险去偷一堆脏碗和刀叉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Indeed. I rushed home and picked up every worthless trinket, every old rag, piece of lint, and loaf of moldy old bread I could find.</Source>
      <Dest>确实。我跑回家拿起我能找到的每一个不值钱的项链，每一块抹布，每一个线头，和每一块发霉的面包。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>When an idea is a success, everyone assumes he actually did it.  See through walls of stone.  When all he really did was stand on his toes.</Source>
      <Dest>当一个主意获得成功时，所有人都以为他的目光真的能穿透高墙。然而他所做的无非就是站在那里而已。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Travelers from the east, however, face no peril other than the occasional divot in the road, and the stare of Vantus' wife.</Source>
      <Dest>然而从东边来的旅人，尚未遇到过比地面上的草皮和万图斯妻子的冷眼更危险的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Well, this beggar's going to own all of Dragonsreach by the time he's done.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，这个乞丐在他还没走到之前就能买下整座龙霄宫。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Now I've got enough worthless books to fill the library in Winterhold, but I'm still holding out hope the market will turn.</Source>
      <Dest>现在我手上这种无用的书已经够塞满整座冬拥城图书馆了，但我仍抱有市场风向转变的期望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What do you plan to do with all that junk?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算用那些垃圾做些什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What do you plan to do with all that junk?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算用那些垃圾做些什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What do you plan to do with all that junk?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算用那些垃圾做些什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What do you plan to do with all that junk?</Source>
      <Dest>你打算用那些垃圾做些什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What do you have for sale?</Source>
      <Dest>你有啥卖的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What do you have for sale?</Source>
      <Dest>你有啥卖的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What do you have for sale?</Source>
      <Dest>你有啥卖的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What do you have for sale?</Source>
      <Dest>你有啥卖的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What do you have for sale?</Source>
      <Dest>你有啥卖的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What do you have for sale?</Source>
      <Dest>你有啥卖的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What do you have for sale?</Source>
      <Dest>你有啥卖的？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>I was, but I changed my mind now that you're on to me.</Source>
      <Dest>是的，但我改主意了，现在我跟你是一伙的了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Some polish spears. Others slay dragons.</Source>
      <Dest>有的人擦矛，有的人屠龙。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>I'm telling Nazeem right now of your plans. You're ruined.</Source>
      <Dest>我正把你的计划告诉纳齐姆，你完蛋了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>I'm telling Nazeem right now of your plans. You're ruined.</Source>
      <Dest>我正把你的计划告诉纳齐姆，你完蛋了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>So what did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>So what did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>So what did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>So what did you do?</Source>
      <Dest>那么你做了什么？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Why Nazeem?</Source>
      <Dest>为什么是纳奇姆？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>You forgot basic knives and forks. Worthless.</Source>
      <Dest>你还忘了最常见的刀叉。它们也毫无价值。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Maybe now, but unlike burned books, they still have utility. </Source>
      <Dest>现在也许是吧，但不像烧毁的书籍，它们依旧是有用的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>In fact, the market may change soon, with blacksmiths too busy forging swords to bother with common dinnerware.</Source>
      <Dest>实际上，当铁匠们都忙着铸剑而无暇打造日用餐具的时候，市场需求也许会迅速转变。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>What sort of junk do you collect?</Source>
      <Dest>你在收集什么破烂？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>I've met broomsticks with more business sense.</Source>
      <Dest>我已发现扫帚的商业意义了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>I've met broomsticks with more business sense.</Source>
      <Dest>我已发现扫帚的商业意义了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Not by themselves, but a thousand forks and knives would be valuable.</Source>
      <Dest>它们本身并不起眼，不过数量大了可就值钱了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Not by themselves, but a thousand forks and knives would be valuable.</Source>
      <Dest>它们本身并不起眼，不过数量大了可就值钱了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Not by themselves, but a thousand forks and knives would be valuable.</Source>
      <Dest>它们本身并不起眼，不过数量大了可就值钱了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>The last one who called me mad, I sewed his mouth shut.  Now he calls me "mmm."</Source>
      <Dest>上一位管我叫疯子的，我把他的嘴缝上了。现在他管我叫"唔唔唔…"</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Is this your long term business plan?</Source>
      <Dest>这就是你这生意的远景规划？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Is this your long term business plan?</Source>
      <Dest>这就是你这生意的远景规划？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>Is this your long term business plan?</Source>
      <Dest>这就是你这生意的远景规划？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>I don't know if revenge is worth living in a troll den like Whiterun.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道为了复仇住在像雪漫那样的巨魔巢穴里是不是值得的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0" Partial="1">
      <Source>I don't know if revenge is worth living in a troll den like Whiterun.</Source>
      <Dest>我不知道为了复仇住在像雪漫那样的巨魔巢穴里是不是值得的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>The finest brooms in Tamriel.</Source>
      <Dest>泰姆瑞尔最好的扫帚。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Glass jars? Of course! They come in broken, and busted.</Source>
      <Dest>玻璃瓶？当然！它们在被发现的时候就已经破损毁坏了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>You don't happen to have any spare brooms, do you?</Source>
      <Dest>你该不会正好有备用的扫帚吧？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Well, people would think he was the Skyforge the way the steam would come out of his ears.</Source>
      <Dest>嗯，到时候他七窍生烟的样子一定会让人想起天空熔炉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Why?  Are you trying to muscle in on my business?</Source>
      <Dest>怎么？你想插手我的生意吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Until next time.</Source>
      <Dest>下回见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>I chuckled, of course, and was about to slide the spoon into my tunic when Belethor asked me, "How much?"  I asked him, "For the silverware?"</Source>
      <Dest>当然，我呵呵一笑，正当我打算把木勺悄悄塞到我衣兜里时，贝莱托尔问我：“多少钱？”我则问他：“这些银器吗？”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Only when I placed the set on the counter, I noticed there was an old wooden spoon lumped in with the silverware.  </Source>
      <Dest>当我把这套银器放在台面上时，我发现其中里混进了一把老旧的木勺。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>It was a family heirloom, and I was loathe to part with it, but it was the only thing in my possession worth a bloody septim.  </Source>
      <Dest>这是我家里的传家宝，我真的不想割舍它。但这是我手里仅剩还值点该死的金子的东西了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Once market demand is high and supply is low, then I make my move.  That's the only way this junk has any value.  This can take months, even years.  </Source>
      <Dest>一旦市场上供不应求，就该我行动了。这是唯一让这堆破烂儿能产生价值的方法。这会耗时数月，甚至数年。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Why, sell it of course. The idea came to me when I was shopping at Belethor's General Goods Store.  </Source>
      <Dest>怎么，当然是卖掉它了。这主意是我在贝莱托尔杂货店买东西的时候想到的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Well, then let their families know.  Someone has to inherit all their junk.</Source>
      <Dest>哎，那就去告诉他们全家吧。总要有人继承他们全部的垃圾。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Too much junk weighing you down?  For twenty gold I can take it off your hands for you.</Source>
      <Dest>包里垃圾太多拿不动了？给我20块就帮你处理掉。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>But if a poor farmer somehow managed to worm his way to the Cloud District...</Source>
      <Dest>但如果一个卑贱的农民不知怎的的攀进了云霄区……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>No thief has the patience to wait this long, not when there are plenty of other things he can steal, and not when his stomach growls for food.</Source>
      <Dest>没有哪个盗贼会有如此耐心等待这么久的，尤其是有大把其他东西可偷，而他们又饥肠辘辘的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Good, you saved yourself a lot of heartache.  I've surveyed the land around here, and this is the best location for a business of this type.</Source>
      <Dest>好极了，你免去了自己许多麻烦。我已经调查过这周围了，这是做这类生意的最佳地段。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Do I look like a dragon slayer?  Wait, that came out wrong.  Makes it sound like I look like a spear polisher.</Source>
      <Dest>我看起来像屠龙的人吗？等下，你这话不对。听起来就像在说我是个擦矛的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>There's no one in all of Tamriel who has a lower opinion of what I collect, and the man who collects them.</Source>
      <Dest>整个塔玛瑞尔大陆都找不到比他更瞧不起我和我所收集的东西的人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>While you're slaving in some mine trying to pluck a flawless diamond, I'll have traded my brooms for seven.</Source>
      <Dest>当你在不知道哪些矿洞里苦苦需找一个完美无瑕的钻石的时候，我已经卖出去七把扫帚了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>My goal is to buy a house in Whiterun, and run my own business in the Market District.  </Source>
      <Dest>我的目标是在白漫城买一栋房子，然后在集市区开一家属于我自己的商店。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Please, do come back. (Laughs) Sorry, I couldn't help myself.</Source>
      <Dest>请务必，再来光顾。（笑声）对不起，我我没忍住。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Remember traveler, pick up everything that isn't nailed to the floor. And maybe those things too if you can manage.</Source>
      <Dest>旅行者，记得拿走所有没被钉在地板上的东西。要是你办得到的话把那些钉住的也一并拿走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>But my motivation is to get a seat at the Jarl's table, right across from Nazeem.</Source>
      <Dest>但我最原始的动机是想在领主的议事桌上得到一个位置，一个刚好面对纳奇姆的位置。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Oh, and where would you rather live? Solitude? An entire city full of people like Nazeem. Riften? You'll lose your home before you get the door open.</Source>
      <Dest>噢，那你更喜欢在哪里生活呢？独孤城？那里满大街都是纳奇姆那样的人。裂谷城？在你打开家门之前你家就会被偷个精光。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Oh, I meant no offense, traveler.  But if you'd like to leave your needle and thread in the box, I'd be willing to waive the fee.</Source>
      <Dest>哦，没有冒犯之意，旅行者。但如果你想把自己的针线留在这个盒子里，我就不收钱了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>All right, then.</Source>
      <Dest>那就这样吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Satchel feeling a bit heavy?  Come see me at my store at Whitewatch Tower.</Source>
      <Dest>感觉背包有点重吗？来白望哨塔的商店见我吧。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>It was about a year ago, after Nazeem had fired me from Chillfurrow Farm for sleeping on the job.  </Source>
      <Dest>大概是一年以前的事情了，在我因为工作时睡觉而被纳奇姆从寒犁农场炒鱿鱼以后。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>But only if you had the patience to move them.  Even Belethor wouldn't buy all the junk in my inventory.  I have to wait until his stock runs low.</Source>
      <Dest>除非你有耐心去搬它们。连贝莱托尔都不会把我货物清单上的什物全买下来。得等到他存货用得差不多的时候。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>And the fool said, "No!  No, the spoon!"</Source>
      <Dest>然后那个蠢货说：“不！不，我是说那把勺子！”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>When he fired me, I thought of ways to get back at him. Poison his food, bed his wife, burn his crops.  In the end though, it wasn't worth it.</Source>
      <Dest>他炒我鱿鱼的时候，我想了各种办法报复他。给他的食物投毒，睡他老婆，烧他庄稼。最后我想想，我觉得不值得。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Anyway, I was desperate for coin, and I decided to sell a set of antique silverware that I had kept packed away in an old sack.</Source>
      <Dest>总之，我当时急需钱，我决定卖掉一套我已经在袋子里整理好的银质古董。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Be seeing you.</Source>
      <Dest>再见。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>I rolled them up in an old cloth, and went to Belethor to get it appraised.  </Source>
      <Dest>我拿了件旧衣服把它们包起来，冲去贝莱托尔杂货店估了个价。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Ah, nothing like a batch of fresh junk to brighten my day.</Source>
      <Dest>啊，没什么东西能像一堆新鲜的垃圾一样让我眼前一亮了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Take a look.</Source>
      <Dest>随便看看。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Greetings.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Ha! Brooms happen to be some of my most popular pieces.  Lots of death means lots of empty rooms and piles of dust.  </Source>
      <Dest>哈！扫帚碰巧是我最受欢迎的商品。大量的人员伤亡意味着一堆的空屋子和满屋子灰。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>None of those things mattered to him, and when all accounts were settled he'd still be rich and I'd still be poor.  </Source>
      <Dest>他根本不在乎这些，而就算我进行了这些报复，他依然富得流油，而我仍是一贫如洗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Some people call this junk, but not Belethor.</Source>
      <Dest>有些人把这叫做垃圾，贝莱托尔可不会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Go ahead. That high-minded fool will laugh in your face, right before he spits in it.  </Source>
      <Dest>你去啊。那个自大的蠢货肯定会冲着你大小，然后吐你一脸口水。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Over-encumbered traveler?  I can help you with that.</Source>
      <Dest>你身上带的东西超重了吗？我能帮你分担一点儿。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Depends on what you mean. But no, I don't plan on being here forever.</Source>
      <Dest>这取决于你想问哪方面。不过，我并不打算永远呆在这里。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>One day I'll take my place at the Jarl's table.  And when I do, the look on Nazeem's face will have made all the struggle worth it.</Source>
      <Dest>会有那么一天，领主的桌子会出现我属于的位置。而当我做到了的时候，纳奇姆脸上精彩的表情将证明我的一切努力都没白费。。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Markarth?  Who wants to live near a prison. And there's no way a Dark Elf like me is moving to Windhelm.</Source>
      <Dest>马卡斯城？谁会愿意住在一座监狱旁边。而且像我这样的黑精灵也没办法搬到风盔城。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Forks, brooms, pretty much everything you don't need.</Source>
      <Dest>叉子，扫帚，一切你不需要的东西。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2" Partial="1">
      <Source>Need something?</Source>
      <Dest>需要些什么吗？</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
