<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<SSTXMLRessources>
  <Params>
    <Addon>3DNPC.esp</Addon>
    <Source>english</Source>
    <Dest>chinese</Dest>
  </Params>
  <Content>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Ahem. Did someone say hero?  Look no further.</Source>
      <Dest>Ahem. 有人说起过英雄吗？ 没有下文了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Elf was the leader.  Only his body was a worthy vessel.</Source>
      <Dest>精灵们才是领导者。只有他们的身体才能成为一个有价值的容器l.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Elf was the leader.  Only his body was a worthy vessel.</Source>
      <Dest>精灵们才是领导者。只有他们的身体才能成为一个有价值的容器l.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Elf was the leader.  Only his body was a worthy vessel.</Source>
      <Dest>精灵们才是领导者。只有他们的身体才能成为一个有价值的容器l.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Elf was the leader.  Only his body was a worthy vessel.</Source>
      <Dest>精灵们才是领导者。只有他们的身体才能成为一个有价值的容器l.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're mad. Your prophecies are the ramblings of a mad woman. Good day.</Source>
      <Dest>你疯了。你的预言是一个疯狂的女人的随笔。好日子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You're mad. Your prophecies are the ramblings of a mad woman. Good day.</Source>
      <Dest>你疯了。你的预言是一个疯狂的女人的随笔。好日子。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Who are you?</Source>
      <Dest>你是谁？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where are your parents now?</Source>
      <Dest>你的双亲现在在哪?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Where are your parents now?</Source>
      <Dest>你的双亲现在在哪?</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't appear as if you came from a broken home.  Yet something broke you.</Source>
      <Dest>或许你并非来自一个破碎的家庭。但确有些什么毁了你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>It doesn't appear as if you came from a broken home.  Yet something broke you.</Source>
      <Dest>或许你并非来自一个破碎的家庭。但确有些什么毁了你。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Strange that they couldn't distinguish your smell from a corpse.</Source>
      <Dest>奇怪的是他们居然不能用气味将你和那些尸体区分开来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Strange that they couldn't distinguish your smell from a corpse.</Source>
      <Dest>奇怪的是他们居然不能用气味将你和那些尸体区分开来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this pact.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我說說這個合約。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this pact.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我說說這個合約。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this pact.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我說說這個合約。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Tell me about this pact.</Source>
      <Dest>跟我說說這個合約。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nothing you say makes sense to me, so it makes no sense to stay.  Goodbye.</Source>
      <Dest>你所讲的毫无意义，没必要在留在这里。再见</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>你好。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An Orc.  Big, green, although you left out the ugly part.</Source>
      <Dest>一个兽人。大个，绿色的。尽管你忽略了最丑陋的部分。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, that was a lovely verse. I'd like to hear another.</Source>
      <Dest>喔～好诗啊好诗，我还想再听一首。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Oh, that was a lovely verse. I'd like to hear another.</Source>
      <Dest>喔～好诗啊好诗，我还想再听一首。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>The Redguard was murdered for corrupting the blood ritual with loose sand.</Source>
      <Dest>这个红卫人被杀是为了堕落之血与散沙的仪式。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know of this pact?</Source>
      <Dest>你对这个约定知道多少？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know of this pact?</Source>
      <Dest>你对这个约定知道多少？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know of this pact?</Source>
      <Dest>你对这个约定知道多少？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know of this pact?</Source>
      <Dest>你对这个约定知道多少？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does Styrr know you're down here?</Source>
      <Dest>Styrr知道你在这里吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does Styrr know you're down here?</Source>
      <Dest>Styrr知道你在这里吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Does Styrr know you're down here?</Source>
      <Dest>Styrr知道你在这里吗？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>An Argonian, a Khajiit, an Elf, and an Imperial.</Source>
      <Dest>一个亚龙人，一个虎人，一个精灵和一个帝国人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>They killed the Khajiit for his cowardice.</Source>
      <Dest>他们因這虎人的怯懦而杀了他。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Easy there, Breton. You shouldn't be down here.  It's dangerous.</Source>
      <Dest>当心，布莱顿人。你不应该在这下面。这很危险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Easy there, Breton. You shouldn't be down here.  It's dangerous.</Source>
      <Dest>当心，布莱顿人。你不应该在这下面。这很危险。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You don't strike me as vain.  Mad perhaps, but not vain.</Source>
      <Dest>或许有点疯狂，但是你对我的打击并不是徒劳的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Then the fates have brought me here. I am your champion.</Source>
      <Dest>命运带我来到了你的面前，我就是你的勇士！</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Pray, pray, pray.  Pray there is no prey, for with it comes the end of days.</Source>
      <Dest>祈祷，祈祷，祈祷，祈祷这里没有猎物，祈祷可以和它一起迎来末日。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Down in shadow, lost in grief, trapped in the void's endless trench.  To unknowable depths and terror's height, goes our downward ascent.</Source>
      <Dest>在阴影中沉沦，在哀痛中迷失，被困在无尽的空虚之中。深不见底的深渊，无止尽的堕落。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The children called her "ugly and vain."  Mother said, "Ignore their game."</Source>
      <Dest>孩子们说她“丑恶又虚荣”。而母亲说，“无视他们的戏弄吧。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Dressed in blood, dress the wound, the egg hunts in secret from the womb.</Source>
      <Dest>衣服浸满了血,包扎着伤口,在子宫里寻找着蛋的秘密。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Daylight felled, moons and stars, eaten as the day.  What is nigh but what has always been.  A single spot, the last page.</Source>
      <Dest>黎明陨落，星星和月亮吞噬者白昼。几近达成却不断完善。简单的标记，最后的章节。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Fear perhaps, love maybe, what is the provenance of true denial?  Know I not, but I know this.  The robe was dressed in blue.</Source>
      <Dest>或许是恐惧，也许是爱，被拒绝的真相起源又是如何？我是不知道，但我知道。这长袍被蓝色装饰着。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The hollows scream words unknown, knells of silence to forewarn, that which cannot be unseen, darkness fathomed daylight's dream.</Source>
      <Dest>山谷喊叫着未知的话语, 丧钟沉默着发出警鸣。那是不能视而不见的,  在黑暗之中追寻阳光的愿望。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Don't pull the tail, let light's anchor fail...</Source>
      <Dest>别拉那条尾巴，让【光之锚】失败吧……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Verses are words, and words perverse.  They speak and yet say none.  Round and round, up and down, until the period comes.</Source>
      <Dest>诗是文字，堕落的文字。它们陈述然而却说的什么也不是。旋转不息，上来下去，直到句号的到来。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The knives said and spoke too clear, "The land will cry with pain, and pray for a time when they could but fear."</Source>
      <Dest>这些【武装者】讲的很明白，“整片土地【的人】都会因痛苦而哭喊。当他们可以【抵抗】却因恐惧而退却时，只会默默祈祷。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Oceans rise, waves and tide, cresting over shoals.  The mad fish sing in bubbled rhyme and play in coral bowls.</Source>
      <Dest>海水潮起，波涛淹没浅滩。疯狂的鱼儿在珊瑚丛中畅游，用有韵律的气泡歌唱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mother said, "Your name is Gwyvane." Father agreed, "It's a lovely name."</Source>
      <Dest>老妈说：“你就叫桂帆好了。”老爸同意：“这名字真可爱嘿。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Pimpled skin and wilted bone, atrophy and darkness groans...</Source>
      <Dest>起疹的皮肤和枯萎的骨骼，虚弱而模糊的呻吟……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The tail said, "I smell another," the knives said, "You smell a corpse."  Bones rattle and bones wake and smells are voices hoarse.</Source>
      <Dest>尾巴说，“我闻到了别的东西。”刀说，“你闻到的是尸体。”骨头嘎嘎作响，苏醒过来，察觉出那些声音有些沙哑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The third with sand between her toes, the fourth with ice upon his breath.  Together in ritual and sunken time, they seek the dismal death.</Source>
      <Dest>第三个趾缝含沙，第四个鼻息含冰。在仪式与沉没之时，索寻着凄凉之死。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The fifth one heard the pact, but did not speak or sign.  Shivered, trembled, fought for warmth in cold's frigid bind.</Source>
      <Dest>第五人听到了协议，但不做声响。颤栗着，发抖着，在寒冷冰凉的束缚里为温暖挣扎。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Met with darkness, met with stones, met with kisses and met with bones.</Source>
      <Dest>遇见黑暗，遇见岩石，遇见吻还有遇见骨头。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Is it wolf or pheasant, spider or fly?  Knives are green, and touch the sky.</Source>
      <Dest>那是狼还是野鸡，蜘蛛还是苍蝇？刀子染上了绿色，飞上了天空。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Well met.</Source>
      <Dest>幸会。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Four mortals said the words, and brought the blight upon this land.  Two knives, one tail, and the hour of death is soon at hand.</Source>
      <Dest>四个凡人道出禁语，瘟疫降临这片土地。手上的不止两把匕首，还有死亡时刻的临近。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Sand in skin, but no sand to touch, the dunes swept over a pact of blood.</Source>
      <Dest>沙子附在皮肤上，却触摸不到，这片沙丘遍布着血之契约。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>In the shade to hide from shades and say the words that felled the day.</Source>
      <Dest>在阴影中躲避其他阴影，还说着抱怨生活的话。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Did you hear what happened to the fishwife?  Spoiled, spoiled beyond repair, never was she always fair.</Source>
      <Dest>你听说卖鱼妇发生了什么事吗？变质，变质到无法恢复，她不会永远都是美丽的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Life, death, life again, brings death upon all daylight's end.</Source>
      <Dest>生死轮回，未曾止息，亡灵飘摇，直至终结。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Names are all we are.  Name it, and it shall be known.  It wears a new name, wears it proud, same as the old.</Source>
      <Dest>对我们而言名字就是一切。给它起个名,然后这个名就会为人所知。它自豪的用上了一个新名字，不亚于旧名字。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Knives cut, and are cut.  Dressed in blood while the other signed.  Sent to the void were the knives, and in its place comes wicked divine.</Source>
      <Dest>刀子切断，然后被切断。刀子浸泡在血液里聆听人们哀叹。刀子被送入虚空，虚空中邪神躁动。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The priest tends to the dead, as the priest should.  The fishwife is not seen or heard or even understood.</Source>
      <Dest>祭司照顾死者，因为祭司应该这么做。没再见过，听说过，也从不会理解那个臭婆娘。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The corporeal become funereal.  Imagination is nothing real.  When five become one, all will kneel.</Source>
      <Dest>有形之物皆悲伤，空想之景全成空。当五归于一，众生皆俯首。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Vestigial, evil, evil, vestigial.  Live again, die no more, the pact was made by mortals four.</Source>
      <Dest>退化，邪恶，邪恶，退化。重活一次，不再死亡，这协议是由四个凡人制定的。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Find it well, find it plain.  All we are is in a name.  </Source>
      <Dest>正确的去理解吧，朴素的去探寻吧。我们所有人的存在归属于同一个名字之下。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The pact is done, signed in blood, and all is soon forgot, for dressed in blood the evil comes and the world is long for naught.  </Source>
      <Dest>血之契约已经成立，一切都将会被遗忘，邪恶踏着鲜血而来，世界将会沦陷。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Speak no further, look no more.  The quickening slows the mortal four.  Salt and dirt, light and stars, meet your destiny from afar.</Source>
      <Dest>不再交谈，不再观察。活泼放慢了四个凡人。盐与尘，光与星，改变你的命运从远处。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For when darkness fells the day and swallows the stars, all that is left to light the path is the fire that burns in mortal hearts.</Source>
      <Dest>因为，当暗黑降临，日月星辰黯淡无光时，唯一能照亮前行之路的，便只剩凡人心中曳动的火光。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Lukewarm sunrise.  The monarch dances, and the dragon lies.   </Source>
      <Dest>冷冷的阳光下，君王翩翩起舞，巨龙尘归于土。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Steel tongues and iron teeth, clack day and night for but a septim's piece.</Source>
      <Dest>钢牙铁齿日日夜夜帮帮作响只换了一点点金币。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>No, yes, yes, and no.  The second dressed, and the third signed, but neither scales nor Empires did she find.</Source>
      <Dest>【没有，有，有，没有。虎人被扒皮了，精灵被标记了，但不论是亚龙人还是帝国人她都没找着。】</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The break of day, the death of light, a new beginning for the night.</Source>
      <Dest>破晓时分，光芒慢慢死亡，而夜晚又到了再次复苏之时。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Insipid, involuntary, blinding infirmity, in that instill death inside the unworthy.</Source>
      <Dest>平淡的,无意识的, 盲目的 弱点, 在那儿逐渐步入死亡于无用之内.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Four mortals made the pact, but another sat in shallows.  No one sees the short, the poor, or the blind in the shadows.</Source>
      <Dest>四个凡人做出了这个约定，但另一个却坐在沙滩上。谁都没有看见阴影之中的【矮子，穷人，或那个瞎子。】</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Signed in blood, dressed in blood...Neither death nor calm or coming spring can stop the scarlet rain or sea.</Source>
      <Dest>以血为势，全身浴血，无论是不平静的死亡，还是春天来临，都不能平息猩红的雨和血海。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>For the seeds have been planted in the void, and the void planted in the seed.</Source>
      <Dest>因为种子被植于虚空之中，而虚空也被种于种子之内。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The land it treads and blood is fed.  Different clothes, same grin, holes in the mask, where skin meets skin.</Source>
      <Dest>它践踏大地，以鲜血为饮。不同的衣着，同样的笑靥，面具上的空洞，那里皮和皮相接。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Knows not, or cares not, or cares too much to care.  Priest moves and Arkay guides, in light is mystery bare.</Source>
      <Dest>不论你理解也否，关心也罢，亦或是关心的太大发了。祭祀的感化连同阿尔凯的指引，都会在神秘的光芒中暴露无遗。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The priest said to the dead one, "These apples I want no more."  The priest said to the wind, "I light these fires so bones are warm."</Source>
      <Dest>牧师告诉亡灵，“我不再想要这些苹果了。”牧师告诉风，“我升起了火，骨头得以温暖。”</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Mother guide me, Father, guide me, strength to watch it all go by me.</Source>
      <Dest>母亲，引导我。父亲，引导我。力量，让我随之而去。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Malacath born, kin to no spell, slave to no other but steel's bell.</Source>
      <Dest>玛拉凯斯诞生了，既不用咒语也不奴役他人，只有丧钟的鸣响。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Malacath born, kin to no spell, slave to no other but steel's bell.</Source>
      <Dest>玛拉凯斯诞生了，既不用咒语也不奴役他人，只有丧钟的鸣响。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Salt and ash, dust and dirt, from whence we came is where we return.</Source>
      <Dest>尘埃落定，灰烬散去，起源之处即是归途终点。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Four mortals made the pact, dressed in blood, signed in blood...</Source>
      <Dest>四个凡人立下契约，同生共死，以血立契……</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>How do you know the scene hasn't been tampered with?</Source>
      <Dest>你们怎么能确保现在看到的这些没有被篡改过。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Redguard, an Argonian, an Elf, and a Nord.</Source>
      <Dest>一个红卫人，一个亚龙人，一个精灵，以及一个诺德人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This pact took place in a catacombs or a crypt.</Source>
      <Dest>此协议达成于某个陵墓或地穴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This pact took place in a catacombs or a crypt.</Source>
      <Dest>此协议达成于某个陵墓或地穴。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I suppose you have no idea how this happened to you.</Source>
      <Dest>我估摸着你也不知道为什么这事会落到你头上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I suppose you have no idea how this happened to you.</Source>
      <Dest>我估摸着你也不知道为什么这事会落到你头上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>I suppose you have no idea how this happened to you.</Source>
      <Dest>我估摸着你也不知道为什么这事会落到你头上。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you be more clear?  Who made this pact?</Source>
      <Dest>你能再明了点吗？谁签的这协议？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you be more clear?  Who made this pact?</Source>
      <Dest>你能再明了点吗？谁签的这协议？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Can you be more clear?  Who made this pact?</Source>
      <Dest>你能再明了点吗？谁签的这协议？</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Khajiit, an Elf, a Nord, and a Redguard.</Source>
      <Dest>一个虎人，一个精灵，一个诺德人和一个红卫人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Khajiit, an Elf, a Nord, and a Redguard.</Source>
      <Dest>一个虎人，一个精灵，一个诺德人和一个红卫人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Khajiit, an Elf, a Nord, and a Redguard.</Source>
      <Dest>一个虎人，一个精灵，一个诺德人和一个红卫人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>A Khajiit, an Elf, a Nord, and a Redguard.</Source>
      <Dest>一个虎人，一个精灵，一个诺德人和一个红卫人。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords crave death.  It made for a worthy sacrifice.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人渴望死亡。这造就了有价值的牺牲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>Nords crave death.  It made for a worthy sacrifice.</Source>
      <Dest>诺德人渴望死亡。这造就了有价值的牺牲。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>You seem ill. Perhaps a bottle of skooma will restore your insanity.</Source>
      <Dest>你貌似生病了。可能一瓶斯库玛能恢复你的错乱。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This being you speak of is a High Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>你说的这个家伙是个高精灵.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="0">
      <Source>This being you speak of is a High Elf.</Source>
      <Dest>你说的这个家伙是个高精灵.</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Seams ran jagged on a curved dome.  Shuddered.  Snapped.  Lost in moans.  </Source>
      <Dest>弧形穹顶的缝合线呈锯齿状。来回摇动。哗哗作响。迷失在呻吟中。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The sand says, "You must find the dead," and the tail says "We found them."</Source>
      <Dest>流沙说，“你要找到死尸,” 尾巴 说 "我们找到他们了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Thrusting pain...unending pain, never will it after.  Heart bleeds, but no blood comes.  Sorrow knows only laughter.</Source>
      <Dest>那撕心裂肺的……永无止境的痛苦，再也不会有了。我的心在滴血，却没有真的血液流出来。我感到悲伤，却只能强颜欢笑。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Four heroes will make tomorrow, to send the blight to endless hollow.</Source>
      <Dest>四位英雄将在明日动身，把枯萎病送往无尽山洞。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>A claws is brought, a wheel is turned and the end is near to ground them.</Source>
      <Dest>龙爪已经带来了，轮盘也开始转动了，结局也在慢慢迫近。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Trust was given, trust was shaken.  Love she kept, so it was taken.</Source>
      <Dest>信任可以给，信任可以丢。爱情她守着，然后被偷走。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Eldawyn,  Eldawyn, a Mer to be scorned.  Plaintive cries and knells of death like echoes of newborn.</Source>
      <Dest>艾德温,  艾德温, 一个受人嘲笑的精灵。哀伤的哭泣和如婴儿呜咽一般的丧钟声。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not many people can find the place, to be honest, since it's not on any map.</Source>
      <Dest>说实话，没多少人能找到这个地方。因为那里在任何一份地图上都没有标示。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The fourth was dressed in shades of red, one soul entered while the other fled.</Source>
      <Dest>第四个包裹在红色的阴影之中。当这个灵魂进入的时候，另一个灵魂趁机逃掉了。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Daylight's end is Nirn's final chapter, sand on the rug, frozen not long after.</Source>
      <Dest>黄昏已至，奈恩将终。沙与兽皮，瑟瑟冰封。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>So it was said, and then signed in blood, but only for three, and not for one.</Source>
      <Dest>就像是谣传的那样，他们在鲜血中留下印记，但是是三个，而不只一个。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Rot and die, maggots and flies, ill omens and ill wind.  The dawn of terror is the dusk of man, and the fishwife knows it's grim.</Source>
      <Dest>腐烂和死亡,蛆虫和苍蝇,和不幸。恐惧的黎明是人类之黄昏。连卖鱼妇都知道他的恐怖。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>But ritual conjured is ritual complete.  Frozen breath cannot halt speech.  </Source>
      <Dest>但召唤仪式的魔法已经完成了。寒气纵刺骨，而终不能封言语.  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The first holds a book, turning time's flow; the second wields a shout to open skybound doors.</Source>
      <Dest>第一步：翻开书，让时间流转；第二步：使用龙吼，打开天限之门。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Not for scales, scales they tip, for malice and quickened life adrift.</Source>
      <Dest>并没有鳞，他们抛弃了鳞，出于他们的恨意，和漂泊生活的艰辛。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The knives nodded to frozen breath, as it read from tome of forgotten death.  Flame rose, flame cold, wretched, wrenching soul of old.</Source>
      <Dest>骑士们随着渐渐冷却的呼吸低下了头，如同在阅读一本被遗忘的亡者的著作。火焰燃起，又渐渐熄灭。悲惨啊，悲惨的古老亡魂啊。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The cat whispered doubt to the knives, but its blades cut through the knee.  It quivered no more, and fur sat matted, lapping meekly at its fleas.</Source>
      <Dest>虎人呻吟着尝试去拔匕首，但是匕首的刀刃刺穿了膝盖。它不再颤抖，身上的毛皮也不再直立，倒伏下来留给身上的跳蚤在其中蹦跳。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Stout as oak, blood like wine, worthy was he of earthly crime.</Source>
      <Dest>如橡树一般健壮，如醇酒一般热血，仿佛就为了在世间犯罪而生。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The third a betrayer whose seeks to redeem, while the fourth is the needle from which we weave.</Source>
      <Dest>第三个人，是个试图弥补的背叛者，而第四个是我们所编织之物的针。</Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>Frozen words, conjured life.  Soul unbound to cause limitless strife.  </Source>
      <Dest>冻结的语言, 诅咒的生命。 灵魂的释放带来无尽的冲突。  </Dest>
    </String>
    <String List="2">
      <Source>The only reason the guard were able to arrest my father is because he was forced to spend the night in Solitude.</Source>
      <Dest>守卫逮捕我父亲唯一可行的理由就是他非自愿而不得不在独孤城过了一夜。</Dest>
    </String>
  </Content>
</SSTXMLRessources>
